<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009182</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/13/2023 09:41:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/13/2023 09:41:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/13/2023 09:40:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/13/2023 09:40:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Identity theft/fraud</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 09:41:05</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4993</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 11:09:14</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FRD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>IDT</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>585416</AddressId>
      <City>MDC226</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 09:41:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 10:39:11</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>585416</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1503</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Division</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Salisbury</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21804</Zip5>
         <Zip4>7201</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.5996894</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.3346613</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/13/2023 09:41:00</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/13/2023 09:41:00</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/13/2023 16:49:50</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 09:41:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:20:52</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments:   MSP form 89A - Uniform Identity Fraud / Theft Reporting Form   Target Red Card credit card paperwork   Kohls credit card paperwork   Synchrony Bank credit card paperwork   Letter addressed to Bramiru Food Inc.   Photocopy of victims license Fax to Amherst PD for report 20-055623  Neighborhood check:   None was conducted based on the nature of the offense  Narrative:   On 3/13/23, I, M/Tpr. A. Edwards, made contact with David Frieman [hereinafter referred to as Frieman] at the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack. Frieman reported that he believed his personal information had been stolen and was used to open or attempt to open several credit card accounts. Frieman advised he has received several items of mail in the past several months beginning around the end of January through the end of February.    I spoke with Frieman in the Salisbury Barrack interview room, which is audibly and visually recorded. Below is a transcript of the interview and not a transcript, therefore some paraphrasing may be used. During the interview Frieman made the following statements:   He began receiving mail at his residence that was addressed to Bramiru Food Inc. of 1503 S. Division Street, Salisbury, MD 21804 in late January 2023.  He marked four or five letters as return to sender and left in his mailbox to be picked up by the mail carrier.  He finally opened one that was addressed directly to him.  He did some internet research and found a business by the name of Bramiru Food Inc. that was reported to have address of 55 Van Pelt Ct, East Amherst, NY 14051.  He also found a website that possibly linked Bramiru Food Inc. to McDonalds but was unsure of what the relationship was.  He was able to locate a corporation number of 3853963 for Bramiru.  He received a letter from PNC Bank in reference toobtaining a business loan.  He has a bank account at PNC Bank and Farmers Bank of Willards.  He has not had any money missing from his bank account and has not noticed any unauthorized charges.  He only has one credit card through PNC Bank.  He receivedthe following letters in reference to accounts that were opened or were attempted to be opened:     Target Red Card credit card       The letter he received contained a credit card, however, he did not have the card at the time he reported the incident.    The letter reported to have a temporary credit limit of $200 and a credit limit of $2,000.    Addressed to Dave Frieman of 1503 S. Division Street, Salisbury, MD 21804.    He advised the card was not activated and no purchases had been made.    He cancelled the card as he did not apply for it.         Kohls credit card (issued by Capital One)       Application number: 0137307130    Address toDave Frieman of 1503 S. Division Street, Salisbury, MD 21804.    The letter was requesting a copy of his identification, proof of residency and a copy of his social security card or taxpayer ID.    He contacted Kohls and advised he had attempted to open the credit card and the account was marked as fraudulent and was not activated.         Synchrony Bank       The letter was in response to a request for a credit account with BRANDSMART.    The letter stated that the company was unable to verify information in the application and his identity could not be confirmed, therefore the credit application was denied.            He received an additional letter addressed toBramiru Food Inc. of 1503 S. Division Street, Salisbury, MD 21804.     The letter appeared to be an order form for Workplace Safety Manuals.   Customer ID: F347384317   Business ID: NY6739056   Requested payment in the amount of $295 to be sent to C.P.S. at 5614 Connecticut Ave NW #190, Washington DC 20015.       Phone number 202-838-0037    Email: cps.safetymanual@gmail.com            He reported that he received an email notification, in December 2022, from Fan Duel which reported that the company had reported a possible breach of customer information.  He believes that this is the only possible manner in which someone would have obtained his person information.  He activated his Fan Duel account in October 2022 and submitted his personal information, bank information and social security number during the registration process.  Hepays the few bills that he has utilizingthe internet and does not use checks for any payments.  He contacted PNC Bank about the fraudulent activity and as set up a multistep verification process for payments and withdraws to prevent any monetary loss.  He was going to contact Farmers Bank of Willards after he left the barrack.  He as already contacted several credit reporting agencies and advised of the fraudulent activity and a flag has been placed on his personal information.  I conducted a work-up of the business name, Bramiru Food Inc., David B Freiman and the address 55 Van Pelt Court that was provided by Frieman. I was able to locate the following information:    Bramiru Food Inc. from Bizapedia.com     Entity type: New York Domestic Business Corporation   Filing state: New York (NY)   Filing date: 2/22/23   Registered agent: Dave Frieman, 1503 S. Division St, Salisbury, MD 21804   Principal address: POB 248, East Amherst, NY, 14051   Company contacts: Filer David Frieman POB 248,East Amherst, NY 14051      Bramiru Inc.from Bizapedia.com(it should be noted the contact persons last name is similar, however, it is spelled different than the victims name.     Entity type: New York Domestic Business Corporation   Filing state: New York (NY)   Filing date: 9/9/2009   Registered agent: David B.Freiman, 55 Van Pelt Court, East Amherst, NY 14051   Principal address: POB 248, East Amherst, NY, 14051   Company contacts: CEO Dave Freiman, East Amherst, NY 14051      55 Van Pelt Court, East Amherst, NY 14051     Appears to a residence street in Google Maps   It is at the end of a caul-de-sac, and does have a residence built upon it however, it appears that a residence is under construction when the image was taken.   The image appears to have been last updated onJuly 2011.      David B. Freiman     Full name: David Bradley Freiman   New York Motor Vehicle Administration       DOB: 8/29/1971    Address: 55 Van Pelt Court, East Amherst, NY 14051    Other ID: F181922243720562771000    Driver Authorization ID: 916992981    Issue date: 5/4/2017    Expiration date: 8/29/2025    Driver license non-commercial status: Valid         Maryland Motor Vehicle Administration       DOB: 8/29/1971    Address: 505 Main St, Apt 334, Gaithersburg, MD 20879    Driver Authorization ID: F-655-135-098-673    Issue date: 8/28/2000    Expiration date: 8/29/2005    Driver license non-commercial status: Surrendered              I contacted the Amherst Police Department and provided the name and address to the dispatcher. I was advised that address was in fact a residence and was in their jurisdiction. The dispatched provided report number 20-055623 as the last report contact with a subject by the name of David Freiman at that address. The report was listed as a fraud/theft related to McDonalds.    On 3/14/23, the Wicomico County States Attorneys Office was contacted and subpoenas were issued for Target Red Card (TD Bank), Kohls andSynchrony Bank. I served the subpoenas to each company via email. The results were not immediately returned and will be forwarded at a later date.  Case open.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 12:39:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 13:03:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Staten</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2991</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Edwards</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alexander</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5096</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498581</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0073</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>58</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/13/2023 09:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 0073</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 10:48:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 10:48:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 10:50:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371458</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>U</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/13/2023 10:50:05</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <DateOfInfo>03/13/2023 10:50:05</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 10:50:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>47</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 11:25:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:34</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>304202</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Frieman</LastName>
               <FirstName>David</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/13/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.19041958E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/18/2021 01:49:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Frieman</LastName>
               <FirstName>David</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/13/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.19041958E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>F655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/18/2021 01:49:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1503</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Division</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21804</Zip5>
               <Zip4>7201</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.5996894</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.3346613</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>603</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9217</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/18/2021 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 11:25:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 11:25:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>7</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 11:28:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 11:28:19</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>7</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Personal information used to open credit card accounts</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>835</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>1</PropertyValue>
         <Value>1</Value>
         <SerialNumber>N/A</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>245276</Property_ID>
         <Make>N/A</Make>
         <Model>N/A</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/28/2023 05:32:05</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/28/2023 05:32:05</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/13/2023 16:49:50</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 05:32:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:20:52</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Synchrony subpoena results</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of supplemental report:  Synchrony subpoena results  Attachments: Synchrony business certification   Two screenshots of credit application  Narrative:   On 3/24/23, I received from Tiffany Franklin from Synchrony in reference to a subpoena that was filed for information related to the credit application that was completed for a BRANDSMART credit card. The email contained a secure attachment, which I was able to download and view several files within it. The files contained the business certification and two screenshots from the application which contained the basic information for the credit application and the application rejection.    None of the documents sent by Synchrony did not have any evidentiary value and did not provide any information that could lead to the identification of a suspect.  Case open.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 05:33:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 05:39:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Staten</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2991</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Edwards</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alexander</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5096</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>