<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-006262</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/17/2023 23:00:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/17/2023 23:00:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/17/2023 22:44:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/17/2023 22:44:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>23-097 "R" NDI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 23:02:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6354</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 09:13:38</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>684673</AddressId>
      <City>MDC508</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 23:32:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/17/2023 23:33:07</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>684673</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I-695</StreetName>
         <City>Pikesville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21208</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.737743</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.381592</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/17/2023 23:02:00</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/17/2023 23:02:00</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/08/2023 09:13:39</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 23:02:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E.) TEAM* The following incident was captured on in-car and body camera  Defendant: Florence S Ndi   TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: * I am trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (March 2013 SFST NHTSA Manual). * I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor as of February 2016. * I am a Certified Breath Test Operator by the Toxicologist of the State of Maryland as of March 2016. * I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of March 2016. * I am a distinguished graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute as of June 2015 * I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of May 2014. * I am a Preliminary Breath Test Instructor as of May 2019. * I am a RADAR and LIDAR Instructor as of October 2019. * I have apprehended more than 1,000 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On February 17, 2023 at approximately 2242 hours, I (Cpl. Wallace #6323) was on patrol in unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle DUI-1 traveling on southbound 795 prior to I-695, Baltimore County, Maryland. I observed a black Hyundai Santa Fe bearing Maryland registration 2BZ8388 traveling in front of my patrol vehicle. The Hyundai continued to swerve left and right and was unable to drive within a single lane. There were multiple other vehicles in the area.    Left over fog line onto shoulder, right.  Right and left in lane.  Right over dotted white line, jerked left (other vehicle in right lane).  Right towards dotted white line, left (other vehicle).  Swerving right and left.  Left towards a tractor trailer, jerked right.  Left towards dotted white line, right over dotted white line, left.  I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the Hyundai on the I/L I-695 at Reisterstown Road on the right shoulder.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Hyundai on the driver side and made contact with the female operator of the vehicle. Her 11-year-old daughter was in the rear seat. I informed the driver the reason for the stop and requested her drivers license and vehicle registration. She was identified by her Maryland drivers license as Florence S Ndi. While speaking with Ndi, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle. I deliberately observed her eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. She stated that she was going home. She continued to repeat herself and say that they were coming from her daughters school. I returned to my patrol vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with.   I returned to the Hyundai and requested her to exit her vehicle and walk to the front. She complied and exited her vehicle. As I communicated with Ndi outside the vehicle, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. She stated that she was at a winter ball at her daughters school. When asked about alcohol consumption she stated not much, then 1 glass of wine. She said she was good. Due to the signs of impairment, I informed Ndi that I wanted her to perform standardized field sobriety tests, to which she agreed to the tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed at the location of the stop. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear. Lighting conditions consisted of headlights, spotlight, and flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Ndi appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. I observed her to be wearing a brown sweater, black dress and brown/black heels (off for walk and turn and one leg stand test).  I asked Ndi the following questions:  Glasses or Contact  Glasses (for driving). Head injuries  No Medication  No Problems with knees or ankles  No  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual.  - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus.    Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes     Moved head when instructed to keep her head still.  WALK AND TURN (5/8 clues observed) The test was properly demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual, but not demonstrated. Ndi stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed.   Instructional Stage:    Lost balance and stepped completely offline to the right 2 times.  Started the test prior to being instructed    Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Stopped prior to the turn.  Turn: Turned right using both feet.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine):    Stepped completely offline on step 2.  ONE LEG STAND (1/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual.  Ndi stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. -Right foot raised.  Balance and Count Stage:    Swayed left and right   PBT #209455 with a result of .09 BrAC.   ARREST Due to the number of observations, I concluded Ndi was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 2300 hours, I placed Ndi under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. Ndi was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and transported to the Baltimore County Towson Precinct for processing.   11-year-old daughter transported to the precinct and released to aunt.   Upon arrival at the precinct, I provided Ndi with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. She listened to the form from the MVA website. At 2340 hours, Ndi agreed to take a breath test.  20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Ndi beginning at 2324 hours. A preliminary search of Ndi was conducted and it revealed that she had nothing in her mouth. Ndi was observed from the time until the time she submitted to the test and she did not put anything in her mouth. The test was conducted by Ofc Pugh of the Baltimore County Police on a certified instrument. Ndi had a result of .09 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 2354 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: ****.09 grams of alcohol****  Ndi was polite and cooperative during the encounter. Ndi was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 23:33:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 20:30:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495657</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 23:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 23:35:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/17/2023 23:35:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>46</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 23:35:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:25</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369421</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ndi</LastName>
               <FirstName>Florence</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>S</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/29/1976 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/17/2023 23:28:21</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F465</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ndi</LastName>
               <FirstName>Florence</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>S</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/29/1976 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>N300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F465</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/17/2023 23:28:21</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 23:36:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 23:36:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 23:35:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/17/2023 23:35:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149937</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AL</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 23:37:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/17/2023 23:37:26</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HYUN</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SANTAFE</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2BZ8388</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>