<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000898</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/08/2023 04:03:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/08/2023 04:03:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/08/2023 03:53:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/08/2023 03:53:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 04:03:44</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5162</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 13:46:41</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MD-2,LUSBY</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>316363</AddressId>
      <City>MDC464</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 04:03:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 02:27:34</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>316363</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Maryland Route 4 at Cove Point Road</StreetName>
         <City>Lusby</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20657</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.436071</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.388674</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/08/2023 04:03:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/08/2023 04:03:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2023 05:32:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 04:03:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:23:00</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Alcohol Influence Report Patrol Vehicle Information U-40 (Marked) is equipped with a mobile recording device, however, it was not operational during this incident. I am also equipped with a BWC (Body Worn Camera), which was operational.  Defendant: Titus, Daniel Robert Date of Birth: 04/14/1986 Date of Arrest: 01/08/2023 Time of Arrest: 0403 Maryland SDX: T-320-135-745-290 License Status  Valid License Restrictions  B Registration Violations  None  Officers Training/Experience * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Anne Arundel County Police Department, Maryland State Police Department, and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police * Certified Drug Recognition Expert since 2017 * Graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute 2019  *Repeat Offender* - Yes  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On 01/08/2023, at approximately 0354hours, I, Trooper Koehler #7524,was conducting routine patrol in the area of H G Trueman Road at Town Square Drive, Lusby, Calvert County Maryland. While traveling north on H G Trueman Road prior to Town Square Drive, I could observe a dark colored passenger car, making a right turn from Town Square Drive onto H G Trueman Road, in front of my patrol vehicle, now headed in the same direction. The vehicle was later identified as a blue Nissan Versa displaying Maryland registration 9ES8929. The vehicle appeared to be traveling at a speed above the posted speed limit as it was quickly gaining distance between my patrol vehicle. I activated my Golden Eagle radar unit (serial number XE05245) in moving/same direction mode and obtained a digital speed reading on the Nissan at 61 mph in a posted 50 mph zone. I continued traveling behind the Nissan making additional observations. The Nissan made a left turn onto Cove Point Road, headed towards Maryland Route 4. The Nissan approached the intersection of Cove Point Road and Maryland Route 4, with a steady red circular light. The Nissan slowed down and rolled through the intersection, failing to make a complete stop at the stop light. The Nissan made a right turn and continued north on Maryland Route 4. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop. The vehicle pulled over immediately in the right shoulder of the highway.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I exited my patrol car and made contact at the driver side B pillar of the vehicle. I made contact with the driver/sole occupant, who was later positively identified via hisMaryland drivers license as Daniel Robert Titus (W/M, DOB : 04/14/1986). Titus was advised that I was a Maryland State Trooper and the stop was being recorded with audio and video. Titus was advised of the reason for the stop. I could see that Titus was avoiding eye contact with me. Titus provided me with his license and stated that the vehicle was his moms. Titus then reached toward the passenger side glove compartment, opening the door and began looking for the registration. Titus stated that he believed, I stopped him for making a California stop. Titus continued rummaging through the glove compartment unable to locate the registration. Titus asked if there was any way I could just run the tags. Titus also asked me if the recorded event captured the fact that I did not use my turn signal prior to stopping him. Titus then began looking for the registration in the sun visor above his head. Titus was questioned about the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from within the vehicle. Titus then pointed out the box of wine, lying on the front passenger floorboard, stating that it was not opened. Titus explained that he had consumed one glass of wine prior to leaving approximately 10 minutes ago. Titus was observed to have bloodshot eyes.  Titus then consented to submitting to the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Titus was wearing black pants, a black hooded sweatshirt, and black tennis shoes. After stepping out of his vehicle and speaking with me face to face, I could smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed in front of Titus vehicle where the roadway was level with no debris. My forward facing, flashing lights were deactivated. Titus stated he was not sick or injured. Titus was asked about being diabetic or epileptic. Titus stated he does have seizures but they are tonic. Titus stated he does not take insulin.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my penwas usedas the stimulus, and held approximately 12 inches from Tituss eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Tituss pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting Nystagmus. When asked, Titus stated that he understood the instructions.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Vertical Nystagmus  Not present  WALK AND TURN (3/8 clues observed)  Prior to Titus performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. An imaginary line was utilized for this test. This test was conducted in front of Titus vehicle.   Instructional Stage: - Lost balance and failed to maintain a heel to toe stance, as instructed.                 -Titus also started walking before instructed to do so.  Walking Stage (1st Nine): -Used his arms for balance on all nine steps  Turn :Correct  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): -Used his arms for balance on all nine steps     ONE LEG STAND (0/4 clues observed)  Prior to Titus performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. After explaining the test, Titus stated that he understood.  Instructional Stage: Remained as demonstrated  Balance and Count Stage: No clues observed                         Titus was offered and refused a preliminary breath test.   ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Titus was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol  -6/6 HGN -3/8 WAT -0/4 OLS -Alcoholic beverage container inside of vehicle -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from breath -Admitted to drinking alcohol prior to operating his motor vehicle.  Due to the number of observations, I concluded Titus was driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. I placed Titus under arrest at 0403 hours. Tituss vehicle was parked and secured on the shoulder of the highway.  Titus was then read aloud the DR-15 Advice of Rights form using the MVA audio file on my computer in my patrol vehicle. After hearing his rights and being provided the form to read along with, Titus, agreed to provide a breath specimen. Sgt. Newman #3029 completed the intoximeter test at 0446 hours, which revealed Tituss breath specimen contained .14 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  Tituss license status at the time of this incident was valid with no restrictions. A DR-15A form was completed and Titus was issued a temporary license. Titus was provided with his copies of the MVA related forms, and his traffic citations.  Titus was released from the Prince Frederick Barrack to a sober driver.   All events occurred in Calvert County, Maryland.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: .14  Case Status : Closed </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 03:21:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 05:14:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6945</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oleksak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jaroslaw</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6300</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Koehler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7524</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490275</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/08/2023 03:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 05:39:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 05:39:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>36</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 05:41:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>257037</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Titus</LastName>
               <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Robert</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/14/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/01/2020 20:29:20</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Titus</LastName>
               <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Robert</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/14/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/01/2020 20:29:20</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11833</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Spruce</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Lusby</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20657</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2566</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.429001</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.36236</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 02:31:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 02:31:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 05:39:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 05:39:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148387</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 05:58:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 05:58:06</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3N1CN7AP3KL810542</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>VRS</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLU</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9ES8929</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>