<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009374</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/14/2023 21:14:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/14/2023 21:14:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/14/2023 19:53:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/14/2023 19:53:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DECEASED PERSON NOT HOMICIDE OR SUICIDE</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 21:14:46</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5585</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/23/2023 10:30:09</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>95102</AddressId>
      <City>MDC100</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 21:14:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 22:38:05</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>95102</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>3428</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>CHURCHVILLE</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>ABERDEEN</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.22182614368646</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.53957158292164</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/14/2023 21:14:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/14/2023 21:14:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>03/14/2023 23:41:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 21:14:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5585</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/23/2023 10:30:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>NARRATIVE On March 14, 2023, at approximately 1954 hours, I, Trooper First Class Reckeweg #7214 of the Maryland State Police currently assigned to the Bel Air Barrack (Unmarked MSP patrol vehicle D-24), was dispatched to a check the welfare of Shipley, Larry Joe (W/M, DOB 10/26/1952) at 3428 Churchville Road, Aberdeen, Maryland 21001. Upon arrival, I contacted Shipley, Terry Harold (W/M, DOB 11/29/1948), who advised me that his brother Larry had not been answering his texts or phone calls since Sunday, and the last time he saw him was Saturday. Terry advised that his brothers wife passed away a couple of years ago, and Larry lives alone in the house. I was then contacted by a neighbor Klara, Terry Michael (W/M, DOB 09/06/1965), who told me that he had not seen Larry in the last couple of days and the lights on the house were completely off, which is not something normal. Terry had a spare key to the garage, where a spare key to the house was found. At approximately 2049 hours, Senior Trooper Whittenberg #6095 arrived on the scene, and we conducted a search of the house. Upon entering the house I observed Shipley, Larry lying on the floor with his face down (between the hallway and living room). Larrys body was blue, he did not have a pulse, and there were obvious signs that Larry was deceased for several days. Larrys physician Silverstein, Christy (DOB10/25/1964), was contacted (410-939-5843) and advised that Larrys death was by natural causes. Due to this Terry Shipley contacted a funeral home to make arrangements to retrieve the body. The Criminal Enforcement Division was contacted and responded to the scene. When S/T Orem #5656 arrived on scene, he was provided all additional information that was gathered on scene and will continue his investigation. The brother of the deceased was advised to contact the Barrack if he would need any further assistance.  I request this case remain open, until S/T Orem has completed his investigation.   All the events occurred in Harford County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 22:37:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 23:36:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Whittenberg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6095</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mott</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6918</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sander</LastName>
            <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5948</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>70</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 22:39:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:35</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371606</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>SHIPLEY</LastName>
               <FirstName>LARRY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>JOE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/26/1952 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/14/2023 22:39:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S140</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>SHIPLEY</LastName>
               <FirstName>LARRY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>JOE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/26/1952 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S140</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/14/2023 22:39:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3428</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>CHURCHVILLE</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>ABERDEEN</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.22182614368646</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.53957158292164</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>D</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 22:39:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/20/2023 12:35:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/20/2023 12:35:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/23/2023 10:30:08</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5656</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 12:35:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5585</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/23/2023 10:30:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> On March 14, 2023 at approximately 2100 hours, I was requested to respond to 3428 Churchville Rd, Aberdeen, MD to assist the Bel Air Barrack with an unattended death. Upon my arrival at the residence, I made contact with the initial arriving Troopers who briefed me on the situation. According to the Troopers, they received a call for service by the decedents brother, Terry Shipley, because he had been unable to make contact with the deceased for several days. When Troopers arrived on scene, they were met by Terry who advised he had tried to gain access to the residence, but was unable to do so. They were then able to locate a house key in the garage which Troopers used to enter the residence with Terrys permission. Once inside, they located the deceased.   After speaking with the Troopers, I went into the residence to observe the scene. Once inside, I located an older, white male lying face down on the floor between the living room and dining room of the residence. The subject was fully clothed wearing pants, a t- shirt and shoes and only his neck, head and arms were exposed. The parts of his body that were exposed were visibly bluish/ purple and it was clearly evident that he had been deceased and in that position for some time. I also observed a small puddle of blood under the deceaseds face that appeared to have come from his mouth/ nose. A search of the decedents body revealed a wallet in his left front pocket which contained a Maryland drivers license with the name Larry Joe Shipley (DOB: 10/26/1952). The photograph from that license was used to positively identify the deceased. An examination of Shipleys body and residence revealed no signs of trauma or any nefarious acts. Photographs were taken of the deceased and the area immediately surrounding his body and were later uploaded to the case file.   Troopers on scene had already learned from Terry Shipley that Larry was being treated by Dr. C. Silverstein for high blood pressure. Troopers obtained a phone number for Dr. Silverstein and called her explaining the circumstances. Dr. Silverstein agreed based on her knowledge of Shipleys health and the circumstances in which he was found to sign his death certificate indicating a natural death. The OCME was also contacted to screen the circumstances. At approximately 2141 hours, I received a phone call from Forensic Investigator Diane Lawder to discuss the incident. After explaining the circumstances to Lawder, she agreed that there was no need for a forensic investigator to respond to the scene and provided an OCME declination number of 23-03438. Terry Shipley would then contact McComas Funeral Home to arrange transportation.   After examining Shipley and the residence, I made contact with Terry Shipley. Terry advised that Larry lives alone in the residence after his wife passed away a few years prior. He went on to say that he last saw Larry on Thursday, March 9, 2023 when Larry stopped by his house to get some medications to take to their father. At that time, everything seemed fine and Larry had no complaints of any health issues. When he spoke with Larry Thursday, Larry did disclose that he had fallen coming up the stairs from the basement a couple days prior, but advised that he had no complications from the fall Terry also stated he knew Larry was on medication for high blood pressure which was being treated by his doctor. He also stated Larry may take medication for cholesterol as well, but he was not certain. Otherwise, Terry indicated Larry was in relatively good health. Terry also advised that Larry is an occasional alcohol drinker, but I did not locate any indication that he had been drinking prior to his death. Terry stated he had been making attempts to contact Larry since Sunday, March 12, but all of his attempts were unsuccessful leading him to drive to the house to check on Larry that night.   At approximately 2220 hours, representatives from McComas Funeral Home arrived on scene and transported the deceased. After Shipley was removed, the residence was secured and the key, Larrys wallet and cell phone were all given to Terry as he was not ready to go into the residence. Case closed as Shipleys cause of death was determined to be natural. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5656</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 12:43:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5656</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 12:44:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hall</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bradley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5585</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Orem</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5656</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>