<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-004619</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/06/2023 00:07:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/06/2023 00:07:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/05/2023 23:53:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/05/2023 23:53:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI Arrest</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 00:07:48</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4899</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/31/2023 12:48:04</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>531048</AddressId>
      <City>MDC140</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/09/2023 02:35:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/09/2023 02:36:02</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>531048</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Capital Beltway</StreetName>
         <City>Hyattsville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>AVE</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.84689</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.89216</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L 214</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 CAPITAL BELTWAY / 0-0 CENTRAL AVE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/06/2023 00:07:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/06/2023 00:07:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/31/2023 12:48:05</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 00:07:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:20:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>L-35 is equipped with a mobile recording device, this incident was recorded. This incident was also recorded with my body-worn camera.  Defendant: Sabrina Antonia Cheshier  Date of Birth: 10/12/1978  Date of Arrest: 02/06/2023  Time of Arrest: 0005 hours  MD License #: MD-10273217580  DUI #: 23-043    TRAINING/CERTIFICATES         Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration on December 5th-8th, 2022.      Trained in administering Preliminary Breath Tests through the Maryland State Police Forensics Science Division on December 9, 2022.       Vehicle in Motion (Phase 1):    On February 5, 2023 at approximately 2353 hours, I, Trooper Stacey #7390 and Trooper Figueroa-Stalk #7353 (field training Trooper) were on patrol enforcing speed on southbound I-495 in the area of Maryland Route 214, in Prince Georges County, Maryland. I observed a black Ford Edge traveling in lane one which appeared to be traveling above the posted speed limit. I directed my Pro Laser 3 serial #LF04533 at the vehicle. I observed a speed of 80 MPH in a posted 55 MPH zone. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the black Ford Edge. I made contact with the driver Sabrina Antonia Cheshier (B/F, DOB 10/12/1978), whom I identified by her Maryland Drivers License.    Personal Contact (Phase 2):    I approached the vehicle via passenger side approach and observed Cheshier, seated behind the drivers seat, retrieving her documents. I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I also noticed a red solo cup, placed on the passenger side floorboard of the vehicle which appeared to contain alcohol. When I questioned Cheshier about the cup, she advised her son, seated in the passenger seat, was 21 (it should be noted, I never asked her sons age or mentioned there being alcohol in the cup. As well as both center console cup holders being empty). Cheshiers eyes appeared to be glassy and bloodshot. Cheshier advised she was coming from a family event and had not been drinking. I then asked Cheshier to exit the vehicle, to perform a series of Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Once Cheshier exited the vehicle, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person.    Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3):  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of the roadway. The weather was clear and approximately 40 degrees. Lighting conditions were dark. The ground was level and free of any debris. My patrol vehicles overhead emergency lights in the front were deactivated prior to field sobriety tests as well as the vehicles spot light. Cheshier was wearing a sweatshirt, jeans, and flat heeled boots. Cheshier appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any signs of visible injuries.   I asked Cheshier the following questions:    Medication: Yes, for high blood pressure.  Medical Conditions: Transplant survivor.   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)    The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from her eyes. Cheshier was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes. Cheshiers pupils were of equal size and showed equal tracking.   Cheshier displayed the following clues:        Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes      Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes      Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes         WALK AND TURN TEST (2/8 clues observed)    Prior toMs. Cheshierperforming the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted.Ms. Cheshier was instructed to place herright foot directly in front of herleft foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary line.Ms.Cheshierwas instructed and demonstrated to place herhands flat at hersides and to remain in that position until told to begin.Ms. Cheshierwas advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Ms. Cheshierwas instructed to keep herhands flat at hersides, keep hereyes focused on herfeet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step,Ms. Cheshierwas explained and demonstrated to keep herlead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with herrear foot to the left to turn completely around.Ms. Cheshierwas again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series.Ms. Cheshierwas instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep herhands down by hersides, look down at herfeet, and count each step out loud.    Instructional Stage:        Cannot keep balance during instruction       Walking Stage (1st set of nine steps):      Does not touch heel to toe for all 9 steps       Walking Stage (2nd set of nine steps):      Does not touch heel to toe for all 9 steps       ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)  Prior to Ms. Cheshier performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. She was instructed to stand with her feettogether and hands down by her side while the instructions were given. During the test she was instructed not to begin the test until she was instructed to start once the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop.Ms. Cheshier advised she had no questions.  Cheshier displayed the following clues:    Raises arms for balance:  0 to 10  11 to 20  21 to 30    Foot down:  0 to 10  11 to 20  21 to 30    Sways:  0 to 10  11 to 20  21 to 30    Cheshier was offered a Preliminary Breath Test to which she refused.    ARREST    Based on the following, I had reason to believe Cheshier was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:        Odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from vehicle and her breath      Took a extended amount of time to obtain drivers license      Red solo cup on passenger side floorboard      Eyes glassy and bloodshot      Odor of an alcoholic beverage      Clues observed during field sobriety         Cheshier was arrested at 0005 hours. Cheshier was transported to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack. At approximately 1211 hours, Cheshier listened to the English audio recording of the DR15 which was played aloud in L-35. Cheshier accepted to take the intoximeter examination test. The test was conducted by Trooper Peris #7511 who is a certified breath intoximeter operator. Cheshier test results were .15 BrAC. Cheshier was given the appropriate citations and was released to Mr. Eric Cheshier at 0150 hours.    All of the above events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.     </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 01:26:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 03:27:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Figueroa-Stalk</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jashaun</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7353</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reid</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7458</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hershberger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gavin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7444</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Floyd</LastName>
            <FirstName>Shawn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4899</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stacey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7390</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494002</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/05/2023 23:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 00:40:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/06/2023 00:40:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>44</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 00:45:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:20</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370834</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cheshier</LastName>
               <FirstName>Sabrina</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Antonia</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/12/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/06/2023 00:44:23</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S165</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cheshier</LastName>
               <FirstName>Sabrina</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Antonia</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/12/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S165</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/06/2023 00:44:23</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9304</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Fox Run Dr</StreetName>
               <City>Clinton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20735</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 00:45:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 00:45:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 00:45:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 00:40:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/06/2023 00:40:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150563</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 00:45:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/06/2023 00:45:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>EDG</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7EM0051</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>