<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009895</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/19/2023 01:49:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/19/2023 01:49:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/19/2023 01:36:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/19/2023 01:36:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The vehicle was stopped for a traffic violation, and the driver was arrested for DUI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 01:50:01</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3033</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 09:26:46</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY/ W SEVENTH ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>586435</AddressId>
      <City>MDC246</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 01:50:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 01:01:25</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>586435</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Catoctin Mountain</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Frederick</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>W</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-77.419596</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.428689</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY / W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>NB CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY RAMP TO W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY SB /W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MM 13</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY SB  /W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY NB /  W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY / W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY / AT W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY NB / W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY / 1120-1179 W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY SB  /  W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY SB /  W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY / 1200-1209 W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>15SB/ W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY NB  / W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>US-15 SB /  W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>NB</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 CATOCTIN MOUNTAIN HWY / 1180-1198 W SEVENTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/19/2023 01:49:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/19/2023 01:49:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/30/2023 11:35:37</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 01:50:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:20:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was recorded; B-68 is equipped with an in-car camera system and body camera. Assisting Trooper- TFC Sweckard (#7221)B-34 is equipped with an in-car camera system and body worn camera. Defendant: Bastien, Allan Mario (1/M, DOB: 02/25/1984)  Date and time of arrest: 03/19/2023 01:48 hours New York Drivers License: 283001478                                           Case Number: 23-MSP-009895  Troopers Certification and training   Trained in Standardized Field Sobriety Test through the Maryland State Police.  Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) in March 2021.  Vehicle in Motion: (Phase 1):  On 03/19/2023 at approximately 0137 hours, I, TFC Devin (#7046) ofthe Maryland State Police Frederick Barrack was operating marked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle B-68. At this time and location, I was on patrol in the vicinity of northbound US Route 15 at West Frederick Street, when I observed a black Ford Fusion, failing to obey traffic control device instructions, which caught my immediate attention. The black Ford Fusion was following behind a tractor trailer that was traveling in lane two.   I positioned my patrol vehicle directly behind the black Ford Fusion, and followed it for a duration of approximately 1 mile. During this distance, I observed the black Ford Fusion cross over the dotted lane divider from lane two into lane one by two tire widths, on one occasion for a distance of approximately 25 yards. I then observed the black Ford Fusion swerve from lane two, into lane one by 1/2 of a vehicle width, on two separate occasions for a distance of approximately 15 yards. The black Ford Fusion was weaving, swerving, and had erratic movements during this observation period. The driver of the vehicle activated the right turn signal to exit from northbound US Route 15 onto West 7th Street in Frederick, Maryland.   After observing the violations,I activated my emergency equipment, to conduct a traffic stop on the black Ford Fusion. The Ford Fusion then took the exit onto West 7th Street as I followed behind. The black Ford Fusion came to a stop on West 7th street in lane number two. The black Ford Fusion was bearing New York registration HDX7974.  PERSONAL CONTACT: (PHASE 2)   Upon contact with the operator, and sole occupant, I introduced myself, and explained the reason for the stop at the drivers side window. I requested thatthe driverprovide hislicense, and registration to the vehicle. While the driver was looking through his wallet, attempting to locate his license, I noticed his hands to be shaking. I identified the driver by his New York State Drivers License as, Allan Mario Bastien 1/M, (DOB: 02/25/1984). During our conversation, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Bastiens breath and person, as well asthe interior of the vehicle. Bastiens speech was slightly slurred and mumbled, during portions of our conversation.I observedBastiens eyes to be bloodshot, glassy, and watery. I asked Bastien how much he had to drink, and Bastien stated, One beer. I then asked how long it has been since he consumed the beer, and Bastien stated, Two hours. While Bastien was attempting to locate the other requested document, I leaned in towards the vehicles open window. At this time, I confirmed that the strong odor was emanating from Bastien breath / person. Bastien explained that he wasnt too sure where he was going, and that he was on his way home. I requested the Maryland State Police Frederick Barrack to start another unit to my location.    Upon the arrival of TFC Sweckard (#7221) of the Maryland State Police, I asked Bastien to exit hisvehicle. Irequested that Bastien perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests in front of his vehicle, and he agreed to do so.Bastien exited the vehicle and slowly walked to the front of his vehicle.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):  The Standardized Field Sobriety Tests were performed in frontof the suspects vehicle, on the right portion of lane two, on West 7th Street. The surface was dry, level, and free of debris. The weather was clear, and it was approximately 43 degrees in temperature. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlamps, and my flashlight. There were no surface defects to the pavement. Prior to the test, TFC Sweckard deactivated the front facing emergency lights of B-68 during all phases of tests. Bastien was wearing sneakers, and did not removethem during any phase of the tests. Bastien was also dressed in warm clothing, including a winter jacket.    I asked Bastien the following questions:  -Daily/Regular Medications- Just an allergy pill during the day.  -Glasses or Contacts- None  -Injuries- Advised that he injured his upper right hip at work.   Prior to conducting the HGN test, I askedBastien to be honest about how much he had to drink.Bastien stated, I had one beer and one mixed drink. This was inconsistent with his previous voluntary admission of just One     beer.   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS:(6/6 clues observed).   I used the end of my indexfinger as a stimulus and held it approximately 12 to 15 inches from Bastiens eyes. His eyes displayed resting nystagmus, and his pupils were equal in size. His eyes also showed equal tracking. He was advised to stand with his feet together, withhis hands down at his sides during the instruction/demonstration and throughout the test. I observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I continued to detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Bastiens breath. Bastien was instructed to follow the stimulus with his eyes only and to keep his head still and positioned straight forward. Bastien attempted the test with the following results.  1. Lack of smooth pursuit - Present in both eyes. 2. Distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation- Present both eyes. 3. Onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees- Present in both eyes.  VERTICAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS- Was present in both of Bastiens eyes. Not a validated clue, but I had to remind Bastien to stop moving his head two times during the HGN test.  WALK AND TURN:(4/8 clues observed).   I explained and demonstrated how to properly perform the test prior to Bastien taking it. Bastien was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot, and touch heel-to-toe. Bastien was instructed, and I demonstrated, how to place his hands flat at his sides, and remain in that position until told to begin. He was instructed to take nine (9) heel-to-toe steps in a straight line. Bastien was told to keep his hands flat at his sides, to keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step out loud.  On the ninth step, Bastien was instructed, and I demonstrated, how to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Bastien was again instructed, and I demonstrated, the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Bastien was instructed that once he began the test, he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, to keep his hands down at his sides, and to count each step out loud.    After I was done explaining the test, I asked Bastien if he understood the instructions, and he stated, Yes. I then asked Bastien if he had any questions before he began the test, and he repeated that he was to take 9 steps in a straight line.I advised that was correct, and then he advised that he understood and had no additional questions.  Instructional Stage: -Completed correctly, but did lift his arms from his sides on several occasions.  Walking Stage: (1stNine Steps) -Steps off-line- with right foot on step 3 by approximately 3 inches. -Misses heel-to-toe- On step, 2,4, and 6 by approximately twoinches on each step. -Incorrect number of steps- 8 steps on the first series. On step one he counted, but did not take the first step.  The Turn: -Improper turn- Bastien placed his feet together and quickly spun in the opposite direction. After turning he stood straight up, paused, and stumbled / leaned forward, in attempt to maintain his balance. Walking Stage: (2ndNine Steps)  -Steps off-line- On step 4 by approximately 3 inches. (right foot)  ONE LEG STAND: (3/4clues observed). Right foot lifted during test. * Prior to this test, Bastien reminds me that he is just three minutes from his home. *  Prior to Bastien performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Bastien was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides. When instructed to start he was to raise the foot of his choice approximately six inches off the ground, point his foot, look down at his foot, and to count out aloud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two), and continue counting until instructed to stop. After I was finished explaining the test to Bastien, I asked if he understood the instructions, and he stated, Yes. I then asked Bastien if he had any questions before he began the test, and he stated, What do I count to. I then advised, until I say stop.  Balancing and Counting Stage:  0-10 Seconds:   -Lifts arms- Approximately 20 inches from his sides on all counts.   11-20 Seconds:    -Lifts arms- Approximately 30 inches from his sides on all counts. -Sways- On counts 11-20 approximately 4 inches side to side.   21-30 Seconds:     - Sways in a circular motion / side to side by approximately two inches.  -Puts foot down on counts 24-27.  -Lifts arms- approximately 30 inches from his sides on all counts.    ARREST:  **Based on the following, I had reason to believe Bastien was operating a motor vehicle Under the Influence of Alcohol.**    Vehicle extensively failed to maintain a single lane while traveling.  Vehicle had erratic movements, and was weaving in its lane of travel.  The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanatingfrom Bastiens breath and person before, and after hisarrest.  Bastiens speech was slurred / mumbled, during our conversation.  Bastiens eyes were glassy, bloodshot, and watery.  Bastien admittedthat he consumed one beer two hours ago. Then advised one beer, and one mixed drink. Then just one mixed drink approximately one hour ago, prior to being stopped.   Inconstant answers of the alcohol that he had consumed, and the amount of time that had passed since his last drink.   Bastien reminded me several times that he was just minutes away from his residence prior to his arrest.   Signs of impairment as he performed the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Results are as follows, HGN-6/6, WAT-4/8, and OLS-3/4.      Based on my observations, I placed Bastien under arrest at 01:48 hours for Driving under the Influence of Alcohol. A search incident to his arrest was conducted on the roadside, and it revealed that Bastien had nothing in his mouth. I did not locate any contraband on his person.    I placed Bastien in the front seat of my patrol vehicle. I played the audio version of theDR-15 Adviceof Rights form audio version for Bastien in English, which is available on the MVA website. Bastien was also provided the DR-15 Advise of Rights form, so he could follow along with the audio. Bastien asked if I could play the audio again, prior to him making his final decision. At 02:28 hours, Bastien elected to refused an Intoximetertest andsignedthe DR-15 Adviseof Rights form.   Bastien was issued several citations for the impaired driving offense, andwas released to his girlfriend, Falon, who was sober adult. Bastien was given all copies of pertinent paperwork before being released. Bastien was polite, and cooperative during the entire process.     I request this case be closed by arrest.     All events occurred in Frederick County, Maryland.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:40:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7046</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 00:50:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweckard</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7221</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Devin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dane</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7046</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Conklin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5549</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Devin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dane</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7046</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Devin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dane</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7046</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499295</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:35:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7046</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 21:38:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499295</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:35:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7046</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 21:39:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499295</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:35:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7046</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 21:38:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499295</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:35:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7046</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 21:37:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499295</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:35:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7046</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 21:37:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499295</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:35:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7046</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 21:36:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:35:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:27</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371996</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Allan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Mario</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Bastien</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/25/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 21:23:17</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A450</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Allan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Mario</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Bastien</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/25/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>A450</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 21:23:17</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>216-17</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>115th</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Cambria HTS</City>
               <StateCode>NY</StateCode>
               <Zip5>11411</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1111</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-73.741231</Longitude>
               <Latitude>40.69956</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:40:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:40:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:40:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:40:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:40:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:35:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7046</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 21:35:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151053</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7046</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 01:00:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7046</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 01:00:00</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>B016971373207176184</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FUS</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>NY</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>HDX7974</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2022</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>