<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-001155</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/10/2023 14:34:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/10/2023 14:34:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/10/2023 14:10:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/10/2023 14:10:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Stolen Vehicle Recovery</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 14:34:52</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/28/2023 20:56:43</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>RSP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>73172</AddressId>
      <City>MDC249</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 14:34:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/11/2023 06:53:00</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>73172</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>580</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>BALTIMORE</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>WESTMINSTER</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.97612352524051</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.565614025807626</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>HERITAGE HONDA</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/10/2023 14:34:49</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/10/2023 14:34:49</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>Y</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/05/2023 06:48:18</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 14:34:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>THIS INVESTIGATION WAS NOT AUDIBLY AND VISUALLY RECORDED  SCENE PROCESSING:  Photographs were taken of the stolen vehicle. A false vin plate (5J6RW2H51MA000200) attached to the frame was removed, revealing the actual VIN of the vehicle (2HKRW2H51NH653562). The vehicle was then towed back to the Maryland State Police Westminster Barracks for storage.  SUSPECT:  Unknown  CHARGES:  None due to no known suspect  NARRATIVE:  On January 10, 2023, at approximately 1350 hours, I, Trooper First Class Mills #6784, was dispatched to Heritage Honda located at 580 Baltimore Boulevard, Westminster, Carroll County, Maryland, in reference to an auto theft case that was being investigated by the National Insurance Crime Bureau (NICB). At this time, I was operating unmarked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle, G-18. Prior to arriving at the scene, I was instructed by Deborah Clark of the NICB to investigate a 2021 gray Honda CRV displaying a potential fraudulent VIN 5J6RW2H51MA000200 by inspecting the VIN plates and component parts to ensure if the VIN on the vehicle was counterfeit. She advised that the Honda was potentially stolen and that the vehicle was underwent a CARCO pre-insurance inspection on 10/24/2022 at Viper Collision, 338 Uniondale Avenue, Uniondale, NY 11553. The registered owner at this time was Jose Elmer Castillo (DOB 09/28/1988 H/M NY Drivers License Number: 556026582 Address: 600 Fulton Avenue, 34E, Hempstead, NY 11550). It was also revealed that there was no shipping record, the first odometer reading In CARFAX is 936 on 10/15/2022, and theEPA label was not consistent with other vehicles of this year, make, and model. During this time, the vehicle had a New York tag assigned to it which was KYS9844, different from what was on it when it was reported stolen. On January 4, 2023, the NICB received a lead that the current owner submitted a fraudulent or altered New Jersey title for this vehicle. NMVTIS had no record of New Jersey ever issuing a title. Shortly after, another lead was discovered by the NICB that the Honda had been recently listed for sale on Cars.com (https://www.cars.com/vehicledetail/fba2a6d5-3d91-4055-bd39-4ad89dffb677/) and was located at Heritage Honda in Westminster, Maryland.  Once I arrived at the scene, I checked the parking lot of Heritage Honda and did not observe the vehicle in question. I then went inside and spoke with the sales manager, who was later identified by his Maryland drivers license as John Walter Schoppert Jr. (DOB 07/06/1988 W/M). I asked him if they had the vehicle in question, and he performed an inventory check by using the last six numbers of the vehicle identification number (VIN), which was 000200. Schoppert Jr. advised that they did have the vehicle and added that it was in their service center due to the vehicle being recently delivered. Schoppert Jr. then escorted me over to the service center and showed me the vehicle that was in the garage bay. I informed Schoppert Jr. of why I wanted to see the vehicle, and he stated that the vehicle was mine and that I could do whatever I needed to do. I then checked the VIN displayed on the lower left corner of the windshield, and it was 5J6RW2H51MA000200. The same VIN number was also listed on the B pillar of the Honda. An additional VIN was checked, which was located under the front right passenger floorboard. The VIN displayed matched both VINs that were observed.  Due to my observations, I contacted Deborah Clark via telephone (240-534-9233) and informed her of my findings. She then placed me on a conference call with her supervisor, Chris Doyle. While on the conference call, Doyle advised me of a theft scheme that was taking place with vehicles. He then asked that I read the engine number to him over the phone, which I completed. Mechanics, Ryan Scott Grossnickle (DOB 06/02/1983 W/M), Kyle Parker Morgan (DOB 06/04/1985 W/M), and Robert Wayne Knight Jr. (DOB 08/07/1994 W/M) assisted me in finding the component numbers. After the engine number was read, Doyle ran a check on the component part, and it was revealed that the engine did not come back to the VIN that was displayed. This confirmed that the Honda returned to the correct VIN and was stolen out of New York. Doyle then advised me that the VINs displayed in the three locations I saw were fictitious. He then advised that if I pulled the carpet up on the front right passenger floorboard, the fictitious VIN could be removed. Grossnickle then removed the passenger door trim and removed the carpet, exposing white Bondo dust. Doyle then advised that the VIN could be removed with a hammer and a small chiseling device. Grossnickle then got the appropriate tools and removed the fictitious VIN that was attached to the frame. Under the fictitious VIN, another VIN was exposed, which was stamped into the frame. The correct VIN that was revealed was 2HKRW2H51NH653562.  Furthermore, an engine code reader was plugged into the electronic control module of the Honda, and it revealed that the Hondas internal computer system had been reprogrammed to display the fictitious VIN. A check through M.E.T.E.R.S. revealed that the Honda was reported stolen through the New York Police Department on 10/02/2022. The vehicle was then stored (MVI 23-001). The reporting and confirming agency was the New York Police Department, and their case number is 2022062006513. According to the original theft report, the theft occurred between 09/30/2022 at 1700 hours to 10/02/2022 at 1300 hours. The value of the Honda at the time of the reported theft was $39,000. The owner of the vehicle, Anna V Duffy (DOB: 01/19/1972), was later contacted via telephone (347-751-4457), and she advised that at no time was anyone given permission to remove or operate her Honda.  Matt Eckenrode of Rockdale Towing removed the vehicle from the scene, and I followed it back to the barrack, where it was secured in the wash bay area.  I request this case to remain open pending a forensic examination of the Honda.  All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 09:18:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/14/2023 02:27:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dale</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2927</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mills</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryder</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6784</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490533</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0480</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>41</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/10/2023 14:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 0480</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/16/2023 19:20:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/16/2023 19:20:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>50</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 07:03:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:54</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365779</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>DUFFY</LastName>
               <FirstName>ANNA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>V</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/19/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 16:54:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>DUFFY</LastName>
               <FirstName>ANNA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>V</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/19/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 16:54:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>288</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Bay 38th</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>BROOKLYN</City>
               <StateCode>NY</StateCode>
               <Zip5>11214</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-73.994263</Longitude>
               <Latitude>40.592851</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>347</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>751</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4457</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/16/2023 19:22:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:35</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/16/2023 19:22:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:35</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240004753</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>Heritage Honda Westminster</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 07:07:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/16/2023 19:22:10</UpdatorDate>
         <BusinessAddress>
            <AddressId>73180</AddressId>
            <StreetNumber>580</StreetNumber>
            <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
            <StreetName>Baltimore</StreetName>
            <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
            <City>Westminster</City>
            <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
            <Zip5>21157</Zip5>
            <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            <Longitude>-76.975434</Longitude>
            <Latitude>39.566197</Latitude>
            <BusinessPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>BUS</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>866</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>804</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9463</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/27/2014 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </BusinessPhone>
         </BusinessAddress>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148486</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>ST</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/16/2023 19:21:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/16/2023 19:21:18</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2HKRW2H51NH653562</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CR-V</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>NY</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>KYB4668</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehConditionCode>G</VehConditionCode>
         <VehDamageCode>0</VehDamageCode>
         <VehicleValue>39000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/14/2023 01:49:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/16/2023 19:12:55</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>821</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>39000</PropertyValue>
         <Value>39000</Value>
         <SerialNumber>2HKRW2H51NH653562</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>241436</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>GRY</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>GRY</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>HONDA</Make>
         <Model>CRV</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/13/2023 12:33:49</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/13/2023 12:33:49</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/05/2023 06:48:18</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6265</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 12:33:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>ATTACHMENTS:   Correspondence with Deborah Clark (NICB)   NYPD Stolen Vehicle Report: 2022-062-006513  NARRATIVE:   On January 10, 2023 I was contacted by the Westminster Barrack Detective Sergeant in reference to this case. Detective Sergeant Petras advised Westminster Troopers were contacted by the National Insurance Crime Bureau (NICB) in reference to a stolen vehicle at Heritage Honda in Westminster, MD. The vehicle was reported to have fraudulent VIN plates concealing the actual VIN of the vehicle which had previously been reported stolen through the New York Police Department (NYPD). Trooper Mills met with representatives of the Honda Dealer and located a fraudulent VIN plate glued over the factory applied number underneath the passenger side floorboard. The plate was removed from the vehicle, and the vehicle was towed and stored at the MSP Westminster Barrack.    I attempted to contact Detectives of the New York Police Department to obtain a copy of the initial police report and determine appropriate follow up. After multiple transfers and a lengthy hold time (30+minutes) I was disconnected and not able to make contact with an officer.    On January 13, 2023 I accompanied CST Roe as vehicle processing was initiated in the MSP Westminster Barrack wash bay. The vehicle was previously stored in this location with an associated chain of custody. CST Roe initiated photographs of the vehicle exterior and interior including the location where the fraudulent VIN plate was applied. The vehicle was extremely clean, and appeared to have been fully detailed prior to its recovery. There was an additional fraudulent VIN plate visible at the bottom of the front windshield on the drivers side. The plate would not be accessible from the interior of the vehicle without modifying and removing interior parts. When observing the exterior of the vehicle, there were plastic moulding and trim pieces that appeared to be missing around the perimeter of the windshield. The rubber gasket around the glass also appeared to have been tampered with. Based on this observation, it is believed the interior window VIN plate may have been replaced be removal of the front windshield. Processing of this location for prints and/or DNA was not immediately accessible and would require additional labor and an outside skilled professional to remove the glass for evidence recovery. Due to this, vehicle processing was discontinued pending contact with the initiating agency and/or interested parties to determine appropriate further action.    On January 13, 2023 I made contact with Phillip Doyle of the Mid-Atlantic Region National Insurance Crime Bureau. Doyle advised this vehicle was identified as suspicious due to the fraudulent VIN number that was applied only appearing in CARFAX shortly after October 2, 2022 which was the date the vehicle was reported stolen. Counterfeit VINs are identified by lack of prior history despite previous ownership and by the suspicious nature of the time-frame they are added to the CARFAX database. It was based on this information that the initial tip was provided to MSP Troopers by NICB.    In reference to the investigation, Doyle reached out to the task force officer involved in the larger stolen vehicle ring which this vehicle was believed to be a part of in the region of New York to North Carolina. The investigating officer relayed through Doyle that a suspect high in the organized criminal activity was previously charged for these vehicle thefts and had since been deported. Further processing of the vehicle was not requested at this time. Doyle did request that the counterfeit VIN plates be removed prior to the vehicle being released. He reported other agencies completing this task by cutting through the glass and prying off the VIN plates. He stated the repairs for such actions are completed through the insurance companies as part of their stolen vehicle recovery process and claim.    I have attached copies of the original correspondence with Doyle and the NYPD Police report to this supplement. I have spoken with D/Sgt. Petras as well as TFC Mills regarding this follow up. This concludes CED involvement with this case.    </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6265</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 12:34:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6265</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/16/2023 16:25:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dale</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2927</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barry</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6265</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/03/2023 19:28:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/03/2023 19:28:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/05/2023 06:48:18</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/03/2023 19:28:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On February 3, 2023, at approximately 1340 hours, I, Trooper First Class Mills #6784, responded to the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack where I met William Banahan, a member of the Investigations and Security Services section of the Maryland Department of Transportation Motor Vehicle Administration, to attempt to remove the fraudulent VIN plate from inside the windshield. Due to no time efficient response from State Farm Insurance (owner of the Honda) to have the windshield replaced in case of damage, picking the VIN plate was the only option. While Banahan attempted to pick the VIN plate, it was discovered that the fraudulent VIN plate was actually a sticker. Once the sticker was removed, a bare piece of shiny gray metal was revealed underneath. No other VIN was located due to the real VIN being removed from the vehicle. Due to the area of the VIN plate and mitigating damage to the windshield, the fraudulent VIN sticker could not be removed intact thus making the removed sticker of no evidentiary value. The Federal Certification Label mounted on the B pillar was also determined to be fraudulent. When the sticker was attempted to be removed, it was revealed that the sticker quality was unlike that of an actual label. When the sticker was attempted to be removed, the top portion of the sticker separated from the adhesive side which stayed affixed to the Honda. The removed fraudulent Federal Certification Label was documented on a MSP Form 67 Chain of Custody and stored at the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack. The internal computer module of the Honda still displays the fraudulent VIN and can only be fixed by a certified Honda repair center due to the encrypted computer system. State Farm was contacted so that they could be advised that the Honda could be removed from the barrack. All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/03/2023 19:30:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/03/2023 19:50:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dale</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2927</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mills</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryder</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6784</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>