<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009190</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/13/2023 11:03:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/13/2023 11:03:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/13/2023 10:55:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/13/2023 10:55:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The missing child was recovered without incident.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 11:03:50</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/20/2023 09:35:06</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>6800 AVIATION BLVD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>687184</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 11:03:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 16:07:36</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>687184</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>6800</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Aviation</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/13/2023 11:03:46</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/13/2023 11:03:46</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>04/20/2023 09:34:36</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 11:03:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/20/2023 09:34:37</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>ACTION TAKEN:   On March 6, 2023, Cpl. Heid was contacted by Anne Arundel County CPS requesting assistance in locating a missing 16 year old female. Cpl. Heid was advised that Seyenna Smith was last seen approximately 18 months ago at a group home in Charles County where she absconded. Cpl. Heid was provided a possible Instagram page for Smith. Since Cpl. Heid was in training, he sent the Instagram page to Special Agent Winn (FBI) to conduct a preliminary inquiry. While reviewing the photos on the page, SA Winn located one photo that showed a vehicle with a clear tag on it. SA Winn was able to confirm the vehicle to belong to Courtney Stanley of Elkton, Maryland.   Cpl. Heid was then able to run Stanley through E-Tix and found that she had been stopped a few weeks prior by TFC McDonald of the MSP JFK Barrack. When contacted, TFC McDonald was able to recall the traffic stop he had made. The driver originally identified herself as Courtney Stanley but he was later able to confirm that her sister, Sabrina Stanley, was the actual driver. Sabrina was subsequently issued additional charges in that matter. TFC McDonald was able to identify Seyenna as the person that was in the vehicle with Sabrina. She had provided a fictitious name as well. Sabrina provided an address of 259 Mackall Street in Elkton as her current address.   On March 13, 2023, Cpl. Heid, SA Winn, and TFC Donald responded to 259 Mackall Street where they made contact with Courtney Stanley. Courtney confirmed that Seyenna who she knew as CeeCee, was with Sabrina at her home approximately 2 weeks ago. Courtney checked her Find my iPhone and was able to place Sabrina at the Sleep Inn on the Fallsway, in Baltimore City. Cpl. Heid, SA Winn, TFC Mueller, SA Belcher and BPD Detective Terry Schurman, responded to the Sleep Inn and were able to make contact with Sabrina in Room 211. Sabrina brought Seyenna out to investigators without incident. Seyeena was interviewed by TFC Mueller and Cpl. Heid but provided no information to indicate that she was the victim of a crime. She did say that she had been working at a strip club on the block. That information will be followed up on by TFC Mueller and BPD. Seyenna was ultimately taken to the Childrens Home in Catonsville, Maryland, where she was released to Social Worker Bonnie Solderberg who would be taking Seyenna to the hospital for a COVID test.  CASE CLOSED</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP1621</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 16:08:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP1621</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 16:09:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Heid</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1621</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>