<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-007429</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/27/2023 09:03:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/27/2023 09:03:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/27/2023 09:03:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/27/2023 09:03:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Delayed disclosure of sexual assault</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/27/2023 09:04:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4970</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/18/2023 07:48:24</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SAS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>17054</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>933</SubBeat>
      <City>MDC149</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/27/2023 09:04:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/28/2023 13:22:22</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>17054</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>532</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>LIBERTY</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>FEDERALSBURG</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>933</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-75.75259005050272</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.69435461922641</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/27/2023 09:03:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/27/2023 09:03:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/18/2023 07:48:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/27/2023 09:04:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>  On February 13, 2023, The Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region (CEDER) investigators were notified by Caroline County Department of Social Services (DSS) about a delayed disclosure of a sexual assault that occurred in Federalsburg, Maryland between the time of 2014 or 2015. The juvenile female victim is identified as Aryiana Lake (DOB: 09/27/2010) (currently at the age of 12), hereinafter referred to as Lake. DSS advised CEDER investigators a Forensic interview would be conducted on Lake on February 27, 2023, at 0900 hours.   On February 27, 2023, at approximately 0930 hours, I, TFC Mingos, arrived at the Caroline DSS office in reference to an interview on Lake. The interview was conducted by CAC coordinator Morris. The interview is detailed below:  Interview: Aryaina Lake (DOB: 09/27/2010):   February 27, 2023, at approximately 0934 hours  Lake stated she was here today about something that happened in the past  Lake stated her grandmother went to the grocery store or something and she was left alone with her grandmothers boyfriend, later identified as Allen Lee Gantt Jr (1/M, DOB:06/23/1989)  Lake stated she was 5 or 6 years old when Gantt asked Lake to touch him on his private areas and stuff  Lake stated she cannot remember her grandmothers boyfriends name.   Interviewer asked Lake to clarify his private areas  Lake stated, his penis.  Lake stated she remembers Gantt telling her if she does it then she will get all the toys and stuff that she wanted, so lake did it.  Lake stated he asked me to touch it and he forced my head down and put it in my mouth.  Lake stated Gantt asked her to touch his penis with her hands.  Lake stated Gantt pushed her head down by the back of her head and held her down with his hands.  Lake stated she was forced to do it so she did it, and when it stopped she went back outside.  Lake stated, he forced his penis inside of my mouth and he kept my head down so I could not get back up.  Lake stated, he kept moving my head up and down.  Lake stated she told him to stop and he said, ok, fine. Lake stated she then went back outside.  Interviewer asked, tell me everything you tasted when this happened.  Lake stated, it tasted gewy. It was white and gewy.  Lake stated she saw something white on the bed before she ran out of the room.  Lake stated she saw a white, gewy, and sticky stuff. It was all over the bed.  Lake stated this incident happened at her grandmothers old house in Federalsburg, Maryland.  Lake stated this was the house where her mother and uncles grew up and where her and her mother stayed at.  Lake stated she does not recall the address of the residence  Lake stated this happened in her grandmothers and her boyfriends bedroom.  Lake stated Gantt had a white shirt and jeans on when it happened.  Lake stated she had all her clothes on.  Lake stated the door was open to the house, she walked in the house and Gantt called her into his bedroom.  Lake and Gantt were the only ones home at the time of the sexual assault.  Lake described Gantts penis as pink.  Lake stated people called grandmothers boyfriend Allen (Gantt).  Lake stated this has only happened once, by Allen and nobody else.  Break in interview_______________________________________________________________  Lake stated she believes she was in kindergarten when this happened.  Lake stated she went to a school in Federalsburg, MD.  Lake stated she was outside by herself playing on her toy car. Lake stated she then went inside to get a drink and that is when Gantt called her.  Lake stated Gantt called her name, so she went into the back bedroom.  Lake stated his private parts were outside his cloths when she first saw him.  Lake stated she saw it and that is when he asked her.  Lake stated she saw the white stuff when she lifted her head up and it went onto the blanket.  Lake stated she tasted something in her mouth and it was white.  Lake stated, it felt like, sticky and weird in my mouth, I then went to the bathroom and spit it out. It was a big glob of white stuff.  Lake stated Gantt did not make any type of noise during or after the assault.  Lake stated after she spit it out, she went back outside.  Lake stated that Gant told her after the incident, please dont tell your grandmother or anybody.  Lake stated she never told anybody about it until about a few weeks ago she advised a guidance counselor about it at school because she was asked a specific question about unwanted touching.  Lake stated she asked Gantt at least 2 times to stop.  Lake stated the house was white and the windows were black.  Lake stated the outside was a big house with a trampoline and a slide.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Lake stated there was a house on both sides of the residence of her grandmothers house.  End of interview_________________________________________________________________  After the interview, the mother of Lake identified as Bridget Allison (DOB: 11/15/1989), hereinafter referred to as Allison was interviewed on February 27, 2023, at 0959 hours. The following interview is documented below: Interview: Bridget Allison (DOB: 11/15/1989):    Allison stated Gantt is the cousin of Lake and Lakes biological father  Allison stated at the time of the assault, Gantt was dating her mother, Friend.  Allison stated Gantt lived with Friend for at least 8 months.  Allison stated Gantt had a daughter who lived with Gantt and Friend whowas approximately 3 years old at the time of the assault  Allison stated Waverly was Gantts daughters name.  Allison stated she has not been in contact with Gantt since he split with her mother, Friend.  Allison stated Gantt is approximately 40 years old, black male.  Allison stated Lake was around 4 or 5 years old during the assault because Lake notified her that at that time she was playing on her pink play truck outside prior to the assault and Lakes brother was not born yet.  Allison stated her son has since been born and her son is 6 years old now.  Allison stated Gantt and her mother split up when her son was an infant.  Allison stated she and Lake were not residing at 532 Liberty Road, Federalsburg, MD 21632 at the time of the sexual assault.  Allison stated Lake would be dropped off at her mothers house to be watched when Allison was working.  Allison stated it was periodically Lake would be dropped off depending on her work schedule but around 2 to 3 times a week.  End of interview_________________________________________________________________  After the interview with Allison, I interviewed Lakes grandmother identified as Felita Germaine Friend (DOB: 12/01/1971), hereinafter referred to as Friend. The following interview is documented below:  Felita Germaine Friend (DOB: 12/01/1971):    Friend stated Allen Gantt Junior is a guy she dated over 5 years ago.  Friend stated she lived with her at 532 Liberty Road, Federalsburg, MD 21632 for about 1 year.  Friend stated previously before living together, Gantt was incarcerated for fleeing and alluding, violation of probation, and no license.  June believed Gantt Birthday is in the month of June, not sure of the year.  Friend stated she met Gantt at her friends residence a while back.  Friend stated Gantt had an older son who she has not met and a young daughter named Waverly Gantt. Waverly Gantt should be around 9- 11 years old currently.  Friend stated Waverly Gantt would come approximately twice a month.  Friend stated Waverly Gantt was incarcerated during the time Waverly was born.  Friend stated Gantt was not incarcerated at any point they were together.   Friend clarified that Gantt went to prison after Gantt went to jail.  Friend stated he was going through the court process while they were together.  Friend stated she had an emotionally abusive relationship with Gantt towards the end and she eventually obtained a protective order against Gantt which was granted.  Friend stated she resided at 532 Liberty Road, Federalsburg, MD 21632 (rented) from 2003 through 2016 or 2017.  Friend stated she believes she lived there for approximately 14 years.  Friend stated Gantt was rarely left alone with Lake and Friend usually never left Lake alone with anyone.  Friend stated he saw no behavioral changes in Lake at that time.  Friend stated Gantt would buy Lake candy and clothes. Lake stated Gantt would also buy clothes for his daughter, Waverly.  Friend stated Gantt attitude started changing towards the end of their relationship as in Gantt was being controlling and did not like to hang around people.  Gantt stated the attitude change started to happen before his sentencing and before her grandson was born.  Friend stated she does not have Gantt phone number and she changed her phone number.  Friend stated she lived with her daughter after she left 532 Liberty Road, Federalsburg, Maryland to save up for an apartment of her own.  Friend stated she moved to a different apartment recently in February 2020.  Friend stated her son currently reside in 532 Liberty Road, Federalsburg, MD.  Friend stated there are 3 bedrooms in the residence and one master bedroom.  Friend stated her sex life with Gantt was ok in the beginning and it faded later on/  Friend stated she did not want Gantt touching her due to his change in behavior.  Friend stated she has not seen Gantt watch any pornography.  Friend stated Gantt had one cell phone.  Friend stated sex was forceful towards the end of the relationship and at one point her son was home from college and he barged in the room and stopped the sexual act.  Friend stated her grandson was still not born by then.  Friend stated Gantt never requested oral sex but it was performed.  Friend stated she remembered Lake had a pink battery-operated toy car that she rode in the backyard around the time of the sexual assault.  Friend remembered this because she would cover up the car with a tarp to protect it from rain.  End of interview_________________________________________________________________   An application of charges will be conducted on Gantt.   Case remains open. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:53:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6295</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/01/2023 14:28:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tilghman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6254</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mingos</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6295</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496826</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1604</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/27/2023 09:03:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:23:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6295</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/28/2023 13:23:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496826</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0322</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/27/2023 09:03:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0322</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:24:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6295</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/28/2023 13:24:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:29:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:50</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370375</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Gantt</LastName>
               <FirstName>Allen</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/26/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13046017E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>02/28/2023 13:28:18</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A450</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Gantt</LastName>
               <FirstName>Allen</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/26/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13046017E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>G530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A450</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/28/2023 13:28:18</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>400</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Bridgeville</City>
               <StateCode>DE</StateCode>
               <Zip5>19933</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.605282</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.74342</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:29:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>12</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:31:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:37</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370376</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lake</LastName>
               <FirstName>Aryiana</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/27/2010 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/28/2023 13:30:24</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lake</LastName>
               <FirstName>Aryiana</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/27/2010 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/28/2023 13:30:24</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:31:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:31:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:31:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:40:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370377</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Allison</LastName>
               <FirstName>Bridget</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Denise</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/15/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/28/2023 13:39:50</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B632</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Allison</LastName>
               <FirstName>Bridget</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Denise</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/15/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>A425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B632</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/28/2023 13:39:50</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>988</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3813</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CPR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:40:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:40:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>51</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:49:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>9667</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Friend</LastName>
               <FirstName>Felita</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Germaine</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/01/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/20/2014 19:07:44</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F653</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F430</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Friend</LastName>
               <FirstName>Felita</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Germaine</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/01/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F653</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F430</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/20/2014 19:07:44</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>532</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>LIBERTY</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>FEDERALSBURG</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.75259005050272</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.69435461922641</Latitude>
               <SubBeat>933</SubBeat>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>443</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9667</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/20/2014 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>439</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6490</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:49:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:44</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/08/2023 11:00:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/08/2023 11:00:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/18/2023 07:48:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:00:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> On March 7, 2023, investigators obtained a warrant for Gantt which was issued by the Caroline County Commissioners office. The following charges are listed below:   SEX OFFENSE FIRST DEGREE  SEX ABUSE MINOR: HOUSE/FAM  SEX OFFENSE SECOND DEGREE   margin-left:8px"&gt;SEX OFFENSE THIRD DEGREE    The Maryland State Apprehension Team (MSAT) have been notified and will attempt warrant service.  Case remains open. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:01:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6295</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:01:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tilghman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6254</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mingos</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6295</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/27/2023 13:10:24</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/27/2023 13:10:24</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/18/2023 07:48:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 13:10:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Case remains open pending arrest warrant service by MSAT.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 13:11:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6295</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 13:11:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tilghman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6254</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mingos</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6295</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/20/2023 14:39:00</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/20/2023 14:39:00</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/18/2023 07:48:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 14:39:00</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> On April 13, 2023, MSAT contacted The Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region (CEDER) investigators and advised suspect, Allen Lee Gantt, hereinafter referred to as Gantt, was apprehended by Georgetown Police Department reference warrant obtained by CEDER investigators. The MSP warrant was held as a detainer until MSP personnel were able conduct an extradition on Gantt.   On April 20, 2023, CEDER investigators retrieved prisoner Gantt, from the Sussex Correctional Institution located at 23203 Dupont Blvd, Georgetown, DE 19947 and transported him to the Caroline County Sherriffs Office. Gantt declined to be interviewed by investigators.   Easton Barrack Troopers took possession of Gantt and served the arrest warrant. Gantt was taken to the Caroline County Commissioners office for the warrant service.   Note: Gantt SID #: 2077146    margin-left:8px"&gt;Gant had an oral swab conducted on him for DNA on April 1, 2021, at the Talbot County Detention Center for the qualifying offense.   Case closed based on arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 14:40:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6295</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/20/2023 14:59:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Antal</LastName>
            <FirstName>Theodore</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4970</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mingos</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6295</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496826</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1604</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>3</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/20/2023 14:59:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 14:59:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6295</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/20/2023 14:59:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496826</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0322</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>3</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/20/2023 14:59:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0322</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 14:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6295</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/20/2023 15:00:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/17/2023 14:57:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/17/2023 14:57:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/18/2023 07:48:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 14:57:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #4 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> On March 2, 2023, I made contact with Friend via telephone for a follow-up interview. I asked Friend if Gantt was serving weekends at the Caroline County Detention center when she was with him. Friend stated yes, and she believed Gantt served 4 to 6 weekends in Caroline County Detention Center when they were together. Friend also advised she believes she was still with him for a short period of time when he was incarcerated prior to Gantt being issued his longer jail sentencing.  padding:0in 0in 1.0pt 0in"&gt; A subpoena was issued to Caroline County Detention Center Department of records in reference to Gantts incarceration dates. Dates for incarceration will also be obtained in the future for Delaware James T. Vaughn Correctional Center located at 1181 Paddock Road, Smyrna, DE 19977.  On March 2, 2023, Incarceration records were received from State of Delaware Department of Correction Central Offender Records. The information obtained states the following incarceration records on Gantt Junior.    02/06/2013 to 03/08/2013 at Central Violation of Probation    margin-left:24px; padding:0in 0in 1.0pt 0in"&gt;    padding:0in; margin-bottom:11px"&gt;09/14/2012 to 02/02/2013 at James T. Vaughn Correctional Institution    On May 17, 2023, Incarceration records were received from Caroline County Department of Corrections reference Gantt. The information obtained states the following incarceration records on Gantt Junior.    2/2/2013-2/2/2013  7/26/2013-08/19/2013  4/4/2014-4/6/2014  4/11/201-4/12/2014  5/30/2014-6/1/2014  6/6/2014-6/8/2014  6/13/2014-6/15/2014  6/20/2014-6/22/2014  6/27/2014-6/29/2014  7/4/2014-7/6/2014  7/11/2014-7/13/2014  7/18/2014-7/20/2014  7/25/2014-7/27/2014  7/31/2014-8/1/2014  8/28/2014-8/29/2014  3/25/2015-5/6/2016  3/25/2017-3/27/2017    After obtaining incarceration records from Caroline County and the state of Delaware including the interviews conducted, I believe the sexual assault occurred between June 2014 to early 2015. This would put the female victim at the approximate age of 4 when the sexual assault occurred.   Case remains closed based on arrest.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6295</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 14:58:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6295</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/18/2023 07:47:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Antal</LastName>
            <FirstName>Theodore</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4970</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mingos</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6295</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>