<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002233</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/19/2023 08:38:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/19/2023 08:38:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/19/2023 08:37:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/19/2023 08:37:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Assist other agency (Sarasota County- Florida) with death investigation</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 08:38:25</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3304</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/15/2023 18:47:15</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>4551</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 08:38:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/09/2023 12:47:32</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>4551</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2433</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Pulaski</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>North East</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21901</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.949987</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.608201</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2433 W Pulasi Hwy</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>North East Barrack</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>TASK FORCE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>119 bethel church</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>119 bethel church rd north east</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MARYLAND STATE POLICE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>RT 40 @  GOLDEN RING ROAD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>716 Falconer Rd, Joppa, MD 21085</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>NORTH EAST BARRACK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>PULASKI HWY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>STATE POLICE BARRACK F</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MARYLAND STATE POLICE BARRACK AND PULASKI HWY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>PULASKI HWY NE BK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>CECIL COUNTY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>LANCASTER , PA</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/09/2023 12:44:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/09/2023 12:44:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40L</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/15/2023 18:47:15</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP4937</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 12:44:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3304</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/15/2023 18:47:15</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Assist Sarasota County PD (Florida) with homicide investigation.     On 1/18/2023 at 0822 hours, Sgt. Piper of the Sarasota County Sheriffs Office (Florida) contacted the Maryland State Police Criminal Investigative Bureau to request assistance for a cold case (potential homicide). They had recently identified a Jane Doe that was discovered in 2007 buried in a shallow grave. All of the persons of interest developed in the investigation currently reside in Maryland. I contacted Sgt. Piper on 1/19/23 at 0939 hours to discuss the case. The Maryland State Police Homicide Unit was requested to assist with various interviews and to author a search warrant for the suspects residence.   On 2/22/2023, Sgt. Mariah Piper provided the following information related to the investigation (probable cause):    margin-left:32px"&gt;On February 6th, 2007, juvenile Tyler Nall was playing in a wooded area just south of the industrial park located at 5438 Ashton Court  Sarasota County (FL). Nall located what appeared to be bones and notified his father, Jay Nall, who contacted law enforcement.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Sarasota County Sheriffs Office deputies responded to the incident location and determined the bones appeared to be human remains. Detectives and Crime Scene personnel responded to the scene, beginning a sixteen (16) yearlong investigation. The case is documented under SSO case # 07-10645.   margin-left:32px"&gt;The victims body was buried in a shallow grave. The victim was laying in the fetal position, wrapped in a twin sized Westpoint Stevens blue bed sheet, and the size of bones suggested the victim was a female. The depth of the grave was two (2) feet five (5) inches.    margin-left:32px"&gt;She was dressed in a shirt, skirt, panties, and double socks. No shoes were found.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Sheriffs detectives canvassed the area for witnesses or video, searched law enforcement databases for leads, solicited the public for information, and processed physical evidence to attempt to identify the female victim and the person or person(s) responsible for burying her with negative results.    margin-left:32px"&gt;On February 9th, 2007, District 12 Medical Examiner Dr. Vega performed the autopsy, and he determined the victim was a white female, between 57 -58 inches tall, an estimated weight of 145  165 pounds, with a full set of teeth with evidence of dental work present. The female victim had brown hair in a ponytail and breast implants.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Dr. Vega located the presence of a hairline fracture of the orbital plate resulting from an apparent blow or other trauma to the front of the head at, or shortly before, the time of death.   margin-left:32px"&gt;Dental analysis revealed the victim has moderate periodontal disease which was not prevalent in younger individuals and the victim was estimated to be in her mid  late 30s. The restorations were old, but sound, and showed evidence the female victim went to the dentist on a fairly regular basis. The dental records were entered into investigative databases.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Mentor Corporation, the company that made the victims breast implants, examined the implants, and concluded the implants were a Style 2000 saline implant manufactured after November 1998 to June 2003. The implants had no serial number and there was no way to identify the victim or locate the doctor who implanted them. Based on the shelf life of the implants, they would have been implanted between December 1998  May 2007.    margin-left:26px"&gt;The toxicology report revealed the prescription drugs Cyclobenzaprine and Diphenhydramine were detected in trace amounts insufficient to cause death.   margin-left:32px"&gt;On July 6th, 2007, Dr. Vega determined the cause of the victims death was undetermined until such time that additional information could be obtained.    margin-left:32px"&gt;A Forensic entomologist examined the presence of the stable fly on the victims body. This insect revealed the victim was exposed to the fly colonization as early as January / February 2006, and as late as December 11th - 19th, 2006. The victims death would have occurred at least 30 days prior to when the remains were found.   margin-left:32px"&gt;Stable Isotope Analysis was conducted by ISO Forensics to determine where in the United States the victim lived at various times based on tooth enamel and hair testing. The results did not generate any leads at the time.    margin-left:32px"&gt;The victims remains were sent to the University of Floridas Department of Anthropology and the FBI who created a craniofacial reconstruction.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Biological evidence from the victims body was sent to the FBI for analysis which yielded no additional leads. Mitochondrial and Nuclear DNA were extracted from the victims remains by governmental laboratories which were then entered into investigative databases, but no match was found.    margin-left:32px"&gt;The case information was entered into the National Crime Information Center (NCIC), Violent Criminal Apprehension Program (ViCAP), National Missing and Unidentified Persons System (NAMUS), The Doe Network, and Florida Unidentified Decedents Database (FLUIDDB). Fliers of the facial reconstruction pictures were also distributed to the public through the news media and newspaper articles.    margin-left:32px"&gt;In 2018, DNA Labs International began a process to develop a DNA profile for genetic genealogy and the victims remains were sent to them for analysis in 2019, 2020, and 2021, but the bone samples were clouded by calcium, and nothing further could be done.    margin-left:32px"&gt;In 2022, new DNA technology (Kintelligence) was validated and made available for use. The victims calcium clouded DNA was run through Kintelligence to remove the calcium and a usable profile was obtained.   margin-left:32px"&gt;In July 2022, the victims DNA was uploaded to GED Match, a service to compare autosomal DNA data files from different testing companies.    margin-left:32px"&gt;A family tree was started based on GED Match information.   margin-left:32px"&gt;In August 2022, the victims DNA profile was entered into the Family Tree database and a genealogist at DNA Labs International made a possible identification of the victim via the family tree.    margin-left:32px"&gt;The possible identity of the victim is Jeana Lynn Burrus, W/F, born July 28th, 1967. She was born Jeana Lynn Aldrich. Through the family tree, the victims mother (deceased), father, and brother were identified, along with other family.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Through this preliminary identification, detectives confirmed Jeana Burrus was living in the Sarasota area at the time the unidentified victim was found. Jeana Burrus had never been reported missing locally or nationally. Furthermore, all activity for Jeana Burrus, to include law enforcement contacts and credit activity, ceased in 2006.    margin-left:32px"&gt;The victims father was identified as James Gary Aldrich, W/M, born 2/22/46. Aldrich currently resides at 1809 Geckler Lane  La Grande, Oregon - at the Grande Ronde Retirement facility.    margin-left:32px"&gt;On January 6th, 2023, your affiant traveled to La Grande, Oregon and made contact withcontacted James Gary Aldrich, W/M, born 2/22/46. During a sworn, audio recorded interview, Aldrich stated he has not spoken to Jeana since December 1973. However, he stated during a conversation with Jeanas brother, Jonathan Aldrich, approximately 10-15 years ago, Jonathan told him that Jeana was moving to a location with Lake in the name [later determined to be 4045 Crockers Lake Blvd. #2217, Sarasota, FL].   margin-left:32px"&gt;Aldrich provided consent for your affiant to collect his DNA buccal swabs to be used in comparison to the DNA profile developed from the Jane Doe remains. The collected swabs were packaged and mailed directly from La Grande, Oregon to DNA Labs International.    margin-left:32px"&gt;On January 17th, 2023, DNA Labs International provided the analysis results, which concluded that James Gary Aldrich, W/M, born 2/22/46 had a 99.99% probability of paternity when compared to the DNA profile of Jane Doe in this case. Based on the analysis results and the fact that Aldrich only had one (1) biological daughter, your affiant was able to positively identify Jane Doe in this case as Jeana Lynn Burrus, W/F, born July 28th, 1967.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Detectives began investigating Jeana Lynn Burrus background. Evidence was obtained via law enforcement records, Florida Department Highway Safety and Motor Vehicles (FLHSMV) records, school records, and Florida Department of Children and Families (DCF) records from Florida, Maryland, and California.   margin-left:32px"&gt;These records revealed that Jeana Burrus was married to James Arthur Burrus, W/M, born March 2nd, 1967, on May 9th, 1998, in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.    margin-left:32px"&gt;They had two (2) children; one (1) biological son, James Austin Burrus, W/M, born October 22nd, 1996, and one (1) daughter from Jamess prior marriage, Brittany Nicole Burrus, W/F, born February 2nd, 1992.   margin-left:32px"&gt;Law enforcement reports and Citrus County (FL) school records show the Burrus lived at 251 S. Highview Ave., Lecanto, Florida from approximately September 2002 to January 2004.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Citrus County Sheriffs Office and Department of Children and Families (FL) reports depict the Burrus family as having an unstable home environment and volatile family dynamic.    margin-left:32px"&gt;On October 28th, 2002, Jamess mother, Judy Koch, and brother-in-law, Daniel Loukota, filed a report with DCF alleging that Jeana was verbally and physically abusive towards Brittany. The report references a past incident in which Jeana hit Brittany on the head repeatedly. Another claim was that James and Jeana left Brittany in the driveway of Judys house without warning and did not pick her up for several weeks.    margin-left:32px"&gt;On October 29th, 2002, the Citrus County Sheriffs Office and DCF investigated the incident. They interviewed James, Jeana, and both children. Jeana denied the allegations, and the claims were determined to be unfounded.    margin-left:32px"&gt;On November 19th, 2002, Jeana Burrus received a criminal traffic citation for driving while license suspended (DWLS). In December, she was sentenced to six (6) months probation.    margin-left:32px"&gt;In the court records, Jeana wrote she was disabled with mental illness (Bipolar disorder) and was receiving social security benefits as she was unable to work.   margin-left:32px"&gt;On January 7th, 2003, Jeana Burrus was operating a vehicle and involved in a rollover crash in Citrus County in which she was ejected from the vehicle. She left the scene and was later found and arrested by Citrus County Sheriffs Office. The Tampa Bay Times published an article about the incident.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Jeana failed to appear for a court date the following month. A warrant was issued, and she was subsequently arrested on 03/01/2003.    margin-left:32px"&gt;On March 7th, 2003, Judy Koch filed a harassment report with Citrus County Sheriffs Office. The report indicated that Jeana was harassing Judy via phone calls, mail, and notes left at her residence. No law enforcement action was taken.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Also on March 7th, 2003, Brittanys biological mother, Renee Johnson, filed a report with DCF alleging Jeanas abuse towards Brittany.    margin-left:32px"&gt;On October 10th, 2003, Burrus employer in Citrus County - Florida, Bonnie Alexander, filed a report with DCF alleging that James and Jeana had a fight the night prior and that James left with Brittany.    margin-left:32px"&gt;The report claimed Jeana beat her children, she was on drugs, and she suffered from Bipolar disorder and schizophrenia. It was also alleged Jeana was writing a book on 100 ways to kill your mother-in-law. The report also alleged Burrus co-worker, Philip Morrison, witnessed Jeana threaten Brittany with a knife.    margin-left:32px"&gt;The Citrus County Sheriffs Office and the Department of Children and Families investigated Bonnie Alexanders claims on 10/10/2003. Jeana was emotional during this encounter and confirmed that James recently left with his daughter, Brittany. At the conclusion of the encounter, law enforcement determined Jeana was emotionally unstable and took her into protective custody under the Baker Act.    margin-left:32px"&gt;On December 17th, 2003, the Department of Children and Families responded to Citrus Memorial Hospital (FL) after Jeana was brought into the emergency room in an altered state of consciousness after taking Percocet, Soma, Hydroxyzine, and Clonipine. The report indicated that James was in Sarasota preparing for the familys move.   margin-left:32px"&gt;In January of 2004, James, Jeana, Brittany, and James Austin moved to Sarasota County (FL).    margin-left:32px"&gt;On January 15th, 2004, Brittany was enrolled in Sarasota Middle School and James Austin in Gulf Gate Elementary.    margin-left:32px"&gt;On April 12th, 2004, James was hired at Gulf Coast Autobody located at 5645 Sarah Ave. in Sarasota. Jeana Burrus body would later be found buried approximately 280 feet in an isolated wooded area behind this business.    margin-left:32px"&gt;School records revealed shortly after the January 2004 move, Brittany transferred schools in August 2004 from Sarasota to San Diego, California where she went to live with her biological mother, Renee Johnson.    margin-left:32px"&gt;On October 24, 2004, Jeana received a criminal traffic citation for driving while license suspended in Orange County, Florida. She appeared in court in January 2005 and received six (6) months probation.    margin-left:32px"&gt;From November 26th, 2004, to November 25th, 2005, James, Jeana, and their two children lived at 6204 Pauline Ave., Sarasota, Florida. The owner/landlord, Nicola Sorrentino, provided detectives with a copy of the signed lease.    margin-left:32px"&gt;On November 22nd, 2005, Jeana was involved in a traffic crash in Sarasota at Upper Beechwood Ave and U.S. 41. She was criminally cited for having no drivers license.    margin-left:32px"&gt;The last known documented contact anyone had with Jeana Burrus was on January 9th, 2006, when she was given criminal and civil traffic citations in Okeechobee County, Florida. Per the traffic citation, Jeana listed her home address as 4045 Crockers Lake Blvd. #2217, Sarasota, FL. Jeana was driving a 2005 Ford Focus FL tag:X98ZAG that was registered to her husband, James Burrus.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Court records revealed that on March 1st, 2006, Jeana failed to appear in court for the Okeechobee County criminal citation. A warrant was issued for her arrest; however, it was never served and years later, the warrant would be cancelled by the State.   margin-left:32px"&gt;Evidence in the form of documents were obtained from James Burrus former employer at Gulf Coast Autobody. These documents revealed that on January 10th, 2006, the day after Jeana received the citations in Okeechobee County, James filed a claim with his auto insurance company for damage sustained to the 2005 Ford Focus during the November 2005 crash.    margin-left:32px"&gt;The documents showed the insurance adjuster completed the estimate for the repairs on the 2005 Ford Focus on January 13th, 2006, strongly suggesting the adjuster was able to inspect the vehicle itself, to complete the estimate.    margin-left:32px"&gt;A receipt dated March 23rd, 2006, revealed parts, to include a hood, were delivered to Gulf Coast Autobody showing the 2005 Ford Focus was still at the shop at that time.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Considering this evidence, this investigation reasonably concluded that James Burrus must have had contact with Jeana after January 9th, 2006, in order to take possession of his 2005 Ford Focus by January 13th, 2006.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Therefore, in addition to Jeana being buried behind the body shop where James was employed, James was also the last person to see Jeana alive.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Sarasota County School records revealed James Austin completed the school year at Gulf Gate Elementary in May of 2006 but never returned in August 2006.    margin-left:32px"&gt;California Department of Motor Vehicle (DMV) records revealed James moved to California in September 2006.    margin-left:32px"&gt;James 2005 Ford Focus was still registered to him, and the vehicle appeared in San Diego, California on October 30th, 2006, for an emissions test.    margin-left:32px"&gt;In August 2008, records revealed James moved back to Maryland where he currently resides at 1239 Deer Park Road, Westminster, Maryland (Carroll County).    margin-left:32px"&gt;In 2011, the 2005 Ford Focus was sold in California and is currently registered to Robert Oel Walters, W/M, born 9/4/58, of El Cajon, CA.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Court records obtained from Carrol County, Maryland revealed that in 2015, James filed for a Pro-Se divorce from Jeana.    margin-left:32px"&gt;The document was handwritten and signed by James. He wrote that he last saw Jeana on or about January 3rd, 2006, which is contrary to the evidence obtained in this investigation.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Citrus County Property Appraiser (FL) and court records revealed James and Jeana owned a home at 251 S. Highview Ave, Lecanto, Florida (Citrus County), prior to them moving to Sarasota County. This residence was foreclosed on in March 2004.    margin-left:32px"&gt;In the divorce filing, James Burrus knowingly provided false address information, stating he last knew Jeana to be living in Citrus County, not Sarasota County as evidence proves. James listed a false address of 53 S. Highview Ave., Inverness, Florida. This was found to be a fictitious address and was an empty wooded area along S. Highview Ave. in Lecanto, FL.   margin-left:32px"&gt;Based on this evidence, it is not unreasonable to conclude that James Burrus knowingly provided this false address information because he did not want process servers or law enforcement inquiring about the whereabouts of Jeana at 4045 Crockers Lake Boulevard #2217, Sarasota, FL.    margin-left:32px"&gt;The divorce was ultimately denied for lack of jurisdiction.   margin-left:32px"&gt;On January 5th, 2023, detectives conducted a sworn recorded interview with James former co-worker at Gulf Coast Autobody, Douglas Graham. Douglas stated some time in 2006, James told Douglas he was getting a divorce because Jeana was cheating on him, and he was moving to North Florida with his son to live with his mother [Judy Koch]. Douglas has not seen or spoken to James since 2006.    margin-left:32px"&gt;This investigation has concluded that James Burrus is the only, and primary suspect in the death of his wife, Jeana Burrus.    margin-left:32px"&gt;James was the last person to see Jeana alive on or after January 9th, 2006. They had a well-documented volatile relationship where Jeana was accused of mentally and physically abusing and/or attempting to kill her stepdaughter and mother-in law giving James plausible motivation to kill her.   margin-left:32px"&gt;Jeana was found buried 280 feet behind the body shop where James worked, further implicating him in her death. He is the only person who had the connection to the burial site, and he had knowledge, access, and opportunity, to place her body there without detection.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Evidence found in this investigation shows that James knowingly provided false information as to the last time he saw Jeana alive and about the last residential address he knew her to live, from a Pro Se Divorce filing in Maryland in 2015, which he signed. In that filing, he cited adultery, desertion, cruelty/excessively vicious conduct against him and his child, again showing he had motive to kill her.    margin-left:32px"&gt;James withdrew his son from school in Sarasota, he quit his job telling a coworker he and Jeana were getting a divorce, and he moved across the country to California arriving in September 2006.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Detectives have confirmed through the Social Security Administration (SSA) that Jeana was receiving monthly benefits for her disability. Payments ceased in 2007 due to SSA having an invalid address and no forwarding address for Jeana.    margin-left:32px"&gt;There has been no evidence found in this case that James has ever returned to Florida or Sarasota County for the past 16 years since Jeanas body was discovered, and there is no evidence that he has ever reported her as a missing person.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Your affiant knows that it is common for persons to communicate via electronic devices, to include cell phones and computers, as well as through written communication. Such devices maintain record of these communications through call logs and messaging applications.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Your affiant also knows that it is common to document ones life through photographs, personal diaries/journals, home videos, and scrapbooking materials such as newspaper articles and publications. In addition to physical photographs, photos and home videos can also be stored on items such as external hard drives and SD cards.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Per James Burrus 2015 divorce filing, he stated Jeana deserted the family in 2006. If Jeana left the family alive as James alleges, it would have been reasonable for her to have taken items of importance, such as her identification cards, bank cards, purse, wallet, jewelry, clothes, and bank documents. Therefore, should James be found in possession of these items, it would reasonably refute his claim of desertion.    margin-left:32px"&gt;Your affiant is requesting the issuance of a search warrant for James Burrus current home, 1239 Deer Park Rd., Westminster, Maryland 21157, to include any and all outbuildings such as barns, sheds, or detached garages in the curtilage. The intent is to recover any matching Westpoint-Stevens brand sheets that Jeana Burrus body was wrapped in, news publications relating to this case, personal diaries/journals, personal computers, cellular phones, Jeana Burrus clothing, bank statements, documents, family photographs, home videos, jewelry belonging to Jeana Burrus, SD cards/external hard drives, wallets, purses, Jeana Burrus identification card, Jeana Burrus credit cards, as well as moving boxes or storage compartments, safes/lock boxes, and safe deposit box keys which may hold the aforementioned items.     A complete background check and biographical sheet has been completed on James Burrus by the Maryland Coordination and Analysis Center. The last listed/known address for Burrus is 1239 Deer Park Road Westminster, Maryland 21157. Vehicles registered to Burrus are also associated with that address.   On 2/24/2023 at 1203 hours, Sgt. Taylor obtained a search and seizure warrant for the Deer Park residence. Sarasota Sheriffs Office Detectives/Personnel, met with homicide investigators on 02/27/23 at 1000 hours at the Golden Ring Barracks to strategize the execution of the search warrant and to simultaneously contact interviews on persons of interest to the investigation (James Burrus, Brittany Burrus, and James Burrus Jr). A plan was devised and on 02/28/2023 at 1000 hours at the Westminster Barracks, investigators from MSP (Northern Narcotics, SOG, Crime Scene, FOB, and Homicide) met with Florida investigators for a briefing. After the briefing, MSP Homicide investigators accompanied Florida investigators and simultaneously responded to three different locations; (1) James Burrus place of employment to make death notification; (2) Brittany Burrus residence (Baltimore City) for an interview; (3) James Burrus residence at 1239 Deer Park Road, Westminster, MD 21157.  Once contact was made with Burrus at his place of employment, he was transported back to the Westminster Barrack to be interviewed. Investigators made contact with Brittany Burrus at her residence and also transported her back to the Westminster Barracks to be interviewed. Additionally, investigators responded to the Deer Park residence and made contact with Lori McFarlin (current girlfriend of Burrus). Also present at the residence was James Burrus Jr and McFarlins adult granddaughter. While investigators from Florida interviewed all persons of interest, MSP investigators executed a search and seizure warrant at 1200 hours. The following items were seized from the residence:    Box of disposable cameras and film from the upstairs portion of the barn in the backyard  Miscellaneous photos and documents from the upstairs portion of the barn in the backyard  Photo album (floral cover) from the upstairs portion of the barn in the backyard  Photo album (no cover) from the upstairs portion of the barn in the backyard   margin-left:8px"&gt;Miscellaneous 8mm cassette tapes from the upstairs portion of the barn in the backyard  James Burrus did not confess to any crimes related to his wifes death. He was subsequently released from the Westminster Barracks. All evidence from the search warrant was singed over and released to Sarasota County Sheriffs Office. This will conclude the requested assistance provided by MSP personnel. Should the need arise, MSP will assist with the investigation as needed/requested.   ASSIGNED INVESTIGATOR: Sgt. Christopher Taylor #4937 INVESTIGATIVE TIME: 10 hrs. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4937</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 12:45:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4937</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/15/2023 13:30:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40L</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Vogt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeremy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3304</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40L</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Taylor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4937</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>