<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011898</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/03/2023 16:21:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/03/2023 16:21:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/03/2023 15:36:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/03/2023 15:36:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Check Welfare, Pedestrian Walking On Highway, Fail To Obey Reasonable Lawful Order, Resisting Address</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 16:21:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4913</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/11/2023 11:09:57</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>RSA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WFC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MD-665/I97</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>689499</AddressId>
      <City>MDC102</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 16:21:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 22:11:57</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>689499</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Md-665</StreetName>
         <City>Annapolis</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21401</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.5503005998688</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.97951702153405</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/03/2023 16:21:41</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/03/2023 16:21:41</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/03/2023 22:48:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 16:21:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:43</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was audibly and visually recorded on the my Axon Body Worn Camera, and on the Axon Digital Video Camera System installed in unmarked Maryland State Police unit, J15.  This incident was also caught on TFC S. Yus Axon Body Worn Camera andon the Axon Digital Video Camera System installed in unmarked Maryland State Police unit, J19.  SCENE PROCESSING:   -I took fourteen (14) digital photographs of Steven Edwards at the Maryland State Police, Annapolis Barrack and Jennifer Road Detention Center.   -I took one (1) digital photograph of the abrasions on my right leg at the Barrack.  PHYSICAL EVIDENCE:   -Fifteen digital photographs.  NARRATIVE: On 04/03/2023, at approximately 1542 hours, TFC S. Yu #7292 and I, S/TPR S. Matthews #5973, responded to the area of Aris T. Allen Blvd (MD Route 665) and Interstate 97, Annapolis, Anne Arundel County, Maryland to check the welfare of a white male (Steven Edwards), wearing a black sweatshirt, black pants and yellow t-shirt who had jumped out of a moving vehicle in the area. The caller, David Edwards, reported that he and his mother were taking Steven William Edwards, W/M, to Shepherd Pratt for a mental evaluation. I located Steven, matching the above clothing description, walking south on the right side of Aris T. Allen Blvd, north of, Riva Road, on the rocky ground, next to Bowens Farm Supply. I got out and walked with Steven and tried to talk to him. I identified myself and advised him he was being audibly recorded. He ignored me and continued to walk. I asked him if he was injured. He ignored me and continued to walk. I asked him to stop walking and speak with me, and I crossed over the guardrail to stop him and check on him. I advised him that I wanted to determine that he was not injured and to investigate the situation. My understanding was that Steven jumped out of a moving vehicle, as he was being taken by family members to the mental hospital. I did not know Stevens name or date of birth; if he was being held against his will; and if he was an adult or juvenile. I stopped Steven, by grabbing onto a pair of black sweatpants he had slung over his shoulder. I held onto his right arm and his back to maintain control of him. Steven did not respond and had a thousand-yard stare, as he appeared emotionless and staring straight ahead. I tried to calmly speak with Steven to obtain his identity, where he lived, and why he jumped out of a car. He continued to stare straight ahead blankly. I advised him I had EMS coming to check on him. I asked him if he needed the ambulance and he did not respond. He attempted to continue to walk away from me. I had Steven sit on the guardrail. On the other side of the rocks, was a 20-foot drop, down to Bowens Farm Supply parking lot. Steven sat on the guardrail and swung his right leg over the guardrail and attempted to cross over the guardrail into the roadway, with oncoming traffic. I physically stopped him and placed my hand on his shoulder to maintain positive control of him. I advised him he could not do that because it was unsafe. He asked me why I had him detained. I advised him that he was being a safety hazard for motorists and to himself. Steven continued to stare blankly. I asked his age because I did not know if he was an adult or a juvenile. I asked him numerous times but he refused to give me an answer. Traffic was heavy coming from Aris T. Allen Boulevard to the ramp to Riva Road. I spoke with Steven calmly but assertively during the interaction. TFC Yu arrived on scene to assist me. Steven asked if I could give him a ride to the Annapolis mall. I advised him that I could and advised him of out policy of handcuffing a person who we relay. I also advised him that I had to identify him as well. He then refused to go to the mall. He stated he could just walk down the ramp to Riva Road. I advised him we were not done our investigation with him. Steven stepped over the guardrail and tried to walk away from us. I grabbed at his left arm to stop him, and he pulled away. At this point, I felt the situation was not safe due to our location on the ramp, near the 20 foot high wall, and Stevens behavior being unpredictable. I wanted to detain him in handcuffs so that we could safely get him off of the roadway, and complete our investigation of the incident. TFC Yu and I were on the roadside of the guardrail and Stevens body was on the other side of the guardrail. I held onto Stevens right arm and hand as TFC Yu held on to Stevens left arm. I ordered Steven to step over the guardrail eight times and he failed to comply. He sunk down and used his body wait to passively resist our effort to stand him up. I stepped over the guardrail and ordered Steven to place his hands behind his back. I advised him that I was placing him in handcuffs and ordered him to place his hands behind his back. Steven began to actively resist my efforts to pull his right hand behind his back. I told Steven to stop resisting and to put his hands behind his back. I ordered him to put his hands behind his back five times. I repeated myself and Steven failed to obey a lawful order. He resisted arrest and physically resisted my and TFC Yus attempts to pull his hands behind his back. We eventually got control of Stevens hands behind his back and placed him in handcuffs. Steven began to scream out loud because he was handcuffed. I searched Steven and recovered his California drivers license from his left pocket. EMS arrived on scene to evaluate him.    He was checked by EMS for any injuries, cleared, and refused medical treatment, Run #2023-22822.    I placed Steven under arrest for failure to obey a reasonable and lawful order, and for resisting arrest.    I placed Steven in my patrol car and transported him to the Maryland State Police, Annapolis Barrack for processing.    At the Barrack, I made contact with Stevens brother, David Edwards, Stevens brother; and Marika Desiree Edwards, Stevens mother. Marika advised me that Steven was just released today from a mental hospital in Washington, D.C. She stated he was in D.C. for a protest. She stated he was caught kidnapping an infant in a stroller and was arrested. He was committed to a mental hospital for 72 hours. She stated she picked him up today and brought him home and he was being aggressive with her and yelling at her in the car. She stated that she and David were taking Steven to Sheppard Pratt for because he agreed to be voluntarily committed. She stated he has been suffering from mental disorders since January 2023. David stated he jumped out of their vehicle as the vehicle was slowing to a stop from Aris T. Allen Boulevard to northbound Interstate 97, and he ran across traffic. They did not provide any evidence that Steven had made any statements about harming himself or anyone else.     Steven was charged on a Statement of Charges, DC-CR-002, Tracking #180001778272, with the following criminal charges:    *CJIS 2-0055, CR 10-201(c)3: Fail To Obey Reasonable and Lawful Order.    *CJIS 1-0600, CR 9-408(b): Resisting Arrest Steven was served with copies of his charges.    As I was processing Steven at the Barrack and completing paperwork, I observed he was making delusional statements and stated he was hearing thoughts that were troublesome. He was anxious at times and calm at other times. It was apparent to me that he suffered from psychosis. I asked him if he wanted to harm himself. He stated he did not.    I took fourteen digital photographs of Steven. I observed he had a small abrasion on his right palm. I did not observe any other signs of injury on his body.     I took one digital photograph of my right leg, where there was an abrasion on my right knee and upper right shin. All photographs are attached to this report.     He was transported to Jennifer Road Detention Center for booking.     All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 18:15:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5973</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 22:06:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Yu</LastName>
            <FirstName>Simon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>O'Connor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4785</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Matthews</LastName>
            <FirstName>Shawn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5973</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501301</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0055</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/03/2023 15:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 0055</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 22:15:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5973</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 22:15:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501301</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0600</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/03/2023 15:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0600</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 22:16:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5973</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 22:16:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>30</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 22:30:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:26</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373334</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Edwards</LastName>
               <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>William</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/26/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13374247E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 22:19:10</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E363</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Edwards</LastName>
               <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>William</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/26/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13374247E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>E363</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 22:19:10</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>103</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Arrowhead</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Millersville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21108</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1804</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.627801</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.111692</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>610</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8565</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 22:30:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 22:30:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 22:39:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>194580</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Matthews #5973</LastName>
               <FirstName>TFC S.</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/12/2018 20:12:21</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T122</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Matthews #5973</LastName>
               <FirstName>TFC S.</FirstName>
               <SLastName>M320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T122</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/12/2018 20:12:21</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>210</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Main</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Prince Frederick</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20678</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.581161</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.538602</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 22:39:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 22:15:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5973</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 22:15:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>