<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013168</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/14/2023 00:22:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/14/2023 00:22:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/13/2023 23:57:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/13/2023 23:57:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>FORD "R" 23-199</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 00:22:23</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 21:11:33</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OLD EASTERN AVE/ EASTERN BLVD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>690605</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 00:22:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 15:21:38</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>690605</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Old Eastern</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Essex</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>BLVD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.46516</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.31258</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 OLD EASTERN AVE / 1023-1023 EASTERN BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>909-913 OLD EASTERN AVE / 901-901 EASTERN BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/14/2023 00:22:22</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/14/2023 00:22:22</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/03/2023 21:11:34</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 00:22:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E) TEAM* MVR Statement: The following incident was captured on in-car and Body camera. Title: FORD R 23-199. ID: 23-MSP-013168 Arrested: Ford, Trey Antione. Certification and training  -Trained in Field Sobriety Test through Maryland State Police Academy.  -Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E)  -Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  - Graduated from The Institute of Advanced Law Enforcement Studies Driving Under the Influence Institute-University of Maryland.  - I have apprehended more than 200 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On April 13, 2023, at approximately 2356 hours, I, TFC. I. Riba Tankari # 7058 with Maryland State Police was traveling westbound MD-150 (Eastern Blvd) west of White Marsh Blvd, Baltimore County, Maryland in lane #1 (left lane). My issued patrol vehicle is Maryland State Police marked unit DUI-3. At that time, I observed a blue Ford F250 bearing Maryland registration 4DJ8849 traveling westbound MD-150 in lane #1 had changed lane into lane #2 (right lane) and continued traveling westbound MD-150 at a high rate of speed and was unable to stay within a single lane. I followed the vehicle and observed the Ford had swerved from lane #2 into lane #1 by more than one (1) tire width on Four (4) separate occasions. I continued to follow the Ford and with my properly functioning patrol vehicle Golden Eagle II radar unit set activated, I obtained a speed reading of 93 in a posted 45 MPH zones. I initiated a traffic stop on the Ford using my emergency equipment. The Ford came to a stop in the area of westbound MD-150 and old Eastern Avenue, Baltimore County, Maryland. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the Ford on the driver side and made contact with the driver and a male passenger sitting in the front passenger seat of the vehicle. I introduced myself and explained to him the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver where he was coming from, and he stated Tavern. I asked the driver where he was heading, and he stated home. I requested his drivers license and registration card. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I observed that the driver had watery and glassy eyes. While speaking to the driver, I noticed his speech was slow and mumbled. I noticed his movements were slow and lethargic while attempting to retrieve the requested documents. The driver was identified through his Maryland commercial drivers license as Ford, Trey Antione. I returned to my patrol vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with. I returned to the vehicle and requested Ford to exit his vehicle and walk to the front of his vehicle and he complied. While outside his vehicle, I again noticed his movements were slow and lethargic. I asked Ford how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed, and he stated, I had few beverages. I asked him how many is few, and he stated he had three bottles Bud Light beer. I asked around what time, and he stated me and my buddy came about eight (8) oclock I think about ten (10) oclock. While speaking with Ford outside his vehicle, I again detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I asked Ford to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and he agreed.  The evaluation surface was dry, flat, and free of debris. No surface defects were observed. My patrol flashlight, his vehicle headlights, and overhead lamp lit the area. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Ford appeared to be in good physical conditions. I asked Ford the following questions: Medical conditions: No. Medications: No. Anything that will prevent you from walking on straight line or standing on one leg: No Glasses or contact: No. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: (6/6 clues observed). The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus - Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes - Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes - Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Notes: * During the HGN test, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Fords breath. WALK AND TURN: (6/8 clues observed). The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Ford stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage: Ford lost his balance to the right on several occasions and to the left on two (2) separate occasions. Ford started too soon on two (2) occasions. Walking Stage (1st Nine): Missed touching heel to toe by more than half inch on counts 1, 3, 7, and 8. Stepped completely offline by one shoe width on count 4. Took eight (8) actual steps when instructed to take 9. Notes *Ford started counting the number of steps with 2. Turn: The turn was not completed correctly; instead Ford moved both feet to turn himself around to left failing to take a series of small steps as instructed and demonstrated. Walking Stage (2nd Nine): Missed touching heel to toe by more than half inch on counts all counts. One Leg Stand Test (2/4 observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Ford stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Right foot raised during the test. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: Swayed body to the right and left. Right foot hit the ground two (2) times. Seconds 11-20: Swayed body to the right and left. Seconds 21-30: Right foot hit the ground two (2) times. Swayed body to the right and left. Preliminary Breath Test:  I explained and offered a PBT to Ford. Ford elected to consent to the PBT and results were .15 BAC. ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Ford was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a motor vehicle safely:  - Driving over the posted speed limit (93 Mph in 45 Mph speed limit zones)  -Unable to stay within a single lane/driving patterns.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath as he conversed with me.  -Eyes watery and glassy.  -Movements slow and lethargic.  -His admissions to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to driving.  -Observed signs of impairment as he performed the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  - Preliminary Breath Test result of .15 BrAC.  Ford was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a motor vehicle on April 14, 2023, at 0016 hours and was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring. A search incident to arrest revealed no weapons or contraband. Upon arrival at the Barrack, Ford was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and it was read to him from the MVA website in English, and he elected to consent to the Intoximeter EC/IR II test at 0051 hours. 20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Ford beginning with his arrest. A search revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. He remained in my custody from the time of his arrest. Nothing was introduced to his mouth at any time. The test was conducted by Sgt. Zinn Intox ID #5496 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument and a result of .13 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath was obtained at 0108 hours. Ford waspolite and cooperative during the encounter.  Ford was given pertinent paperwork and released from the Barrack to his friend pending an appearance in the District Court of Maryland for Baltimore County at a later date.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 15:25:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/26/2023 15:59:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Speak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7219</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502573</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/14/2023 00:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 15:22:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 15:23:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 15:22:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374281</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>FORD</LastName>
               <FirstName>TREY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ANTIONE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/25/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/14/2023 15:10:59</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>FORD</LastName>
               <FirstName>TREY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ANTIONE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/25/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/14/2023 15:10:59</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1934</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Victory</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Halethorpe</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21227</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.669687</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.246351</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>689</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5454</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 15:24:22</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 15:24:22</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 15:24:22</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 15:22:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 15:22:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151951</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 15:25:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 15:25:41</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FTNW21L84EA16352</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2004</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>F25</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4DJ8849</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>6</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleValue>1000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>