<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000473</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/04/2023 19:51:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/04/2023 19:51:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/03/2023 00:01:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/03/2023 00:01:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>01/04/2023 18:56:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>Welfare Check</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 19:01:34</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5829</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/05/2023 23:08:42</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WFC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>679368</AddressId>
      <City>MDC516</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 19:01:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/04/2023 19:55:30</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>679368</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>280</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Shore Acres</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
         <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
         <SubNumber>348</SubNumber>
         <City>Prince Frederick</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20678</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.581794</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.545639</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/04/2023 19:01:31</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/04/2023 19:01:31</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>01/05/2023 23:08:41</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 19:01:34</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5829</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/05/2023 23:08:42</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>  This incident was recorded utilizing the agency-issued AXON body-worn camera assigned to Trooper P. Hernandez #7266.    Narrative:    On January 4, 2023, at approximately 1824 hours, the Calvert County Emergency Control Center broadcasted a call for a welfare check of a suicidal juvenile at, 280 Shore Acres Way, Apt. 348, Prince Frederick, Md 20678. I advised the Maryland State Police Prince Frederick Barrack that I would be en route to the address.    Upon arrival, at approximately 1829 hours, I made contact with Shirlita Venee Commodore (B/F DOB: 05/11/1988) who was identified by her Maryland Learners Permit. I spoke with Shirlita Commodore and advised her that I received a call for a suicidal juvenile at her residence. I advised Shirlita Commodore that the call was in reference to Serena Commodore, and she quickly stated that the call must be for her daughter, Ziyara Commodore (B/F DOB: 11/07/2007). Shirlita Commodore stated that her daughter was inside the apartment. I asked Shirlita Commodore if I could talk to Ziyara Commodore to make sure she was okay. Shirlita Commodore agreed and went inside to get her daughter.    I made contact with Ziyara Commodore who was wearing baggy pajama pants and an oversized hoodie. I immediately noticed that Ziyara Commodore was upset. Ziyara Commodore barely made eye contact with me, and she spoke with a soft and quiet voice the entire time I was talking to her. I advised Ziyara that I was at the residence because I received a call for a suicidal subject. I asked Ziyara Commodore if she had any idea on what I was talking about, and she nodded her head, yes. I told Ziyara Commodore that I was there to check up on her well-being and wanted to make sure she wasnt going to harm herself. I asked Ziyara Commodore if she had any suicidal thoughts, and she stated that she was suicidal yesterday, but she was not currently feeling suicidal. I asked Ziyara if she had any thoughts about killing someone else, and she stated, no. I proceeded to ask Ziyara Commodore if she wanted to hurt herself or someone else, and she also stated that she did not. Prior to speaking with Ziyara Commodore, I was informed that Ziyara wrote a goodbye letter the day prior, but she was seen present at school at, Calvert High School, 520 Fox Run Blvd, Prince Frederick, Md 20678 earlier that day. I asked Ziyara Commodore if it was true that she wrote a goodbye letter that day before, and she nodded her head, yes. Ziyara Commodore stated that she did not want to talk to anyone and wanted to be left alone. Ziyara Commodore appeared to start crying, so in an attempt to calm her down I told her that she could go inside the apartment while I spoke to her mother.    While speaking with the mother, Shirlita Commodore, she seemed to be extremely confused on what was happening. I advised Shirlita Commodore that I received information that her daughter was possibly suicidal. I asked Shirlita Commodore if she was aware of the situation, and she stated that she was not. I asked Shirlita Commodore if she has noticed anything strange with her daughter lately, and she stated that her daughter has seemed normal. Shirlita Commodore stated that her daughter does well in school, has friends, and is well-behaved around the house. Shirlita Commodore stated that, occasionally, Ziyara gets bored from being in the house, so they go out and do activities like shopping together. Shirlita Commodore stated that they moved to Calvert County from Charles County approximately a year and a half ago, but the transition seemed to be smooth, so she does not believe that the transition would cause Ziyara Commodore to feel the need to harm herself. I also told Shirlita Commodore that her daughter wrote a goodbye letter the day prior. Shirlita Commodore was shocked to hear the news, and stated that she had no clue about it. Prior to my arrival, I was informed that Ziyara Commodore did not attempt suicide due to the fact that she was scared of the repercussions that would come along with it. I informed Shirlita of this information. I advised Shirlita that the Calvert County Mobile Crisis Team (MCT) is available if she, or her daughter, needed to speak them. I advised her that MCT has personnel that are highly trained for situations like this one. I told Shirlita Commodore that MCT would be able to better help the situation by talking with Ziyara and providing her the help she needs to include, treatments and medications, or any other resources available to her. Shirlita requested to speak to MCT, and asked if they could talk to her and Ziyara.    At approximately 1845 hours, MCT arrived on scene. I spoke with Belinda Barber who is a therapist with MCT. Crystal Sandurov was also on seen. Sandurov is a nurse with MCT. Upon arrival, Barber spoke with Ziyara while I was present, and Ziyara came to the conclusion that she would like to speak with Barber one on one. Ziyara Commodore and Barber stepped aside and spoke privately. After speaking with Ziyara Commodore, Barber advised that Ziyara agreed to talk with MCT in front of her mother, but inside the apartment. Barber advised that she no longer needed me as Ziyara was not a threat to herself or others at that time. I advised Barber that I could stand by and wait for them to conclude, but Barber stated that I was no longer needed. Due to Ziyara not meeting the criteria for an emergency petition, and MCT no longer needing me, I cleared the scene. No signs of injury, distress, or abuse were observed.    After clearing from the scene, I spoke with Ziyaras school counselor, Julie, along with Calvert High Schools school resource officer, DFC Dean Naughton. I made both parties aware of the situation and outcome of the call. Both parties stated that they would keep an eye out for her, and will stay in touch if needed.    At approximately 2222 hours, I made contact with Barber via telephone in an attempt to gather any further information that was obtained after I cleared the scene. Barber advised that she spoke with the Commodore family for well over an hour. Barber stated that she was able to encourage Ziyara Commodore to be transported to MCTs clinic for further evaluation and assessment. Barber stated that she found Ziyara Commodore to be in need of hospitalization. Barber stated that she was able to encourage Ziyara to seek more treatment via the hospital. Barber stated that Shirlita Commodore drove to MCTs clinic to pick her daughter up and transport her to the Calvert Health Medical Center.    Case closed.    All events occurred in Calvert County, MD.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 20:04:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7266</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/05/2023 22:42:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5829</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hernandez-Miguel</LastName>
            <FirstName>Pavel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7266</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>15</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 19:58:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:05</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365228</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Commodore</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ziyara</FirstName>
               <DOB>11/07/2007 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/04/2023 19:57:34</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Z600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Commodore</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ziyara</FirstName>
               <DOB>11/07/2007 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Z600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/04/2023 19:57:34</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>280</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Shore Acres</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>348</SubNumber>
               <City>Prince Frederick</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20678</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.581794</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.545639</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 19:58:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:33</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 19:58:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:33</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 20:02:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:31</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365229</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Commodore</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shirlita</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Venee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/11/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/04/2023 20:00:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S643</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Commodore</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shirlita</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Venee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/11/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S643</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/04/2023 20:00:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>280</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Shore Acres</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>348</SubNumber>
               <City>Prince Frederick</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20678</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.581794</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.545639</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 20:02:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>