<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-001546</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/13/2023 11:32:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/13/2023 11:32:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/13/2023 11:32:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/13/2023 11:32:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Fleeing and eluding/obstruction hindering</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 15:23:44</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3267</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 12:21:19</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OBT</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>213125</AddressId>
      <City>MDC206</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 15:23:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/17/2023 15:35:43</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>213125</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Center</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>North East</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.94809000000008</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.62472003875036</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>COMFORT INN NORTH EAST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FLYING J</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/13/2023 15:23:41</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/13/2023 15:23:41</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40J</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/07/2023 12:10:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 15:23:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 12:10:20</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>  On 01/13/2023 at approximately 1136 hours, members of the Maryland State Police-Stategic Operations Group-North (SOG-N), were conducting a crime suppression initiative in the North East area of Cecil County, MD. At this time, investigators (S/T Pettit #5084 and SGT. Cox #4760) were conducting a patrol check of the Flying J, 1 Center Dr. North East, MD 21901 when they observed a Flying J manager speaking with a female subject. As investigators approached the area, they observed the female walk away and enter the front right passenger side of a blue Chrysler PT Cruiser. Investigators made contact with the manager who advised that they have been having issues with the female and requested investigators to trespass the female and the driver from the property. While speaking with management, investigators observed the vehicle drive through the parking lot and out of view.     Investigators then continued the patrol check when they observed the vehicle parked behind a large commercial vehicle and identified the registration to be (MD-9AK9800). It should be noted that investigators were operating CE-100 a gray unmarked Ford Explorer equipped with License Plate Readers (LPRs) and each investigator was wearing a green tactical vest clearly marked State Trooper.     Investigators made contact with the occupants of the vehicle, identified themselves as State Troopers and stated the reason for the contact (Trespassing them from the property). The emergency equipment of CE-100 was not activated at this time. The driver was identified by his MD identification card as Anthony Joseph Todd (W/M DOB: 11/09/1988) and the second occupant, located in the front right passenger seat, provided the name Kristina Jolene Conley (W/F DOB: 10/20/1995). The female occupant did not produce any picture identification and advised that she did not have an identification card/drivers license in her possession. A check of the driver revealed that he was not wanted but his driving privilege was suspended in the state of Maryland. A check of Kristina Conley was conducted by investigators through the in-car computer via CAPWIN and a photograph was produced. There were physical discrepancies between the female passenger and the photograph of Conley. Investigators then requested the female passenger to step out of the vehicle in an attempt to observe her physical descriptors. At this time, the blue Chrysler PT Cruiser sped off from parking lot. Investigators then attempted to conduct a traffic stop on the vehicle and activated the emergency equipment of CE-100. The PT Cruiser left the parking lot of the business, failing to yield to oncoming traffic and turned left on Lums Rd. Investigators continued to follow the vehicle as it quickly turned down Center Drive, a one-way/dead end driveway to another local business. It should be noted that the vehicles turn signals were never activated and the vehicle was driven in a reckless and negligent manner as it crossed the double yellow line. The vehicle then conducted a U-turn on Center Dr. and quickly exited back onto Lums Rd. without stopping and without any regard for other vehicles. MSP-North East Barrack was notified of the incident and was advised that the vehicle was failing to stop for investigators. The blue Chrysler PT Cruiser continued down Lums Rd and again quickly turned down another one way/dead end driveway to another local business and traveled at a speed greater than reasonable. Investigators followed the vehicle up the second driveway but then deactivated the emergency equipment of CE-100 and discontinued following the vehicle as the PT Cruiser sped through a parking lot turned around and again traveled towards Lums Rd. Investigators requested that MSP-North East Barrack broadcast a description of the vehicle to Cecil County Law Enforcement for fleeing and eluding. Due to the actions of the driver, the investigators were hindered from concluding their investigation into the trespassing complaint.  An application for charges was filed for Anthony Joseph Todd regarding the above incident and a criminal arrest warrant was issued for Todd for Obstructing/Hindering and related traffic offenses.  On 01/18/2023, SOG-N investigators were conducting a crime suppression initiative in the North East area of Cecil County. At this time, investigators were conducting a patrol check of the North East Plaza when they observed a Blue PT Cruiser parked in a parking lot adjacent to the local businesses. Upon further observation, investigators identified the Blue PT Cruiser bearing Maryland registration 9AK9800 to be the same vehicle that fled from them on 01/13/2023. Investigators positioned their vehicle to block the PT Cruiser from fleeing and made contact with and identified the occupants to be Anthony Todd and Kristina Conley. Anthony Todd was placed into custody without incident for the arrest warrant. He was later taken before the Cecil County District Court Commissioners Office and held on a $5000.00 bond. He was subsequently remanded to the Cecil County Detention Center.  Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5084</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 15:43:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5084</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/02/2023 13:33:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cox</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4760</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Peterson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Glen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3267</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pettit</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5084</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490927</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0043</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>18</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/13/2023 11:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0043</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5084</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 15:36:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5084</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/17/2023 15:36:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490927</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14589</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>18</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/13/2023 11:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP5084</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 15:37:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5084</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/17/2023 15:37:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5084</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 15:42:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:18</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366388</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Todd</LastName>
               <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Joseph</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/09/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/17/2023 15:41:56</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Todd</LastName>
               <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Joseph</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/09/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/17/2023 15:41:56</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5084</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 15:42:22</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>