<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002491</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/20/2023 21:28:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/20/2023 21:28:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/20/2023 21:06:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/20/2023 21:06:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>CDS / FIREARM / PWID</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 21:28:13</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 20:13:06</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>LIBERTY RD/ MCDONOGH RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>681250</AddressId>
      <City>MDC519</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 21:28:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 16:56:12</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>681250</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Liberty</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Randallstown</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.79534</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.36741</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>8919-8933 LIBERTY RD / 3611-3611 MCDONOGH RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/20/2023 21:28:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/20/2023 21:28:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/30/2023 14:02:33</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 21:28:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6039</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/15/2023 10:05:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Related Reports: Maryland State Police unmarked vehicle D-24 is equipped with a mobile recording device. The incident was recorded from my BWC. Vehicle Search Report 23-MSP-002454 (Submitted on Delta) Property Records PH #339311, PH #339310 Vehicle Storage Report MVI# N/A Maryland Gun Center Case Report: MDGC Case #202300506 Firearm Tracking Number: N/A (There are no known records of this firearm being stolen) Scene processing The recovered CDS was captioned on MSP Form 63 (Property Record PH #339310) and MSP Form 67 (Request for Laboratory Examination and Chain of Custody) and stored according to MSP policy and procedure. The CDS will be forwarded to the MSP Crime Lab for processing. The recovered firearm, ammunition, and magazine were captioned on MSP Form 63 (Property Record PH #339311) and MSP Form 67 (Request for Laboratory Examination and Chain of Custody) and stored according to MSP policy and procedure. The firearm will be forwarded to the MSP Crime Lab for processing. Copies of all statements of probable cause and statements of charges are attached to the case file. Physical evidence Item A: One cardboard box containing one hundred eighty-two (182) containing suspected marijuana. Weight: 2.80 pounds (PH #339310) Property Section Item: One Black Glock 9MM Handgun (serial #BCWU149) Item: One black color magazine for a .9MM caliber Glock handgun (PH #339311) Item: One clear zip lock bag containing fifteen (15) rounds of 9MM ammunition Count: 15 (PH#326202) Suspects/Defendants: Burgess, Paris Randel (B/M, DOB 06/06/1995) 9017 Hamor Road, Randallstown, Baltimore County, Maryland 21133 Maryland Soundex B-622-267-673-730-425  Narrative On January 20, 2023, at approximately 2106 hours, I, Trooper First Class Reckeweg #7214 of the Maryland State Police, was on duty, operating an unmarked patrol vehicle, D-24. I was in lane one (1) on Green Cone Drive and Liberty Road. At this time, I observed a gray Acura MDX without two front lights (Headlights were off) traveling in lane one (1) on westbound Liberty Road prior to Green Cone Drives. I pulled behind the Acura and initiated a traffic stop as I activated my emergency lights and equipment. The Acura stopped in lane one (1) on McDonough Road after Liberty Road. I then observed the Acura bearing Maryland registration 93060CK. I contacted the driver by the drivers side window and advised the reason for the traffic stop. Upon contact with the driver, I immediately detected the strong odor of raw and burnt marijuana emanating from inside the vehicle. I asked the driver for his drivers license and registration. I identified the driver as Burgess, Paris Randel (B/M, DOB 06/06/1995, Maryland Soundex B-622-676-730-425)) by his Maryland drivers license. I asked Burgess where he was coming from, and he advised that he was coming from a restaurant. I observed a brown duffle bag on the rear right passenger floor mat. I asked Burgess if he could pull the duffle bag to the front. Burgess reached for the duffle bag with his right arm and put the duffle bag in his lap. Burgess then pulled a purple plastic bag out of the duffle bag (imprinted Rainbow Dragon / Cannabis Flower 3.5g) and advised that it was marijuana/cannabis.Later Burgess advised that he does not possess a medical marijuana/cannabis card. K-9 Corporal Fohs #5215 of the Maryland State Police arrived on scene to assist with the traffic stop. I asked Burgess to exit the Acura and walk to the front of my patrol vehicle. At the front of my patrol vehicle, I advised Burgess that I had detected the strong odor of marijuana/cannabis emitting from inside the Acura which he replied that he had smoked marijuana prior to the traffic stop. Burgess stated, you smell marijuana because I just smoked. I advised Burgess that I would search the vehicle, and Burges became extremely nervous as he was moving his hands up and down, stating, hold on, I am not gonna lie, yall make me really nervous; he smelled weed, I showed him a pack of weed. Burgess kept repeating that he was nervous. After Burgess was removed from the Acura, a probable cause search based on the odor of raw and burnt marijuana was conducted. While searching the Acura, I located the following items: A brown duffle bag located on the right rear passenger side containing one hundred and eighty-two (182) (PH #339310) plastic bags containing a measured total amount (2.80 pounds) of greenish-brown vegetable matter, suspected marijuana which I identified through my training, knowledge, experience and previous drug arrests as marijuana. One (1) black in color 9MM Handgun (serial# BCWU149), located in the rear pocket of the front passenger seat, which was easily in reach of Burgess, loaded with fifteen (15) rounds of 9MM ammunition with one round in the chamber.   Based on my training knowledge and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, my involvement in controlled dangerous substance investigations, and previous drug arrests. A large amount of marijuana (2.80 pounds including packaging) and the amount in which the marijuana was packaged (180 small bags of approximately 3.5 grams each) inside the duffle bag is consistent with the distribution of controlled dangerous substances and not personal use. Furthermore, no paraphernalia used for smoking was located inside the Acura, which indicates to me that the marijuana was intended for distribution. I know marijuana is a Schedule (I) controlled, dangerous substance. Based on my training, knowledge, experience, and previous drug arrests, I know that subjects involved in the sales of controlled dangerous substances will commonly possess firearms to protect themselves and their product. I believe that the handgun/firearm located inside the Acura in the rear pocket of the front passenger seat, which was easily within reach of Burgess, was possessed as a nexus to a drug trafficking crime.  At approximately 2123 hours, Burgess was placed under arrest and transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack for processing. The total weight of the marijuana was weighed by Corporal Fohs #5215 of the Maryland State Police and found to be 2.80 pounds (P#339310), including packaging. One (1) Black in color Glock 9mm Handgun, serial #BWU149 (PH#339311), fifteen (15) rounds of 9mm ammunition (PH #339311) was verified By Corporal Fohs. At approximately 0230 hours, I, Trooper First Class Reckeweg #7214, advised Burgess of his Miranda Rights. Burgess waived his Miranda Rights and agreed to answer my questions. I asked Burgess why he had a large amount of marijuana inside the brown duffle bag, and he advised that he smoked a lot of weed, so it was for personal use. I then asked Burgess why he had a firearm inside the Acura, and he replied that he was scared for his life. I asked Burgess where he got the handgun/firearm from, and he replied I do not want to answer any more questions. No more questions were asked of Burgess at this time. Master Trooper Plumadore, #2632 of the Maryland Gun Center, was contacted in reference to the Black Glock 9mm Handgun/firearm serial #BWCU149 located inside the Acura. Master Trooper Plumadore later advised me via email that Burgess was prohibited from possessing a firearm (MDGC case #2023-00506). Burgess was convicted of regulated firearm stolen-possess/transfer/dispose of (PS-5. 138) (misdemeanor) plead date 06/27/2017, and CDS possess with intent to distribute (CR-5-602) (Felony) plead date 10/07/2020. The attached charges were provided to me by the Maryland Gun Center. A copy of the Maryland Gun Center response is attached to this report. The Maryland Gun Enforcement Division was notified of this arrest. Sergeant Sawa of the Maryland State Police was contacted. At approximately 0946 and 1047 hours, Burgess was in front of Baltimore Commissioner #8112 (Virtual). Burgess was held without bond and transported to the Baltimore County Detention Center. Burgess was given copies of all pertinent paperwork. Burgess cooperative during processing. All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 10:26:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 10:26:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>70</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fohs</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5215</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Forrester</LastName>
            <FirstName>Douglas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1174</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491874</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0493</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/20/2023 21:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0493</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 16:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 16:57:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 16:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:13</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366897</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Burgess</LastName>
               <FirstName>Paris</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Randel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/06/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 16:34:46</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Burgess</LastName>
               <FirstName>Paris</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Randel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/06/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 16:34:46</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9017</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hamor</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Randallstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21133</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3735</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.795975</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.374203</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 16:59:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 16:59:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 16:59:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 16:56:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 16:56:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148948</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 17:00:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 17:00:41</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2HNYD18966H529516</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2006</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>ACUR</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>93060CK</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 17:02:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 17:02:20</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>15</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>182 SMALL BAGS CONTAINING MARIJUANA / WEIGHT INCLUDED PACKAGING</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>241998</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>2.8</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>LB</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 17:06:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 17:06:13</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>15</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>ONE BLACK IN COLOR HANDGUN PH#339311</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>610</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <SerialNumber>BCWU149</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>241999</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>GLOCK</Make>
         <Model>19G</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 17:08:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 17:08:01</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>15</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>15 HOLLOW POINT ROUNDS </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>424</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242000</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>15</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 17:09:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 17:09:22</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>15</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>ONE BLACK IN COLOR 9MM MAGAZINE FOR A GLOCK 19G</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>611</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242001</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 17:10:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 17:10:33</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One iPhone cellphone black in color </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>489</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242002</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <Model>iPhone</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/14/2023 18:06:22</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/14/2023 18:06:22</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/15/2023 10:05:59</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP1174</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 18:06:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/15/2023 10:06:01</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>TEST FIRE   On February 21, 2023 I, D/Sgt. Douglas Forrester # 1174 of the Maryland State Police completed a test-firing of the following firearm by firing two test shots with the firearm. I am currently assigned to the Golden Ring Barrack located at 8908 Kelso Drive, Essex, MD 21221. I can be contacted by email at douglas.forrester@maryland.gov or by phone at 410-780-2706.   Make: Glock  Model: 19  Caliber: 9MM  Serial Number: BCWU149   I certify that this firearm is operable and capable of being fired. The test shots have been forwarded to the Maryland State Police Firearm/Toolmark Unit for NIBIN database entry and storage. I attended the MSP Forensic Buddy training and successfully completed a competency test. I successfully completed re-certification on December 14, 2022.  See attached Maryland State Police OTS Firearm Test Fire Certificate Form MSP 21-30. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP1174</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 18:07:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:09:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burton</LastName>
            <FirstName>Graham</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Forrester</LastName>
            <FirstName>Douglas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1174</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>