<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013529</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/16/2023 14:21:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/16/2023 14:21:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/16/2023 13:32:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/16/2023 13:32:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>04/16/2023 19:00:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>Rayshima Lesheer Schoolfield was arrested for second degree assault for punching her niece in the face.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 14:22:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1773</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/01/2023 08:33:58</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>61910</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 14:22:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/28/2023 14:01:05</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>61910</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2011</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Cropper</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Pocomoke City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21851</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.597697</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.063871</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/16/2023 14:21:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/16/2023 14:21:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/28/2023 23:24:22</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 14:22:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:47</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was captured on BWC and labeled on Axon Evidence 23MSP013388. TFC. Phillipss BWC was alsoutilized.  Scene Processing: Aunt and niece were in a verbal domestic that turned physical over the residences being messy. The aunt assaulted the niece by punching her in the right side of her face. The niece had evidence of injury under her right eye. Three (3) photos attached to this report.  Evidence: One (1) Maryland State Police Domestic Violence Supplement (MSP Form 246) Three (3) digital photographs of Corbins injury.  Narrative:  On April 16, 2023, at approximately 1332 hours, I, Tfc. Pinto #7212, responded to 2011 Cropper Court, Pocomoke, Worcester County, Maryland for the report of a verbal argument in progress.  Upon my arrival, I made contact with Rayshima Lesheer Schoolfield (B/F 05/07/1990), who was identified by her Maryland identification card. Standing next to Schoolfield was a friend of hers. I asked Schoolfield what happened before I arrived and she advised her and Kaliyah My-Ria Corbin (B/F 01/14/2004), who was later identified by her Maryland Drivers License, attacked her. I asked Schoolfield what made Corbin attack her and she advised it was over making the residence, that belongs to her mother, a mess. Schoolfield stated she didnt know what happened but when she came back everyone had an attitude, was angry, and Corbin charged her. Schoolfield then pointed to a scratch on her left forearm and advised it was from Corbin. While looking at the scratches on Schoolfields arms, I observed them to appear an old injury due to being scabbed over and healing. Schoolfield then advised she wanted to press charges. I asked Schoolfield if she lives at the residence and she advised she did. I asked Schoolfield who owns the residence and she stated her mother and father. I asked Schoolfield who she had the argument with and she stated her niece Corbin. I asked Schoolfield if Corbin lives at the residence and she stated when she wants to. I asked Schoolfield if she asked Corbin to clean the residence. Schoolfield stated no, when she came back to the residence, Corbin told her that her and her children who stay at the residence are messy. I asked Schoolfield what started the arguing and she stated that Corbin and her mother were mad that the residence was messy. I asked Schoolfield if she agrued with her mom at all and she advised she did not.  After making contact with Schoolfield, I made contact with Corbin. I asked Corbin what happened before I arrived on scene and she stated that she was inside the residence cleaning and when she came outside to get laundry out of the trunk of her vehicle, Schoolfield came outside and started arguing with her and hit her in the face. I asked Corbin what caused the argument and she advised that she told Schoolfield that she needed help with keeping the residence clean and not be messy. I asked Corbin what caused the agreement and she advised it was because she told Schoolfield she needed to get up and help clean the residence. Corbin went onto explain that Schoolfield then came outside the residence and stated that she needs to keep her mouth shut. I asked Corbin if she lives at the residence and she advised she does. I asked Corbin what her relation to Schoolfield was and she advised it is her aunt. I asked Corbin who owned the residence and she stated Schoolfields mother Ruth Anne Copes (B/F 01/14/1952), who was identified by her name and date of birth. I asked Corbin if Copes observed her and Schoolfield arguing and Schoolfield hitting her In the face and she advised she did. I asked Corbin if she has any injuries from when Schoolfield punched her and she advised she didnt think so. I asked Corbin if Schoolfield hit her first and she stated she did and that is how it all escalated anyway. I asked Corbin where she was hit in the face and she stated all around her face. I asked Corbin if she remembers scratching Schoolfields left arm and she advised she did not. At this time, I asked Corbin to look into the rearview mirror of a vehicle in the driveway and asked her to see if she has any injuries to her face and she advised it was red under her eye.  While looking at Corbins eye, I observed redness/ bruising under her right eye. Three (3) digital photographs attached to this report.  I then made contact with Copes. I asked Copes what she observed and she stated Schoolfield and Corbin were arguing inside the residence. Copes stated she asked them to stop arguing and when one would stop the other would continue. Copes advised when Corbin came outside and opened the trunk of her vehicle, she observed Schoolfield hands go to Corbins face. Copes then stated she then observed Schoolfield push Corbin and she fell to the ground. Copes stated she observed Schoolfield and Corbin begin to physically fight until her son came and broke them up. I asked Copes if she observed any injuries on Corbin and she stated she has a bruising under her right eye. While speaking with Copes, I observed Corbin turned her back to me and I observed dirt on the back side of her shirt like she had been on the ground. After making contact with Copes, I made contact with Corbin and completed a Maryland State Police Domestic Violence Supplement Form (MSP Form 246). Attached to this report.   I made contact with Schoolfield and her friend again. I asked Schoolfields friend if she witnessed the fighting between Schoolfield and Corbin and she advised she didnt wish to speak to me due to it being a family matter.  Schoolfield was placed under arrest at 1426 hours for second degree assault. Schoolfield was transported to Pocomoke Police Department, located at 1500 Market Street, Pocomoke, Worcester County, Maryland for processing.  Schoolfield was seen by the Ocean City Commissioner and held on $5000 bond.  After being seen by the commissioner, Schoolfield stated she had scratches in her breast area from Corbin and stated she wanted to press charges on Corbin. Schoolfield was advised she could go to a Worcester County Commissioner in order to apply for charges.  A search of the holding cell was conducted by PFC Northam, from the Pocomoke Police Department, and she advised that a underwire from a bra was located inside the holding cell. PFC Northam stated a cell search was conducted before Schoolfield was placed inside and it was clear.  Schoolfield was transported the Worcester County Jail located at 5022 Joyner Road, Snow Hill, Maryland.  Cleared by arrest.  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 12:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/28/2023 14:15:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phillips</LastName>
            <FirstName>Riley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7211</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502937</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 14:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 14:01:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/28/2023 14:03:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 14:01:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:02</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>302999</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>SCHOOLFIELD</LastName>
               <FirstName>RAYSHIMA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LESHEER</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/07/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/07/2021 07:40:17</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S414</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>SCHOOLFIELD</LastName>
               <FirstName>RAYSHIMA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LESHEER</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/07/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S414</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/07/2021 07:40:17</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2011</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Cropper</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Pocomoke City</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21851</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.597697</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.063871</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 14:08:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:06</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 14:08:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:06</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>19</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 14:05:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:19</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>361466</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>CORBIN</LastName>
               <FirstName>KALIYAH</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MY-RIA</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/15/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/19/2022 20:14:23</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C615</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>CORBIN</LastName>
               <FirstName>KALIYAH</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MY-RIA</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/15/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C615</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/19/2022 20:14:23</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2011</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Cropper</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Pocomoke City</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21851</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.597697</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.063871</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>735</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7969</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/19/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 14:05:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>71</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 14:07:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:03</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>344434</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Copes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ruth</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/14/1952 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/25/2022 04:41:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Copes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ruth</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/14/1952 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/25/2022 04:41:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2011</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Cropper</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Pocomoke City</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21851</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.597697</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.063871</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 14:07:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 14:07:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>