<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012672</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/10/2023 00:49:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/10/2023 00:49:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/09/2023 23:26:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/09/2023 23:26:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>CHECKED WELFARE OF DISABLED VEHICLE. DRIVER OF VEHICLE WAS VISIBLY AND AUDIBLY INTOXICATED. WHILE ATTEMPTING TO GAIN COMPLIANCE FOR FIELD SOBRIETY, KNOTT FLED ON FOOT. KNOTT CONTINUED TO RESIST ARREST THROUGHOUT THE DETAINMENT PROCESS.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 00:49:51</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5635</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 19:57:22</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>RSA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WFC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>LEONARDTOWN / GALLANT GREEN RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>690313</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 00:49:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/11/2023 06:00:26</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>690313</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>8200</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Leonardtown</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Hughesville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20637</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.784071</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.537983</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/10/2023 00:49:49</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/10/2023 00:49:49</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/27/2023 19:57:23</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 00:49:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:28</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was captured on my body-worn camera. This incident was captured on my in-car rear facing camera, H-27. This incident was captured on TFC Fosters body worn camera and in-car camera H-13.  NARRATIVE:  DUI #: 23- 064  Defendant: Knott, Michelle Marie  Maryland drivers license: K530603585169  Subsequent offender: Yes  Intoximeter results: Refusal  CERTIFICATIONS AND TRAINING: Certified RADAR/LIDAR operator Certified in the administration of standardized field sobriety tests Certified in advanced roadside impaired driver enforcement training  VEHICLE IN MOTION (Phase 1)  On 04/09/2023 at 2339 hours, I Trooper Shank #7587, was dispatched to a welfare check on a vehicle in a ditch located at northbound MD RT. 5 @ Gallant Green Rd. It was reported that there were people running around on the side of the road attempting to wave down people driving by. Upon arrival, I identified a silver Chevrolet Impala (Registration - VA: UDT8252) parked on the shoulder of the road in the grass. Two passengers of the disabled vehicle quickly exited the vehicle and approached me, attempting to engage in conversation. The passengers were identified as Trevon Marquise Butler (DOB: 10/9/94) and Foday Badara Ladie Jr. (6/7/97). Both passengers explained they ran out of gas and that somebody was on their way with gas to help. Butler was visibly intoxicated based on the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath, slurred speech, and inability to follow simple commands. I asked who was driving the vehicle, to which Ladie told me that it was the female in the drivers seat. I later identified the driver as Michelle Marie Knott, DOB: 03/05/1990, by her MD drivers license.  PERSONAL CONTACT/PRE-ARREST SCREENING (Phases 2 and 3)  While speaking with Ladie, Knott proceeded to step out of the vehicle, stumbling into her car and slamming the door shut in the process. Knott then walked away from the vehicle ignoring basic commands to stay closer to the vehicle. When Knott finally responded, I was met with hostility, threats, and aggressive behavior. I was told by Knott to not touch her. Knott yelled at me, You do not know what the fuck I will do to you. Knott slurred her speech throughout the brief conversation. Butler continued to approach me with his hands up, continuously getting close and attempting to take control of the situation. I requested other units to the scene due to the chaotic nature of the scene. Knott returned to her vehicle and sat in the drivers seat.  When another unit arrived (TFC Foster #6937), I approached Knott again and opened the drivers side door. Knott was leaning on the door with her head held up by her arm. I noticed her eyes were visibly glassy. Based on the slurred speech, stumbling/balance issues, glassy eyes, and the aggressive behavior, I determined Knott to be under the influence of alcohol. Knott also displayed notable behavior swings throughout the encounter. Aggression and hostility were the primary traits observed. I asked Knott where they were coming from and Knott told me Lexington Park. I also asked where they were going, to which Knott responded Charlotte Hall, despite telling me that she had not been driving. Both passengers identified Knott as the driver various times throughout the incident. Neither of the passengers had a valid drivers license, and the car is registered to Knott. At this time, I requested Knott to step out of the vehicle to complete field sobriety testing. Knott told me, Leave me the fuck alone and that she was calling her aunt to come pick her up.  At this time another vehicle pulled in front of the location. TFC Foster remained with Knott and the passengers while I contacted the driver of the vehicle. The driver of the vehicle explained that he was driving in the area and the occupants in the grass flagged him down. He offered to go get gas to assist them. I instructed the driver to pull off to the side of the road temporarily and I walked back to TFC Foster.  Knott eventually complied and exited the vehicle. Both passengers continuously yelled at Knott in an attempt to calm her down. Knott would continue her aggressive behavior towards TFC Foster. Knott continuously stated, Do not touch me. I attempted to de-escalate the situation several times by simply explaining what was happening and why it was happening. Knott continued to ignore me while walking away. Butler then exits the vehicle and begins to be assertive about going to get the gas from the other vehicle. I gave three separate orders to get back into the vehicle, to which Butler eventually complied. I once again asked Knott to comply and complete field sobriety; Knott replied, Im not doing shit. Knott verbally refused to complete field sobriety and continued to be aggressive. TFC Foster tells Butler he may go get the gas to fill up the car. Butler asks several times if we want to search him. Knott gets very close to both TFC Foster and myself when discussing what we were going to do with the situation and Knott is instructed to back up. I told Knott, You told us to leave you alone and now youre coming at us. Knott responds by yelling, Leave me the fuck alone. Knott begins to walk away, then suddenly turns around and quickly moves towards TFC Foster in a threatening manner. Knott comes within an inch of TFC Fosters face and begins to use hand gestures around his face.  TFC Foster attempts to grab Knotts wrist to detain her due to the threatening behavior. Knott yanks her arm away and proceeds to run away from the vehicle. Knott runs into the middle of MD RT. 5, a dark and unlit area with a vehicle passing by. I ordered Knott to get out of the roadway, as her safety became a pressing issue. This began a foot pursuit to which Knott was caught by TFC Foster when running back around her vehicle. TFC Foster used a controlled take-down from the rear to lower Knott into the grass. At this time, Knott pinned her right arm underneath her body, so we would not be unable to place handcuffs on her. I utilized a soft empty hand technique by muscling her right arm out from underneath her body and placing her hand behind her back. At this time, TFC Foster placed his handcuffs on her and we moved Knott onto her side in a recovery position. Once in the recovery position, Knott continued to thrash her legs. TFC Foster and I then assisted Knott to a standing position by lifting her body upward with her arms. Knott continued to yell profanities and tell us not to touch her. Ladie began to yell at Knott to, Shut up and let them talk.  ARREST  Knott was arrested at this point for concerns over her safety, driving under the influence and fleeing on foot. Knott was searched by Deputy Bagwell #A680 of the Charles County sheriffs office on scene and placed into the front seat of my police cruiser H-27. Knott did not willingly go into the police cruiser, as she used her feet to prevent the door from closing. Knott stated, Im not getting in shit when ordering her into the vehicle. TFC Foster had to forcibly push her feet into the vehicle to close the door. In-car rear facing camera was activated at this time.  EMS was called on scene to ensure that Knott was not injured, despite being told she did not want EMS. EMS arrived at the scene and Knott once again refused any treatment or help.  While seated in the police cruiser H-27, Knott continued to ask why she was being arrested. I explained that she was being arrested for fleeing on foot and driving under the influence of alcohol/driving while impaired. Knott ignored me every time and continued to ask why she was being arrested. Knott had notable mood swings throughout her time in the vehicle. Knott would begin yelling and then suddenly calm down to a relaxed state. Knott closed her eyes various times and appeared to be nearly falling asleep. For two minutes and ten seconds, Knott calmly says a few words while keeping her eyes shut for most of the time. Knott would be in a calmed state for a span of 11 minutes and 40 seconds. Knott then changes her mood and goes back to being aggressive and hostile. Knotts mood would steadily escalate. Knott continued to yell profanities at me calling me a bitch as well as making homophobic statements.  On two separate incidents while seated, Knott unbuckled her seat belt and attempted to flee. Knott was able to open the car door at one point, before being forced back into the vehicle. While attempting to pull up the DR-15 Advice of Rights audio file, Knott headbutted my in-car computer and began kicking the interior of the vehicle. Knott damaged the air conditioning vent, breaking one of the brackets (cost estimate for vent, plus installation - $568.33). Knott also broke a charging cord to my GPS navigation system, snapping the USB in half (cost estimate - $19.99). Knott was then transferred to Deputy Bagwells police cruiser with a caged backseat as a result of the violent actions. Knott once again refused to enter the vehicle, using her foot to keep the car door open. Knott was forced into the police cruiser by both Deputy Bagwell and TFC Foster.  Knott was transported to Charles County Detention Center and custody was released. While at the detention center Knott told me several times that she was going to sue me. I read Knott the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Knott refused the intoximeter at 0152 hours on 04/10/2023. Knott was charged with 16356 TA 21 902 a1: (Driving, Attempting to drive) vehicle while under the influence of alcohol: 16356 1 0600 CR, 9-408(b): Resist/Interfere with arrest 14583 TA 21 902 b1: (Driving, Attempting to drive) veh. while impaired by alcohol: 14583 14590 TA 21 904 b2: Attempt by driver to elude uniformed police by fleeing on foot: 14590  All events occurred in Charles County, MD.   Application of charges was completed for Malicious Destruction of Property. These items include the air conditioner bracket of police cruiser H-27, as well as my personal navigation system charging cord. Price estimates for the air vent are included as an attachment. The ford dealership was unable to give me a physical copy of the installation estimate, however I was informed the cost of installation would be $385.00.  I request that this case remain open pending summons service for malicious destruction of property charges. The total cost of repairs is $588.32.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 00:27:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 11:34:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Foster</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6937</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nain</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7452</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barth</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0104</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Esh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5635</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shank</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7587</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502076</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0600</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/09/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0600</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 23:52:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 23:52:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502076</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14590</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/09/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14590</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 23:53:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 23:53:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502076</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/09/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 23:54:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 23:54:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502076</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/09/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 23:57:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 23:57:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502076</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3 4025</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/09/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3 4025</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 01:13:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/13/2023 01:13:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 00:02:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:31</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>246529</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Knott</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michelle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/05/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.27333466E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>09/24/2019 03:30:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Knott</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michelle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/05/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.27333466E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>K530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/24/2019 03:30:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>29025</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Three Notch</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>4</SubNumber>
               <City>Mechanicsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20659</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3291</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.7706868</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.4659337</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>212</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>840</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0975</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/24/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>230</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8760</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 00:26:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 00:26:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 00:26:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 00:26:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 00:26:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 01:25:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:30</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373953</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>SHANK</LastName>
               <FirstName>RYAN</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/11/2023 01:23:32</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>SHANK</LastName>
               <FirstName>RYAN</FirstName>
               <SLastName>S520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/11/2023 01:23:32</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9500</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mitchell</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>La Plata</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20646</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.981642</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.566611</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 02:17:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 02:17:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>25</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 00:44:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374112</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>LADIE</LastName>
               <FirstName>FODAY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>BADARA</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/07/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>04/13/2023 00:42:46</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>LADIE</LastName>
               <FirstName>FODAY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>BADARA</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/07/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>L300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/13/2023 00:42:46</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PA</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 00:44:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>28</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 00:48:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:31</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>185561</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <SSN>2.13435596E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Butler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trevon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marquis</MiddleName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B346</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T615</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <SSN>2.13435579E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Butler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trevon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marquise</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/09/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13435576E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B346</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T615</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Butler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trevon</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B346</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T615</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Butler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trevon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marquise</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/09/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/29/2018 03:15:48</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B346</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T615</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Butler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trevon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>M</MiddleName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B346</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T615</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <SSN>2.13435596E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Butler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trevon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marquis</MiddleName>
               <SLastName>B346</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T615</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <SSN>2.13435579E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Butler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trevon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marquise</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/09/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13435576E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>B346</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T615</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Butler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trevon</FirstName>
               <SLastName>B346</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T615</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Butler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trevon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marquise</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/09/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B346</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T615</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/29/2018 03:15:48</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Butler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trevon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>M</MiddleName>
               <SLastName>B346</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T615</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>22050</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Willow Spring</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>208</SubNumber>
               <City>Lexington Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.448911</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.245376</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetName>POB 83</StreetName>
               <City>Chaptico</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20659</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>21543</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Old Missouri</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Lexington Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.454992</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.258908</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>46563</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Valley</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>7005</SubNumber>
               <City>Lexington Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.464506</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.267928</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>21155</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Lexwood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Lexington Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.484458</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.250635</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>558</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8870</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/17/2018 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>309</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1837</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/17/2018 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>572</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4781</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/30/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PA</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 00:48:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 00:55:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:25</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374113</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>FOSTER</LastName>
               <FirstName>MATTHEW</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/13/2023 00:53:34</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F236</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>FOSTER</LastName>
               <FirstName>MATTHEW</FirstName>
               <SLastName>F236</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/13/2023 00:53:34</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9500</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mitchell</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>La Plata</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20646</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.981642</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.566611</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 02:18:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 02:18:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 11:31:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:28</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374533</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bagwell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Deputy</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 11:30:20</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bagwell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Deputy</FirstName>
               <SLastName>B240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 11:30:20</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 11:31:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 02:32:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 02:32:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240010642</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName> State Of Maryland</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>W</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:17:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 08:19:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151840</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 00:11:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/11/2023 00:11:01</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2G1WB58K889215076</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2008</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>IMP</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4D</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>UDT8252</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151903</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>VI</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:20:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 08:20:09</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FM5K8AR6HGC57643</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>XPL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>PV</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>EM</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>H-27</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>ST</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehicleValue>183</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 01:09:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/13/2023 02:14:28</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>CHARGING CABLE CONNECTING FROM NAVIGATION SYSTEM TO 12V ADAPTER</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>568</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>19.99</PropertyValue>
         <Value>19.99</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>247131</Property_ID>
         <Make>GARMIN</Make>
         <Model>USB-C Vehicle Power Cable</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/12/2023 15:33:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/12/2023 15:33:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/27/2023 19:57:23</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/12/2023 15:33:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:28</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was recorded on an in-car and body-worn camera system (H-13). The body-worn camera was knocked off of my person during arrest, was located shortly after placing the arrestee in a vehicle, and placed back on my person.  NARRATIVE:    On Sunday, April 9, 2023, at approximately 2353 hours, I, TFC Foster #6937 while operating unmarked MSP patrol vehicle H-13, responded to the area of northbound Route 5 (Leonardtown Road), north of Route 231 (Prince Frederick Road), Hughesville, Charles County, MD 20637 to assist Tpr. Shank #7587 on a check the welfare call for service. The call for service was originated due to a female jumping in and out of the roadway. Tpr. Shank had requested an additional unit to assist due to the aggression and lack of cooperation displayed by an individual on scene. Upon my arrival, I observed a silver passenger vehicle that appeared disabled in the grassy median area off of the left side of the roadway and Tpr. Shank attempting to verbally request a female to exit out of the drivers seat of the vehicle. I further observed two additional male occupants sitting in the vehicle. While Tpr. Shank was attempting to verbally gain compliance at the drivers side of the vehicle, I observed the female becoming increasingly irate and shouting aggressively at Tpr. Shank. She was refusing to exit the vehicle.    I attempted to make contact with her, also via the drivers side, when I became aware, Tpr. Shank was attempting to conduct standardized field sobriety tests, to determine whether I may have been able to verbally gain compliance. I asked her to exit the vehicle and she responded with several expletives and shouting. She continued to refuse to exit her vehicle and demanded we leave the scene. As our verbal commands were being refused, Tpr. Shank and I attempted to disengage/deescalate and convene at the back of her vehicle to determine if there was a more efficient way to gain compliance, while also allowing the female to calm down.    After few moments, all three occupants had exited the vehicle. The two male occupants, one a friend, and the other, later determined to be the boyfriend of the female, were attempting to explain to Tpr. Shank and myself that they ran out of gas and were just waiting for additional fuel; however, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from all three individuals. Tpr. Shank reiterated to me that all occupants had conveyed to him that the female was driving the vehicle, Tpr. Shank detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage, and he intended to conduct standardized field sobriety tests on the female. It was apparent that the two males intentions were to continue to drive toward their destination once fuel had arrived. I observed another passenger vehicle arrive at the scene ahead of us and Tpr. Shank went to make contact with that vehicle to ascertain their, if any, involvement, while I remained with the three individuals. Tpr. Shank responded back to my location and advised they were dropping fuel off.    The boyfriend advised me his girlfriend was pregnant and gets really emotional. In the short period of time I had been on scene, I observed the female display extremely irate and aggressive characteristics randomly and unprovoked. The female also would display a few short moments of calm and silence, but would reengage and interject herself back into a conversation, becoming extremely irate and aggressive again. She did this several times. The female then aggressively interjected herself into our conversation shouting expletives and demanding we leave the scene. I advised the female that we could not just simply leave the scene and she began to aggressively lunge toward me several times, and in one moment, was inches from my face, shouting. Her hands would come up to her waist as she stepped closer to me, coming within a few feet of me each time. I instructed her to step back; however, she continued to shout at and threaten me. She then, abruptly and aggressively, lunge toward me, coming within arms-length of me.    At that point, I attempted to detain her; however, she pulled her arm away and took off running across Route 5, a major highway in Charles County, in a particular area that was poorly illuminated. As it was my intention to detain her so that we could, in a more secure environment, more efficiently bring the investigation to a peaceful conclusion and I was concerned for her safety running in a dangerous area. Tpr. Shank and I pursued her on foot. The female continued running southbound in the northbound lanes shouting dont touch me. She then proceeded running back toward the grassy median via the gap in between my patrol vehicle and Tpr. Shanks marked patrol vehicle, and then north up the grassy area back toward her vehicle. I eventually caught up to her at the front of her vehicle and was able to, utilizing a controlled takedown from the rear, bring the female to the grassy ground and secure here left wrist behind her back while Tpr. Shank secured her right wrist, which she passively resisted; however, I was able to secure her in handcuffs. The female then began crying just before resorting back to yelling expletives.    Tpr. Nain #7452 arrived shortly after placing the female in handcuffs. Tpr. Nain and I remained with the female until Tpr. Shank was able to move his vehicle closer to us, as she was still tensing up and trying to shake free from Tpr. Nain and I. I escorted the female to the front seat of Tpr. Shanks patrol vehicle where I attempted to secure the female in the seat; however, once there, the female began to tense up, push back, and refuse to get into the vehicle. Utilizing muscling techniques, I was able to secure the female in Tpr. Shankss patrol vehicle.    After a few minutes, it appeared the female had calmed down significantly. I asked the female if she needed any medical attention or if she was injured in any way. She advised she was not. I advised her I would be requesting emergency medical services anyway for a check-up, as she had advised she was two and a half months pregnant. While speaking with her at the window, I was advised the female was Knott, Michelle Marie (DOB: 03/05/1990), verified by her MD drivers license.    After securing Knott, I made contact with the two males again to try and explain the process moving forward and that they would need to acquire transportation as they did not possess valid drivers licenses. During this time, EMS personnel arrived and attempted to tend to Knott. Knott ultimately refused any medical treatment, and after several minutes began to become irate again. She began kicking the passengers side glovebox and screaming. It was at this time, I determined it would be safer for Knott and Tpr. Shank, that we utilize the caged patrol vehicle of a Charles County Sherriffs Office deputy on scene.    While attempting to secure Knott in the deputys patrol vehicle, she began to become increasingly irate and was passively resisting. As she was seated on the rear passengers seat (the caged portion), she locked both of her legs out and pinned her feet against the door so we were unable to close it. After several minutes of utilizing the same muscling techniques I had used when secured her in Tpr. Shanks vehicle, I was finally able to get her legs in the vehicle and have the deputy shut the door.  The deputy transported Knott to the Charles County Detention Center as Tpr. Shank followed behind.  All events occurred in Charles County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/12/2023 16:13:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6937</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/13/2023 14:18:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Young</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6101</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Esh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5635</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Foster</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6937</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/14/2023 01:37:52</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/14/2023 01:37:52</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/27/2023 19:57:23</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 01:37:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:28</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was recorded on body-worn camera system.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; NARRATIVE: font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  On Sunday, April 9, 2023, at approximately 2353 hours, I, Trooper Nain #7452 who is currently assigned to the La Plata Barrack, while operating marked patrol vehicle H-28. I responded to the area of northbound Route 5 (Leonardtown Road), north of Route 231 (Prince Frederick Road), Hughesville, Charles County, MD 20637 to assist Tpr. Shank #7587 and (Trooper First Class) TFC Foster # 6937 on a check the welfare call for service. The call for service was originated due to a vehicle in the ditch with people running around. Tpr. Shank had requested an additional unit to assist due to the aggression and lack of cooperation displayed by an individual on scene and attempted to flee on foot.    Upon my arrival to the Scene, I approach TFC Foster who was placing a female in handcuffs. TFC Foster and I remained with the female until Tpr. Shank was able to move his vehicle closer to us, as she was still tensing up and trying to shake free from TFC Foster and I. TFC Foster and I escorted the female to the front seat of Tpr.Shanks patrol vehicle. TFC Foster attempted to secure the female in the front passenger seat; however, once there, the female began to tense up, push back, and refuse to get into the vehicle. I observe TFC Foster utilizing what appear to be a muscling technique. TFC Foster was able to secure the female in Tpr. Shankss patrol vehicle. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;    TFC Foster asked the female if she needed any medical attention or if she was injured in any way. She advised she was not. TFC Foster advised her he would be requesting emergency medical services anyway for a check-up, as she had advised she was two and a half months pregnant. The female was later identified by her Maryland drivers license as Michelle Marie Knott (W/F, DOB: 03/05/1990). I then walk over to the other two passengers and asked if they had any identification. One of the male occupants advice he was Knotts boyfriend, he was identified by his Maryland identification as Trevon Marquise Butler (B/M, DOB: 10/09/1994). The next passenger was identified by his Maryland identification as Foday Badara Ladie Jr. (B/M, DOB: 06/07/1997).   font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;   After Knott was secured in Tpr. Shanks patrol vehicle, I stood by Tpr. Shanks Patrol vehicle to keep an eye on Knott. TFC Foster made contact with Butler and Ladie Jr to explain the process moving forward and that they would need to acquire transportation as they did not possess valid drivers licenses. During this time, EMS personnel arrived and attempted to tend to Knott. Knott ultimately refused any medical treatment, and after several minutes, began to become irate again. She began kicking the passengers side glove-box and screaming. It was at this time, I determined it would be safer for Knott and Tpr. Shank, if we utilize the caged patrol vehicle of Deputy Bagwell #A680 a Charles County Sherriffs Office Deputy on scene. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;   While TFC Foster was attempting to secure Knott in Bagwells patrol vehicle, she began to become increasingly irate and was passively resisting. As she was seated on the rear passengers seat (the caged portion), she locked both of her legs out and pinned her feet against the door so we were unable to close it. After several minutes of utilizing what appear to be the same muscling techniques TFC Foster had used when securing her into Tpr. Shanks vehicle, TFC Foster was finally able to get her legs in the vehicle. Deputy Bagwell was able to shut the door. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  Deputy Bagwell transported Knott to the Charles County Detention Center as Tpr. Shank followed behind.  I remain at the scene till First Choice Towing arrived to secure and remove the vehicle from the roadway.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; All events occurred in Charles County, Maryland. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 01:39:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7452</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 12:00:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barth</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0104</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Esh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5635</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nain</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7452</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/19/2023 12:52:16</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/19/2023 12:52:16</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/27/2023 19:57:23</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 12:52:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:28</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was Captured on Body Worn Camera (BWC).  Attachments: The charging Documents/Summons.  Narrative:    On Monday, April 19, 2023, at approximately 1308 hours, I, Trooper Nain #7452 who is currently assigned to the La Plata Barrack received a telephone call from Michelle Marie Knott (W/F, DOB:03/05/1990) who stated she received a message that the Maryland State Police La Plata Barrack had some paperwork for her. I advised Knotts that I had a Summons in my possession for her and if it was possible to arrange a place to meet. Knotts stated she was at the Deluxe Inn located at 6705 Crain Highway, La Plata, Maryland. I made contact with Knott who singed the Summons and received a copy for her records.    I request this case be closed with summons being served.    All events occurred in Charles County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7452</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 12:55:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7452</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:26:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Esh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5635</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nain</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7452</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>