<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-010941</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/27/2023 09:27:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/27/2023 09:27:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/27/2023 09:26:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/27/2023 09:26:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Poss/Distribute Child Pornography</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 09:27:38</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 11:23:09</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>CAC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>3536 GREENMOUNT AVE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>688680</AddressId>
      <City>MDC103</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 09:27:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 09:51:50</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>688680</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>3536</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Greenmount</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/27/2023 09:27:35</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/27/2023 09:27:35</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>03/31/2023 10:30:44</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 09:27:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 11:22:50</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments: - Copy of Cybertip125506272  Narrative:   In February 2023, the Maryland State Police Computer Crimes Section / Maryland Internet Crimes Against Children Task Force received NCMEC CyberTip # 125506272. The Cyber Tip, generated by Facebook, indicated that a subject uploaded child pornography to the internet. The Cyber Tip was reviewed by Sgt. Pitcher #5360, and multiple child pornography files were observed.   A review of the files determined a total of size (6) video files constituting child pornography were posted to the Facebook account. Only two of the video files are described below, as they are the only two which differ.  -vb6oRDr3nbmX0IkY281698195_742586640088517_2105595981756119049_n.mp4 (Posted 4 times) IP Address: 192.30.144.186, Upload: 05-18-2022 18:38:56 UTC This five (5) second video captures a nude Caucasian prepubescent female laying down on her back. There is another Caucasian prepubescent male who is performing oral sex on the female. Based on the physical characteristics of the female and being devoid of pubic hair, it appears she is approximately 4-6 years of age.  -Qrrepcu6bqQUgX33281008276_1131622091027495_8717355397980939501_n.mp4 (Posted 2 times) IP Address: 192.30.144.186 Upload: 05-18-2022 18:38:02 UTC This 1 minute 47 second video captures a nude prepubescent asian female astride a nude male. The female is seen placing the erect penis of the male in her vagina, engaged in sexual activity. Based on the physical characteristics of the female, it appears she is approximately 10-12 years of age.   The following suspect information was obtained and provided by NCMEC: Name: Alfred Griffin Mobile Phone: +14439390251 (Verified) Date of Birth: 01-21-1970 Approximate Age: 52 Email Address: agriffin@i-e-institute.org (Verified) Email Address: agriffin@intei.org (Verified) Screen/User Name: alfred.griffin.37 ESP User ID: 759982955 Profile URL: https://www.facebook.com/alfred.griffin.37   A check was conducted and indicated Griffin is/was employed by the Baltimore City School System and the Mayors Office.   It should be noted the two posted videos are viral videos and do not appear to be a self production by Griffin. Also, it should be noted there were approximately 15 password change events captured on Griffins account prior to the uploads of these videos. These password change events occurred at various locations, in various countries. The IP address2402:800:6173:2d1d:2573:21fd:76e3:818 was captured during a password change event that occurred on 5/18/2022 at04:51:58-07:00. An open source search was conducted an the IP address geo-located to Hanoi, Vietnam.   A knock and talk will be conducted in this case.  Case remains open. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5360</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 09:52:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5360</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 10:22:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pitcher</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5360</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/10/2023 11:12:18</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/10/2023 11:12:18</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/10/2023 11:22:50</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5360</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 11:12:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 11:22:50</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>NARRATIVE:  Since the initial investigation, I was able to make contact with the suspect in this case.   On 3/29/2023, I attempted to conduct a knock and talk at the listed address. I did not receive an answer at the door but was able to make contact with an unknown female via Ring Doorbell. She refused to provide her name but indicated if I left a card, she would be in contact with Griffin and have him contact me. Later that day, I received an email from Griffin. Griffin indicated he would be available on 3/30//2023 to speak with me.   On 3/30/2023, I made contact with Griffin and discussed the details of this case with him. Griffin indicated he has not utilized Facebook for approximately 10 years and has not signed on since then. Griffin indicated he works for the Baltimore County School System. Griffin stated he did not recognize the Facebook user name and does not recall that being his name associated with the account when he did have an account. Griffin advised the email address associated with the account were no longer active, and they have not been for some time. Griffin stated he has not seen or been in possession of child pornography.   Based on the interview with Griffin, it appears this was a hacking event and he is not to be considered as a suspect in this case.  Case closed, unfounded. No additional leads to pursue.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5360</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 11:13:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5360</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 11:18:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pitcher</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5360</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>