<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-010945</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/27/2023 10:01:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/27/2023 10:01:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/27/2023 08:53:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/27/2023 08:53:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Child Abuse and Neglect</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 10:01:08</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 12:50:32</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>CAC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WFC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>688687</AddressId>
      <City>MDC152</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 10:01:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/05/2023 12:26:23</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>688687</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>164</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Humberson</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Friendsville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-79.450035</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.678084</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/27/2023 10:01:06</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/27/2023 10:01:06</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/02/2023 12:47:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 10:01:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:52:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>    On 3/27/2023, I was contacted by the MSP - McHenry Barrack. The Duty Officer, Sgt. Bittinger, notified me of an overall concern with the safety and welfare of a sixteen year old boy. The boy was identified as Aden Matthew Harvey Goldsborough. Aden was reportedly found inside his neighbors residence, located at 167 Humberson Road, in Friendsville, MD. Aden was discovered in his neighbors house while he was attempting to take food from their residence. When Aden was found, he remained polite and cooperative with the owners of the residence. As the family spoke to Aden, they realized Aden was starved for food, he was unkept, and he became emotionally fearful of questions pertaining to the notification of his parents. Due to the potential signs of abuse, neglect, and the overall concerns of safety, Aden Goldsborough was transported to the MSP - McHenry Barrack to investigate his overall welfare.      I notified the Garrett County Department of Human Services about the details of the case and they assigned a Child Protective Social Worker, Amanda Richardson, to investigate.      Amanda Richardson and I responded to the MSP-McHenry Barrack to speak with Aden Goldsborough. Jennifer Combs, an additional Child Protective Social Worker, was also present. Upon arriving to the MSP - McHenry Barrack, I was advised Aden had been given food, drink, and he had been allowed to brush his teeth and use the bathroom facilities. Nonetheless, Aden did appear to be unkept and he appeared thin and malnourished. Aden appeared reserved and he remained respectful despite his condition. Aden exhibited an overall fear as he expressed he did not want his parents to find out if he said something and he did not want to return to his parents house. Aden was asked to speak with us about his situation. He agreed. Upon asking Aden to come into a private office, Aden was introduced to Amanda Richardson, Jennifer Combs, and I. After building rapport with Aden, he stated his name and advised he lives at 237 Humberson Road, in Friendsville, Garrett County, MD. Aden advised he lives at the address with his dad, Keith Schmidt, and his stepmother, Daniel Alexander. Aden advised he was the only child in the home. Aden advised he has limited, to no contact, with any other family members. Aden stated he has no further contact with his biological mother and her name was Monica Goldsborough. Aden explained he has lived at his current address in Friendsville for a few years. Aden explained before he lived at his current address, he lived in Baltimore, MD. When Aden was asked about school, Aden explained he does NOT attend the local public school because he was forced to begin the (online) Abeka Christian Academy in Pensacola, FL, in October 2022. Aden appeared dissatisfied with his quality of education and advised he was not getting any help with his schooling from his parents and his grades were not good. Aden advised he did attend the Northern High School in Garrett County, but he was forced to stop because his dad made him quit. Aden advised he was enrolled in the ROTC program, and he expressed he liked it, but when he had to get a haircut his dad got mad at the ROTC Instructor. Aden advised Principal Maddy had to get involved and his dad removed Aden from the school. Aden advised this occurred in October 2022. Aden was asked what happened today that brought him to where he was. Aden advised he got up this morning, at approximately 0700 hours, he was locked outside, and he was hungry. Aden stated he went to the neighbors house and tried to get some food. Aden explained when his stepmother gets up in the morning, she will leave to go to work around 0730 hours. Aden advised his stepmother has some type of job at the Health Department. Aden explained when his mother leaves their house at 0730 hours, he is forced to walk outside with her and the door of the residence is locked behind them. Aden advised he is locked outside until she returns in the evening. When asked what he does outside during the day, Aden advised he is told to go outside and watch the chicken. The chicken was described to live in a chicken coop behind their house and the chicken would free range in their yard. Aden advised he would have to watch the chicken all day and protect the chicken from predators, like a hawk or a wolf. Aden advised he would have to do this seven days a week. Aden advised he would be let outside around 0730 hours, stay outside till about 1100 hours, and wait until his dad would wake up. Aden advised (sometimes) his Dad would let him back in the house for a few minutes around lunch time and then he would have to go back outside and watch the chicken again until his mother came home. Aden also advised he has been locked outside after dark and he has slept outside overnight without being allowed to enter his parents house. Aden explained his dad does not work, and his dad is usually home, but his dad will not allow Aden in the house. Upon asking why he is not allowed in the house, Aden advised his dad believes he eats all the food and he does not trust Aden around his dads belongings. Aden explained his dad has Huntingtons Disease and his dad does not ever want to be woke up while he is sleeping. Aden explained his father can get very mad. Aden stated he spends long periods of time outside regardless of the weather. Aden explained as he is outside, he is not allowed to use the bathroom in his house and he often has to use the bush to relieve himself. Aden advised he has urinating and defecated outside because he is unable and not allowed to enter his parents house to use the tiolet. Aden advised he has found a secret way into the house, but he had to find a screwdriver to use and get in through a window. Aden advised this was difficult to do because of the cold temperatures and he explained his fingers would get numb from trying to take out the screws and get into the house. Aden advised he has been caught inside of his parents house before and his parens get very mad at him. Aden commented his dad does hit him on the top of the head and his dad has become physical with him if he does not listen to him and stay outside. Aden advised he currently does not have any injuries from him being struck from his father because he stays outside. Aden advised his dad was arrested before and he was taken away for a few months in Baltimore, MD. Aden commented and appeared fearful as he stated, I am scared of my dads anger. As Aden advised he spent all of his days outside, we asked what he does at night if he is allowed inside the house. Aden advised he usually gets something small to eat at dinner like rice and sometimes meat. Aden advised he usually stands at the island in the kitchen to eat. As Aden was asked why he would not sit at a table or chair, he simply explained he does not ever sit, or ask to sit down. Aden described being fearful to make any movements which would anger his father in the house. Aden remained and appeared incredibly uncomfortable and concerned about his parents finding out what he was reporting. Aden advised he tries to never ask questions and he never asks why things are happening to him. Aden remained soft-spoken and had a humble and stoic personality. As I asked Aden to describe his meals through the week, Aiden advised he does not get to eat breakfast before he is let outside. Aden found it difficult to state how many lunches he gets a week, but estimated he would only get about 3-4 lunches per week and he stated he would normally get something at dinner. Aden advised he only attempted to ask the neighbors for food because he was hungry and he had no other way to get food from anywhere else. Aden advised he would often ask for peanut butter on bread or try to get something small so he was not taking so much from someone else. When Aden was asked to explain the inside of his house, Aden advised he does have a bedroom in his house. Aden advised he does school, but he has no internet service at his parents house and he can only watch DVDs for school. Aden advised he only has a few clothes in his room and not a lot of belongings. Aden expressed he has no phone and he had no way of contacting anyone for help. Aden continued to express his fear and being afraid to reach out due to the consequences he believed he would sustain if his parents found out. Aden explained his parents residence did not have a working shower in the home and there was one working toilet. Aden advised his parents house only has one bathroom and the sink and the shower do not work in the bathroom. When asked where Aden would cleanse himself, Aden advised he would have to wash his body in the basement, in a downstairs sink. Aden advised he did this one or two times a month. Aden estimated he has not taken a shower in over a year. Aden advised he does not know how his dad cleaned himself, but he was aware his stepmother washes her hair in the downstairs sink. Aden also stated he does not brush his teeth and he believed it has been a few months since he has brushed his teeth. Aden advised the last time he was at a Doctors Office was a few years ago in Baltimore, MD. Aden was able to state there were not any known guns in the house, other than a paintball gun. As Aden was asked if there was any food in the house, Aden explained there was some food and his parents went to the store yesterday, but he is not allowed to eat the food. Aden simply advised he is forced outside and he does not get to eat or drink. Aden advised he does chores such as rake leaves, watch the chicken, and he cleans the seven cat litter boxes from the house. Aden expressed to us that he wanted to have a new life and he was concerned what was going to happen to him. As we finished our conversations, Aden was asked to remain in the room with Jennifer, while we left to speak about the situation. Upon consulting with Amanda Richardson, it was believed the actions alleged against the parent(s) were considered abusive and/or neglectful. It was also believed there was a substantial risk of harm to place Aden back with his parents and the decision was made to place Aden Goldsborough in Foster Care.      As we walked back into the office with Aden, we explained to him what the decision was and how things were going to proceed. When Aden was advised he was going to be placed with another family, he took in a deep breath, closed his eyes, and exhaled for a long period of time. Aden stated, Good as he clasped his hands. Aden noticeably smiled for the first time as we explained to him he would be going to see a Doctor, he would be enrolled in school, and he would be with another family today as he was assisted through the process.      The Garrett County Department of Human Services scheduled a medical evaluation with Dr. Sisler on 3/28/2023. The findings of the medical evaluation are pending.      An Emergency Shelter Care Hearing was scheduled and held on 4/4/2023. After the hearing, it was ruled Aden Goldsborough would remain in the custody of the State of Maryland.      All events did occur in Garrett County, MD.      Case remains open.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 21:12:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4756</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/05/2023 11:58:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zais</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6241</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kline</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7112</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mcgee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2173</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Delmas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4756</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7189</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500348</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0173</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 08:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0173</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 21:07:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4756</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 21:07:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500348</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1614</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 08:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1614</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 21:08:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4756</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 21:08:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500348</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0844</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 08:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0844</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 21:10:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4756</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 21:10:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 12:18:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:59</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373477</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Schimidt</LastName>
               <FirstName>Keith</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alexander</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/29/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14296588E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 12:17:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Schimidt</LastName>
               <FirstName>Keith</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alexander</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/29/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14296588E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 12:17:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>237</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Humberson</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Friendsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21531</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1038</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.448875</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.677599</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>504</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7498</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 20:14:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CD</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 20:14:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 12:18:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 12:20:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:27</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373478</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Alexander</LastName>
               <FirstName>Danielle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Renee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/14/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.22786225E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 12:20:23</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Alexander</LastName>
               <FirstName>Danielle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Renee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/14/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.22786225E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>A425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 12:20:23</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>237</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Humberson</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Friendsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21531</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1038</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.448875</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.677599</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>521</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9875</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 20:13:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CD</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 20:13:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 12:20:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/27/2023 13:38:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/27/2023 13:38:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/02/2023 12:47:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6241</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 13:38:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:52:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> W-06 is equipped with an in-car camera. Body and in-car cameras were working properly. Body camera footage available.  On March 27th, 2023, myself and other troopers were dispatched to respond to 184 Humberson Road in Friendsville, MD regarding a possible burglary and welfare check of a juvenile.    I arrived on the scene and walked inside the residence. I observed TFC. Kline interviewing the two complainants and I observed TFC. C. Bradley interviewing a juvenile in the kitchen. The juvenile, later identified as Aden, was standing in the kitchen crying and appeared distraught. It was learned that Aden had entered into the complainants house, without permission, looking for some food to eat because he is being fed a very minimum amount at his residence. Aden had written a letter to the complainants expressing the way he is being treated at home and why he is asking for food when his parents are not around. The complainant and her husband expressed their concern to us as well. The complainants husband commented that he is always seeing Aden out in the front yard or around the house during the day standing around no matter what type of weather conditions were outside. The complainants said they have given him food in the past and have always wondered how Adens living conditions were. While speaking with Aden, he was very apologetic and polite to the complainants and law enforcement at the scene. The complainants explained that they did not have interest in perusing any charges and just asked us to assist him in any way we could. Prior to making contact with Adens father, at his residence across the street, Aden began crying again in fear that his father would kill him if he found out police were involved.    Myself and other troopers made contact with the father, identified as Keith Schmidt, at his front porch at 237 Humberson Road. When Keith opened the door, I noticed he unlocked the deadbolt on the door before it was opened. I explained to Keith that there was an anonymous complaint about the well-being of his son Aden and that we needed to speak with Aden. To further alleviate any further conflict with Aden and his father, we did not mention to Keith that his son was at the neighbors residence at this time. Keith said that he should be around the back of the house watching the chicken, but sometimes he wonders away. We asked Keith why Aden would be outside watching a chicken in the backyard, and he replied by saying that he cannot be trusted inside the house because he will eat everything. Therefore, he is locked outside most of the day. Keith was asked if Aden had any type of eating disorder to which he replied he did not. We asked Keith if we could step into the residence to check on the current living conditions in the home. Initially, Keith agreed and that he would just need to secure the dog inside. Moments later, Keith returned to the door stating that he changed his mind, we would not be entering his house and that we were free to leave his property, to which we did.    I responded back to 184 Humberson Road to transport Aden back to the barrack. While traveling back to the barrack with Aden, I had an opportunity to speak with him. Aden explained that his step mother currently works at the health department in Grantsville, MD and his father does not work. When she leaves for work in the morning around, 0730 hours, he is woken up and told to go outside where he spends the day watching their pet chicken in the yard, no matter what kind of weather conditions are present outside. Around the afternoon hours, if his father is awake, he asks for lunch if he gets the courage to and is forced back outside. Around 1730 hours when his mother returns home from work, she unlocks the front door and allows Aden to go inside. While speaking with him, I could tell he hasnt been brushing his teeth. Aden said the upstairs bathroom is under construction with just a toilet, and he was told he is not permitted to use the kitchen sink because he has previously gotten toothpaste on the dishes, even though his parents brushed theirs in the sink. Aden explained that he was taken out of public school in 9th grade and now is being home schooled. Aden is handed DVD recordings that he is able to watch in the evening hours after he has finished his chores but receives very little help from his parents on schooling. Aden also mentioned that if he gets in trouble, a part of his punishment is to sleep outside. He is also not permitted to access the internet or have a cell phone. When I asked Aden what he likes to do for fun, he said there is nothing fun. I also asked Aden if there was anything at his house that makes him happy. Aden replied with just my cat. Aden was very distraught about the incident stating he just doesnt want his parents to be in trouble. He advised that he was very upset about leaving his family but was looking forward to a new beginning and having a new family. After arriving at the barrack, Aden spoke to a member of CPS for an interview.  All events occurred in Garrett County, MD.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6241</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 13:39:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6241</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 07:41:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bittinger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Blair</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0199</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zais</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6241</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/28/2023 07:08:22</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/28/2023 07:08:22</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/02/2023 12:47:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:08:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:52:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>VIDEO/AUDIO: My Maryland State Police Issued body camera was activated during the incident.   On 3/27/2023 at approximately 0858 hours, I, TFC. Bradley was dispatched to 164 Humberson Rd, Friendsville, MD 21531. The complainant was later identified as Andrew Scott Meyers by his Maryland drivers license. Meyers was reporting a 16-year-old boy attempting to break into houses in search of food. I arrived on scene and made contact with Meyers, who told me he caught a 16-year-old boy attempting to break into his parents house at that address. The 16 year-old-boy was later identified as Aden Mathew-Harvey Goldsborough. Meyers told me he caught Goldsborough doing the same thing approximately one week ago at this residence and another neighbors residence, each time Goldsborough was attempting to get food. Meyers did not report the incidents, but only warned Goldsborough to stop what he was doing. Meyers also provided me with a note he received on his doorstep from Goldsborough, asking Meyers for food. That morning, Meyers wife, Tonya Mathis, was inside of the house at that address sleeping. She woke up to the sound of someone inside of the home and found Goldsborough in the kitchen area with food in his hands. Meyers told me they did not want Goldsborough charged for the incident, but they want him to get help that he does not appear to be getting at home. Meyers continued, advising me he consistently sees Goldsborough outside, no matter the weather conditions. Meyers directed me inside of their residence to speak with Goldsborough, but warned me Goldsborough seemed very afraid his parents were going to find out about the incident.  I made contact with Goldsborough, who was crying, shaking, and continuously rubbing his hands together from what appeared to be nervousness and fear. I asked Goldsborough if he needed any medical attention, he advised he did not. As I spoke with Goldsborough, I observed what appeared to be a severe amount of plaque build-up on his teeth, as if he had not brushed his teeth for an extended period. I asked Goldsborough to explain why he is always looking for food and asked about his living conditions. Goldsborough advised me of the following:  Goldsborough lives with his father and his fathers wife, Keith Alexander Schmidt and Danielle Alexander at 237 Humberson Rd, Friendsville, MD 21531. Goldsborough moved there with his father approximately three years ago from Baltimore. While they lived in Baltimore, Schmidt was arrested one time for assaulting Goldsborough. Goldsboroughs father has Huntingtons disease, which affects his emotions and he easily gets mad. Goldsborough is no longer going to school and is being home-schooled. Which, consists of him playing a pre-recorded disc with lessons on them, but he is not monitored by his parents while playing them. Schmidt stays up late at night and sleeps late into the mornings. Schmidt and Alexander do not allow Goldsborough to remain inside the home while they are not present and awake. Goldsborough cannot to freely access food and must remain outside of the residence until they allow him in. He remains outside of the house and watches their one chicken from approximately 0830 until 1730 each day. He does not get breakfast each day and occasionally gets lunch with permission from his parents.    I responded to Goldsboroughs residence with TFC Kline and TFC Zais to make contact with Schmidt. TFC. Zais told Schmidt we were there to check on Goldsboroughs living conditions and asked if Goldsborough was inside. Schmidt told us Goldsborough should be outside because he is not trusted inside of the house or he would steal all of the food inside. Schmidt said when he first got custody of Goldsborough; he was overweight from eating too much. I asked Schmidt if he was still big now and he replied, No hes thin now, hes a little guy now. We asked Schmidt to allow us inside of the residence to observe Goldsboroughs living conditions. Schmidt replied that Goldsborough should be outside if we wanted to talk to him and guided us to the back yard of the residence beside a chicken cage. Schmidt told us that location in the backyard is where he normally stays, near the chicken. Goldsborough is not allowed inside the residence if Schmidt is not there or if he is sleeping. Schmidt ultimately refused to allow us inside of the residence to see what Goldsboroughs living conditions were like. Schmidt said Danielle was working at the Garrett County Health Department and was not home at the time.  I made contact with Ronald Wayne Friend, who resides at 256 Humberson Rd, directly across from Goldsboroughs residence. Friend told me he too sees Goldsborough outside with a chicken often, even during inclement weather. Friend told me that a few days prior, Goldsborough knocked on his door and asked to use his restroom because he was locked out of his house. After using his restroom, Goldsborough returned to the backyard area.   Garrett County Social Services was contacted and TFC. Zais transported Goldsborough to the McHenry barrack to meet with them and M/T. Brick. While at the McHenry barrack, I provided Goldsborough with a toothbrush and toothpaste. I asked him if he brushes his teeth at home, he said he is not allowed because he gets toothpaste on the dishes that are in the sink when he does.  All above events occurred in Garrett County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:40:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7189</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 07:27:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mcgee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2173</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7189</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>16</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:22:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:19</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372777</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Goldsborough</LastName>
               <FirstName>Aden</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Mathew-Harvey</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/22/2006 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 07:22:05</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G432</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A350</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Goldsborough</LastName>
               <FirstName>Aden</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Mathew-Harvey</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/22/2006 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G432</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A350</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 07:22:05</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>237</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Humberson</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Friendsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21531</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1038</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.448875</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.677599</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 14:43:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 14:43:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:25:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372779</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Schmidt</LastName>
               <FirstName>Keith</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alexander</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/29/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 07:24:54</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Schmidt</LastName>
               <FirstName>Keith</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alexander</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/29/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 07:24:54</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>237</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Humberson</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Friendsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21531</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1038</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.448875</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.677599</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>504</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7498</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:25:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 20:17:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:31:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:57</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372780</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Meyers</LastName>
               <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Scott</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/29/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 07:31:25</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A536</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Meyers</LastName>
               <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Scott</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/29/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A536</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 07:31:25</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>365</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Humberson</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Friendsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21531</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.446763</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.677764</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:31:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>R</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:31:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:31:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:34:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372781</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mathis</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tonya</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Renee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/29/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 07:34:11</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mathis</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tonya</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Renee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/29/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 07:34:11</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>365</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Humberson</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Friendsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21531</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.446763</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.677764</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>574</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9747</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>321</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8393</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:36:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:36:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>66</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:38:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:19</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372783</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Friend</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/06/1957 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 07:38:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F653</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R543</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Friend</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/06/1957 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F653</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R543</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 07:38:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>256</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Humberson</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Friendsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21531</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1038</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.448611</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.677137</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>746</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5678</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:38:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 07:38:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/22/2023 21:30:33</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/22/2023 21:30:33</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/02/2023 12:47:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 21:30:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:52:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>     On 3/27/2023, after Aden Goldsborough had been transported to the MSP - McHenry Barrack and later placed into care by the Department of Social Services, an attempt was made to notify the parents of the decision. Two social workers, Amanda Richardson and Jennifer Combs, responded with me to 237 Humberson Road in Friendsville, MD. Upon knocking on the door, both Keith Schmidt and Danielle Alexander quickly walked outside on the front porch and immediately closed the door behind them. Upon introductions being made, Keith and Danielle announced their son had been missing. As Aden had been missing for nearly four hours at this point, it was not clear why neither parent had not reported and/or called about their sons welfare. As the incident was explained to them, they were advised Aden was being placed into foster care by the Garrett County Department of Social Services. The appropriate paperwork was served on both, Keith and Danielle, by the Department of Social Services. As they were advised there would be a separate investigation completed by each agency, they advised they understood the Department of Social Services investigation and my criminal investigation. As I asked if they would want to speak with us about the alleged allegations against them, they advised they did not want to speak to us, particularly me, to explain any portion of Aden being allegedly neglected. I asked if they would cooperate with the investigation and allow us to enter the home to prove, or disprove, the allegations against them. Upon asking, they advised Amanda and Jennifer could enter the home, but not me as a law enforcement officer. At this time, Amanda and Jennifer entered the home with Danielle. Keith and I remained on the front porch with little to no talking. Prior to leaving the home, it was observed the back of the residence housed a chicken coop as described by Aden. Amanda and Jennifer advised they would be able to testify to the conditions of the interior of the home as they observed them and took multiple photographs.       I also received a handwritten letter from TFC Bradley which was recovered by Adens neighbor, Andrew Meyers, at his residence. A copy of this letter was placed in the case file. The letter was asking Andrew for food and was asking for Andrew to deliver the food in a way to not alert Adens parents, or to notify them in any way.       A neighborhood check was completed of the surrounding homes around the victims residence. Upon completing the neighborhood check the following was discovered:        Walt and Cindy Meyers - this residence is located at 167 Humberson Road. This residence is slightly above and within sight of Adens home. This residence is the home which was entered by Aden in an attempt to get food. Walt and Cindy were adamant about not pursing charges against Aden as they believed the situation was greatly concerning for a child to have to enter a home to simply get something to eat. Walt and Cindy expressed it was clear Aden only wanted food and was trying to survive. Cindy mentioned there were valuables lying around, including money, but the only thing Aden was discovered with was a small bag of food. Walt and Cindy explained their daughter-in-law, Tonya, found Aden standing in the kitchen. Walt and Cindy expressed Aden was never an issue with Tonya, and Aden appeared emotionally upset as he remained polite and humble. Walt and Cindy advised Aden has asked them for food in the past, but he has never entered their home until now. Walt and Cindy expressed when Aden would ask for food he would only want small things and tried to pass it off as the food was for his chicken. Walt and Cindy eventually came to believe the food was not for his chicken. Walt and Cindy noticed Aden would be outside his residence all the time, even during inclement weather. Walt and Cindy stated they would often see Aden standing in the rain or being outside all day long with his chicken. Walt and Cindy advised they also heard Aden was told by his parents that the neighbors were pedophiles and instructed Aden to not leave his parents property. Walt and Cindy remained concerned about Adens overall welfare.        Jeffrey and Sandra Thomas - this residence is located at 232 Humberson Road and is directly across the road from Adens residence. Jeffrey advised Aden has tried to make a connection with their family in the past as Aden would attempt to deliver mail and/or packages to their home in an attempt to make contact with them. Jeffrey advised he kept Aden at a distance as he was suspicious of Adens family. Jeffrey advised they began to get concerned as he would often see Aden standing outside for hours, and Aden was always left alone. Jeffrey advised Aden would often be standing or walking around outside, beside a chicken, for a long portion of the day.        Ryan Scott Friend - this residence is located at 284 Humberson Road. Ryan advised he was familiar with Aden as he would often see him standing outside not necessarily doing anything. Ryan advised Aden had lived at the address for about a year. Ryan advised he would see Aden standing outside with a chicken, even during times when it was cold and raining. Ryan explained Aden would often only have a single layer of clothing on with no coat. As I spoke with Ryan, he expressed he likes to walk his dog during the very late to midnight hours. Ryan advised even at the hour of midnight, when Ryan was walking his dog, he would get startled when he would expectantly walk up on Aden who was just standing still in his yard in the dark. Ryan advised Aden was quiet and appeared to have no known reason to be standing there. Ryan believed the situation to be very odd.        Mia Alexander - this residence is located at 369 Humberson Road and is out of sight, but the location would require the homeowner to drive by the victims home if they would leave. Mia advised she was not familiar with Aden as she had just moved in less than a week ago.        Alexander Meyers and Tonya Mathis- this residence is located at 365 Humberson Road. The residence is within sight of the victims residence. Alex and Tonya also use property which is directly beside and across from Adens residence. Tonya advised she was the one who discovered Aden in Walt and Cindys home. Tonya advised she placed her daughter on the bus that morning, and she went back to bed. After a short period of time, Tonya advised she heard someone in the kitchen area, and she was not expecting someone to be there. When she eventually walked out into the kitchen, she saw Aden standing in the pantry holding a small bag of food. Tonya advised Aden did not attempt to do anything other than stand there. The bag Aden was holding was found to contain a can of chicken soup, a snack cake, chips, and a piece of apple pie. Tonya advised, It was like he was trying to make himself a meal. Tonya advised Aden was emotional and did not want his parents to find out about him being in their house. Tonya advised the house is not typically locked and nothing was damaged. As Tonya spoke with Aden she became concerned and felt something was horribly wrong. Tonya advised it was apparent Aden was terrified of his parents. As they went back and forth with Aden on having to do something, Alex advised he gave Aden a choice of them either calling the police or them having to call his parents. Alex stated Aden immediately chose the police. Alex advised this surprised him that a sixteen-year-old would rather call the police than his own parents. This was stated to make the situation even more concerning. Tonya and Andrew advised Aden had asked them for food in the past, and he has asked them to use their bathroom before, because he could not get into his home. It was a growing concern as they grew increasing concerned as to why he could not access food and/or use his own bathroom. When they asked, Aden would simply advise them he would not want to wake up his Dad. Tonya and Andrew advised Aden would often ask for a peanut butter sandwich and then say it was for his chicken. Tonya and Alex also advised they would often see Aden in the yard outside his home, by himself, for most of the day. They explained Adens father was believed to have Huntingtons Disease, and he would always stay in the house. The mother, Danielle, would reportedly leave for work in the morning. When Danielle would return home from work at the end of the day, Aden would walk to the front porch, from somewhere in the yard, and Danielle and Aden would walk in the house. Andrew and Tonya advised Aden would not be allowed in the house because Aden explained to them, he would wake up his Dad, so he was forced to stay outside every day and guard his chicken. Alexander and Tonya also advised the day Aden was found in Walt and Cindys home multiple law enforcement units responded. As Andrew and Tonya became aware of the situation, they noticed after the police left, Keith and Danielle came outside and ran around the outside of their home and cleaned things up for over twenty minutes. Tonya and Alex advised it was apparent Keith and Danielle were concerned about who may return and see what was left behind at their home. Alexander and Tonya also expressed Keith had been racing up and down the road in his vehicle directly after the incident occurred as he appeared very angry after DSS had responded to his address.        Sarah Meyers - this residence is located at 391 Humberson Road. Sarah advised she observed Aden standing outside in the mornings about 20-30 minutes before the bus would come by in the mornings. Sarah advised he was not in school, and she did not understand why he was outside. Sarah advised Aden was always with a chicken, and he was always alone. Sarah believed Aden lived at his residence for about a year. Sarah advised her in laws (Walt and Cindy) do not lock their home and Aden was just looking for some food. Sarah reported since Aden had been removed from his residence, her son has noticed Aden in school. Aden was stated to have been improving as her son knew Aden and reported him to now be happy and smiling.        Jack Thomas - this residence is located at 398 Humberson Road. Jack expressed he has seen Aden outside, but simply stated, I keep to himself. Jack did not want to be involved.        The results of the medical evaluation were also made available. A copy of this report was placed in the case file. The medical evaluation included a complete narrative section by Dr. Sisler. The generalized items reported included, but was not limited to, the following:        Patient - Aden Goldsborough       Height - 67.55 inches (34th percentile)       Weight - 112 pounds (9th percentile)       BMI- 17.4 (5th percentile)       General appearance - thin in appearance, he is quiet and reserved in demeanor, he has poor hygiene with dirt discoloring his neck, teeth have prominent plaque buildup present with poor dental hygiene, significantly dry skin over entirety of trunk and extremities, hair is sparse and absent in some locations, and he has minor abrasions.       Problems- consist of moderate protein calorie malnutrition, calorie malnutrition, abnormal vision, and a victim of child neglect.        The foster parent reported Aden was found wearing multiple layers of clothing (sweatpants) under his pants. Aden reported he was concerned it would be cold if he was left outside.         A consultation will be made with the Garrett County States Attorneys Office to pursue criminal charges against both parents.         All events did occur in Garrett County, MD.         Case remains open.                       </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 21:32:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4756</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/30/2023 12:12:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mcgee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2173</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Delmas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4756</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/18/2023 18:57:31</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/18/2023 18:57:31</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/02/2023 12:47:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/18/2023 18:57:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:52:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #4 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>   Upon presenting this case to the Garrett County States Attorneys Office, it was determined criminal charges would be pursued against Keith Schmidt and Danielle Alexander. The investigation showed Keith Schmidt and Danielle Alexander were the only other individuals residing in the same residence as the victim, Aden Goldsborough. Keith Schmidt and Danielle Alexander were found to be Adens family members / parents. According to the findings in the investigation, Keith Schmidt and Danielle Alexander failed to give the proper care and attention to Aden Goldsborough(16). This failure to provide the proper care and attention resulted in the harming and/or decline of Adens health and welfare. The investigation found Aden Goldsborough was placed in harm, or placed in a substantial risk of harm, while being under the care of Keith Schmidt and Danielle Alexander. The investigation found, Aden was left outside for extended periods of time during inclement weather, he was left without basic needs such as food and bathroom facilities, educational options were lacking, and he was not provided the proper medical care and/or was receiving the proper preventative medical maintenance to sustain his overall health and welfare.Prior to being placed into care by the Department of Human Services, Aden Goldsborough weighed 112 pounds at sixteen years of age. This weight medically falls within the 9% tile for Adens age and gender. Adens body mass index was measured to be 17.4, which showed to be in the 5% tile for his age and gender. These conditions were medically confirmed by Dr. Sisler, upon her medical evaluation, as additional issues of hygiene, malnutrition, and multiple concerns of neglect were further observed.     The Department of Human Services Child Protective Workers, Amanda Richardson and Jennifer Combs, will be available to testify to the conditions of the interior of the residence where Aden Goldsborough resided. Images were taken from inside the home by the social workers. These images were uploaded into Veripic and placed in the case file.The Department of Human Services continues to maintain custody of Aden Goldsborough. The Child Protective Service Worker, Amanda Richardson, has made an Indicated finding against Keith Schmidt and Danielle Alexander for Child Neglect.     An Application for Statement of Charges was filed with the Garrett County Commissioners Office on 5/23/2023. Keith Schmidt and Danielle Alexander were each charged with Neglect of a Minor and Contributing to the Circumstances of a Child. A warrant was requested. Upon finding probable cause, a criminal summons was issued for Keith Schmidt and Danielle Alexander.     On 5/24/2023, I responded to 237 Humberson Road, in Friendsville, MD. Upon making contact with Keith Schmidt and Danielle Alexander, I explained I had in my possession two criminal summonses issued by the Garrett County Commissioner. Upon explaining the process to both of them, the criminal summonses were signed and served without incident. Keith and Danielle continued to not want to speak about the case and elected to remain silent.     On 5/30/2023, the family court proceeding was completed. Upon completion of the family court case, the child, Aden Goldsborough, was ruled to be a child in need of assistance. Aden Goldsborough remains in the custody of the State.     All events did occur in Garrett County, MD.     Case closed on arrest(s).        </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/18/2023 18:58:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4756</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/30/2023 21:34:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mcgee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2173</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Delmas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4756</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500348</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0173</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>4</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/24/2023 20:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0173</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 20:08:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4756</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 20:08:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500348</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1614</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>4</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/24/2023 20:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1614</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 20:08:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4756</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 20:08:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500348</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0844</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>4</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/24/2023 20:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0844</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 20:08:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4756</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 20:08:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 12:54:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377924</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Richardson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Amanda</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leigh</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/17/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 12:54:12</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R263</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A553</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Richardson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Amanda</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leigh</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/17/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R263</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A553</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 12:54:12</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12578</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Garrett</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Oakland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21550</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.398949</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.419907</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>533</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3000</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 12:54:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 12:58:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:52</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377925</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Combs</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jennifer</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 12:57:50</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C512</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J516</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Combs</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jennifer</FirstName>
               <SLastName>C512</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J516</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 12:57:50</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12578</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Garrett</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Oakland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21550</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.398949</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.419907</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>533</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3000</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4756</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 12:58:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>