<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002214</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/19/2023 02:03:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/19/2023 02:03:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/19/2023 01:45:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/19/2023 01:45:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop. Driver was arrested for DWI by Controlled Dangerous Substance.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 02:03:59</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0104</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/03/2023 09:44:44</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>680987</AddressId>
      <City>MDC574</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 02:04:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2023 05:19:47</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>680987</AddressId>
         <StreetName>N/B Rt 301 S/O Pembrooke Sq</StreetName>
         <City>Waldorf</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20602</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.876841</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.615879</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/19/2023 02:03:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/19/2023 02:03:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/02/2023 19:51:10</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 02:03:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:19</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Traffic stop. In-Car Camera Operational, H-26. This incident was recorded on TFC Thomas Body-Worn Camera.  Driver:  Antoine Charles Hursey, B/M, DOB: 07/15/1992   Maryland SDX:  MD-10272696972   Address:  6915 Coldstream Ct, Bryans Road, MD 20616  Vehicle: MD 3Z8893 - 1998 Mercury Grand Marquis  Location: N/B Route 301 S/O Pembrooke Square.  Training and Certificates:   Trained and certified in administering the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Safety Administration.   Completed LIDAR and RADAR training through the Maryland State Police.  Completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E) training in June 2019.   Completed Crisis Intervention Training in September 2020.  Distinguished Graduate of the Maryland Highway Safety Office and University of Maryland DUI Institute in July 2022.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Recipient of the Maryland Highway Safety Office DUI Award for Consecutive Years (2020 and 2021)  PHASE 1  VEHICLE IN MOTION Narrative:  On 01/19/2023, at approximately 0145 hours, I, TFC Thomas #7065 of the Maryland State Police was on routine patrol in the area of northbound Route 301, south of Pembrooke Square in Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland. At that time, I observed a gray Mercury Grand Marquis bearing Maryland Historic Registration 3Z8893 traveling in front of my vehicle in lane #2. I observed the Mercurys passenger-side front and rear tires travel halfway into lane #3 on three separate times. I positioned my vehicle behind the Mercury, activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop.  PHASE 2  PERSONAL CONTACT  I made contact with the driver and asked him for his license and registration. The driver exhibited slow, slurred speech and appeared disoriented. I asked the driver if he consumed any alcoholic beverages that night and the driver responded by saying, No. The driver was identified through his Maryland Drivers License as Antoine Charles Hursey (AA/M, DOB: 07/15/1992). The driver continued to show signs of disorientation and lethargy due to impairment. I then looked at the passenger inside the vehicle and she appeared to be impaired as well.  PHASE 3  PRE-ARREST SCREENING  I asked Hursey if he would conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests and he responded by saying, Yes. I asked Hursey if he suffered from High Blood Pressure and he responded by saying, No. I further asked Hursey if he ever had any head trauma, brain tumors or concussions and he responded by saying, No. I asked Hursey if he took any intoxicating substances or medications for any injuries and he responded by saying, No. I asked Hursey if he suffered from any medical issues that would prevent him from completing the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests and he responded by saying, No. I observed Hursey having difficulties maintaining his balance.   The three tests administered to Hursey were the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus, Walk and Turn and the One-Leg Stand tests. Hursey conducted the tests in comfortable shoes and clothing. All tests were performed on a level surface, free of debris and in a well-lit area.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)   The first test conducted was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held 12-15 inches fromHurseys eyes. Hursey was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping hishead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hiseyes until told to stop. Hurseys pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking and extremely constricted. Hursey advised he understood the instructions. On several occasions, I observed Hursey not looking at the pen several times and moving his head from side to side and I had to repeat the instructions for him to watch the pen with his eyes only.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in Both Eyes.  2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in Both Eyes.  3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in Both Eyes. Vertical Nystagmus  Not Present.  WALK AND TURN (8/8 clues observed)  Prior to Hursey performing the test, Iproperly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Hursey was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel-to-toe. Hursey was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in that position until told to begin. Hursey was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel-to-toe on every step. Hursey was instructed to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, it was explained and demonstrated to Hursey to keep his left foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps with his right foot to turn completely around. Again, it was explained and demonstrated to Hursey during the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Hursey was instructed that once he began the test, he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. Hursey advised he understood the instructions.  Instructional Stage: 1.) Attempted to Begin Test Too Early. 2.) Could Not Maintain his Balance. Walking Stage (1st Nine): 1.) Missed heel-to-toe on steps 1, 3 7, 9 and 10. 2.) Stepped off-line between steps 10 and 11. 3.) Raised arms more than 6 inches from his side to maintain balance. 4.) Incorrect number of steps. Hursey took 12 steps. 5.) Stopped walking during test.  Improper turn: Hursey did not complete a series of small steps as directed per the instructions and stumbled on the turn.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): 1.) Missed heel-to-toe on steps 1, 3 5, 6 and 10. 2.) Stepped off-line between steps 10 and 11. 3.) Raised arms more than 6 inches from his side to maintain balance. 4.) Incorrect number of steps. Hursey took 14 steps. 5.) Stopped walking during test.  ONE LEG STAND (Could Not Complete Due to Impairment)  Prior to Hursey performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Hursey was instructed to stand with his heels together and his hands down by his sides while the instructions were given, and during the test. When instructed to start, Hursey was instructed to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, Hursey was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop.Hursey advised he understood the instructions. Instructional Stage: Failed to Maintained Balance. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: Due to his impairment, Hursey began to take steps and began walking and did not raise his foot. I asked Hursey if that was the instructions given and Hursey responded by saying, Yes. I advised Hursey that I did not give him instructions to take steps forward during the One-Leg Stand test.  LACK OF CONVERGEANCE: (Did Not Observe)  The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held 12-15 inches fromHurseys eyes. Hursey was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping hishead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hiseyes until told to stop. I advised Hursey that I would move then pen in a circular motion and Hursey was to follow the pen. I also explained that I would come close to Hurseys face but would not make contact or touch him. I again observed Hursey with constricted pupils. Hursey advised he understood the instructions. I had to advise Hursey several times to follow the pen. 1.) Hurseys eyes did not converge   I offered Hursey a Preliminary Breath Test (PBT), to which he agreed with a .00 BrAC. I could smell a chemical type smell resembling Phenylcyclohexylpiperidine (PCP) emitting from Hurseys breath as he provided a breath sample into the PBT. Based on my training, knowledge and experience as a Maryland State Trooper and in making DUI and DWI arrests, his slow depressed reflexes, constricted pupils and his disoriented, confused and lethargic demeanor, I believed Hursey was too impaired to operate a motor vehicle. I placed Hursey under arrest for driving while impaired by a Controlled Dangerous Substance at 0203 hours. I believed Hursey did not know his whereabouts and exhibited extreme disorientation.   Hursey was transported to the Maryland State Police La Plata Barrack for processing.    While in the Barrack, Hursey was advised of his DR-15, Advice of Rights on 01/19/2023 at 0223 hours. Hursey was explained the form, and asked if he had any questions. Hursey responded by saying, No. At 0230 hours, Hursey signed the DR-15, Advise of Rights Form and agreed to submit to an Intoximeter test with a result of .00 BrAC. Hursey was advised of his Fifth Amendment (Miranda Rights) via MSP 180. Hursey waived his right to counsel and agreed to be questioned by a Drug Recognition Expert (DRE). At 0445 hours, the Maryland State Police HQ Duty Officer advised that a DRE could not be located in a timely manner.   Hursey was processed for Driving While Impaired by a Controlled Dangerous Substance and Driving Vehicle While Impaired by Drugs that Cannot Drive Safely. Hursey was released to a sober driver at the Barrack.  Charges:    TA 21-902(d1i)  Driving While Impaired by A Controlled Dangerous Substance   TA 21-902(c1i)  Driving Veh While So Far Impaired by Drugs Cannot Drive Safely  TA 21-901.1(b)  Negligent Driving  TA 21-901.1(a)  Reckless Driving  TA 21-201(a1)  Driver Failure to Obey Properly Placed Traffic Control Device Instr.  All events occurred in Charles County, MD.  Cleared by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 06:32:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7065</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/28/2023 15:43:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burroughs</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5968</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thomas II</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7065</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Walker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quintina</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4988</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thomas II</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7065</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thomas II</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7065</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491597</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/19/2023 02:03:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 04:51:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7065</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/19/2023 04:54:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491597</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/19/2023 02:03:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 04:51:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7065</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/19/2023 04:55:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>30</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 04:51:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:40</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366541</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hursey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Antoine</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/15/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/19/2023 03:26:47</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hursey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Antoine</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/15/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/19/2023 03:26:47</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>821</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3404</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 04:56:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:40</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 04:56:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:40</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 04:56:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:40</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 04:56:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:40</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 04:52:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7065</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/19/2023 04:52:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148814</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 04:51:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7065</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/19/2023 04:51:30</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2MEFM75W1WX604167</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>1998</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MERC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>GMQ</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3Z8893</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>12</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>