<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-003814</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/30/2023 16:00:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/30/2023 16:00:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/30/2023 15:29:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/30/2023 15:29:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Responded to the Salisbury Barrack for a complaint of a past Domestic Assault.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 16:00:18</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5274</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/24/2023 09:05:48</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>682381</AddressId>
      <City>MDC226</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 16:00:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/17/2023 14:40:57</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>682381</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2307</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Pine</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Salisbury</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.572622</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.39038</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/30/2023 16:00:15</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/30/2023 16:00:15</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 09:05:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 16:00:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Incident Type:2nd-degree Domestic assault  Suspect: Devin Christian James 05-31-2001 # (443)-523-0264  Victim: Alyssa Nicole Rivera-Gerben 12-09-2000 # (443)-397-5509  Attachments: Photos of injuries Messages from suspect  Scene Processing:Recovered photos of injuries from Gerben. Uploaded to Vera-Pic.  Neighborhood check: N/A for this incident.  Body Cam: https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=2cf0764c284e4596807fc508ae83511epartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=8c43c56e0825453a8c7535435f8df97dpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=bee8c785600a46fca50a78ca3043931fpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1   Narrative:    On 01-30-2023 I, TFC. Norfolk 7120 responded to the Salisbury State Police Barrack lobby for a complaint of assault that have occurred in the past.    I arrived at the scene and met with the victim/complainant identified as Alyssa Nicole Rivera-Gerben 12-09-2000. Gerben explained to me multiple incidents that occurred with her ex-boyfriend identified as Devin Christian James 05-31-2001. Gerben was advised that the conversation was being recorded by my body camera, and Gerben acknowledged the body camera. Gerben advised me of three specific incidents that she believed needed to be documented. I am listing these events by the date in which they happened.  December 1st, 2021- Gerben and James were in his vehicle in the area of Rt. 13 business by the Volkswagen dealership when an argument ensued. Gerben stated that James undid her seat belt after hitting her multiple times and drug her into the drivers seat into his lap. Gerben was able to see the speedometer of the vehicle, and it said approximately 80mph in a posted 45 mph. James then said that he would wreck his vehicle and kill them both before striking another vehicle causing an accident that was handled by MSP Salisbury barrack. Gerben advised that the Troopers on the scene asked her if she was okay and if anything, else happened. Gerben told them no nothing else had happened due to the question being asked directly in the presence of James. Gerben was afraid to say anything for repercussions that may come from James.Gerben did not receive medical attention for the accident.  January 23rd, 2022- Gerben stated that she and James got into an argument about Gerben wanting to break up with James due to his actions involving the accident. Gerben said that after she told James this he took her car keys and would not allow her to leave the bedroom they were inside during the incident. Gerben stated that she tried to leave the room and that he was actively blocking the only exit. James then grabbed Gerben and threw her onto a bed and put a pillow on her face pressing down with his hands in an attempt to suffocate Gerben. Gerben advised that she was under the pillow for approximately 1 minute before she lost consciousness and stopped fighting back. Once Gerben stopped moving James removed the pillow from Gerbens face and attempted to revive her. Gerben said that James was scared that he may have killed her.Gerben has sent me time-stamped photos of the bruising caused by this incident along with screenshots of the conversation between her and James about this incident after the fact. In the messages, James states Honey I just wanted u to calm down. Gerben did not receive medical help for this incident.  February 2nd, 2022-Gerben stated that she went over to James house due to him being emotionally distraught from a court case that he just had for a separate incident. Gerben said that James was trying to revive the relationship and Gerben denied him saying that she did not want to date him anymore. Gerben stated that James just started yelling and threw her on the floor before he started strangling her with both of his hands until she lost consciousness. Gerben has photos of this incident time-stamped for the day the assault occurred along with ones from a couple of days later. Gerben said that after this incident she did not go to the hospital. Gerben said that she had an extremely difficult time swallowing food or talking for a couple of months after the incident due to the trauma inflicted. Gerben also sent me photos of bruising and cigarette burns on her skin from more incidents that involved James.   Gerben advised that the reason she waited so long to report these incidents was that she did not want to relive these events until James new girlfriend reached out to her about assaults she has endured. Gerben said they got lunch to discuss how James is assaulting the new girlfriend also. Gerben advised that this person does not want to talk to the police about the following incident. Gerben advised she was told by the new girlfriend that James took her keys during an argument so that she couldnt leave the house. The new girlfriend tried to run out of the house into the garage to escape James before James picked up some kind of blunt object and beat the new girlfriend until she had blood running out of her mouth and she lost consciousness. Gerben was advised that the police were never called for this incident, but James uncle intervened in some way after the assault occurred.   Gerben said to me that she was worried more for the safety of future girlfriends James may have. Gerben is afraid that James actions toward women are becoming progressively more violent. Gerben is ultimately afraid that James may end up killing someone if no intervention occurs.  On 02-17-2023 at 1440 Hours I, TFC. Norfolk 7120 contacted Gerben via the telephone in reference to this case. I asked if she still wanted to pursue charges. Gerben advised that she did. I will be contacting Gerben on my next shift to set up another meeting with her in person, so I can gather more information.  All events occurred in Wicomico County MD  I request this case be left open pendingfurther review and an attempt to pursue charges within statute limitations. Case Open        </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7120</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 16:17:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7120</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/17/2023 14:52:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bruce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6083</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norfolk</LastName>
            <FirstName>Wyatt</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7120</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7120</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 16:12:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>328132</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>James</LastName>
               <FirstName>Devin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christian</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/31/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/03/2021 13:43:41</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>James</LastName>
               <FirstName>Devin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christian</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/31/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/03/2021 13:43:41</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2307</StreetNumber>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21804</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3341</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.5724958</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.3908231</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>523</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0264</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/03/2021 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 13:09:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7120</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 16:12:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:41</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7120</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 16:15:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:54</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>367631</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Rivera Gerben</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alyssa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/09/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/30/2023 16:15:12</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R162</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A420</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Rivera Gerben</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alyssa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/09/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R162</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A420</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/30/2023 16:15:12</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>204</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Bridge</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Mardela Springs</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21837</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.758842</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.459127</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>397</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5509</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7120</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 16:15:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:40</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/22/2023 12:00:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/22/2023 12:00:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 09:05:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/22/2023 12:00:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>CED Initial/ Interview - Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: CED Initial/ Interview - Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben  Attachments: ACRS Report 21-MSP-048999 Maryland State Police Form 78 Consent to Search and Seize  Victim: Name: Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben DOB 12/09/2000 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 204 Bridge Street, Mardela Springs, Wicomico County, Maryland 21873 Phone: 443-397-5509  Suspect: Name: Devin Christian James DOB 05/31/2001 Race: White / Sex: Male Address: 2307 Pine Way, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-523-0264  Evidence: 1) One (1) Compact Disc containing a recorded interview of Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben, stored in agency case file. 2) Twenty nine (29) photographs/ screenshot photos of Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerbens injuries, uploaded to VeriPic 3) One (1) Compact Disc containing eighteen (18) video files provided by Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben, stored in agency case file  Narrative: On March 7, 2023, at approximately 0915 hours, I, Corporal Nicholas R. Hager, #6001 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region conducted an interview with Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben [hereinafter referred to as Alyssa]. The interview was conducted at the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack and was recorded. During the interview Alyssa described four (4) incidents which occurred between her and Devin Christian James [hereinafter referred to as Devin]. Below is a synopsis of the interview and not a transcript therefore some paraphrasing may be used:   September 2021     Alyssa described an incident in which Devin grabbed her by her ponytail and pulled her to the ground   Alyssa was confused by this incident   Alyssa said Devin then pinned her down   Alyssa said Devin has Borderline Personality Disorder          December 1, 2021     Alyssa identified Devin as her boyfriend at the time and said they lived together   Alyssa said she and Devin lived at 2703 Pine Way, Salisbury, Maryland 21801 from September 2021 to December 1, 2021, when she moved out   Alyssa went through Devins phone the night before and was upset by what she found and Devin was cheating on her   Alyssa andDevin were traveling N/B on US RT 13 in the area of Gordy Road [Volkswagen Dealership]   Alyssa and Devin began arguing about her wanting to go home   Alyssa said Devin grabbed her by her hair and begantraveling 80 MPH in what Alyssa described as a 45 MPH zone   Alyssa said Devin then made the statement I am going to crash this car and kill us both   Alyssa described Devin pulling her toward the drivers seat on top of him   Alyssa said Devin then struck a white SUV   After the crash Devin exited the vehicle and began yelling at the driver of the white SUV   Alyssa exited the vehicle and attempted to grab Devin to get him to calm down at which time he pushed Alyssa into the vehicle   Alyssa said she felt like she almost lost her life   [This crash was investigated by the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack 21-MSP-0048999]         Unknown date betweenDecember 2021 and January 2022     Devin gave Alyssa a ride home to 204 Bridge Street, Mardela Springs, Wicomico County, Marylandat which time she attempted to break up with him   Devin puts car in reverse and speeds away from her house while she was still inside the vehicle   Alyssa said her fight or flight kicked in, and she jumped out of the moving vehicle   Alyssa has photographs of the injuries from jumping out of the vehicle which were taken on January 23, 2022          Approximately January 23, 2022     Alyssa said at this time Devin was living in an RV next to a house he was building   Alyssa was attempting to leave because Devin was getting overwhelmed   Alyssa attempted to get her keys to leave and Devin took the keys and would notlet her leave   Alyssa said Devin grabbed a pillow and began to suffocate her   Devin also told Alyssa I have the power to kill you right now   Alyssa said that she could not breathe   Alyssa began to scream for help   Alyssa said she lost consciousness   Alyssa ran to Devins uncle Brian at which time Devin gave her the keys and allowed her to leave   Alyssa said she though Devin was going to kill her   Alyssa said before this incident Devin was choking and slapping her   Alyssa later saidshe was unable to swallow the same after   Alyssa said she went home and took photographs of her injuries          February 2, 2022     Devin was concerned about an upcoming court date and asked Alyssa to spend time with him   Alyssa went to Devins house / RV   Devin is instantly upset about Alyssas mother   Alyssa could tell Devin was getting mad and asked him to give her glasses to her, so she could leave   Devin begins punching his own leg repeatedly   Devin throws Alyssas glasses across the RV   Alyssa told Devin if he broke her glasses she was going to fuck you up   Devin then grabs Alyssa by the hair and drags her to the middle of the RV and threw her on the floor   Alyssa said Devin then got on top of her and squeezed her hands so hard that she had bruises   Alyssa said after this incident she was unable to write at school due to the injuries to her hands   Alyssa said Devin grabbed her head and slammed it onto the floor of the RV three (3) times   Alyssa said she started to loseconsciousness   Alyssa said Devin spit in her face and slapped her repeatedly   Alyssa said Devin continued to assault her choking her leaving her no airway to breathe   Alyssa said she again lostconsciousness   Alyssa told Devin that she did not want to be with him anymore and that is what set him off   Alyssa said that she thought she was going to die   Devin made many threats to kill Alyssa and her family   Alyssa has not had contact with Devin since this incident   Alyssa thensaid she reached out to Devin in September but has since blocked him          Alyssa has spoken to Mallory who is a therapistat Chesapeake Mental Health in Salisburyabout the above incidents   I spoke with Alyssa about the option of conducting a monitored phone call in reference to this case. Alyssa said that she would consider this option. I also spoke with Alyssa about the contents of her cell phone where she has photographs and evidence stored. Alyssa provided me with consent to review the contents of her cell phone. I completed a Maryland State Police Form 78 Consent to search and seize which Alyssa signed. Alyssa had photographs, screenshot images and videos of injuries stored in a file on her cell phone which she allowed me to transfer to my Maryland State Police issued cell phone.  During the interview Alyssa brought her personal journal which she allowed me to view a limited portion of. Alyssa also allowed me to make a photocopy of three (3) pages of her journal which will be documented in a further supplement.  Case open, investigation continuing.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/22/2023 12:01:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/12/2023 07:04:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493197</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0910</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/30/2023 15:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 0910</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 10:03:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/23/2023 10:03:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/23/2023 10:15:29</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/23/2023 10:15:29</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 09:05:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 10:15:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Journal Entries by Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: Journal Entries by Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben  Attachments: Three (3) photocopies of journal entries provided by Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben  Victim: Name: Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben DOB 12/09/2000 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 204 Bridge Street, Mardela Springs, Wicomico County, Maryland 21873 Phone: 443-397-5509  Suspect: Name: Devin Christian James DOB 05/31/2001 Race: White / Sex: Male Address: 2307 Pine Way, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-523-0264  Evidence: Three (3) photocopies of journal entries provided by Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben, stored in agency case file.  Narrative: On March 7, 2023, I, Corporal Nicholas R. Hager, #6001 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region obtained three photocopies of Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben [hereinafter referred to as Alyssa]s journal. The journal entries are as follows:   4/1/21  Ive been through alor. since Jan 31 I wanna write it down Ig so I can forget it but still have it documented somewhere. February 2nd I told Devin I didnt want him in my life anymore, that I hate him. He went crazy slamming me to the ground, dragging me by my hair off the bed, slamming my head in the ground x3, spit in my face, made fun of my dad, he slapped me repeadtly to where I lost consciousness  giving me a black eye. He choked me leaving no airway access for what felt like forever, but it was probably 60 seconds. I lost consciousness again. each time I regained consciousness he would be in my face screaming. Saying the meanest things. I made him think I changedmy mind, I told him I lovedhim,  that I needed something from my car. I got out. I escaped. Finally. I havent talked to him since. I realize now he never loved me. Ive come to terms with it. Its been so hard. Why did I let myself go through all of it? If he wanted Kaitlyn so bad why go for me? I am so strong, Ive been healing everyday. Working more hours, doing good in school, making new friends, I am 126 pounds now. I go to the gym 4/5x a week  I love it, its become my hobby      Saturday: July 3rd Okayy I got alot to catch up on. Ive had strep the past couple days which sucks but Im recovering. I met a boy that I actually like so that worrying lol.  Monday: December 6th Bitch... 5 months with that boy. July  august were so much fun. Him  I smoked weed, fucked, made cole, tripped on acid, sh rooms, you name it. We were in love. Rabbits in love. He became my best friend, my safe place, my everything. The abuse didnt start until late september. He didnt want me to go home on sophias 16th birthday.  I stayed. He said he was going to kill himself. He wanted me to stay the night everyday. first it was 2 nights, then 4, then eventually I was moving everything in. He made me cut off contact with my mom, Lizzie, sokyra, Alyssa even at times my sister. He started falling into more of a depressive  angrier states      He began to scream /yell at me sometimes in my face. Once I started acting like I was going to leave he has pinned me down, chocked me, slapped me, spit in my face 3 times. Insulted me, my sister  my deceased father. Which I am numb about now. He hated my music, my favorite movies, my tattoos, my family, my cats, I could never have an opinion. He talked about his ex all the time, compared me to her alot or how I was so much better. It all sorta makes sense now knowing she was in the same situation as me. After it all Why did I stay, let it happen? over  over. We were always arguing or fucking or smoking. Even after all of it I still want him. Why I want him in my life. He doesnt deserve it I know. Im stupid. How can you love someone, so deeply, madly even when they put you through so much shit. Made you feel so worthless. like nothing special, like everyone else. I keep saying its that dick. He could always make me cum,  always made sure I did,  first. He would build me up, love bomb me, give me gifts,   Case open, investigation continuing. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 10:16:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/23/2023 10:47:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/23/2023 10:50:05</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/23/2023 10:50:05</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 09:05:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 10:50:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Chesapeake Health Care Subpoena</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: Chesapeake Health Care Subpoena  Attachments: Chesapeake Health Care Subpoena  Victim: Name: Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben DOB 12/09/2000 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 204 Bridge Street, Mardela Springs, Wicomico County, Maryland 21873 Phone: 443-397-5509  Suspect: Name: Devin Christian James DOB 05/31/2001 Race: White / Sex: Male Address: 2307 Pine Way, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-523-0264  Narrative: While conducting the interview with Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben [hereinafter referred to as Alyssa] on March 7, 2023, I, Corporal Nicholas R. Hager, #6001 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region learned that Alyssa disclosed some or part of the incidents to a Mental Health provider from named Mallory from Chesapeake Health Care. On March 22, 2023, I made contact with Chesapeake Health Care Records Department, Cornita Price [hereinafter referred to as Price] in an attempt to gain more details and specific dates of the incidents in which Alyssa provided me during the interview. Price informed me that Alyssa received treatment from Therapist Mallory Lloyd and Psychiatrist Deborah Anderson. Price informed me that she is unable to provide me with therapist notes due to federal laws however could release Psychiatrist treatment information. I completed a subpoena for the following information which was reviewed and signed by the Wicomico County States Attorneys Office:   Mental Health records, medical records, documents, reports, letters, correspondence and materials in your possession, control, safe keeping or to which you have access to involving the examining and/or treatment of Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben DOB 12/09/2000 by Deborah Anderson and Mallory Lloyd from the following time frame:  November 20, 2021 to March 1, 2022  The above subpoena was served on Chesapeake Health Care / Cornita Price at 12145 Elm Street, Princess Anne, Somerset County, Maryland 21853 on March 22, 2023, at 14:23 hours [2:23 p.m.]   Case open, investigation continuing.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 10:51:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/23/2023 11:01:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/05/2023 11:37:33</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/05/2023 11:37:33</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 09:05:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/05/2023 11:37:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Additional Victim Information</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: Additional Victim Information  Victim: Name: Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben DOB 12/09/2000 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 204 Bridge Street, Mardela Springs, Wicomico County, Maryland 21873 Phone: 443-397-5509  Suspect: Name: Devin Christian James DOB 05/31/2001 Race: White / Sex: Male Address: 2307 Pine Way, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-523-0264  Narrative: On April 19, 2023, I, Corporal Nicholas R. Hager, #6001 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region was contacted by Alyssa Nichole Rivera Gerben [hereinafter referred to as Gerben]. Gerben informed me that she had been in contact with a friend who had also been assaulted by Devin Christian James and her friend was willing to speak to me about the investigation. Gerben provided me with he following information in reference to her friend:  Name: Caitlyn Goodwin Phone: 443-366-1109  I contacted Caitlyn Goodwin by telephone who agreed to speak to me about the investigation on April 24, 2023.  Case open, investigation continuing.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/05/2023 11:43:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/05/2023 11:47:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>5</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/05/2023 11:48:06</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/05/2023 11:48:06</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 09:05:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/05/2023 11:48:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Interview - Caitlyn Nichole Goodwin</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: Interview - Caitlyn Nichole Goodwin  Attachments: Maryland State Police Form 78 Consent to Search and Seize Twenty-two (22) screenshot photographs  Victim 1: Name: Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben DOB 12/09/2000 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 204 Bridge Street, Mardela Springs, Wicomico County, Maryland 21873 Phone: 443-397-5509  Victim 2: Name: Caitlyn Nichole Goodwin DOB: 01/03/2001 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 7580 Fentral Avenue, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-366-1109  Suspect: Name: Devin Christian James DOB 05/31/2001 Race: White / Sex: Male Address: 2307 Pine Way, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-523-0264  Evidence: One (1) Compact Disc containing recorded interview of Caitlyn Nichole Goodwin, stored in agency case file Twenty-Two (22) screenshot photographs, attached to this report  Narrative: On April, 24, 2023, at approximately 1029 hours [10:29 a.m.] I, Corporal Nicholas R. Hager, #6001 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region conducted an interview with Caitlyn Nichole Goodwin [hereinafter referred to as Goodwin]. The interview was conducted in the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack interview room and was recorded. Below is a synopsis of the interview and not a transcript therefore some paraphrasing may be used:   Goodwin and Devin Christian James [hereinafter referred to as James] dated for approximately three (3) years  Goodwin and James dated before and after Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben [hereinafter referred to as Gerben]  Goodwin said she and James dated from approximately January 19, 2019, to June 2021 and January 2022 to September 11, 2022  Goodwin has not had communication with James since November 4, 2022  Goodwin and James resided together in a motor home and with James aunt and uncle at 2308 Pine Way, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland  Goodwin described an incident which she said was the most recent andoccurred approximately August 15-16 of 2022 which was when Goodwin said that she realized that James might kill her. Goodwin said she and James had gotten a cat and James became angry that the cat was meowing. James became angry with Goodwins tone of voice. Goodwin said James then got on top of her when she was on the bed and put his hands around her neck attempting to choke her out. Goodwin said she almost passed out from James choking her however he let go just prior to her passing out. Goodwin said James then began to punch her legs as hard as he could while she was pinned down by her neck. Goodwin was attempting to exit the residence at which time James began smacking her across the face to the point that she had blood in her mouth. Goodwin said that she began to vomit and was spitting blood. Goodwin said while she was trying to exit the residence she attempted to get to the garage where she could lock herself in. Goodwin then attempted to call James uncle to get help at which time James kicked the door in the garage, took Goodwins phone and threw it across the garage. Goodwin said James then picked up an unknown pole and began striking her over the back with the pole. Goodwin said she thought that James had broken her back. Goodwin said she was in so much pain that she was unable to sit down.Goodwin said when James was choking her she accepted the fact that if she was going to diethat washow she was going to die  Goodwin said she was always in fear for her life  Goodwin described another incident which occurred approximately between February and April 2022 in which James held her hostage inside the motor home with a knife. Goodwin said she and James had gotten into an argument about Gerben. Goodwin said she was attempting to exit the motor home however James continued to throw her on the bed. Goodwin said that James pulled out a pocket knife, opened it up, held the knife up to her stomach, attempted to hold the knife up to her neck and said I could just kill you right now and kill myself.  Goodwin said that during the time she and James were together James had a Xanax problem  Goodwin said James also has made threats to kill her family  During the interview, Goodwin provided me with written consent to review her cell phone. Goodwin was read and signed a Maryland State Police Form 78 Consent to Search and Seize form at 1052 hours [10:52 a.m.] Goodwin was provided with the opportunity to have the contents of the messages between her and James to be forensically downloaded however she declined. Goodwin provided me with twenty-two (22) screenshot photographs of what she described as conversations between her and James. Goodwin sent the photographs to my agency issued cell phone which have been attached to this report.  While reviewing the screenshot photographs, I observed the contact information to be the following Name: Devin (planet emoji) Photo: Male with a white dog Phone: 443-523-0264  Case open, investigation continuing.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/05/2023 11:49:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/05/2023 13:44:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493197</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1420</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>5</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/30/2023 15:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1420</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/05/2023 12:08:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/05/2023 12:08:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/05/2023 12:05:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:13</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>212952</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Goodwin</LastName>
               <FirstName>Caitlyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nichole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/03/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/20/2018 16:44:56</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G350</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C345</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Goodwin</LastName>
               <FirstName>Caitlyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nichole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/03/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G350</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C345</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/20/2018 16:44:56</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>34782</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sandyfield</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Pittsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21850</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2309</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.405604</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.393535</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>366</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1109</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/20/2018 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/05/2023 12:08:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/05/2023 12:08:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>6</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/10/2023 09:50:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/10/2023 09:50:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 09:05:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/10/2023 09:50:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Contact with Devin Christian James</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: Contact with Devin Christian James  Victim 1: Name: Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben DOB 12/09/2000 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 204 Bridge Street, Mardela Springs, Wicomico County, Maryland 21873 Phone: 443-397-5509  Victim 2: Name: Caitlyn Nichole Goodwin DOB: 01/03/2001 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 7580 Fentral Avenue, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-366-1109  Suspect: Name: Devin Christian James DOB 05/31/2001 Race: White / Sex: Male Address: 2307 Pine Way, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-523-0264  Narrative: On May 2, 2023, at approximately 1400 hours [2:00 p.m.] I, Corporal Nicholas R. Hager, #6001 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region contacted Devin Christian James [hereinafter referred to as Devin] by telephone. I attempted to set up an interview with Devin however he said he would need to call me back.  On May 5, 2023, I was contacted by Cindy McDonald who informed me that she was representing Devin, and she was not going to have him make a statement.  Case open, investigation continuing.    </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/10/2023 09:51:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/10/2023 09:56:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>7</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/19/2023 07:19:26</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/19/2023 07:19:26</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 09:05:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 07:19:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Contact with Chesapeake Health Care</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: Contact with Chesapeake Health Care  Victim 1: Name: Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben DOB 12/09/2000 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 204 Bridge Street, Mardela Springs, Wicomico County, Maryland 21873 Phone: 443-397-5509  Victim 2: Name: Caitlyn Nichole Goodwin DOB: 01/03/2001 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 7580 Fentral Avenue, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-366-1109  Suspect: Name: Devin Christian James DOB 05/31/2001 Race: White / Sex: Male Address: 2307 Pine Way, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-523-0264  Narrative: On May 18, 2023, I, Corporal Nicholas R. Hager, #6001 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region contactedChesapeake Health Care Records Department, Cornita Price [hereinafter referred to as Price] by telephone in reference to the records subpoena which was served on March 22, 2023. Price informed me that she forwarded the subpoena to the Mental Health department and she was still waiting for a response from them, Price said as soon as she gets a response she will reach out to me.  Case open, investigation continuing.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 07:20:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 07:23:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>8</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/19/2023 07:25:14</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/19/2023 07:25:14</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 09:05:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 07:25:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Charges for Devin Christian James</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: Charges for Devin Christian James  Attachments: Arrest Warrant D230129480 Arrest Warrant D230129491  Victim 1: Name: Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben DOB 12/09/2000 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 204 Bridge Street, Mardela Springs, Wicomico County, Maryland 21873 Phone: 443-397-5509  Victim 2: Name: Caitlyn Nichole Goodwin DOB: 01/03/2001 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 7580 Fentral Avenue, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-366-1109  Suspect: Name: Devin Christian James DOB 05/31/2001 Race: White / Sex: Male Address: 2307 Pine Way, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-523-0264  Narrative: On May 18, 2023, I, Corporal Nicholas R. Hager, #6001 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region completed an Application for Statement of Charges [DC/CR 1] for Devin Christian James [hereinafter referred to as James] in reference to Alyssa Nicole Rivera-Gerben [hereinafter referred to as Rivera-Gerben] and Caitlyn Nichole Goodwin [hereinafter referred to as Goodwin]. The DC/CR 1 was forwarded to the Wicomico County District Court Commissioners Office for review and the following arrest warrants were issued for James:  Arrest Warrant D230129480 in reference to Rivera-Gerben was issued charging James with the following:  1) CR 2 206 - ATT 2ND DEG. MURDER 2) CR 3 203 - ASSAULT - SEC DEGREE 3)CR 2 206 - ATT 2ND DEG. MURDER 4) CR 3 202 - ASSAULT - FIRST DEGREE 5) CR 3 203 - ASSAULT - SEC DEGREE 6) CL- FALSE IMPRISONMENT 7)CR 3 202 - ASSAULT - FIRST DEGREE 8)CR 3 203 - ASSAULT - SEC DEGREE  Arrest Warrant D230129491 in reference to Goodwin was issued charging James with the following:  1)CR 3 202 - ASSAULT - FIRST DEGREE 2)CR 3 203 - ASSAULT - SEC DEGREE 3)CL- FALSE IMPRISONMENT  Both arrest warrants were forwarded to the Maryland State Apprehension Team - East to locate and serve on James.  Case open, investigation continuing.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 07:26:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 07:48:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>9</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/23/2023 12:53:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/23/2023 12:53:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 09:05:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 12:53:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Case Update</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: Case Update  Victim 1: Name: Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben DOB 12/09/2000 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 204 Bridge Street, Mardela Springs, Wicomico County, Maryland 21873 Phone: 443-397-5509  Victim 2: Name: Caitlyn Nichole Goodwin DOB: 01/03/2001 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 7580 Fentral Avenue, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-366-1109  Suspect: Name: Devin Christian James DOB 05/31/2001 Race: White / Sex: Male Address: 2307 Pine Way, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-523-0264  Narrative: On May 22, 2023, the Maryland State Apprehension Team - East located Devin Christian James [hereinafter referred to as James] and placed him under arrest for Arrest WarrantsD230129480 andD230129491. James was taken before a District Court Commissioner for an initial appearance where he was held without bond.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 12:54:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/23/2023 13:00:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493197</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0910</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>9</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/23/2023 13:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 0910</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 13:01:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/23/2023 13:07:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493197</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1420</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>9</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/23/2023 13:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1420</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 13:01:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/23/2023 13:07:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493197</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0920</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>9</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/30/2023 15:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 0920</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 13:07:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/23/2023 13:07:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>10</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/24/2023 07:50:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/24/2023 07:50:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 09:05:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 07:50:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Chesapeake Health Care Subpoena Response</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: Chesapeake Health Care Subpoena Response  Attachments: Maryland State Police Form 67 Medical Records Business Certification  Victim 1: Name: Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben DOB 12/09/2000 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 204 Bridge Street, Mardela Springs, Wicomico County, Maryland 21873 Phone: 443-397-5509  Victim 2: Name: Caitlyn Nichole Goodwin DOB: 01/03/2001 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 7580 Fentral Avenue, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-366-1109  Suspect: Name: Devin Christian James DOB 05/31/2001 Race: White / Sex: Male Address: 2307 Pine Way, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-523-0264  Evidence: Medical Records provided by Chesapeake Health Care, stored in Salisbury Barrack Temporary Storage  Narrative: On May 23, 2023, I, Corporal Nicholas R. Hager, #6001 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region was contacted by Cornita Price [hereinafter referred to as Price] in reference to the records subpoena which was served on March 22, 2023. I responded to the Chesapeake Health Care Records Office where I took possession of the requested medical records for Alyssa Rivera-Gerben [hereinafter referred to as Rivera-Gerben] at 1423 hours. I reviewed the records and observed the following:   On 01-27-2022 Rivera-Gerben was seen by Deborah Anderson, CRNP-PMH and reported that she had recently left a very verbally abusive and sometimes physical relationship with her boyfriend which she lived with and that she sometimes gets paranoid about her ex coming to get her.  The above listed evidence was documented on a Maryland State Police Form 67 and stored in the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack Temporary Storage.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 07:51:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/24/2023 08:05:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>11</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/19/2023 07:40:04</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/19/2023 07:40:04</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 09:05:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/19/2023 07:40:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Contact with Brian Keith Davis</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: Contact with Brian Keith Davis  Witness: Name: Brian Keith Davis DOB: 09/01/1963 Race: White / Sex: Male Address: 2308 Abbott Dr, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21804 Phone: 410-251-8912  Victim 1: Name: Alyssa Nicole Rivera Gerben DOB 12/09/2000 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 204 Bridge Street, Mardela Springs, Wicomico County, Maryland 21873 Phone: 443-397-5509  Victim 2: Name: Caitlyn Nichole Goodwin DOB: 01/03/2001 Race: White / Sex: Female Address: 7580 Fentral Avenue, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-366-1109  Suspect: Name: Devin Christian James DOB 05/31/2001 Race: White / Sex: Male Address: 2307 Pine Way, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 Phone: 443-523-0264  Narrative: On October 18, 2023, I, Corporal Nicholas R. Hager, #6001 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region contacted Brian Keith Davis [hereinafter referred to as Davis] In reference to the incident in which Caitlyn Nichole Goodwin [hereinafter referred to as Goodwin] stated that she called Davis for help. Contact was made with Davis via telephone and he provided the following information:   Davis recalls the incident and has reviewed the report which was provided by Devin James [hereinafter referred to as James]Attorney  Goodwin called Davis to calm Jamesdown  Davis went to the residenceand observed verbal arguments, no signs of injury on either party  Neither partymentionedinjuries  Davis heard James tellCaitlyn to leave multiple times however she would not leave.  James threatened to call the police on Caitlyn  Davis said he was ultimately able to get Caitlyn to leave the residence  Case closed by arrest.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6001</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/19/2023 07:41:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 07:51:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>