<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-005217</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/10/2023 12:23:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/10/2023 12:23:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/10/2023 12:22:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/10/2023 12:22:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Criminal Telephone Misuse / Harassment</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 12:24:02</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 09:54:32</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>HMP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>House of Delegates</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>683785</AddressId>
      <City>MDC102</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 12:24:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 11:07:43</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>683785</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Hanover Ccu</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/10/2023 12:23:59</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/10/2023 12:23:59</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/15/2023 09:54:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 12:24:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 09:54:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments - T-Mobile Court Order - Apple Court Order  Narrative  On 02/10/2023, Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division, Computer Crimes Unit was contacted by the Maryland State Police Legislative Division in regards to an on-going incident involving telephone misuse. It was reported at approximately 0920 A.M., an individual identifying themselves as Adahi Saline (unknown spelling) began calling the Speaker of the Houses main phone line (410-841-3800) on a continuous basis from a T-Mobile cell phone number, 443-864-1747 (SUSPECT PHONE NUMBER). The callers voice was described as a voice belonging to an adult male. At approximately 1018 hours, Sgt At Arms, Sgt. Robert Parham advised the caller to stop calling, at which time, the unknown caller advised if attempts to use deadly force on him were made, he would be eager to kill him. The subject then began shouting profanity such as cock sucker, and speaking about illegal immigrants. It was also determined the caller attempted to contact the main office line multiple times on 02/09/2023 at approximately 2:00 P.M., but eventually stopped calling.  TFC Crowe conducted an open-source query of the phone number and determined it to be serviced by T-Mobile. TFC Crowe authored a request for a Court Order requiring T-Mobile to provide subscriber information and call records pertaining to the reported phone number.  On 02/13/2023, the same individual began calling the main line again around 0900 hours. Troopers within the Legislative Division reported the same individual was now calling from a private number and at times the caller ID would only display 100. Utilizing a law enforcement database, Troopers were able to link the incessant calls to a suspect. The suspects information is set forth below: Name: LILLY, Ade Salim William (SUSPECT) DOB: 06/20/1988 MD SDX: L400031758472 Address: 5748 Flagflower Place, Columbia, MD 21045  The same day, TFC Crowe, TFC Cooke, CPL Heid, and SGT Pitcher responded to 5748 Flagflower PL in Columbia, Maryland. TFC Crowe and TFC Cooke made contact with Ade Salims father, Tony Andre Lilly (DOB: 04/14/1959). He refused to open the locked storm door of the townhouse and immediately asked if there was a search warrant. Mr. Lilly was advised we were investigating a number of phone calls that were believed to have been made by his son. Mr. Lilly responded by repeating that his son was not home, and would not provide Troopers with additional information as to his whereabouts.  The SUSPECT later confirmed his identity by immediately calling the Speakers Office line and stating I heard you sent armed men to my fathers house. Now I will send armed men to yours.  On 02/14/2023, TFC Crowe received compliance from T-Mobile pursuant to the Court Order. T-Mobile reported the SUSPECT PHONE NUMBER is serviced through TracFone and no subscriber details were available. The records show the phone was purchased in March of 2022, but no identifying information is required for service through TracFone.  TFC Crowe conducted a review of the calls made by the SUSPECT PHONE NUMBER, and observed the following: On 02/09/2023, the SUSPECT PHONE NUMBER contacted the Speakers Office Main Line a total of 5 times between the hours of 04:18PM and 04:31PM local time. On 02/10/2023, the SUSPECT PHONE NUMBER contacted the Speakers Office Main line a total of 76 times between the hours of 09:36AM and 011:18AM local time. *** A number of additional calls were made, but the scope of the court order was limited to historical records prior to signature. ***  On 2/15/2023, TFC Crowe was made aware of an email sent to several Howard County Government email addresses criticizing the County Government utilizing extremely vulgar and sexually offensive language. The email was sent from the email address, alilly06@aol.com on 02/14/2023 at 07:35 PM. The subject of the email being: YOURE ERADICATING THE U.S. SLAVE-DESCENDED POPULATION IN THIS COUNTY TO RATIONALIZE PRIORITIZING FOREIGN COLONISTS OVER US! The email was signed, Ade Salim.  That afternoon, TFC Crowe prepared a request for a Court Order requiring Apple to provide any account details related to the IMEI and IMSI listed in the T-Mobile return. The Court Order was signed by the Honorable Michael Malone, Judge of the Circuit Court for Anne Arundel County. TFC Crowe transmitted the signed order to Apple the same day via email.  That evening, a Safety Bulletin was created and disseminated by MCAC requesting anyone receiving calls from and individual identifying himself as Ade Salim, to contact TFC Crowe via email. As of this date, SALIM was continuing to call the Speaker of the Houses main phone line, as well as the Annapolis and Waterloo Barracks requesting information regarding the two Troopers that had visited his fathers house. Over the phone, Mr. Salim made the comment, they brought my family into this, so I will bring their family into it as well, or words to that affect.  On 03/02/2023, TFC Crowe received production from Apple related to the device utilized to make the phone calls to the Speaker of the Houses main phone line. Apple provided the following information about the owner of the device, set forth in relevant part, below: - Apple ID: alilly6@aol.com - First Name: Ade - Last Name: Lilly - Country: United States - Account Status: Active - Created On: 03/18/2018 - Address Line 1: 5748 Flagflower Place - City: Columbia, Maryland - Postal Code: 21045-2502 - Day Phone: 4438641747 - Verified Phone: 4438641747  TFC Crowe reviewed the iCloud Logs information provided by Apple and determined the IP addresses utilized between 01/28/2023 and 02/15/2023 belong to T-Mobile and Liberty Cablevision of Puerto Rico. During this time period where the calls were made, it appears that SALIM has been accessing his mobile service and residential internet in and around San Juan, Puerto Rico.  Case Status OPEN / PENDING  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 11:15:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6726</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 11:22:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pitcher</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5360</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Crowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6726</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494603</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0340</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>11</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/10/2023 12:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0340</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 11:08:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6726</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 11:08:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 11:13:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371812</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lilly</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ade Salim</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>William</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/20/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 11:12:57</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A324</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lilly</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ade Salim</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>William</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/20/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A324</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 11:12:57</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>864</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1747</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 11:13:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/01/2023 06:49:29</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/01/2023 06:49:29</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/15/2023 09:54:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 06:49:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 09:54:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments - Written Statement: FSGT S. Bojnowski - Written Statement: SGT R. Parham - Written Statement: Karen Cassidy - Written Statement: Matthew Jackson - CAD Detail CC#2023-00068358 - Application for Statement of Charges  Narrative  Since the initial report, TFC Crowe collected written statements from involved parties and authored an application for statement of charges. On 05/31/2023, the application was forwarded to the Office of the Commissioner for Anne Arundel County. An arrest warrant for LILLY, Ade Salim (DOB: 06/20/1988), was issued the same day on two counts of telephone misuse related to the repeated and obscene calls made to the Maryland Speaker of the Houses Office. (Warrant ID: D230111475)  Based on LILLYs last known location in Puerto Rico, and communications made by LILLY to Howard County Police Department stating he is not planning to return to Maryland, I am requesting this case be suspended until the warrant service can be completed.  Case Status SUSPENDED</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 06:50:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6726</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 07:01:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Crowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6726</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/30/2023 09:42:16</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/30/2023 09:42:16</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/15/2023 09:54:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/30/2023 09:42:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 09:54:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments - Email Correspondence (Ms. Firmin Statement)  Narrative  On Wednesday, August 30th, 2023, TFC Crowe received additional correspondence related to harassing and obscene phone calls made by LILLY on 08/29/2023. A complaint was made by Ms. Michelle Firmin who answered the phone at the office of Delegate Pena-Melnyk and spoke with LILLY. Though the phone number associated with the call was listed as PRIVATECALLER, the individual on the line identified himself as Ade Salim, which directly correlates to the phone calls received earlier in this investigation. The attached email includes Ms. Firmins full statement. LILLY made obscene and insulting statements toward Ms. Firmin, including calling her stupid and a cracker ass bitch, that is obsessed with him. According to Ms. Firmin, LILLY called the office line 15-20 times between 05:05PM and 05:25PM.  Though this case has already been placed in a suspended status, this supplement is submitted as a record of additional behavior related to this investigation. At the time of this report, there is an open arrest warrant for LILLY based on similar behavior detailed in previous supplements to this report. LILLY is still believed to be living in/or around San Juan, Puerto Rico with no intention of returning to Maryland.  Case Status SUSPENDED</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/30/2023 09:43:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6726</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 10:45:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Crowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6726</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>