<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011938</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/03/2023 20:38:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/03/2023 20:38:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/03/2023 20:05:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/03/2023 20:05:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI - 23-019 - Tolliver</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 20:38:52</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/12/2023 14:49:45</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>2836 CHESTNUT RIDGE RD,GRANTSVILLE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>689531</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 20:38:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/05/2023 15:18:01</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>689531</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2836</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Chestnut Ridge</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-79.10459</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.6898</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>ROUNDABOUT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/03/2023 20:38:50</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/03/2023 20:38:50</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/11/2023 02:48:33</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 20:38:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Driver: Allante Lorenz Tolliver PA OLN: 34497716 DUI #: 23-019 Video: My in-car cameras and body worn camera were activated during the incident. Subsequent Offender: No VEHICLE IN MOTION:  On 4/3/2023 at approximately 2000 hours, I, TFC. Bradley, was dispatched to Chestnut Ridge Rd at U.S. Rt. 219 Bypass for a motor vehicle collision. Prior to my arrival, the McHenry barrack emergency dispatcher notified me that witnesses observed one of the drivers from the collision throwing items out of a bag and away from his car, appearing to try and hide them before police arrived. I arrived on scene at approximately 2010 hours. PERSONAL CONTACT:  I made contact with Allante Lorenz Tolliver, who was identified by his Pennsylvania drivers license. Upon making contact with Tolliver, I immediately detected the strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person and observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. Tolliver told me he was driving South on U.S. Rt. 219 bypass approaching Chestnut Ridge Road in his white Mitsubishi Outlander bearing PA registration: MBL6230. Tolliver observed a white Jeep Wrangler in the roundabout on Chestnut Ridge Road, traveling North. He believed the Jeep was slowing down to let him proceed before colliding with the passenger side of the Jeep in the roundabout with the front of his Mitsubishi. I made contact with the driver of the white Jeep Wrangler bearing DE registration: PC56180, who was identified as Robert Aaron Kilduff Junior by his Maryland drivers license. Kilduff told me he was driving his Jeep north on Chestnut Ridge Rd in the roundabout at the Rt. 219 bypass roundabout. As he was passing the entrance from the roundabout, he observed the white Mitsubishi traveling at a high rate of speed, fail to yield at the intersection, driver over the raised curb area and strike the left side of his jeep. The other occupants within the Jeep were identified as Jacob Foster Kilduff (front right seat), Ethan Matthew Cain (rear left seat), and Lucas Tristan Oliveira (rear right seat). Each driver and occupant advised they did not suffer any injuries.  I observed yield signs to be upright and facing traffic coming from the U.S. Rt. 219 bypass into the roundabout at that intersection. I also observed heavy front-end damage to the front of the Mitsubishi and moderate damage to the passenger side of the white Jeep. While on scene, multiple fire/EMS personnel approached me to tell me Tolliver threw multiple items in front of his car and off the roadway before my arrival. I walked to the area they directed me to and found one miniature bottle of New Amsterdam Vodka.  I returned to Tolliver and asked him how many drinks he had that night, he replied, I didnt, I wasnt drunk, it was a roundabout, I couldnt see at the light and we hit each other. I asked if the answer to my question was none. He told me no and that he had one beer earlier. As I spoke with Tolliver, I noted his speech to be slurred and I continued to detect the strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I offered Tolliver to submit to field sobriety tests, he agreed. PRE-ARREST SCREENING:  The evaluation was performed on the raised curb area of the roundabout on Chestnut Ridge Rd. The concrete surface was flat and free of any debris other than a light, even cover of small pieces of gravel. I deactivated the emergency lights of my patrol vehicle and ensured the surrounding emergency vehicles deactivated their emergency lights that were illuminating towards Tolliver. The weather was clear and approximately 55 degrees Fahrenheit. Lighting conditions consisted of multiple vehicles headlamps, overhead streetlamps and my flashlight. Tolliver appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any physical injuries, limps or limb ailments. Tollivers back faced towards my patrol vehicle. I asked Tolliver the following questions: How many alcoholic beverages consumed before operating the vehicle: One regular beer. When was it consumed: Two hours ago Physical or medical disabilities: No Recent injuries: No Medications: Dicyclomine daily Glasses or contacts: No/none observed  As I spoke with Tolliver, I continued to detect the strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person, observed his eyes to appear bloodshot and glassy and noted his speech to be slurred. Tolliver was wearing a white sweater with butterflies, black pants and black sneakers. HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN) TEST (6/6 CLUES OBSERVED)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. My black ballpoint pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Tollivers eyes. Tolliver was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the stimulus with his eyes only until told to stop. Tollivers pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Tolliver advised he understood the instructions.   Tolliver displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.   Tolliver displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.   Tolliver displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.  *Tolliver did display vertical nystagmus. WALK AND TURN TEST (5/8 CLUES OBSERVED)  Prior to Tolliver performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test was to be conducted. Tolliver was instructed to place his right foot in front of his left and touch heel to toe. Tolliver was instructed to place his hands at his side and to remain in that position until told otherwise. I asked Tolliver if he understood, he advised he did. Tolliver was advised to take nine (9) steps straight out in front of him, touching heel to toe on every step. He was to keep his hands down at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step Tolliver was demonstrated and explained to keep his lead foot planted and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around without stopping. Tolliver was explained and demonstrated the second series of steps to be performed identical to the first series. Tolliver was advised once he started the test, he was not to stop until the test was completely finished. After explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked Tolliver if he understood the instructions, he replied he did. Instructional Stage:     margin-left:8px"&gt;Tolliver started the test too soon one time.  First Nine:    Tolliver raised his right arm during the first nine portion of the test.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Tolliver took (10) actual steps for the first nine portion of the test, contrary to instructions.  The Turn:     margin-left:8px"&gt;Tolliver pivoted the front of both feet to turn around, contrary to instructions.   Second Nine:    Tolliver stopped walking at the beginning of the second nine.  Tolliver raised his arms during the second nine.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Tolliver took (10) actual steps for the second nine portion of the test, contrary to instructions.  ONE-LEG STAND TEST (3/4 CLUES OBSERVED)  Prior to Tolliver performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Tolliver was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands down to his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. Tolliver was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start, and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately six (6) inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, keep his toe pointed forward, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand two, one thousand three...) and to continue the test until told to stop (30 seconds). Tolliver advised that he understood all the instructions. He balanced on his right leg with his left leg raised. Seconds 0-10:    Tolliver raised his arms during the first ten seconds.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Tolliver swayed during the first ten seconds.  Seconds 11-20:    Tolliver put his foot down during the second ten seconds.  Tolliver raised his arms during the second ten seconds.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Tolliver swayed during the second ten seconds.  Seconds 21-30:     margin-left:8px"&gt;Tolliver swayed during the third ten seconds.  ALPHABET F-T  Tolliver advised he is familiar with the English alphabet and agreed to recite the alphabet starting at the letter F and ending at the letter T. Tolliver recited it as follows: F, G, H, I, K, L, M, N, O, P, Q, U, R, S, T, U, V, W, Z. COUNT BACKWARDS 59-36:  Tolliver agreed to count down, starting at 59 and ending at 36.     margin-left:8px"&gt;Nothing to report.  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT):  I read Tulliver the MSP 102 (Preliminary Breath Test Advisement of Rights) and asked him to submit to a PBT. Tulliver agreed to submit to a PBT at approximately 2037 hours with results of .182 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. ARREST/DR-15 ADVICE OF RIGHTS:  Due to the facts above, I placed Tulliver under arrest for DUI at approximately 2038 hours. At approximately 2048 hours, I checked Tullivers mouth for any foreign objects, none were observed. I read Tuller his DR-15 Advice of Rights and provided him the opportunity to read along as I read if he chose to do so. At approximately 2057 hours, Tulliver refused to submit to a breath test. Tulliver was transported to the McHenry barrack for processing.  Tulliver was provided with all of his copies of paperwork, advised not to drive for 12 hours and released to his friend, Holly Reider. As I made contact with Tulliver throughout the evening, I continued to detect the strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person, observed his eyes to appear bloodshot and glassy, and noted his speech to be slurred.  Case closed by arrest. An ACRS report was completed and attached. All above events occurred in Garrett County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 18:49:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7189</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/05/2023 18:49:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kline</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7112</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7189</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bittinger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Blair</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0199</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7189</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7189</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501341</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/03/2023 20:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 15:19:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7189</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/05/2023 15:21:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 15:19:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:23</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373336</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Tolliver</LastName>
               <FirstName>Allante</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lorenz</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/25/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 22:55:13</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A453</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Tolliver</LastName>
               <FirstName>Allante</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lorenz</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/25/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A453</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 22:55:13</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>101</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>N</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>5 Points</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>West Chester</City>
               <StateCode>PA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>19380</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.57516</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.970894</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>708</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>631</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8777</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 15:22:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 15:22:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 15:22:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 15:19:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7189</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/05/2023 15:19:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151604</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 15:19:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7189</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/05/2023 15:19:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JA4J4UA88NZ091990</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MITS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>OUT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>PA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>MBL6230</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>