<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-028677</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/13/2023 22:47:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/13/2023 22:47:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/13/2023 22:47:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/13/2023 22:47:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Assist Frederick Police Department at MSP Frederick</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 00:37:31</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3033</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/01/2023 10:53:59</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>Assist Other Agency</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>33453</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>510</SubBeat>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 00:37:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 00:45:18</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>33453</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>110</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>AIRPORT</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <StreetSuffixCode>E</StreetSuffixCode>
         <City>FREDERICK</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>510</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-77.37710064842739</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.40483954714474</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MSP FREDERICK /  AT GAS PUMPS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MSP FREDERICK / @ PUMPS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FREDERICK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MSP FREDERICK/ @ PUMPS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FREDERICK COUNTY LAW ENFORCEMENT CENTER</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FREDERICK CITY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MSP FREDERICK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/14/2023 00:37:30</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/14/2023 00:37:30</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>11/01/2023 10:53:59</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 00:37:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3033</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/01/2023 10:53:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Body Worn Camera- Not functional for Sgt. VonStein Body Worn Camera- Officer Ross/ Deputy McLeroy were both functional  On 8-13-2023 at approximately 2247 hours, I observed a white male enter the front lobby of 110 Airport Dr, Frederick, MD. The male began pacing back and forth in the lobby and appeared to be profusely sweating. At that time Cpl. Mattingly opened the lock set of doors in the lobby at which time the male entered and went to the Frederick Sheriffs Department side. The male began going off stating that they were trying to steal all his money and that he was being robbed. I then asked him who he was referring to, and he advised that his ex-girlfriend. The male then stated several times that they were going to steal his $250,000 from his PNC bank card, and they installed hardware on his phone to get all his information. At that time Officer Ross from Frederick City PD arrived and advised that the subject was involved in a domestic dispute at the Super 8 Motel off Monacacy Blvd. At that time the male who was later identified as Grant Eric Myers (7-1-93) was being interviewed by Officer Ross. Myers had severe mood swings throughout the entire interaction with both officers. Myers refused to corroborate with the investigation and stated that we were involved in taking his money, and was becoming extremely agitated. Myers asked for a drink several times when I got him three cups of water in an attempt to deescalate Myers. Myers then stood up from the chair while speaking with Officer Ross and them began throwing his phone destroying it inside the LEC. At that time due to the extreme mood swings and violent acts, Officer Ross and I placed Myers into handcuffs without using force. Once Myers was placed into handcuffs Officer Ross requested EMS. EMS arrived at scene at which point Myers started having mood swings with them, and he would not allow EMS to check any vitals. Myers then allowed EMS to place a pulse-ox on his finger where he then pulled away from them after approximately 5 seconds and stated that he didnt want any help. Myers then began to stat several times that he would give us anything we wanted to be released and that his family was rich. After EMS as well as police spoke with Myers and advised him that we were there to help him he calmed down and stated he would go with EMS. Myers then stood up while in handcuffs and started walking to the stretcher with EMS. Myers then took off running slamming into the interior set of door at which time the doors opened, and he continued running through the lobby in handcuffs. Myers then approached the exterior set of doors running slamming his head into the glass exiting the building. Once exciting the doors Myers fell to the ground at which time Officer Ross, Deputy McLeroy and I got Myers under control and placed him in a recovery position. Myers had a bloody nose from striking the door while exiting the building. Myers was then sitting on the ground. The severe mood swing started again where he began to try to get up and kick at police and EMS. EMS then provided Myers with medication at which point he became a little more controllable while placing him inside the ambulance. Both doors were checked, and no damage was observed. Officer Ross returned and photos were taken of the exterior door where you could see Myers face print on the glass door. Officer Ross along with another Officer went inside the ambulance for the safety of EMS personnel. Officer Ross completed an Emergency Petition on Myers.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4488</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 00:47:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4488</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 01:47:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stein</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3033</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Vonstein</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4488</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>