<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025711</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/18/2023 22:31:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/18/2023 22:31:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/18/2023 21:03:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/18/2023 21:03:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Responded to 3 subjects fighting, domestic related, one was transported for an Emergency Petition.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 22:31:18</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4783</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 08:29:29</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ABT</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>EP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>701335</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 22:31:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 20:11:38</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>701335</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>79</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Eyeopener</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Oakland</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-79.366764</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.546951</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/18/2023 22:31:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/18/2023 22:31:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/04/2023 08:29:11</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 22:31:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>BWC Operational  Scene Processing: Photographs of injuries sustained to Matthew, Megan, and Brandon were taken and uploaded to Veripic per Maryland State Police Policy.  Physical Evidence: Photos of injuries sustained to Matthew, Megan and Brandon. MSP Form 76 Written Statements Completed by Brandon, Yvonne, Megan. Written Statement from Witness Katherine Hoppes MSP Form 246 Domestic Violence Supplement  Suspect: Hoppes. Matthew Ryan W/M DOB: 02/22/1984  Victims: Hoppes, Brandon Allen W/M DOB: 01/21/1982 Baker, Megan Lynn W/F DOB: 10/11/1985 Hoppes, Yvonne W/F DOB: 10/21/1956 Kuhn, James Allen Harley W/M DOB: 03/08/1995  Narrative: On July 18, 2023 at approximately 2104 hours I, TFC Mohr #7118, was on duty in uniform operating marked Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle W-26. At that time, I was dispatched to 79 Eyeopener Lane, Oakland, MD for an assault in progress. Upon my arrival I made contact with a female later identified as Baker, Megan Lynn (W/F DOB: 10/11/1985.) I asked Megan what happened, Megan responded, My brother is drunk, he punched me in the face. I observed swelling and some redness on the right cheek bone of Megan. I asked Megan to explain what happened, Megan explained that her two brothers were fighting and arguing and she tried to get past them and she got punched in the face by Matt.   I then made contact with and identified Hoppes, Brandon Allen (W/M DOB: 01/21/1982.) I observed Brandons shirt to be ripped. I asked Brandon what happened, Brandon stated, I came home from the store, and I could hear my brother and mom arguing, I came in the house and asked what the issue was, and he started coming at me in a fighting stance. Brandon continued to explain that he attempted to keep his distance away from his brother with his arm reached out. Brandon continued to explain that his brother attempted to grab a chair to hit him, but his mother stopped him. Brandon continued that his brother again came up to him in a threatening manner. Brandon attempted to create distance by placing his hand on his brothers chest. Brandon advised thats when his brothers dog bit him on his right forearm. I observed a bite mark on his right forearm. Brandon continued at that point his brother tried to punch him. Brandon advised he put his brother in a headlock and pushed him to the ground. Brandon continued that his sister, Megan, attempted to close the screen door to the house so the dog did not try and enter and bite anyone else. Brandon stated, When my sister started to walk past us thats when he sucker punched her. Brandon continued that when he saw his sister get punched, he punched his brother and pushed him down the stairs and told him to leave. Brandon advised that his mother was downstairs and his brother grabbed her and pushed her into the wall.  I made contact with Hoppes, Matthew Ryan (W/M DOB: 02/22/1984.) I observed Matthew had several lacerations on his arms and blood coming from his lip. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his person. I observed Matthew to have an open Bud Light Beer Can in his hand. Matthew freely stated, Ill go to jail, I deserve to be there. Matthew placed his hands behind his back and turn around to be handcuffed. I explained that he wasnt under arrest, and we were just trying to figure out what was going on. Matthew stated, Im going to jail anyway on the 15th in Wicomico County. Matthew continued to be uncooperative and would not tell us what happened. I asked Matthew what happened to his arm, Matthew stated his dog bit him when they were fighting. Matthew stated, They tried to gang up on me, when I saw that bitch I saw blood. Matthew stated, You see her up there, shes the fiddler the started all this. Matthew was pointing to a window in the upstairs of the residence. I observed a female in the window with several small children. Matthew continued to ask to be arrested and to be taken to jail. Matthew routinely stated that he hadnt seen his daughter in 2 years due to Judge Marst. Matthew used multiple profanities and racial slurs while speaking with me. Matthew continued to repeat the same utterances for the entire time I spoke with him. While speaking with Matthew I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath, I observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. Matthew stated, They tried to gang up on me, Ive been to war, what do you expect of me.  I took photographs of the injuries sustained by Brandon, Megan, and Matthew.  I made contact with Hoppes, Yvonne Frances (W/F DOB: 10/21/1956). Yvonne is the mother of Brandon, Megan, and Matthew. I asked Yvonne what happened. Yvonne stated, My one son got drunk and started fighting my other son. My drunk son punched my daughter, and pushed me against the wall. Yvonne explained that Matthew was in the military, and he currently suffers from Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder.  At that time, Megan was transported by Garrett County Paramedic Ambulance 952 to Garrett Regional Medical Center, 251 N 4th Street, Oakland MD. (Reference EMS Run #23-05930).  I requested Yvonne and Brandon to complete MSP Form 76 Written Statements which were scanned and uploaded to this report.  Brandon completed a MSP Form 246 Domestic Violence Supplement which was scanned and uploaded to this report. Brandon stated on scene he wanted to press charges against Matthew.  Cpl. Arnold #4752 made contact with a witness Hoppes, Katherine who explained that Matthew had approached her drunk and angry. Katherine attempted to separate herself from Matthew when his dog bit her. Katherine provided a written statement which was scanned and uploaded to this report.  I asked Matthew if he would be fine paying for a hotel room for the night and returning sober tomorrow morning. Matthew agreed. I transported Matthew to the Quaint Inn, 2704 Deep Creek Drive, McHenry MD 21541. While completing the registration for a room Matthew stated he refused to pay for the room. Matthew began to make utterances about his family killing his dog and if that happened he would kill everyone in Garrett County. Matthew continued to utter that the only way he was staying in the hotel would be if the State of Maryland paid for it. Matthew continued to make utterances of racial slurs and what would happen if his dog was killed. At that point, I determined Matthew was a danger to himself and others. I placed Matthew in custody and transported him to the University of Pittsburgh Western Maryland Hospital, 12500 Willowbrook Rd, Cumberland MD 21502 , for an Emergency Petition. While en-route to the hospital Matthew stated, Mohr listen, if my dog is killed I will find you and kill you. Matthew continually called me racial slurs. Matthew then placed his feet on to the front of my dashboard. I instructed Matthew to remove his feet. Matthew stated, No, make me. I pulled my patrol vehicle on to the shoulder and exited the vehicle. When I approached the passenger side of my vehicle Matthew still had his feet on the dashboard. As I requested another unit, Matthew complied and placed his feet down. I adjusted the seat so Matthew could not raise his legs up. On the drive, Matthew continually threatened to harm anyone who hurt his dog. Matthew asked to stop for his last meal because once he got to jail he would starve himself to death. Matthew continued to ask to stop for a last meal.  Once I arrived at UPMC, Matthew was asked to change into hospital attire, Matthew began to get uncooperative getting inches from several Hospital Staffs faces. Matthew eventually complied and placed on the hospital gown. Matthew then attempted to give a urine sample and urinated into a cup. Matthew dipped his fingers into his urine then turned around and flicked the urine onto the face of a hospital nurse, later Identified as Kuhn, Jaymes Allen. Jaymes stated he did not want to press charges against Matthew. Matthew was then given medication to calm him down, and he went to sleep.  On July 19, 2023, at approximately 1400 hours I responded back out to 79 Eyeopener Lane to follow up with Yvonne and Megan. Megan and Yvonne completed a MSP Form 246 Domestic Violence Supplement. I asked Yvonne if she would like to press charges on Matthew, Yvonne stated, No. I asked Megan if she would like to press charges on Matthew. Megan stated, Im not sure, I feel like he needs rehab over jail time. I instructed Megan that she can have time to decide if she wanted to press charges or not and referred her to the Garrett County Commissioners Office. I made contact with Brandon again, and confirmed that he still wanted to press charges on Matthew. Brandon stated, Yes, he needs to learn his lesson.  On July 19, 2023, at approximately 2140 hours, Garrett County Commissioner Dickerson issued a Criminal Summons for Matthew formally charging him with: CR 3-203 Assault Second Degree  A copy of the summons was scanned and uploaded to this report.  I request this case remain open pending summons service.  All events occurred in Garrett and Allegany County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 19:09:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7118</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 01:00:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Arnold</LastName>
            <FirstName>Norman</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4752</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Arnold</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4885</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Arnold</LastName>
            <FirstName>Norman</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4752</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mohr</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7118</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515154</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/18/2023 21:03:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 17:13:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7118</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 17:13:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 17:22:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:07</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382977</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hoppes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
               <DOB>02/22/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 17:21:58</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hoppes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
               <DOB>02/22/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 17:21:58</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>18306</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Ashley</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>104</SubNumber>
               <City>Hagerstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21740</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.736222</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.694566</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>614</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2683</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 20:23:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 17:24:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:07</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382978</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hoppes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Katherine</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/31/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 17:23:52</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K365</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hoppes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Katherine</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/31/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K365</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 17:23:52</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>28296</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Canterbury</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21801</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.631461</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.432664</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>713</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5719</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 17:24:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:06</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 17:27:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:18</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382979</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Baker</LastName>
               <FirstName>Megan</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/11/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 17:26:53</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Baker</LastName>
               <FirstName>Megan</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/11/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 17:26:53</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9826</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sharptown</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Mardela Springs</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21837</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2217</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.750527</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.464565</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>614</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2126</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 20:20:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:16</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>41</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 17:29:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:18</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382980</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hoppes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Allen</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/21/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 17:29:20</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hoppes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Allen</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/21/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 17:29:20</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>28296</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Canterbury</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21801</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.631461</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.432664</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>366</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5194</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 20:19:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>66</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 17:31:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:18</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382981</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hoppes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Yvonne</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/21/1956 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 17:31:17</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Y150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hoppes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Yvonne</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/21/1956 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Y150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 17:31:17</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>30701</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Victoria</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Delmar</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21875</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2047</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.5468892</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.4486103</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>235</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1418</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 20:18:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/19/2023 01:46:59</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/19/2023 01:46:59</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/04/2023 08:29:11</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 01:46:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On July 26, 2023, at approximately 2300 hours I contacted Matthew via telephone to inform about his criminal summons and to inquire when he could respond to the Maryland State Police McHenry Barrack to be served his paperwork. Matthew stated he could not hear me over the phone multiple times. I attempted to speak louder, but Matthew hung up the phone. I immediately called Matthew back, and he could clearly hear me. I advised Matthew he had a criminal summons, and he needed to respond to the barrack to be served. Matthew began to yell and curse over the phone and stated, Maybe you should learn when to fucking call someone, not at 11 o clock at night. I explained to Matthew that I work a rotating schedule and this time was my scheduled shift. Matthew continued to use vulgar language and racial slurs before hanging up the phone.  On August 3rd, 2023, at approximately 0700 hours I again attempted to make contact with Matthew. The call went to voicemail and a message was left.  On August 07, 2023, at approximately 0900 hours I again attempted to make contact with Matthew. The call again went to voicemail, I again left a message and informed Matthew if he didnt respond to the barrack the summons would turn into a Criminal Arrest Warrant. Matthew called the barrack and spoke with PCS Chaney at approximately 1644 hours. Matthew was given pertain information regarding his summons and the potential for it to become a warrant.  The criminal summons expired on 08/18/2023. Matthew was not able to be served.  I request this case remain open.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 01:48:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7118</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 01:58:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Arnold</LastName>
            <FirstName>Norman</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4752</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mohr</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7118</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/03/2023 14:55:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/03/2023 14:55:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/04/2023 08:29:11</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 14:55:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On September 13, 2023 A Criminal Arrest Warrant was issued for Hoppes.  On September 30, 2023 at approximately 1900 hours, I contacted Hoppes via telephone and explained he had new paperwork he had to be served. Hoppes stated that he now lived on the Eastern Shore of Maryland, and would respond to the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack to be served.  On October 2, 2023 at approximately 1200 hours Matthew Hoppes responded to the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack. Hoppes was placed under arrest by Trooper Barfield #7185 and transported to Worcester County Detention Center where he was held pending a bond review.  Case Closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 14:58:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7118</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 22:10:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Arnold</LastName>
            <FirstName>Norman</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4752</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mohr</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7118</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/04/2023 08:10:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/04/2023 08:10:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/04/2023 08:29:11</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP4410</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 08:10:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The purpose of this supplement is to change incident status to closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4410</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 08:11:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4410</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 08:11:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sigmund</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4783</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Theodore</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4410</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515154</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>3</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/04/2023 08:12:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4410</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 08:12:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4410</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 08:12:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>