<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-021860</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/18/2023 05:16:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/18/2023 05:16:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/18/2023 04:46:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/18/2023 04:46:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/18/2023 05:16:13</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 12:35:20</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>77.8 MM I95 NB,ABINGDON</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>698176</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/18/2023 05:16:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/09/2023 04:24:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>698176</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>77</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>8 Mm I95 Nb Abingdon</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.28899495</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.4653360333333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/18/2023 05:16:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/18/2023 05:16:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/22/2023 12:21:32</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/18/2023 05:16:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:27:56</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police, Barrack D Marked MSP Vehicle D-12. In-Car Camera Operational.  Defendant: Ndungu, Jacob Manyara Date of Birth: 04/08/1982 Date of Arrest: 06/18/2023 Time of Arrest: 0515hours DUI #: 23-160(Bel Air) Blood test Result: REFUSAL  BEHAVIOR/CONDUCT:Ndungu was uncooperative and argumentative.  CERTIFICATION  TRAINING NHTSA Trained/certified to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Test (SFST) Preliminary breath test operator certified Certified Radar/Laser Operator  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On June 18, 2023,at approximately 0446hours, I, Trooper Kumador #7052 of the Maryland State Police, Bel AirBarrack was patrolling Northbound I-95 in the area of 77.8 Mile Marker in Aberdeen, HarfordCounty, Maryland. I was operating a marked Maryland State Police vehicle, D-12 in lane 2. I observed a dark color vehicle approaching from behind at a high rate of speed. The vehicle passes my patrol vehicle traveling in the far-right lane. I observed the vehicle was unable to maintain lane and veered off almost completely on to the right shoulder and quickly corrected back into the travel portion. I identified the vehicle as a green Subaru Outback, displaying Maryland registration 6EM6616.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I made a driver side approachof the vehicleand made contact with the operator, a blackmale. I introduced myself and the reasonfor the stop. The driver repeated the reason for the stop and stated that he has video too. As the driver spoke to me, I detected a strong odor of alcoholic beverage on his breath. I also observed an opened container of beer in the center console cup holder. I asked the driver where he was traveling from, and he stated he was coming from his friends birthday party. I asked the driver how much alcoholic beverages he had consumed and he stated that he does not drink. I reminded the driver about the beer in the center console and he stated that the beer was not at his side. While asking the driver further questions, he stated that I finished my drink, this is his drink while pointing to the beer in the center console. The driver later changed his story by saying I did not finish my drink, you can test me I identified the driver by his Maryland drivers license as Ndungu, Jacob Manyara, DOB: 04/08/1982. There was also a black male passenger in the vehicle who advised that they were coming from a birthday party. Ndungus eyes were heavily bloodshot and glassy. His speech was slurred.      PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   Due to the overwhelming odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from Ndungus breath, the presence of opened container of beer in the center console accessible to the driver, the admission to consuming alcoholic beverages before the traffic stop, VIP bar wristband on his wrist as well as his unsafe manner of operating the vehicle on the highway, I had reasons to believe that he was driving under the influence of alcohol. I advised Ndungu about my intention to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests to which he agreed. Upon the arrival of additional units, I requested Ndungu to exit his vehicle for the tests, to which he agreed. The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder in front of my patrol vehicle. The shoulderwasflat and free of any debris and the temperature was approximately 68 degrees.I asked Ndungu the following questions: Contacts-No,Glasses-No, andAny Injuries-No.Any medication: No.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the Tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Ndungus eyes. Hewas instructed to look straight ahead, keeping hishead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hiseyes until told to stop. I asked himif he understood the directions, and he advised yes. His pupils were equal in size and did show equal tracking.   Lack of Smooth Pursuit - present  The distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation  present  The onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  present.  Vertical-present   WALK AND TURN (4/8) Before Ndungu performed the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. He was instructed to place hisright foot directly in front of hisleft foot and touch heel-to-toe. He was instructed to place hishands flat at hisside and to remain in the position until told to begin. Hewas advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. He was to keep his hands flat at hisside, keep hiseyes focused on hisfeet, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, he was demonstrated and explained to keep hislead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around to hisleft with hisrear foot to turn completely around. He was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. He was then instructed that once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep hishands down by hisside, look down at hisfeet, and count each step out loud.  During the instructional stage:I explained and demonstrated the starting position to Ndungu andplaced him in thestarting position. Instead of placing his right foot in front of his left foot, he placed his left. He indicated verbally that he understood my instructions and had no question for me. He stated I just take what you just say  Walking stage (1st Nine).    He took only 3 steps instead of 9  Stepped offline during the teststeps.  Turn: The turn was unsatisfactory. Ndunguturned swiftly in one fluid motion, instead of taking a small series of steps toward his left as he was instructed.  Walking stage (2nd Nine).    He took 3 only steps instead of 9  Missed heel-to-toe by more than an inch   ONE LEG STAND (0/4) Prior to Ndunguperforming the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. He was instructed to stand with hisheels together and hands down by hisside, while the instructions were given and during the test. He was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of hischoice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While hisleg was raised, he was to keep hisleg straight, watch hisraised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one thousand-two), and to continue the test until told to stop.      He did not raise his foot as instructed   PRELIMINARY BREATH A preliminary breath test was offered to Ndungu and he declined to submit to the test.  ARREST Based on the following, I havereasons to believe that Ndunguwas operating his vehicle while under the influence of alcoholand unable to operate safely    Extremely strong odor of alcoholic beverage on his breath  Admission to consuming alcoholic beverages an hourbefore the traffic stop,  Unable to maintain lane discipline on the road way-swerving  Observed signs of impairment as he performedthe Standardized Field Sobriety Tests unsatisfactorily.  I arrested Ndunguat 0515hours for driving his vehicle while under the influence of alcohol. Ndungulistened to the Englishaudio version of DR-15 Advice of Rights in its entiretyin my patrol vehicle and at the conclusion, he voluntarily agreedtosubmit to the test. Itransported himto the Maryland State Police, Bel Air barrack for processing where he signed the paper copy of the DR-15 at the barrack at 0555 hours.  20-MINUTES OBSERVATION PERIOD. Ndungus observation started as soon as he was arrested and his oral cavity check was completed at 0518 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT:  Breath test was explained and offered to Ndungu by Cpl. Workman #6608 with a result of insufficient sample. Ndungu was coached how to blow into the instrument and he did not follow that instructions. The Cpl. later conducted a simulation test after the driver failed to submit sufficient test. The result came back success indicating that the equipment was functioning properly.  Ndungu was charged with driving a vehicle while under the influence of alcohol and other DUI related charges.  Ndunguwasgiven copies of all pertinent paperwork andlater released to a sober licensed driver at the barrack.  Ndungu after his arrest stated that he had 1 Bottle Guinness at a Club about 2 hours before the stop. He indicated that he was at his friends house for birthday party and later went to the Club. He had a VIP Bar wristband on his wrist. The extreme odor of alcohol emitting from his breath as he speaks in my patrol vehicle, the heavily bloodshot eyes and the manner of driving as well as the SFSTs results were indicative of alcohol in excess of one bottle. Ndungu was evasive with information nor willing to provide it.  Closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/09/2023 04:19:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/09/2023 04:49:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allen</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7267</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Turner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6761</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kumador</LastName>
            <FirstName>Linford</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7052</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511296</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/18/2023 04:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/18/2023 06:52:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/18/2023 06:52:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>41</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/18/2023 06:53:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>380210</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ndungu</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jacob</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Manyara</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/08/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.91619341E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>06/18/2023 06:42:44</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N352</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J210</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ndungu</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jacob</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Manyara</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/08/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.91619341E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>N352</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J210</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/18/2023 06:42:44</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>503</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Plaza</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <City>Aberdeen</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21001</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.190902</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.520729</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>730</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3285</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/18/2023 06:53:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/18/2023 06:53:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/18/2023 06:53:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/18/2023 06:53:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/18/2023 06:52:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/18/2023 06:52:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>