<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-020586</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/08/2023 19:33:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/08/2023 19:33:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/05/2023 00:18:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/05/2023 00:18:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>06/05/2023 06:00:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>Rape</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/08/2023 19:33:50</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3572</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/18/2023 12:08:47</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>RAP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>664154</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/08/2023 19:33:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 15:04:01</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>664154</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>809</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Heritage</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Oakland</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21550</Zip5>
         <Zip4>1746</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-79.382126</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.404451</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/08/2023 19:33:47</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/08/2023 19:33:47</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/18/2023 12:08:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/08/2023 19:33:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>SCENE PROCESSING:    Digital photographs of the scene were taken and uploaded into Veripic. Items from the scene (fitted bed sheet, comforter, underwear) were collected and secured as evidence in the McHenry Barrack evidence locker. The items were documented on MSP Form 67 Request For Laboratory Examination - Chain of Custody Log. Photographs of the suspect/victim text conversations were forwarded via email. The email documents will be placed in the case file.  NARRATIVE:    On 06-08-2023 at 1817 hours, I was dispatched to respond to 809 Heritage Drive, Oakland, Maryland 21550 for a reported rape. Upon arrival, I made contact with Cody Clifton Brill and Macy Lynn Brill, the parents of Morgan Ann Brill. Macy wanted to report that her daughter, Morgan, was raped by a friend on Sunday night (06-04-2023). Macy stated that on Monday, 06-05-2023, Morgan told her details of the incident and for the past few days they have been deciding how to handle it. Macy stated the family has relatives at the Garrett County Sheriffs Office, so they decided to report it to the Maryland State Police for investigation. Macy stated on the night of the incident, she and her husband Cody went to bed before midnight and did not wake up until around 0600 hours Monday morning. Cody stated he heard Morgan come home at 0018 hours.   I asked Morgan if she wished to have her parents in the room during the interview, and she stated, Yes. I asked Morgan to explain the events as they happened chronologically the night of the rape. Morgan stated she was out drinking with her friend, Joshua Collins. She stated Joshua did not have anything to drink and was driving her around. Morgan stated she had two wine coolers and 3-4 cups of tequila. She stated she was drunk enough that she did not know exactly what was going on at all times. Morgan stated it was normal for Joshua not to drink and to drive her home. Joshua went inside of Morgans home and down to her bedroom with her which also was not abnormal. Morgan stated they have been friends since sixth grade but have slowly got more serious this past year. Morgan has told Joshua that she has never wanted to be in a relationship with him but believes he wants to be closer. Morgan stated they have had some physical activity and attraction recently but have not had sexual intercourse. On that night, Morgan told Joshua she was laying down to go to sleep. She said she remembers going in and out of consciousness due to being intoxicated. Morgan awoke and realized Joshua had his fingers in her vagina. She then realized her pants were off and so were his. She believes she passed out again and then awoke to find Joshua on top of her having sexual intercourse for a period of time. Morgan stated it was not consensual. Morgan advised that was the last thing she remembered and does not remember what time Joshua left her house.   The next day, 06-05-2023 at 1732 hours, Morgan and Joshua began texting about what happened the night before. Morgan showed me the saved text conversation on her phone between her and Joshua. Morgan asked Joshua, Did you rape me? He said, No, just finger. The conversation continued for a while with Morgan repeatedly asking Joshua if he raped her, had sex with her, or was inside her. Joshua repeatedly denied all of these. Morgan asked Joshua if she needed to take a pregnancy test or go to the hospital for a rape kit. Joshua then replied, Im sorry Morgan. Just the tip. Morgan told Joshua that he lied to her, and he replied, I lied to you, and I am so sorry. I didnt want to think that it happened. Im still in denial that I even did it. Morgan replied, Josh you raped me. Joshua replied, I know. Im sorry Morgan. Morgan advised she has not talked to or texted Joshua since Tuesday, 06-06-2023 and that she has blocked his number.   Morgan stated she and Joshua have a mutual friend, Tommy Sweitzer (301-616-4801). Sweitzer told Morgan that Joshua confessed to him in person that he did rape Morgan. I asked Morgan if she is currently on birth control, and she stated she is not. I asked Morgan if she has been to the hospital for a SAFE exam, and she stated she has not. Morgan stated she took a Plan B pill on Tuesday, 06-06-2023. I encouraged Morgan to go to the hospital and get the SAFE exam completed.   Macy Brill stated she sent a message to Joshua on Instagram ordering him to never contact Morgan again. Joshua stated, I am sorry for everything. I do not deserve to be alive anymore. I asked Morgan if she is currently in fear of Joshua based on the recent events. Morgan stated she is not afraid. I explained the process of obtaining a Protective Order from the Garrett County Commissioners Office. I asked Morgan, Macy, and Cody if there was anything else I should know about the incident. Macy told Morgan she should tell me about the recent statements Joshua has been making. Morgan stated Joshua has been talking about having a fetish for sleeping girls. He also told her he has been having homicidal thoughts and has made a list. I asked Morgan if she has ever seen this list or know of anybody on it, and she stated, No.   I asked Morgan if there was any evidence remaining in her bedroom. She stated she cleaned her room but has not changed her bedding. She stated there is blood on her sheet, and she has not slept in her bed since the incident happened. I observed the bedding as Morgan described and took photographs and collected the bedding as evidence. The items collected were a white sheet, gray comforter, and a pair of purple underwear. Morgan stated the underwear were washed, but they were the pair she was wearing the night of the rape. I asked Morgan if there were any other items in the room that Joshua may have touched, and she stated there were not.   I made contact with MSP CED Investigator, Cpl. Couter who advised to take the initial report and forward the case to McHenry Barrack CED. Cpl. Couter stated a follow-up with Morgan and interview of Joshua would occur tomorrow, 06-09-2023.    Case to remain OPEN and will be forwarded to Sgt. Ross, McHenry CED.    </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5049</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/08/2023 21:27:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5049</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/08/2023 23:15:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brennan</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5146</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Broadwater</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0215</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nelson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Aaron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5049</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510021</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1102</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/05/2023 00:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1102</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5049</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/08/2023 21:14:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5049</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/08/2023 21:14:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5049</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/08/2023 21:21:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 15:04:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>379337</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Collins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Martin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/08/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/08/2023 21:19:39</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Collins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Martin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/08/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/08/2023 21:19:39</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>799</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sand Flat</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Oakland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21550</Zip5>
               <Zip4>6916</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.3365</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.440227</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>501</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3282</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 17:56:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5049</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/08/2023 21:21:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>19</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5049</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/08/2023 21:25:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 15:04:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>379338</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Brill</LastName>
               <FirstName>Morgan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/15/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/08/2023 21:24:29</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M625</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Brill</LastName>
               <FirstName>Morgan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/15/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M625</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/08/2023 21:24:29</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>809</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Heritage</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Oakland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21550</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1746</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.382126</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.404451</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>321</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4262</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5049</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/08/2023 21:25:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:12</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5049</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/08/2023 21:25:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:12</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/16/2023 17:34:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/16/2023 17:34:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/18/2023 12:08:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 17:34:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On June 16, 2023 at approximately 1500 hours I responded to 1076 Pysell Crosscut Rd, Oakland MD to assist Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division with a Warrant Service. I was briefed that Collins, Joshua Martin (W/M DOB:08/08/2004) had an active warrant for 2nd degree rape. The warrant was confirmed by the Maryland State Police McHenry Barrack PCO. I placed Collins under arrest without incident and transported him to the Garrett County Commissioners Office where he was released on an Unsecured Personal Bond.  All events occurred in Garrett County, MD.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7118</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 17:48:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7118</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/16/2023 17:51:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Theodore</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4410</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mohr</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7118</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/19/2023 08:36:44</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/19/2023 08:36:44</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/18/2023 12:08:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 08:36:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 6/9/2023, I was made aware of this investigation and I was assigned to this case.  I reviewed M/Tpr Nelsons report. I first took note of who was reporting the rape. Macy Brill, Morgans mother, was the one reporting the rape allegations. I also observed M/Tpr Nelsons statement that Morgan stated she and Collins have slowly become more serious over the past year and they, Have had some physical activity and attraction recently but have not had sexual intercourse. I needed to schedule an interview with Morgan and I contacted her by telephone on the same date.  I established contact with Morgan by telephone. It was agreed upon that she would provide an interview at the McHenry Barracks on 6/12/2023 outside the presence of her parents. I explained to Morgan that we would be speaking about actions that may be difficult and embarrassing to talk about. I further explained she would need to be honest with me if there was any sexual activity between her and Collins in the past. I brought up what was stated in M/Tpr Nelsons report of how she and Collins have had some physical activity and have become closer over the past year. Morgan stated she does not consider Joshua Collins a boyfriend and she stated the two never had consensual intercourse. She did admit the two have gone down on each other from time to time and those times were consensual. I asked her to elaborate what she meant by gone down and she was referring to fellatio and cunnilingus.  I also asked her if she acted upon M/Tpr Nelsons recommendation of the SAFE kit and protective order. She stated, No. I asked her if she planned on obtaining these services. Morgan stated she did not believe she needed a protective order and was not in fear of Joshua Collins. She stated she was not sure if she would have a SAFE kit initiated. I explained to her the importance of the SAFE kit and the evidentiary value and also that it was her choice to make. After this, I ended the telephone conversation.  MORGAN BRILL INTERVIEW   On 6/9/2023 at approximately 0930, Morgan Brill responded to the McHenry Barrack accompanied by her father. I escorted Morgan into the barrack conference room to conduct the interview. The interview was audibly recorded utilizing my MSP issued audio recorder. The following is a paraphrase of this interview and the interview can be heard in its entirety on the attached recording.  Morgan stated she and Joshua have been really close friends since the sixth grade. Morgan confided in her father and Morgans father told Morgans mother about the incident. Morgan stated she asked her mom to contact the police after several days of processing the information. She explained she was feeling depressed on Sunday, June 4th and she decided to contact Joshua to spend time with him. Morgan stated Joshua drove to her house and from there, they drove Morgans vehicle to an overlook to talk. At some point, the two went to Joshuas house. Morgan stated she consumed a couple of wine coolers and three glasses of tequila. I questioned her of the tequila was straight or if it was mixed with other liquid. She stated it was a mixed drink and described the glass to be a taller glass and full to the top with the drink. Morgan remembers telling Joshua that he was not to do anything to her that evening. She described herself as being intoxicated by the end of the night. According to Morgan, Joshua was not consuming any alcohol and Morgan is the one who was getting her own drinks.  I questioned Morgan as to why she would have to tell Joshua not to do anything to her prior to becoming intoxicated. According to Morgan, she and Joshua are engaged in sexual activity with one another. She stated she and Joshua do engage infellatio and cunnilingus. These acts are mutual and she has never let Joshua have sexual intercourse with her. I asked her if she performed fellatio on Joshua that evening. She stated, No.  Morgan stated the two then drove back to her place and entered her bedroom from a door in the basement. The basement door leads directly into Morgans bedroom. She stated her parents were asleep by the time Joshua and Morgan arrived. She believed by this point, it was already early Monday morning (June 5th) by the time she arrived back home. She stated she and Joshua were on her bed. It is not uncommon for Joshua to be in her bed due to the closeness of their relationship. Morgan believes she blacked out from the amount of alcohol she had consumed earlier. She stated at one point, she woke up and Joshua was rubbing her vagina and breasts above her clothing. She stated she woke again to find her pants and underwear off and Joshua rubbing his bare penis against her thigh area. She also remembers Joshua digitally penetrating her because she could feel him inside her vagina. Morgan stated she could not remember full details because of her intoxication level, but she did not believe she ever told him to Stop nor does she remember telling him, No. Morgan stated she remembered something feeling different during this encounter. She stated she has had sexual intercourse with an ex-boyfriend in the past and knows what a penis feels like. She stated she remembered feeling this sensation inside her vagina at some point. She was not positive that Collins penetrated her vagina with his penis, however, during a Snapchat conversation later in the day, Collins admitted to putting the tip of his penis into Morgans vagina.  Morgan showed me the Snapchat conversation which was saved to her cellphone. During this Snapchat conversation, Morgan attempts to figure out what actually occurred in her bedroom during the early morning hours. She asks Collins, Are you sure you didnt have sex with me? Collins swears he did not and Morgan continues to press him by stating she remembered him on top of her because she remembered seeing his arms and something was inside her. She then asks, So what was inside of me? Collins replies, My fingers to which Morgan replies, No, I saw them. Later in this conversation, the last few lines read: Josh: Im sorry Morgan Morgan: So you did? Josh: Just the tip Morgan: You lied to me Josh: I lied to you and I am so sorry I didnt want you to think that it happened Im still in denial that I even did it Morgan: Josh you raped me Josh: I know...  Morgan also showed me a message which her mother, Macy Brill, sent to Joshua Collins on Tuesday, June 6th. It read: Josh. I have no words. All I can say is do not, ever contact Morgan again. No call texts nothing. She has to heal from this.At the very least you owe her that.  Reply from Collins: I am sorry for everything. I cannot express how deeply sorry I am. I never wanted to hurt her but I have hurt her in the worst way possible. I do not deserve to be alive anymore. I will never forget how good you were to me and how I took that all for granted. I am sorry for everything.  During the course of the interview, I explained the investigative effort of a consensually monitored telephone call. After discussing the technique, it was agreed upon to attempt this at a later date.  After this interview, I sent a request to Snapchat to preserve Morgans and Collins conversation betweenJune 3, 2023 to June 12, 2023.  CONSENSUALLY MONITORED TELEPHONE CALL On 6/16/2023 at approximately 1000, Sgt Ross and I responded to Morgan Brills residence in an effort to conduct a consensually monitored telephone call between Morgan and Joshua Collins. Morgan agreed to have the conversation audio recorded. Morgan signed the MSP Consensual Monitoring Form (MSP 177)  At approximately 1015, Morgan was able to establish telephone contact with Joshua Collins. Utilizing my Maryland State Police issued audio recorder (registered device GNTF0069), I successfully captured the telephone conversation. During this conversation, Morgan spoke about the night in question. Collins did not deny penetrating Morgans vagina with his penis. At 7 minutes and 17 seconds into the recording, the conversation is the following: Collins:Im not denying it anymore. I know what I did. Morgan: So you know what you did? Collins: Yeah. Morgan: Okay, then say it. Collins: I raped you. The entire recording is sixteen minutes and fifty-four seconds in length. This recording has been attached to the case file. Prior to the monitored telephone call, I obtained four pictures of Morgans bedroom. These have been attached to the case file.  ARREST OF JOSHUA COLLINS On the same date, I applied for charges against Joshua Collins. A warrant was issued by the Garrett County District Court Commissioner. TFC Mohr and I responded to Collins place of employment which is Martins Auto Parts located at1076 Pysell Crosscut Rd, Oakland, MD 21550. Collins was taken into custody without incident. I read Collins his Miranda Rights and he did not make any statements about the allegations. He also did not request a lawyer at that time. He was transported to the McHenry Barrack for processing.  While at the McHenry Barrack, I attempted a recorded interview and I read Collins his Miranda Rights once again in order to make sure he fully understood his rights. Collins requested a lawyer and no questions regarding the allegations were asked. TFC Mohr and I worked in conjunction with the arrest processing. I collected a DNA sample utilizing a DNA Database Collection Kit. This kit is standard procedure for those arrested and charged for certain crimes. Rape in the second degree is one of the crimes where a DNA sample is collected. Before the end of my shift, the DNA collection was taken to the U.S. Post Office in Accident, Maryland and dropped in the mail at approximately 1650 hours.  At this time, I request this case remain open pending further investigation. I am waiting to hear from Maryland State Police Crime Lab concerning the submission of the bed sheet and Morgans underwear. During the consensually monitored telephone call, Joshua Collins stated he did not ejaculate. Submission and analysis of these articles has to be approved by the MSP Crime Lab. A supplement will follow concerning these two articles of evidence.  Case Status: Open  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 08:39:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5177</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/20/2023 15:31:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Romanchak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5177</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/05/2023 18:15:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/05/2023 18:15:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/18/2023 12:08:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5049</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/05/2023 18:15:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>  This case has been transferred to McHenry Barrack CED, M/T Romanchak. See related supplements for status of case.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5049</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/05/2023 18:17:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5049</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/05/2023 18:18:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Broadwater</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0215</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nelson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Aaron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5049</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/24/2023 10:38:30</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/24/2023 10:38:30</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/18/2023 12:08:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 10:38:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #4 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 7/20/2023, I received correspondence from Morgan Brill advising me of recent contact with Joshua Collins through Snapchat. I was provided with screenshots of this conversation between Morgan and Joshua.  The chat appears to be initiated by Joshua Collins. The Snapchat accounts in which this conversation is held are the same two accounts listed in the initial report. The writer of the chat begins, Hey. I know Im not supposed to message you or talk to you. I am trusting you not to say anything about this. But I really need to talk to you Morgan. I have attached the images to this report due to the length of the conversation.  The Garrett County States Attorneys Office has been made aware of this chat between Collins and Brill.  A special prosecutor has been requested for this case. Once the prosecutor is determined, I will be made aware of moving forward with testing of the underwear and bedsheets for DNA and also applying for a search warrant for Snapchat. Due to the admission on the consensually monitored telephone call, these efforts may not be needed and I am awaiting guidance on these two remaining matters.  Case remains closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 10:40:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5177</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 10:51:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Romanchak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5177</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>5</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/15/2023 08:21:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/15/2023 08:21:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/18/2023 12:08:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 08:21:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #5 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On August 9, 2023, I authored and executed a search and seizure warrant on Snap Inc. for the conversation which took place between Snap accounts joshuamcollins1 and morgan.a10. Screenshots have already been reviewed and obtained for the conversation between Joshua Martin Collins and Morgan Brill. The search warrant was signed by the Honorable Judge Stephan Moylan and electronically submitted to Snap Inc. through their law enforcement portal. An acknowledgement was sent by Snap Inc. stating it had been received and will be reviewed.  On August 14, 2023, I met with Tommy Sweitzer at the McHenry Barrack for a recorded interview. I had spoken with Sweitzer by telephone early on in the investigation during the month of June. During that telephone conversation, he advised that Joshua Collins confided in him that he sexually assaulted Morgan Brill. Tommy also stated how Collins mentioned either turning himself into the police or committing suicide for what he had done to Morgan.  I recorded this interview of Tommy Sweitzer and he recalled being with Joshua Collins on June 5, 2023. He stated he and Collins were driving to Thomas Subaru in Cumberland and Collins stated he needed to tell Tommy something. Tommy stated Collins then stated he sexually assaulted and fingered Morgan. Tommy stated he was taken back and did not know what to say. Tommy then stated it was during the ride back from Cumberland that Collins stated that he had not told the entire truth and that he actually raped Morgan Brill. Again, Tommy stated he did not know what to say and he has not spoken with Collins since that day.  I asked Tommy if there were any other statements made by Collins. Tommy stated Collins did make a statement concerning what he (Collins) should do as far as turning himself into the police or possibly committing suicide. Tommy does not recall any other details of the conversation. Tommy did show me that Collins reached out to him through Snapchat just asking how he was doing. Tommy did not respond to the message.  Case remains closed.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 08:22:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5177</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 09:07:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ross</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3572</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Romanchak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5177</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>19</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 09:04:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 15:04:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>385172</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tommy</FirstName>
               <DOB>02/09/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/15/2023 09:01:52</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S326</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tommy</FirstName>
               <DOB>02/09/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S326</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/15/2023 09:01:52</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>304</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>D</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>1</SubNumber>
               <City>Oakland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21550</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-79.385469</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.397271</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>616</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4801</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 09:04:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>6</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/14/2023 08:48:47</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/14/2023 08:48:47</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/18/2023 12:08:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/14/2023 08:48:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #6 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 9/8/2023, I was provided with the results from Snapchat for the executed search and seizure warrant dated August 9, 2023.  Snapchat was unable to disclose any sent videos, photos and conversations which may have existedduring the time frame requested. An explanation was provided which stated, Please be advised that we are unable to comply with narrow requests for only that content sent from (or, alternatively, only that content sent to) to a Snapchat account.  Any information sent by Snapchat Inc. has been copied to a CD and attached to the case file. It has also been relayed to the prosecuting attorneys office.  Case remains closed. Any additional investigation will be documented on a supplement.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/14/2023 08:53:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5177</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/14/2023 09:11:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ross</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3572</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Romanchak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5177</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>7</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/15/2023 15:00:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/15/2023 15:00:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/18/2023 12:08:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/15/2023 15:00:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #7 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This supplement was created to update the offense status as cleared by arrest. No other details have been changed in the report.  Case remains closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/15/2023 15:03:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5177</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 15:03:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ross</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3572</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Romanchak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5177</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510021</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1102</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>7</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/16/2023 15:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1102</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/15/2023 15:00:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5177</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 15:02:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>