<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-015037</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/03/2023 06:10:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/03/2023 06:10:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/03/2023 06:10:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/03/2023 06:10:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect is prohibited from possessing firearms and ammunition and was found to have access to/possession of a non-regulated firearm (shotgun) within his residence.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 13:05:08</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0965</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 09:05:38</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>Suspect's Residence</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>690358</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 13:05:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/03/2023 08:27:12</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>690358</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>13451</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Olde Oak</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Charlotte Hall</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20622</Zip5>
         <Zip4>3686</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.851521</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.41457</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/28/2023 13:05:06</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/28/2023 13:05:06</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40R</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:04:42</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 13:05:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> On April 10, 2023 at approximately 1852 hours, TFC M. Posch #6749 and CPL M. Johnson #6369 responded to the area of 26978 Thompson Corner Road, Mechanicsville, St. Marys County, Maryland for an assault. Upon arrival Troopers contacted an off-duty Prince Georges County Police Officer, Braden James Dalton, who advised he observed the suspect, identified by Troopers later as Kevin Michael Newhart (W/M, DOB: 08/16/1973), yelling at two women on the side of the road. Dalton advised he stopped to check on the situation and Newhart assaulted him. The subsequent investigation resulted in Newhart being arrested for Assault Second Degree and Driving Under the Influence. Following their investigation, I, ST S. DiToto #5416, was advised by both involved Troopers that Newhart had made statements about having a firearm. CPL M. Johnson advised while Newhart was at MedStar St. Marys Hospital, he was making derogatory racial statements about how CPL M. Johnson would handle a firearm compared to how he holds or handles a firearm. CPL M. Johnson advised these statements were not captured on his body-worn camera because they occurred in the Hospital where Newhart or others were receiving medical treatment at the time. I was also informed Kevin Newhart had an active warrant through Louisiana. An active out of state arrest warrant would prohibit Kevin Newhart from possessing firearms as he is considered a fugitive from justice.   I then reviewed TFC M. Poschs and CPL M. Johnsons body-worn camera footage from the incident. I observed that upon arrival, Troopers contacted Braden Dalton. While Dalton explained the incident to Troopers, he stated that Newhart mentioned having a firearm. Dalton believed from the statements the firearm may be in Newharts vehicle at the scene. Dalton stated he did not observe a firearm and did not check or search Newharts vehicle. During the remaining course of the investigation, I did not observe the vehicle checked or searched for any firearms. The vehicle was removed from the roadway and Troopers cleared the scene with Newhart. I observed no other statements or information pertaining to the possible firearm.   I conducted a check of multiple resources for additional information regarding Kevin Newhart and access or ownership of firearms. I found no records in MAFSS (Maryland Automated Firearm Services System) and no hunting record information in Department of Natural Resources. I located a Facebook profile for Newhart and confirmed his identity by comparing the name and profile photograph to his images on body-worn camera and his Maryland MVA photograph. I then located a profile for a subject who was commonly referred to as Newharts wife, Holly Elaine Baily (W/F, DOB 06/11/1974). This Facebook profile had the name Holly Bailey (Newhart) and featured a profile image with Holly Bailey and Kevin Newhart. While observing the content within her profile, I observed a photograph posted by Holly Bailey on 03/22/2020 showing Kevin Newhart standing outside holding a camouflage shotgun. The location of the image could not be determined. Further investigation into Newhart confirmed his address to be 13451 Olde Oak Drive, Charlotte Hall, Charles County, Maryland. I additionally conducted a full check of law enforcement resources and criminal histories regarding Kevin Newhart and located multiple criminal convictions that prohibit Newhart from possessing firearms and ammunition under Maryland Public Safety Article. Those prohibiting circumstance are captioned below.  1. Court Case #: 1993CRS001084  Listed Offense: Felony Stolen Goods  Disposition: Convicted Guilty  Court System: Wayne County Court (North Carolina)  Disposition Date: 05/24/1993  2. Court Case #: 1995CRS019160  Listed Offense: Assault on Govt. Office  Disposition: Convicted Guilty   Court System: Wayne County Court (North Carolina)  Disposition Date: 09/02/1997   3. Court Case #: 1995CRS019161   Listed Offense: Resist Arrest  Disposition: Convicted Guilty  Court System: Wayne County Court (North Carolina)  Disposition Date: 09/02/1997  4. Court Case #: 2001CR059768   Listed Offense: Carry Concealed Weapon   Disposition: Convicted Guilty   Court System: Wayne County Court (North Carolina)  Disposition Date: 12/10/2001  5. Court Case #: 2003CR060569   Listed Offense: Resist Public Officer  Disposition: Convicted Guilty   Court System: Wayne County Court (North Carolina)  Disposition Date: 03/17/2004  6. Court Case #: 2005CRS056421  Listed Offense: Forgery of Instrument (Felony)  Disposition: Convicted Guilty   Court System: Wayne County Court (North Carolina)  Disposition Date: 11/16/2005  7. Case # 20-01822A   Agency: East Baton Rouge Parish Sheriffs Office   Offense: Active Bench Warrant: FTA - HarassingCommunication  Date Entered: 9/17/2020    After I identified the charges I observed the name, date of birth, and other identifying information within the record matched the known information for Kevin Newhart. I observed multiple booking photographs related to his arrests in North Carolina and found they matched his known photographs as well. It was also found there was a North Carolina drivers license number (24213890) associated with the records and a check of that returned a North Carolina DMV record with matching name, date of birth, and photograph. I contacted the clerk for the Wayne County Court and verified the existence of the above captioned cases. I submitted a request for Certified True Test copies of the available record for each case and received certified documentation in return for each of the above cases.   On July 3, 2023 at approximately 0610 hours, ST D. Buckalew #5687 and I conducted a knock and talk at a Salem travel trailer parked at 13451 Olde Oak Drive, Charlotte Hall, Charles County, Maryland (as this was suspected to be where Kevin Newhart resides). As we approached, Newhart and Bailey exited the trailer and contacted us. I identified myself and explained the reason for the visit being Newharts mention of a firearm during the April 2023 incident. Newhart explained that he owns a BB Gun that is a replica of a firearm and he was only trying to explain thats what it was during the incident to prevent it being mistake for a real firearm. As Newhart explained this, he asked to go inside and retrieve the BB Gun to show us what he was talking about. He was permitted inside and I asked if I could go with him, to which he replied absolutely. I was allowed into his trailer to show view airsoft pistol that looked similar in appearance to an actual handgun. Newhart said that he had the airsoft gun in his vehicle and was not threatening anyone with it. Newhart said he also had an airsoft rifle which he displayed as well. At the same time and while standing just inside the entryway of the trailer near the living room/kitchen areas, I observed, in plain view, a Mossberg 500 12-gauge shotgun (S/N: V1526704) leaned against the trailer wall. This was in a common area where both Newhart and I were standing. Newhart said the shotgun was unloaded and belongs to his wife. I asked Newhart to hand the shotgun to me as I could see it was unloaded at the time and I took possession and examined the shotgun. Newhart and Bailey both said the firearm had not been fired and was purchased by Bailey last year. Both advised there was no other firearm or ammunition inside their trailer. Both advised the Facebook photograph was taken when living in Louisiana and they did not own or have access to that shotgun. I observed the shotgun in the photograph was camouflage and this one was all black. Newhart was advised he is prohibited from possessing firearms due to the above captioned circumstances. Newhart advised he wanted to get his North Carolina record expunged and he had thought the Louisiana issue was closed by payment of a citation. I instructed Newhart to follow up with the appropriate agencies/court systems in the appropriate jurisdictions. While in contact with both, Bailey located and provided a receipt from purchasing the firearm. The receipt was dated 02/25/2023 from JMJ Firearms, 29015 Three Notch Road, Mechanicsville, St. Marys County, Maryland, and listed the matching serial number and listed Holly Bailey as the customer. I took a photograph of the receipt to attach to this report, but left the original with Bailey. I completed an MSP Form 67 (Chain of Custody) and MSP Form 203 (Firearms Disposition Notification). I advised Newhart and Bailey of the status of this case and the firearm. The interview was concluded and the shotgun was seized and transported to the La Plata Barrack where it was stored as evidence in accordance with MSP Policy under Property Record #P-343754.   Charges will follow review with the Charles County States Attorney. Case remains open.   Above events occurred in Charles County, Maryland.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 08:18:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/03/2023 08:38:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Warrick</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6324</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ditoto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5416</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504456</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0439</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/03/2023 06:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0439</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 08:27:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/03/2023 08:27:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>49</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 08:28:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 13:21:37</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374005</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Newhart</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/16/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/11/2023 16:21:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Newhart</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/16/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>N630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/11/2023 16:21:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>13451</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Olde Oak</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Charlotte Hall</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20622</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3686</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.851521</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.41457</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>225</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>266</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2931</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 13:21:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 13:21:37</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 08:28:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>49</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 08:31:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/03/2023 08:31:03</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>384144</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bailey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Holly</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elaine</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/11/1974 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/03/2023 08:30:31</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bailey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Holly</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elaine</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/11/1974 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/03/2023 08:30:31</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>13451</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Olde Oak</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Charlotte Hall</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20622</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3686</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.851521</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.41457</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>225</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>907</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1041</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 08:31:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 08:31:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 08:31:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 08:27:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/03/2023 08:27:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 08:33:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/03/2023 08:33:53</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Black Mossberg 500 12-gauge shotgun, S/N: V1526704</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>MSPSP</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>477</PropertyValue>
         <Value>477</Value>
         <SerialNumber>V1526704</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>252532</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>Mossberg</Make>
         <Model>500</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/08/2023 13:20:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/08/2023 13:20:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40R</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:04:42</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/08/2023 13:20:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> Following review with the Charles County States Attorneys Office, this case was forwarded to Charles County Grand Jury for indictment. On 09/22/2023 an arrest warrant was issued for Newhart for PS 5-206 (Shotgun Possession Felony Conviction) and PS 5-205 (Shotgun Possession Disqualification) as a result of the indictment. The warrant was assigned by the Circuit Court to the Charles County Sheriffs Office. I, ST S. DiToto #5416, contacted the Sheriffs Office and advised them Newhart is currently in custody at the St. Marys County Detention Center in relation to another case. A detainer was sent from Charles County to St. Marys County. Case remains open pending service of the arrest warrant.   On November 3, 2023 the case was re-presented to Grand Jury at the direction of Charles County States Attorneys Office. A new arrest warrant was issued as a result of that indictment. The status of this case remains the same.  Above events occurred in Charles County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/08/2023 13:38:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/08/2023 13:38:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sawa</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2916</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ditoto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5416</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/06/2023 13:20:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/06/2023 13:20:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40R</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:04:42</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 13:20:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> Since the previous narrative, the arrest warrant remained active as a detainer for Kevin Newhart, who was in custody in St. Marys County Detention and Rehabilitation Center. On November 21, 2023 a hearing was held in Charles County Circuit Court where a private defense attorney entered his appearance on behalf of Kevin Newhart. At the hearing the Judge granted a motion to recall the warrant. The defense attorney was electronically served a summons and copies were forwarded to Newhart. Case closed by arrest.  Above events occurred in Charles County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 13:22:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 13:22:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dulski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Steve</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0965</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ditoto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5416</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504456</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0439</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>2</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/06/2023 13:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0439</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 13:20:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 13:20:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>