<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-022703</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/24/2023 11:59:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/24/2023 11:59:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/24/2023 11:27:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/24/2023 11:27:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/24/2023 11:59:32</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/12/2023 12:53:10</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>698799</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/24/2023 11:59:34</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/25/2023 10:17:30</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>698799</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>28743</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Llandaff</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Easton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.083007</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.726069</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/24/2023 11:59:29</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/24/2023 11:59:29</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/26/2023 10:09:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/24/2023 11:59:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:03</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Alcohol Influence Report Patrol Vehicle Information I-26 (Marked). I was equipped with a BWC (Body Worn Camera) only.  Defendant: Gale Jr, Charles Samuel Date of Birth: 11/26/1970 Date of Arrest: 06/24/2023 Time of stop: 1135 Time of Arrest: 1155 Maryland SDX: MD10273045716 License Status  Valid License Restrictions  None Registration Violations  Expired registraiton  Officers Training/Experience * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Anne Arundel County Police Department, Maryland State Police Department, and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police Department * Certified Drug Recognition Expert since 2017 * Graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute 2019 *2023 Frederick Police Department Green Lab  *Repeat Offender* - YES  On 06/24/2023, at approximately 1130hours, I, Trooper Koehler #7524,was on routine patrol, conducting an abandoned vehicle check on west bound Route 50 at Beaver Dam Road, Trappe, Talbot County Maryland. I received notification from the Duty Officer to start towards the Oxford area. We had received a call, for an attempt to locate. The caller advised that they had observed a possible intoxicated driver who was driving recklessly and they were following it. The caller was advised to be in a white SUV and the suspect was advised to be operating a black dually pick-up truck and trailer. The caller advised that they were both located at 28743 Llandaff Road.   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)   I had just turned on Old Trappe Road from Route 50, heading towards Llandaff Road. I verified if the caller was still out with the possible intoxicated driver. I was advised that they were still in the area. I further requested to confirm the type of vehicle that we were attempting to locate. It was confirmed to be a black dually with trailer. At the same time, I had observed a black dually Chevy Silverado(without trailer) turning right off of Llandaff Road, onto Old Trappe Road, in front of my location. Behind the Chevy, was another white SUV, following behind. It was also confirmed that the complainant was in a white Suburban. I observed the two vehicles traveling on Old Trappe Road, toward Boh Brooks Road. The Silverado slowed, and turned left onto Boh Brooks Road. I began following the black Chevy down Boh Brooks Road, and observed the brake lights on both the passenger side and driver side rear, activate, however, the brake light located in the center, on top of the cabin of the truck, was inoperative. I also could see that the registration displayed was 8AD7339, with an expiration year displayed as 2021. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop. The vehicle came to slow, rolling stop, blocking the roadway. As soon as the vehicle, stopped, the driver, almost immediately opened the driver door and walked out, back, towards my patrol vehicle.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the driver/sole occupant, who had a staggered walk back towards me. The driver was later positively identified via hisMarylanddrivers license photograph as Charles Samuel Gale Jr(B/M, DOB: 11/26/1970). As we approached each other, Gale stated, that he didnt know why she called the police, further stating that he does tent delivery. Gale then stated that no one talked to him. Gale then stated he was followed for like a minute. Gale then stated he dropped his trailer off. Gale was advised that I was a Maryland State Trooper and the stop was being recorded. I then informed him of the reason for the stop. Gale stated he would grab the registration for me. Gale then entered the driver compartment of the vehicle by sitting on the driver seat, and reaching over into the glove compartment, on the passenger side. Gale grabbed a piece of paper and looked at it. Gale handed me several pieces of paper, all of which were not the registration for the vehicle. Gale was then asked to provide his license. Gale then stated he did not have it, indicating that it was in his other truck. I asked Gale about weapons, to which he indicated he did not have any. I asked Gale if he was headed to drop off a tent or pick one up. Gale then stated that his dad lives right down the road as he pointed in that direction. Gale was asked again about his travel itinerary, as the question was not answered. Gale then confirmed he was headed home because he was done. Gale was asked to provide the registration and proof of insurance. Gale then reached toward the center compartment grabbed something, and lifted his hands up, like he was confused. Gale then opened the center console and grabbed a registration card and then handed it to me. The registration card was for a trailer and not for the vehicle he was operating. Gale continued looking through other documents. I told Gale that the registration card he had just handed me was for a trailer. Gale then stated that he really doesnt know, because it was his fathers truck. Gale then stated he didnt know why she did that. Gale informed me that she followed him. Gale then stated that he was steady stopping because he was trying to locate an address. I then asked Gale to tell me what exactly this other female did. Gale shook his head, stating that she was real abrupt, then stating maybe because he didnt belong in her neighborhood. Gale then stated that he was just doing business. I asked Gale what she was saying. Gale then stated he didnt know what she was saying because he didnt give her time to say anything. Gale then stated that she pulled up beside him, telling him not to move.   Gale then provided me his name verbally. Gale stated, he didnt know his date  um. I told him that I would write it on the back of the card he had provided me. In the process of doing so, I asked Gale to confirm his middle name. Gale stated it was on the paper he provided. It was not. I asked him to provide it to me again. Gale stated it was S for sams. Gale then stated Sams Services. I again asked him for his middle name. Gale then got upset with me, loudly stating, Samuel!. I told Gale that I was asking him. Gale, stated, your good homie. While still confirming his middle name, Gale showed me a piece of paper, with the word, SAMS on it, stating that was his middle name and the company was named after it.   While speaking with Gale, I could detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath. Gales eyes were blood shot and his speech was slurred. I could also see initially, his drunk like walk, back towards my patrol vehicle. Gale was also up and down emotionally, at times showing relaxed inhibitions.   Gale was asked about his consumption of alcohol. Gale then stated he had a sip and that he wouldnt lie to me. Gale was then asked what exactly it was he had a sip of. Gale asked me if he was going to lose his license. I told him that I was just asking him a question. I asked him if I was allowed to talk to him. Gale informed me that was ok. Gale then stated he had a sip. Gale was asked again, what the sip was of. Gale stated, vodka.    Gale was asked, and agreed to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Gale stated, evidently, Im already and paused, looking at me. Gale stated he wasnt denying that he hadnt had nothin. Gale was asked about his license being valid. Gale state, yea, dam right, all day. Gale again informed me that he had a sip of alcohol and he was worried. Gale was then asked if he had more than one drink. Gale stated naw.   Gale was asked to step out of the vehicle and walk back to his vehicle with me. Gale did so, however, I could see, that he had a drunk-like walk, back to the rear of his vehicle with me. Gale then was observed to lean into the rear of his truck for balance, as we discussed his work.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   Gale stated that he was not sick or injured. Gale was asked about being diabetic or epileptic. Gale stated he has type two diabetes. Gale stated he had been diagnosed with type two since he was like 7. Gale stated that he doesnt take insulin. I asked Gale how he was feeling right now. Gale stated he was feeling alright. Gale interrupted, stating that he just wants to go home. Gale stated that he wasnt taking any drugs or medications. Gale had no deformities. Gale was asked about his hip issue. Gale then pulled down part of his pants, showing me a large scar on his right hip. Gale then stated that he cant walk straight or stand straight. Gale was asked about when the injury happened. Gale looked down, and thought about it for a moment. Gale then stated he wrecked a scooter about 10 years ago. Gale repeated himself, stating that he just wanted to go home and that he just wanted to get this over with. It should be noted, that Gale further advised me that he was not wearing contacts, however, he was supposed to wear glasses. Gale was asked, and stated his glasses were not in the vehicle. Gale then stated that the state of Maryland denied him his license, until he came back with his glasses. Gale then stated he was supposed to be driving with his glasses. Gale was then asked if he was near or far sighted. Gale informed me that he did not know. Gale was then asked if he had trouble seeing things far away or up close. Gale stated, that he did not know.   Prior to any testing, my overhead forward flashing lights were deactivated. The weather was overcast with minimal wind. Gale was wearing a plain gray t-shirt and blue hospital scrub pants and gray tennis shoes. While speaking with me outside of his car, directly in front of me, I could, again, smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath.     HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The red light of my penwas usedas the stimulus, and held approximately 12 inches from Gales eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Gales pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting Nystagmus. When asked, Gale stated that he understood the instructions.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Vertical Nystagmus  Present  OBSERVATION: Gale had to be reminded to follow the red light with his eyes.    WALK AND TURN (7/8 clues observed)  Prior to Gale performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Gale was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. He was instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. He was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. He was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, he was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Gale was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. He was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. After providing the instructions, Gale stated he understood. The area where testing was conducted was level, however, there were multiple loose, small rocks, scattered around. I selected an area with the least amount of loose stone, that I could see.  Instructional Stage: - Started too soon.   -Lost balance during instructional phase  Walking Stage (1st Nine): - Raised arms for balance steps 3-9.  - Stopped after taking nine steps and asked how to turn  Turn :Incorrect, failing to keep his lead foot planted on the ground.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): -Missed heel to toe on step 2, 3, and 9  -Incorrect number of steps, taking 10  -Raised arms for balance on all 10 steps    Observation: Prior to instructional phase, Gale stated that he could not do this test, again pulling part of his pants down, to show me the scar. Gale stated that he couldnt even walk a straight line when Im theres nothing wrong. Before even giving him any instructions to the test, Gale became argumentative, saying I wanted him to put up his right hip. When beginning the instructional phase, and pointing out an imaginary line in front of him, I instructed Gale to put his foot on that line. Gale, then asked, what line?. While initially maintaining the heel to toe stance, Gale was observed to raise his hands off of his sides, for balance. Gale interrupted my instructions, stating that he cant keep balance. Gale was observed to sway side to side, while attempting to maintain the instructional stance. While still providing instructions, to Gale, after the demonstration, Gale, again, interrupted me, stating that he has a replacement hip. The turn instructions had to be repeated. Gale counted out loud on the 10th step on the second nine. Gale failed to count out loud on steps 1-9 on the second nine steps. Gale appeared to be unsteady on his feet.   ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)  Prior to Gale performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Gale stated that he understood the instructions.  Instructional Stage: Remained as demonstrated  Balance and Count Stage: -swayed while standing  -put foot down after 10 seconds   -raised arms for balance   Observation: Gale raised his foot when told to begin, and almost immediately dropped it to the ground, telling me to hold on. The test was re-started.   Gale then raised the opposite foot after he dropped his foot after 10 seconds. That foot dropped almost immediately after he raised it. Gale then stated he had no balance on that side. Gale was asked if he wanted to try it one more time with the other leg. Gale then stated he couldnt stand on that leg because he was not sturdy. Gale stated he wasnt sturdy on the other leg as well.                           PBT was offered. Gale initially stated, no, when asked if he was willing to do the PBT. I confirmed, that his answer, was in fact, no. Gale stated, he told me that he had a drink and he wasnt going to lie to me. Gale was then asked to rate himself, on a scale from 1 to 10, with 1 being completely sober, and 10 being as drunk as he has ever been. Gale then asked if he was being placed under arrest, as he put his hands on his head. Gale stated, 3. Gale then stated, he had a beer. Gale was then asked again to be clear, if he was refusing the preliminary breath test. Gale then stated he wasnt refusing and if I wanted him to do it, he would do it.   PBT result - .20 Brac    ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Gale was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol  -6/6 HGN -7/8 WAT -3/4 OLS -VGN present -Poor balance and coordination during SFSTs -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from breath -Admitted to drinking alcohol prior to operating his motor vehicle -inconsistent about what exactly he had to drink -bloodshot eyes -impaired memory -emotional at times -relaxed inhibitions at times -argumentative -difficulty following instructions -drunk like walk -used vehicle for support while standing at rear of motor vehicle with me -responded with 3 as being the level of intoxication -observed to be possibly impaired, operating motor vehicle recklessly by other motorist on roadway    Due to the number of observations, I concluded Gale was driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. I placed Gale under arrest at 1155 hours. Gale was placed in handcuffs and seated in the front seat of my patrol vehicle. The owner made arrangements for the removal of the vehicle.   Gale was read aloud the DR-15 Advice of Rights form using the MVA audio file. Gale was also provided the form to read along with. Gale requested to speak with a lawyer. Gale was provided ample time and opportunity to speak with one. After having no success, Gale ultimately agreed to take the breath test at 1241 hours. Cpl. Moore #2269 conducted the breath test at 1305 hours, which found Gales breath specimen to contain an alcohol concentration of .20 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  Gales license status at the time of this incident was valid with no restrictions. A DR-15A form was completed and Gale was issued a temporary license. Gale was provided with his copies of the MVA related forms, and his traffic citations.  I spoke with the complainant over the phone, after the conclusion of the arrest. The complainant was identified as Stratton Shan Goodman (W/F, DOB: 5/1/1992). Goodman advised earlier that day she was pulling out of a driveway on Waverly Road, in Easton, Talbot County Maryland. She observed a black dually Cheverolet pick up truck and trailer traveling behind her. Goodman became concerned when she observed the truck, driving all over the road, like a ping pong back and forth. Goodman stated she had pulled over, into the left lane, allowing the truck to pass her. Goodman stated that the truck then stopped right next to her. Goodman stayed in her vehicle, rolled down her passenger side door window and made contact with the operator of the truck. Goodman stated that the operator was looking for Route 50. Goodman stated that the operator had slurred speech, had the hiccups, looked distressed, lost and confused, and dramatic. Goodman stated that she was approximately 8 feet away from the operator of the truck and was unable to smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage. Goodman provided the operator with directions on how to get to Route 50. Goodman asked the operator of the truck if he was drunk. The operator got upset and began driving away, down Waverly Road, towards Peach Blossom Road. Goodman began following the vehicle and contacted police. Goodman stated that the truck was traveling south on Peach Blossom Road, toward Llandaff Road. Goodman approximated the speed of the vehicle being 70 mph at this point. Goodman also confirmed that the trucks travel was still reckless, as it was observed to be driving on shoulder, in and out of the roadway and on grass at times, from Waverly Road, all the way to Llandaff Road. Goodman advised that there were two other occupants in her vehicle that witnessed the incident as well and later identified as Shari Wilcoxon and Evan Cocke. Goodman was able to provide me with photographs of the truck and trailer that she observed operating recklessly on the roadway. A video was also taken of the reckless operation. Goodman confirmed that the person she observed operating the black Chevrolet dually truck was Gale Jr. The video was sent to me via email, by Goodman and subsequently copied on a CD. The CD was placed in a completed property envelope and submitted with an attached MSP #67 chain of custody form. The photographs were uploaded in attachment section of this report.  Gale was issued the following traffic citations: driving vehicle under the influence of alcohol, driving vehicle while impaired by alcohol, driving under the influence of alcohol per se, negligent driving, reckless driving, failure to display license on to officer on demand, failure to display registration card on demand, displaying expired registration plate, and one repair order for the vehicles brake light. A sober driver responded to the barrack and took control of Gale with no further incident.  All events occurred in Talbot County, Maryland.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: .20</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 15:02:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/26/2023 08:56:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Caraballo</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5793</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Moore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2269</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Koehler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7524</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>512139</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/24/2023 11:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 10:54:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/25/2023 10:54:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 10:57:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:19</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>380830</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Goodman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stratton</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/01/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 10:56:50</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G355</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S363</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Goodman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stratton</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/01/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G355</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S363</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 10:56:50</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>27991</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Waverly</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Easton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>786</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6559</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 10:57:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>64</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 12:41:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:54</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>380831</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Wilcoxon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shari</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Simpson</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/15/1959 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 12:41:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W422</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Wilcoxon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shari</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Simpson</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/15/1959 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W422</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 12:41:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>27991</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Waverly</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Easton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>310</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4669</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 12:41:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 12:46:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:13</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>380832</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cocke</LastName>
               <FirstName>Evan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>James</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/17/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 12:45:53</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cocke</LastName>
               <FirstName>Evan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>James</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/17/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 12:45:53</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>59</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Battersea Bridge</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Lutherville-Timonium</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21093</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>703</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>200</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1125</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 12:46:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:17</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>52</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 12:47:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:54</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>295965</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Gale</LastName>
               <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Samuel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/26/1970 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>01/30/2021 21:15:52</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Gale</LastName>
               <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Samuel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/26/1970 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>G400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/30/2021 21:15:52</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6345</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Trappe</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21673</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.066014</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.723507</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 12:56:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 12:56:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 10:54:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/25/2023 10:54:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154548</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/26/2023 06:53:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/26/2023 06:53:50</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1GCJK33121F173182</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2001</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SLV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8AD7339</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2022</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>