<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-005590</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>98</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/13/2023 08:49:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/13/2023 08:49:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/13/2023 08:49:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/13/2023 08:49:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>MD Automotive Dismantler and Recycler failure to keep records as required - Tremendos Pick and Pay</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 08:49:14</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1456</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 10:08:32</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>West of intersection</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>22752</AddressId>
      <City>MDC216</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 08:49:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/28/2023 13:03:28</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>22752</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>21891</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Dover Bridge</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Preston</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21655</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.947492</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.745539</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/13/2023 08:49:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/13/2023 08:49:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>98</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/07/2023 09:59:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 08:49:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP1456</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 09:59:58</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23-MSP-005590 RAPID Compliance Inspection / Automotive Dismantler Recycler (ADR) - Tremendo Pick and Pay  ATTACHMENTS: MSP 245A, MARYLAND STATE POLICE Automotive Dismantler/Recycler Transportation Article, Title 15, Electronic Audit form               MSP 245B, MARYLAND STATE POLICE Automotive Dismantler/Recycler Transportation Article, Title 15, Inspection Form               20 Photographs of vehicles               RAPID Transaction Reports               Copy of ETIX Citation and Warnings   This investigation began on Friday, February 10, 2023, at approximately 1000 hours, when I, Cpl. Jean L. Davenport #4718, MSP PCSD/RAPID Compliance Officer, was in the area of Dover Bridge Road in Preston, and observed a white flat bed tow truck with the name of Tremendo on the drivers side door, and the tow truck was transporting and towing two (2) vehicles. On the flatbed was a brown colored GMC SUV and on the tow dolly pulled behind the tow truck was a silver Honda passenger vehicle. I followed this tow truck into the lot of Tremendos Pick and Pay, 21891 Dover Bridge Road, Preston, Caroline County, MD 21655, and took a cell phone photo of the vehicles (attached to report). The Honda had a partial tag bracket and a round emblem on the back. The GMC had a sticker in the lower seven (7) inches of the left corner of the rear window.   On Wednesday, February 15, 2023, I accessed the Regional Automated Property Information Database (RAPID) and ran a 14-day transaction report (attached) for this shop, revealing the two (2) vehicles observed going into the lot on February 10, 2023, had not been entered into RAPID as required. Transportation Article 15 requires the vehicles to be entered into RAPID by the end of the next business day. I further conducted a search of all Tremendo Pick and Pay Transactions beginning with their first entry in August 2022, and no entries were listed matching the above vehicles.I contacted Caroline County Sheriffs Office RAPID Administrators to see if there were any reporting trends for this shop with negative results.   On Monday, February 27, 2023, at approximately 1245 hours, I drove to Tremendos Pick and Pay in Preston, MD, and met with employee Aileen who advised she was the only one there at the time and other employees had gone to lunch. I asked Aileen to produce the paperwork for the two (2) vehicles taken in on February 10, 2023. She went to the back office and came back with one (1) title for a Mitsubishi vehicle and advised that was the only one from February 10th. She then called the owner, Samuel Plata, on her cell phone and placed him on speaker for me to talk with Samuel. Samuel advised he was in Washington DC and was not available until tomorrow.   Aileen directed me to an area in the back lot where the GMC make/model vehicles were located and pointed to the brown GMC Arcadia at the open end of the row. I also located the silver Honda Accord at the open end of the row of Honda make/model vehicles. I took pictures of the vehicles and uploaded them to this report.     On the brown GMC Arcadia SUV, I observed the engine and front end of the vehicle had been removed, and the vehicles front frame was resting on two (2) old tire rims. I observed on the glass of the back window of the brown GMC, two (2) decals in the lower left corner, matching the description of the vehicle observed going into the lot on February 10, 2023. On the front windshield glass, I located two (2) Inspection Stickers indicating the vehicle may be registered in the state of Pennsylvania. On the inside of the drivers side door, I located VIN 1GKEV13757J159675, and ran a wanted check on the VIN to see if the vehicle had been reported stolen with negative results.    On the back of the silver Honda Accord passenger vehicle, I observed a partial tag bracket with part of an orange MD Agriculture metal license plate protruding from under the tag bracket, and two (2) stickers; one to the right of the license plate indent and one on the top left area of the trunk. The make, model, color, partial license plate bracket and the round emblem located to the right of the tag, are consistent with the vehicle that was observed going into the lot on February 10, 2023. On the dash, behind the windshield and on the inside of the drivers side door, I located VIN 1HGCP26878A014244. I ran a wanted check on this vehicle to see if the vehicle had been reported stolen with negative results. The vehicle registration check for this VIN indicated MD license plate tags A085963, were last registered on this vehicle and both plates returned to MVA due to Title Transfer on September 22, 2021. The vehicle registration was in the name of Jamahl Anthony Dukes, and the tags were flagged as suspended on February 3, 2023.   While in the back lot, I observed crushed vehicle off to the right and the crushed vehicle were stacked more than two (2) vehicles high. I took a photograph and uploaded to report of a pile of vehicle appearing to be three (3) and possibly four (4) crushed vehicles high. This is in violation of Transportation Article 15-513(b) for crushed vehicle storage density limits.   I also observed a large amount of un-crushed vehicle spread out throughout the property (see attached photos). Transportation Article 15-513 (a) allows for no more than 250 un-crushed vehicle storage density limits per acre of land.Since setting up the business in July 2022 (see MSP Dealer Set Up report 22-MSP-028023), the vehicle inventory has grown extensively, and it is possible Tremendos may be exceeding theamount of vehicles per acre. I counted 90 vehicles just in the front left area of the lot. And the make shift vehicle lifts and tire rim jacks used to remove parts from the vehicles appears to be a MOSHA violation (see attached photos).    Aileen then stated that Samuel sent her a picture of the GMC Arcadia Title to her cell phone and indicated he had the title with him in DC. When I left the shop at approximately 1330 hours, the shop was not able to locate the title or paperwork for the acquisition of the Honda and the GMC vehicles. This is a violation of Transportation Article15-509 (h) relating to notification, reporting, and document retention requirements.     I then emailed Maryland Department of Transportation inspectors reference the observed violations. I also spoke on the phone (410-819-5860) with a representative of Maryland Occupational Safety and Health Association (MOSHA) Easton Office, Karl Owens (karl.owens@maryland.gov), who advised unless I observed an employee under the suspended vehicles, there wasnt anything they could enforce. He explained there is no enforcement action they could take if a customer was accessing and removing parts from under the vehicles.    On Tuesday, February 28, 2023, at approximately 1330 hours, I received a call from Samuel Plata who explained the documents for the vehicles were in his tow truck, and it was totally his fault that he forgot to give them to the employee who enters them into RAPID. He stated he was having issues with his tow truck that day and machines breaking down. He stated would have the paperwork relayed to the shop today and the vehicles would be entered into RAPID immediately. I then text him a copy of the Dealer Set Up Inspection List to provide him further guidance.   On Wednesday, March 1, 2023, I conducted an on-line search of RAPID and found the GMC Acadia had been entered into RAPID, however, the transaction was still missing tow vehicle information. At approximately 1230 hours, I drove to Tremendos and met Samuel and conducted an on-site inspection and educational visit. Using MSP 245B Inspection Form (copy attached to report), I reviewed with Samuel and employee Aileen, the License Regulations and Records Requirements. I also reviewed their hard copy of the Title and paperwork associated with the GMC purchase and the paperwork was completed to my satisfaction.   Samuel stated the green MDOT stickers for vehicle inventory was not being currently used, and the stickers were coming from the other shop in PG County.   Samuel stated there was an issue with the Honda Accord and when his driver went to pick up the vehicle, the female seller did not have the title, only the vehicle registration which was in another name. Samuel stated they dont take vehicles without titles and this vehicle was going to be returned to the seller and/or registered owner.   I issued an ETIX citation to Samuel for TA 15-509(h), Failure of Auto Dismantler/Recycler to Comply with Reporting Documents and Retention Required (Citation Number 1790KHZ). I also issued three (3) ETIX warnings for associated violations.    Case closed. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4718</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 10:28:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4718</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/02/2023 09:39:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>98</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Haas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jesse</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1456</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>98</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davenport</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4718</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494985</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17767</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>48</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/01/2023 14:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>ETIX for TA Title 15 </Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17767</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4718</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 10:24:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4718</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/01/2023 14:21:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494985</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>07</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16808</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>48</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/13/2023 08:49:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>crushed vehicle stacked more than 2 high</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16808</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4718</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 10:10:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4718</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/01/2023 14:22:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494985</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>07</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16805</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>48</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/01/2023 14:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>Etix issued for TA Title 15 </Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16805</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4718</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 10:12:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4718</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/01/2023 14:21:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494985</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>07</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16802</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>48</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/01/2023 09:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>ETIX warning</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16802</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4718</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/02/2023 09:43:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4718</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/02/2023 09:43:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4718</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 10:25:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:19</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>349924</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Plata</LastName>
               <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Orlando</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/22/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/20/2022 12:23:30</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Plata</LastName>
               <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Orlando</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/22/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/20/2022 12:23:30</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>13</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Vale</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Capitol Heights</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20743</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.9078874</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.8864821</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>498</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1542</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/20/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4718</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 10:27:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4718</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 10:27:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150382</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4718</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:25:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4718</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/28/2023 13:25:01</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1GKEV13757J159675</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2007</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ACA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>TO</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BRO</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>PA</VehicleLicStateCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150383</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4718</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 13:25:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4718</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/28/2023 13:25:55</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/28/2023 13:24:17</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1HGCP26878A014244</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2008</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ACC</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>CP</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>