<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-015445</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/01/2023 02:38:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/01/2023 02:38:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/01/2023 01:26:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/01/2023 01:26:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI arrest of Jorge Diaz-Perez.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/01/2023 02:38:39</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 06:42:57</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>20999</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/01/2023 02:38:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 04:39:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>20999</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1500</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Market</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Pocomoke City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21851</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.552778</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.064318</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>POCOMOKE PD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/01/2023 02:38:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/01/2023 02:38:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/20/2023 19:06:18</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/01/2023 02:38:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:52:31</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Jorge Diaz-Perez No Drivers License Breath Test Result: Refusal DWI Citation #: 4MB0J79 DWI MVR/Body Cam #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-015445 (Axon View XL Software).   TROOPER CERTIFICATES / TRAINING / SPECIAL ASSIGNMENTS  1. Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. 2. Certified SFST Instructor. 3. Chemical Breath Test Operator. 4. Graduate of the University of Marylands DUI Institute. 5. Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. 6. Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.). 7. Trained in Cannabis Impairment Detection (Maryland State Police). 8. Assigned to the Berlin Barrack V Special Enforcement Team (focusing exclusively on DUI enforcement) from October 2017 - June 2022.   NARRATIVE   -PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION-  I did not observe the vehicle in motion. The traffic stop was conducted by Patrolman White #0170 of the Pocomoke City Police Department on 05-01-2023 at approximately 0119 hours. The traffic stop was conducted on U.S. Route 13 northbound near Brantley Road, and the driver was placed under arrest for traffic charges. Corporal A. Rhode #0171 contacted the Berlin Barrack for assistance with the driver (a Hispanic male) due to a language barrier. Corporal Rhode believed the driver had also been driving the vehicle while under the influence of alcohol, but the driver did not speak English and no accurate information could be obtained from him. I responded to the Pocomoke City Police Department (1500 Market Street) at approximately 0127 hours from the northern part of the County.   -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT-   Prior to contact with the driver, I was informed of the following:  Patrolman White conducted a traffic stop on an orange 2006 Chevrolet Cobalt bearing Virginia registration 7643BBL for a speed violation (93 MPH in a posted 55 MPH zone). The driver advised he did not have a drivers license. One (1) open 12-ounce Heineken beer and one (1) open 32-ounce Modelo beer were observed in plain view on the floorboard of the vehicle. The driver was placed under arrest and subsequently transported to the Pocomoke City Police Department for processing.  I made contact with the driver at approximately 0209 hours. All communication with the driver was done in the Spanish language. I am a native Spanish speaker and also hold a minor in Spanish from Troy University. I asked the Hispanic male where he was from originally, and he replied: Guatemala. I asked the driver if he understood the reason why he had been stopped, and he responded: I was driving a little fast over the speed limit. I asked the driver if he possessed a current and valid drivers license, and he stated: No.  At this time, I identified myself as Trooper Ruiz with the Maryland State Police and advised the driver that our interaction was being audibly and visually recorded. The driver was identified by his name and date of birth as Jorge Perez-Diaz (DOB: 04-24-1999). Perez-Diaz had no form of identification on his person. I asked Perez-Diaz where he had been traveling from, and he responded: From Virginia to Maryland. To Princess [Anne], to visit a friend. I asked Perez-Diaz how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed earlier in the evening, and he replied: 3. I asked Perez-Diaz what kind of alcoholic beverages had he consumed, and he advised: Modelo. When asked at approximately what time had he finished consuming his last drink prior to driving, Perez-Diaz stated: Like at 11.   As Perez-Diaz spoke, I made the following observations:  1. I intentionally observed his eyes to be glassy and bloodshot.  2. I smelled the distinct and strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person as he interacted with me.   I informed Perez-Diaz that I wanted him to perform field sobriety tests which he agreed to submit to.   -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING-  STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)  The evaluation was performed in the Processing Room of the Pocomoke Police Department. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of overhead lighting. I asked Perez-Diaz if he had any significant medical issues with his eyes, arms, or legs which would prevent him from performing the field sobriety tests or if he had taken any medication prior to driving. Perez-Diaz responded: When the sun is bright, I cant see and No. Perez-Diaz appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries, limps, or any limb ailments.  Diaz-Perez was wearing a black tank top, black jeans, and gray socks.   **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**  1. Diaz-Perez displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  2. Diaz-Perez displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  3. Diaz-Perez displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.    **WALK AND TURN: 5 of 8 clues**  1. Diaz-Perez could not maintain his balance during the Instruction Phase. Diaz-Perezs feet broke from the start position on three (3) occasions, and he stumbled to his right each time.  2. Diaz-Perez missed heel-to-toe on ALL steps during both series. All misses were of more than half an inch.  3. Diaz-Perez stopped walking after the first series. I had to prompt Diaz-Perez to continue the test as instructed.  4. Diaz-Perez did not complete the turn in a satisfactory manner, turning to his right which was contrary to my instructions.  5. Diaz-Perez was unable to maintain a straight line and stepped off the line on steps 1 an 9 during the second series.   **ONE LEG STAND: 0 of 4 clues**   ADDITIONAL ANNOTATIONS REFERENCE FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS  Walk And Turn (WAT):  A. The floor tile joints were used as a straight line for this test.  One Leg Stand (OLS):  A. At no point during this test did Diaz-Perez look down at his raised foot as instructed. Instead, he looked at me. B. Diaz-Perez did not starting counting until second 18, which was contrary to my instructions.   PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)  After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Diaz-Perez the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Diaz-Perez submitted to a preliminary breath test with a reading of 0.16 BrAC.   ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Diaz-Perez was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Driving vehicle in a negligent manner as described by Patrolman White #0170  DRIVING SKILLS IMPAIRED. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot. * Admission to consuming more than one (1) alcoholic beverage prior to operating a motor vehicle. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests. * PBT result of 0.16 BrAC.  I determined that Diaz-Perez was impaired by the presence of an alcoholic beverage in his system that adversely affected his ability to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests properly can also adversely affect the persons ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. I placed Diaz-Perez under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0225 hours on 05-01-2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Diaz-Perezs mouth for any foreign objects and none were found.    ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)  Diaz-Perez was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Diaz-Perez was given his Advice of Rights via the SPANISH audio version of the DR-15 Form (played through the patrol vehicles Bluetooth speakers). At the conclusion of the audio version, I verbally re-explained the drivers license sanctions and penalties (section printed in red) to Diaz-Perez. Diaz-Perez stated that he understood his Advice of Rights and refused to submit to a breath test at approximately 0258 hours on 05-01-2023.   TRANSPORT / RELEASE  Diaz-Perez was subsequently transported to a friends residence (30515 Hickory Road, Apt #1, Princess Anne). During transport, the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Diaz-Perez continued to be strong. Diaz-Perez was released to a sober person at approximately 0358 hours on 05-01-2023.   CHARGES  Diaz-Perez was charged with the following citations:  1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (4MB0J79) 2. Driving Vehicle While Impaired By Alcohol (4MC0J79)   Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/08/2023 07:32:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/16/2023 17:29:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Drew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504864</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>11</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/03/2023 04:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:39:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 04:40:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504864</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>11</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/03/2023 04:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:39:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 04:41:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:39:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375984</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Diaz-Perez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jorge</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/24/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/03/2023 04:06:05</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D216</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Diaz-Perez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jorge</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/24/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D216</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/03/2023 04:06:05</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>16150</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Lankford</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>BOX</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>202</SubNumber>
               <City>Bloxom</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>23308</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.58864</Longitude>
               <Latitude>37.819187</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:41:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:41:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:39:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 04:39:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>