<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-020995</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/11/2023 23:28:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/11/2023 23:28:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/11/2023 23:08:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/11/2023 23:08:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI arrest of Tina Marie Husak.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 23:28:37</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/15/2023 05:01:17</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN EXPY/ RACETRACK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 23:28:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 18:23:54</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>EXPY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.170578</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.38053</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 E/O 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB/ 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 PRIOR 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MERGING OFF OF 90 INTO OCEAN PINES</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB BETWEEN BRIDGE AND OCEAN PINES EXIT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB PAST 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11083-11086 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1296-1352 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/11/2023 23:28:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/11/2023 23:28:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/15/2023 04:56:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 23:28:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:01</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Tina Marie Husak [SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER] Arizona SOUNDEX: D03973397 Breath Test Result: Refusal DWI Citation #: 4PC0J79 DWI MVR/Body Cam #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-020995 (Axon View XL Software).   TROOPER CERTIFICATES / TRAINING / SPECIAL ASSIGNMENTS  1. Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. 2. Certified SFST Instructor. 3. Chemical Breath Test Operator. 4. Graduate of the University of Marylands DUI Institute. 5. Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. 6. Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.). 7. Trained in Cannabis Impairment Detection (Maryland State Police). 8. Assigned to the Berlin Barrack V Special Enforcement Team (focusing exclusively on DUI enforcement) from October 2017 - June 2022.   NARRATIVE   -PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION  On 06-11-2023 at approximately 2308 hours, I (Corporal J. Ruiz #6312), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating marked MSP vehicle V-15 in the area of Maryland Route 90 eastbound, just west of Coastal Highway (Ocean City). I was stationary on the right shoulder area, monitoring all westbound traffic. At that time, I observed a silver sedan traveling westbound pass my location. I made the following observations on the same vehicle:   APPROACHING THE ASSAWOMAN BAY BRIDGE  1. The vehicles right headlamp was not illuminated.   ASSAWOMAN BAY BRIDGE  2. From the side mirror of my patrol vehicle, I could see the vehicles left tires were directly on top of the solid yellow center double line on one (1) occasion. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane.   I safely entered the roadway and closed in on the same vehicle while still on the Assawoman Bay Bridge.   AT ST. MARTINS NECK ROAD  3. The vehicles right tires were directly on top of the solid white shoulder line on one (1) occasion. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane.   ST. MARTIN RIVER BRIDGE  4. The same sedan began following an SUV too closely (less than 1 car length in between vehicles). The vehicle would increase its speed, follow the SUV too closely for several feet, then decrease its speed.   NEAR MILE MARKER 8  5. The vehicle again increased its speed, followed the SUV too closely for several feet, then decreased its speed.   PRIOR TO THE MARYLAND ROUTE 589 EXIT  6. The vehicle again increased its speed, followed the SUV too closely for several feet, then decreased its speed.   ADDITIONAL OBSERVATIONS   7. The vehicle failed to maintain proper lane position due to pronounced and excessive weaving (alternately moving toward one side of the lane and then the other) during the entire duration of my observations.  8. Total distance traveled was approximately 4.83 miles.    DWI INDICATORS / REASON FOR STOP  The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHSTA) published a The Visual Detection of DWI Motorists booklet in March 2010. The research revealed that DWI cues related to problems in maintaining proper lane position include:  1. Weaving 2. Weaving across lane lines 3. Drifting  4. Varying speeds 5. Following too closely  All of the above DWI indicators were exhibited by the silver sedan prior to my initiating a traffic stop on the same vehicle.   TRAFFIC STOP  I activated the emergency lights to my patrol vehicle, initiating a traffic stop on MD Route 90 westbound at the MD Route 589 exit. The vehicle was a silver 2003 Acura 3.2TL bearing Maryland Registration 4EG6479.   -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT  I made contact with the driver via the driver side door, and I immediately smelled the faint odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop and requested the drivers license and the registration card to the vehicle. The driver immediately stated: Are you kidding me? The driver appeared to have difficulty presenting her documents to me, as she struggled to locate them throughout the car and her purse. The driver was identified as Tina Marie Husak by her Arizona drivers license. I asked Husak where she was traveling from, and she responded: Work. Dead Freddies. I asked Husak how much she had to drink earlier in the evening, and she replied: I havent been drinking.    As Husak spoke, I made the following observations:  1. I intentionally observed her eyes to be glassy and bloodshot.  2. Husak displayed a glazed look/expression on her face as she interacted with me.  3. When asked about how much she had to drink earlier in the evening, Husak would not make eye contact with me as she answered.  4. When asked why there would be any reason for me detecting the odor of alcoholic beverage from inside the vehicle, Husak responded: No, not that I can think of.   I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Husak.   I later returned to the Acura and requested Husak exit the vehicle and walk to the front of it, to which she complied. While at the front of the vehicle, I continued to speak with Husak. I asked Husak again where she was traveling from, and she stated: Dead Freddies. Husak advised that she was a hostess at the restaurant.  During my second interaction with Husak, I observed the following:  1. When asked how many total alcoholic beverages had she consumed prior to driving, Husak replied: Nothing.  2. As Husak spoke, I smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. I informed Husak that  based on her driving and the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle  I wanted her to perform field sobriety tests which she agreed to submit to.    -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING  STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder area. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and vehicle headlamp. Weather was clear and approximately 67 degrees. I asked Husak if she had any significant medical issues with her eyes, arms, or legs which would prevent her from performing the field sobriety tests or if she had taken any medication prior to driving. Husak responded: No. Husak advised that the glasses she was wearing were not prescription eyeglasses. Husak appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries, limps, or any limb ailments.  Husak was wearing a black long sleeve casual shirt, gray leggings, and black athletic-type shoes.   **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**   1. Husak displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.   2. Husak displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  3. Husak displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.   **WALK AND TURN: 6 of 8 clues**  1. Husak could not maintain her balance during the Instruction Phase. Husaks feet broke from the start position on two (2) occasions, and she stumbled to her right each time.  2. Husak missed heel-to-toe on step 2 during the first series. Husak missed heel-to-toe on step 1 during the second series. All misses were of more than half an inch.   3. Husak raised her arms for balance (higher than 6 to her sides) during both series.   4. Husak stopped walking after the first series, which was contrary to my instructions. I had to prompt Husak to continue the test as instructed.  5. Husak did not complete the turn in a satisfactory manner, turning to the right and losing her balance which was contrary to my instructions.  6. Husak was unable to maintain a straight line and stepped off the line on all steps during both series.    **ONE LEG STAND: 3 of 4 clues**  1. Husaks body swayed to the left and right on counts 13, 16, and 23.  2. Husak put her left foot down on counts 1 and 13.  3. Husak raised her arms for balance (higher than 6 to her sides) on counts 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, and 16.   ADDITIONAL ANNOTATIONS REFERENCE FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS // ADDITIONAL TESTING  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN):  A. Husak removed her glasses for this test only at my request. B. Husak displayed vertical nystagmus. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus is an involuntary jerking of the eyes (up and down) which occurs when the eyes gaze upward at maximum elevation. The presence of this type of nystagmus is associated with high doses of alcohol for that individual and certain other drugs.  Walk And Turn (WAT):  A. Husaks body swayed to the left and right during the Instruction Phase of the test. B. Husak did not count her steps out loud during the second series, which was contrary to my instructions.  One Leg Stand (OLS):  A. Husak placed her hands on her hips during counts 5 to 9, which was contrary to my instructions. B. At no point during this test did Husak look down at her raised left foot as instructed. Instead, she looked directly out in front of her.   **ALPHABET TEST**:  Husak advised that she was a high school graduate and that she was capable of reciting the English alphabet and numbers. I instructed Husak to recite from the letter F to the letter S.   -Completed satisfactorily.   **COUNT TEST**:  I instructed Husak to count backwards from 36-19.  -Husak counted down to 14. When asked if she could remember at what number she had been instructed to stop at, Husak replied: No.   PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)  After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Husak the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Husak submitted to a PBT with a reading of 0.174 BrAC.    ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Husak was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Driving vehicle in a negligent manner which caused it to commit 2 lane violations in addition to following another vehicle too closely and excessive weaving  DRIVING SKILLS IMPAIRED. * Faint odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot. * Glazed look/expression on face. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. * My observed signs of impairment as she performed field sobriety tests.  * PBT result of 0.174 BrAC.  I determined that Husak was impaired by the presence of an alcoholic beverage in her system that adversely affected her ability to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests properly can also adversely affect the persons ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. I placed Husak under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 2327 hours on 06-11-2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Husaks mouth for any foreign objects and none were found.    ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)  Husak was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. While explaining what the DR-15 Form was, Husak became highly agitated and freely uttered in a loud tone: I am not cooperating with you. I just was fucking going home from work. Husak then told me to put the DR-15 Form away. I was originally going play the audio version of the DR-15 to Husak. Husak demanded I read it to her. I read the DR-15 Form to Husak verbatim. Husak refused to submit to a breath test at approximately 2345 hours on 06-11-2023.   PROCESSING  All processing occurred in my patrol vehicle. During all aspects of processing (completion of the DR-15A Form and issuance of traffic citations), the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Husak continued to be strong. When asked to sign the DR-15 and DR-15A Forms, Husak made an exaggerated X on each form as her signature. As I handed all paperwork to Husak, she snatched it from my hand. Husak then balled up the paperwork like trash and placed it inside her purse.   RELEASE  Husak was subsequently transported to her residence (9504 Peerless Road, Bishopville). Husak was released at approximately 0012 hours on 06-12-2023.   SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER DETAILS  A check of the E-tix system revealed that Husak was previously charged with DUI on two (2) occasions:  1. 10-30-2020 (Baltimore County  accident related)  2. 01-14-2022 (Worcester County)   CHARGES  Husak was charged with the following citations:  1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (4PB0J79) 2. Driving Vehicle While Impaired By Alcohol (4PC0J79) 3. Failure To Display Two Lighted Front Lamps (4PD0J79) 4. Failure To Obey Traffic Control Device (4PF0J79) 5. Following Too Close (4PG0J79) 6. Negligent Driving (4PH0J79)   Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 18:39:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 20:58:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510430</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/13/2023 18:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 18:23:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 18:26:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510430</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15566</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/13/2023 18:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15566</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 18:23:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 18:26:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510430</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/13/2023 18:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 18:23:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 18:26:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510430</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/13/2023 18:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 18:23:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 18:25:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510430</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/13/2023 18:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 18:23:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 18:25:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510430</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17088</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/13/2023 18:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17088</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 18:23:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 18:27:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>54</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 18:23:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>379637</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Husak</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tina</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/05/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/12/2023 19:56:20</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H220</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Husak</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tina</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/05/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H220</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/12/2023 19:56:20</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9504</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Peerless</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Bishopville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.239203</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.412023</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>541</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>261</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7287</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/12/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 18:28:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 18:28:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 18:23:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 18:23:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154060</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 18:29:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 18:29:14</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/12/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>19UUA56603A009370</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2003</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>ACUR</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ATL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4EG6479</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>8</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>