<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-031762</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/10/2023 03:39:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/10/2023 03:39:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/10/2023 03:21:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/10/2023 03:21:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>SULLIVAN "R" 23-489.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/10/2023 03:39:44</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:21:54</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>25 MM BALTIMORE BELTWAY INNER LOOP EB, LUTHERVILLE TIMONIUM</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>706470</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/10/2023 03:39:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 11:11:34</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>706470</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>25</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm Baltimore Beltway Inner</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>LOOP</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.62432485</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.4146092666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/10/2023 03:39:41</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/10/2023 03:39:41</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/06/2023 20:21:54</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/10/2023 03:39:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E) TEAM* MVR Statement: The following incident was captured on in-car camera. Title: SULLIVANR 23-489. ID: 23-MSP- 031762 Arrested: Sullivan 3rd, Daniel Joseph. Certification and training  -Trained in Field Sobriety Test through Maryland State Police Academy.  -Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E)  -Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  - Graduated from The Institute of Advanced Law Enforcement Studies Driving Under the Influence Institute-University of Maryland.  - I am a certified EC/IR II Intoximeter operator.  - I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor.  - I have apprehended more than 250 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On September 10, 2023, at approximately 0317 hours, I, TFC. I. Riba Tankari # 7058 with Maryland State Police was traveling inner loop I-695 west of I-83 south, Baltimore County, Maryland in lane #3 (right lane). My issued patrol vehicle is Maryland State Police unmarked unit DUI-6. At that time, I observed a black Ford Mustang bearing Maryland registration 4DJ6309 traveling inner loop I 695 in lane #1 (left lane) passed my patrol vehicle and appeared to be traveling over the posted speed limit then changed lane into lane #2 (middle lane). I followed the Ford and observed the vehicle was unable to stay within a single. I observed the Ford had swerved from lane #2 into lane #3 by one tire width on two separate occasions and by more than one tire width on one occasion. I observed the Ford had swerved from lane #2 into lane #1 by half vehicle width on one occasion. I continued to follow the Ford and with my properly functioning patrol vehicle Golden Eagle II radar unit set activated, I obtained a speed reading of 81 in a posted 55 MPH zone. I again observed the Ford had crossed the dotted white line from lane #2 into lane #3 on two separate occasions. I initiated a traffic stop on the Ford using my emergency equipment. The Ford came to stop in the area of Inner loop I-695 and west of York Road, Towson, Maryland on the right shoulder. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the Ford on the driver side and made contact with the driver (the sole occupant) of the vehicle. I introduced myself and explained to him the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver where he was coming from, and he stated from the City. I asked the driver where he was heading, and he stated going back to my house. I requested his drivers license and registration card. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle I observed that the driver had glassy eyes. The driver was identified through his Maryland drivers license as Sullivan 3rd, Daniel Joseph. I returned to my patrol vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with. I returned to the Ford and I requested Sullivan to exit his vehicle and to walk to the front of his vehicle and he complied. While outside his vehicle, Sullivan stated can I just admit, I shouldnt be driving, I thought I was good and then when I was driving I was like, I shouldnt be, I thought I was good, but then when I was driving, how you pulled me over, I know. Im not. I asked Sullivan how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed, and he stated around six, seven beers, I asked him what kind of beer, and he stated Seltzers. I asked him is that a bottle, cup or can, and he stated can. I asked around what time, and he stated nine PM. While speaking with Sullivan outside his vehicle, I again detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I asked Sullivan to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and he agreed. The evaluation surface was dry, flat, and free of debris. No surface defects were observed. My patrol flashlight, overhead lamps, and his vehicle headlights lit the area. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Sullivan appeared to be in good physical conditions. I asked Sullivan the following questions: Medical conditions: Im dyslexic, no serious medical issues. Medications: No. Anything that will prevent you from walking on straight line or standing on one leg: No Glasses or contact: No. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: (6/6 clues observed). The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus - Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes - Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes - Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Notes: * During the HGN test, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Sullivans breath. WALK AND TURN: (4/8 clues observed). The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Sullivan stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage: Sullivan lost his balance to the right on four separate occasions. Sullivan started too soon on two separate occasions. Walking Stage (1st Nine): Stepped completely offline by one shoe width on count 7 and 9. Turn: The turn was not completed correctly; instead Sullivan turned to his right failing to take a series of small steps as instructed and demonstrated. Walking Stage (2nd Nine): Stepped completely offline by one shoe width on count 1 and 7 One Leg Stand Test (2/4 observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Sullivan stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Left foot raised during the test. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: Swayed body to the right and left. Seconds 11-20: Swayed body to the right and left. Seconds 21-30: Swayed body to the right and left. Raised right arm more than six (6) inches from his side for balance. Preliminary Breath Test:  I explained and offered a PBT to Sullivan. Sullivan elected to consent to the PBT and results were .10 BAC. ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Sullivan was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a motor vehicle safely:  -Unable to stay within a single lane/driving patterns.  -Driving over the posted speed limit (81 Mph in 55 Mph speed limit zone)  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath as he conversed with me.  -Eyes glassy.  -His admissions to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to driving.  -Observed signs of impairment as he performed the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  - Preliminary Breath Test result of .10 BrAC.  Sullivan was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a motor vehicle at 0341 hours and was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack. A search incident to arrest revealed no weapons or contraband. Upon arrival in the Barrack, Sullivan was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and it was read to him from the MVA website in English. Prior to making decision, Sullivan requested to call his attorney and I agreed. Sullivan attempted to reach his attorney and was unable to reach his attorney. After failing to reach his attorney, Sullivan called his friend who he claimed is also an attorney. Sullivan refused to consent to the Intoximeter EC/IR II test at 0438 hours. A properly functioning instrument and operator were available. Sullivan was polite and cooperative during the encounter.  Sullivan was given pertinent paperwork, released from the Barrack to his grandmother pending an appearance in the District Court of Maryland for Baltimore County at a later date.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 11:17:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 23:15:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>521214</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/10/2023 03:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 11:12:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 11:14:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 11:12:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 11:15:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>387714</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>SULLIVAN</LastName>
               <FirstName>DANIEL</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>JOSEPH</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/03/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>09/13/2023 11:03:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S415</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>SULLIVAN</LastName>
               <FirstName>DANIEL</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>JOSEPH</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/03/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>S415</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/13/2023 11:03:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2102</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hammond</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Marriottsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21104</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1137</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.923275</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.384716</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>865</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5142</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 11:15:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 11:15:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 11:15:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 11:13:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 11:13:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157060</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 11:16:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 11:16:48</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FA6P8CF9J5107451</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2018</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MUS</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4DJ6309</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleValue>1000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>