<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-034819</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/04/2023 11:10:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/04/2023 11:10:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/04/2023 11:09:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/04/2023 11:09:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Members of the Firearms Enforcement Unit were contacted by the D/Sgt. Johnson of the Maryland State Police Berlin Barracks "V" in reference to a prohibited person in possession of firearms. D/Sgt. Johnson advised that Fidelia Ann Kurtz (White/Female: 11/23/1989) was convicted of DUI and possession of a firearm. A court order was issued for Kurtz's firearm to be surrendered to the state by the Worchester County District Court. Kurtz was contacted and willing to surrender her firearms to investigators.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 11:10:26</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5448</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 15:36:08</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>226450</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 11:10:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 09:24:42</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>226450</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>29695</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Ringneck</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Salisbury</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.5855223006508</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.31885532964786</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/04/2023 11:10:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/04/2023 11:10:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40R</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/19/2023 15:36:08</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 11:10:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5448</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 15:36:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>SCENE PROCESSING: Body Worn Camera was utilized during the duration of the incident footage link:https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=75c9a4542d3648a18bcb572458d4f343partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  NARRATIVE: On October 2, 2023, members of the FEU were informed D/Sgt. Johnson of the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack in regards to Fidelia Ann KURTZ (W/M DOB: 11/23/1989). KURTZ was found guilty of DUI on July 15, 2023, inWorchester County, Maryland District Court (Case Number: D-024-CR-23-002232). During her arrest, KURTZ was found carrying a firearm on her person (Make: Ruger Model: LC9S Caliber: 9 Serial Number: 45342182), which was not seized upon her arrest. D/Sgt. Johnson explained to investigators that upon her arrest the firearm was relinquished back to KURTZ. D/Sgt. Johnson advised investigators that KURTZs firearm has a court order to be forfeited to the state of Maryland, by the Worchester County District Court. Additionally, due to KURTZs conviction, she was placed on three-year supervised probation.   Investigators contacted Agent Olsen of the Wicomico County Parole and Probation and explained the investigation that KURTZs firearm must be forfeited to the State due to a Worchester County District Court Order. Furthermore, Agent Olsen advised that KURTZ is currently on probation, and due to her probation conditions, she cannot be in possession of any firearms or ammunition.    KURTZ was queried through the Department of Natural Resources (DNR) database with an active result (harvesting a deer with a rifle on December 5, 2015), and the Maryland Automated Firearms Services System (MAFSS) database with a positive result:   Make: Ruger Model: LC9S Caliber: 9 Serial Number: 45342182   Investigators contacted KURTZ via telephone, identified themselves, and explained the nature of the call, which KURTZ acknowledged. During the conversation, KURTZ advised that she had the firearm in her possession, and with her cooperation, investigators made arrangements to conduct a knock-and-talk to surrender her firearm with investigators at her residence.   On October 6, 2022, members of the FEU made contact with KURTZ at her residence at 29695 Ringneck Place, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21804. KURTZ was presented with a Consent to Search form (MSP 78), which he agreed to and signed granting investigators access to her residences. While at the KURTZs residence the following firearm was seized:   Make: Ruger Model: LC9S Caliber: 9 Serial Number: 45342182   No other firearms were located at KURTZs residence, despite her active harvest of a deer on December 5, 2015. FEU members provided KURTZ with a copy of her Consent to Search and Seize Form (MSP 78).   Investigators transferred the firearm to the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack V. Investigators processed the firearm per Maryland State Police policy (PH-339054).    Investigators contacted the Assistant States Attorney Michael Calabrese of Wicomico County. The facts and findings of the case were presented and discussed with SA Calabrese, and it was determined that Wicomico County States Attorneys Office would decline the prosecution of KURTZ.   Investigators updated Agent Olsen and provided her with all pertinent documentation.   All the above events occurred in Wicomico County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6169</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 09:29:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6169</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 09:32:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Keidel</LastName>
            <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5448</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lomax</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6169</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6169</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 09:25:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 09:25:57</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382875</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Kurtz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Fidelia</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/23/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 22:28:48</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K632</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F340</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Kurtz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Fidelia</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/23/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>K632</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F340</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 22:28:48</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>29695</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Ringneck</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.5855223006508</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.31885532964786</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6169</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 09:25:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6169</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 09:28:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6169</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 09:28:15</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>MSPRI</PropertyTypeCode>
         <SerialNumber>45342182</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255042</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>BLU</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>Ruger</Make>
         <Model>LC9S</Model>
         <Quantity>0</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>