<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-018016</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/20/2023 17:40:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/20/2023 17:40:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/20/2023 07:07:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/20/2023 07:07:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Assist Mount Airy Police CDS arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 17:40:36</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5562</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 19:19:27</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>21947</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>MT AIRY</SubBeat>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 17:40:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/20/2023 17:45:42</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>21947</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1401</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>MAIN</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>MOUNT AIRY</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>MT AIRY</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-77.16502053056736</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.36697072242561</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>DUNKIN DOUGHNUTS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/20/2023 17:40:35</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/20/2023 17:40:35</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>05/28/2023 19:19:27</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 17:40:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5562</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 19:19:27</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was captured on Body Worn Camera and In car Camera Body camera documentation for Mount Airy Police case number 23-000273  Attachments: None  Narrative:  On 5/20/2023 at approximately 0700 hours I was stopped by a citizen later identified as Gregory Lawson who advised there was a silver passenger car in the Mount Airy McDonalds parking lot with a female slumped over the wheel. Lawson advised that he observed an African American Male knocking on the window and the operator woke up. I contacted Officer Gebhart of the Mount Airy Police Department and advised him of the information. Officer Gebhart pulled into the 711 parking lot to make observations. At this time the vehicle was stopped in front of McDonalds not in a parking spot blocking the travel portion of the parking lot. As officer Gebhart entered the parking lot the vehicle backed up and exited the McDonalds parking lot turning right onto Ridgeside Drive. I observed the vehicle slow for the stop sign at Ridgeside Drive and South Main Street the vehicle did not come to a complete stop prior to making the right-hand turn onto South Main Street. Officer Gebhart initiated a traffic stop on the vehicle on South Main Street at Dunkin Donuts.  Officer Gebhart had the driver exit the vehicle and I obtained names and date of births of the passengers. Officer Gebhart completed MVA and wanted checks on the passengers. The front seat passenger had a warrant through Frederick County Maryland. Officer Gebhart had the front seat passenger exit the vehicle for the warrant. While Officer Gebhart was speaking with the passenger I walked back up to the vehicle to watch the remaining passenger. At this time I observed two used Hypodermic needles on the front passenger seat of the vehicle. I advised officer Gebhart and all 3 occupants of the vehicle were detained. At this time a probable cause search of the vehicle was completed. I assisted Officer Gebhart with the search. I observed a glass pipe contain suspected CDS residue Cocaine and another clear glass pipe contain suspected CDS residue Cocaine in the drivers side door pocket. I advised Officer of the items and locations I did not remove the items from the vehicle.  Officer Gebhart arrested the driver and front seat passenger of the vehicle.  All of the above events occurred in Carroll County MD  I gave the rear passenger Clarence Edward David a ride to Food Lion in New Market MD.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5895</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 17:47:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5895</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/26/2023 02:51:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Karas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5562</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Horner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jonathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5895</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>