<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-027766</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/05/2023 23:11:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/05/2023 23:11:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/05/2023 22:53:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/05/2023 22:53:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Two vehicle accident resulted in the arrest of the driver of V1 for DUI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/05/2023 23:11:23</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5948</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 01:30:38</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>ADY RD/ MINE BRANCH RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>703032</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/05/2023 23:11:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 00:57:09</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>703032</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ady</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Street</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.33064</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.6356</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3280-3329 ADY RD / 900-949 MINE BRANCH RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/05/2023 23:11:21</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/05/2023 23:11:21</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/16/2023 06:01:39</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/05/2023 23:11:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:02:26</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-car camera and body worn camera operational, Unmarked Car D25.  Maryland State Police, Bel Air Barrack DWI #23-195 23-MSP-027766  Defendant: Cole Montgomery Spangler Defendant Address: 109 Theodora Ct, Forest Hill MD 21050 DOB: 01/07/2000 Date of Arrest: 08/05/2023 Time of Arrest: 2326 hours Subsequent Offender: No Minor in the vehicle: No Driver License Number: MD DL S-152-122-609-022 CDL: No  First Observation:  On 08/05/2023 at approximately 2253 hours, I, Trooper Allen #7267, was dispatched to a two vehicle head on collision in the area of Ady Rd and Mine Branch Rd. Upon my arrival, I saw a silver Infiniti sedan that experienced heavy front-end damage, multiple airbag deployment, and was on an embankment off the roadway. I also saw Chevrolet Silverado that had sustained heavy front-end damage and was disabled in the roadway. Harford County Sheriff then informed me that the driver of the sedan was in the ambulance and gave me his Maryland license. I then met with the driver of the Infiniti.  Phase Two- Personal Contact:  I identified the driver as Cole Spangler (W/M DOB 01/07/2000) and met with him while on the ambulance. I asked Spangler what happened and he reported that he was driving too fast, and that he was avoiding a deer in the roadway. Spangler then reported that he lost control of his vehicle after avoiding the deer and then collided with the vehicle in the opposing traffic lane, and after the collision he went off the roadway to the right. I asked Spangler if he had anything to drink which he first denied. I then met with the driver and passengers of the other vehicle. I first met with the passenger of Cindy Kaczorowski, Kaczorowski reported that she first saw the vehicle due to sparks that were coming off his vehicle. The striking vehicle then hit their vehicle on the front driver side. The other witnesses in the Chevrolet reported that they saw sparks coming from the vehicle prior to colliding with the Chevrolet. I was also informed by Cpl. Turner #6761 that a county deputy reported that Spangler did admit to drinking alcohol prior to driving. I then met with Spangler again and asked him to clarify the accident. Spangler then clarified that he did strike a guardrail prior to hitting the vehicle. I then asked him why he lied to me about drinking alcohol, to which Spangler continued to deny that he had any alcohol prior to driving. When I told him that a Deputy reported to me that Spangler admitted to the deputy that he drank alcohol, Spangler then admitted to drinking two Miller Lite beers prior to driving. While speaking with Spangler, I was able to detect a mild odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. I then asked Spangler to partake in standardized field sobriety testing which he consented too.     Phase Three- Prearrest Screening  Standardized Field Sobriety Test:  The evaluation administered to Spangler was on the paved roadway of Ady Rd and Mine Branch Rd during the nighttime hours. Spangler was tested facing away from any emergency equipment. The roadway was level and free of debris and deformities. When I asked Spangler if he had anything to drink or if he used any substances, Spangler admitted to drinking alcohol but denied consuming CDS.  Questions: Glasses or contacts: None Medical conditions: None  Injuries: None.  Medications: None   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) (6/6 Clues observed) (Instructed and Understood/ Defendants Response: YES) The first test administered was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. A stimulus pen was used and held approximately 12 inches from Spanglers face. I instructed Spangler to follow the stimulus with his eyes and eyes only. He was also instructed to stand with his feet together and hands to his side. I asked Spangler if he understood the instructions which he stated he did.The following observations were made:  Lack of smooth pursuit: 2 clues observed Distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation: 2 clues observed Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees: 2 clues observed Vertical Nystagmus: not present. Total Observed Clues: 6/6  Walk and Turn Test (1/8 Clues Observed) (Instructed and Understood/ Defendants Response: Yes) The second test offered to Spangler was the Walk and Turn. I instructed Spangler to stand in the starting position by placing his right foot in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe.I then instructed Spangler to remain in that position and that he was not to begin the test until told to do so. I then explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. I instructed Spangler to take 9 heel to toe steps while keeping his hands to his side, and continuously look at his feet while counting aloud. On the ninth step, I explained that Spangler was to keep his lead foot planted, while he took a series of small steps around his lead foot with his rear foot to turn completely around and take an additional 9 steps in the same manner. I then reminded Spangler that he was not to start or stop the test until it was completed. I then asked Spangler if he understood the instructions, which he stated that he did.    Instructional stage: Stepped out of the starting position: Not present Started too soon: No  Walking stage:   First Nine Steps:  Toe to Heel:not present Stepped off line: on step 1  Used arms for balance: not present Second set of nine steps:  Toe to Heel: not present  Stepped off line: on step 2 and 3 Used arms for balance: not present Number of steps: Correct number of steps on both sets.  Stopped during the test: Not present.  The Turn: Satisfactory.   Total Clues (1/8)  One Leg Stand (0/4 Clues observed) (Instructed and understood/ Defendants Response Yes) I instructed Spangler to assume the starting position for the One Leg Stand test by placing his feet together and keeping his arms by his side. I also told Spangler to not begin the test or move from the starting position until he was instructed to do so. Spangler stated that he understood the instructions. I demonstrated to Spangler, once instructed to do so, he was to raise one of his feet approximately 6 inches off the ground and to point his toes forward to let the foot be parallel to the ground. I then instructed Spangler to look at his toes the entire time while he counted by thousands aloud. (Thousand one, thousand two) I told Spangler to continue to count until told to stop. I asked Spangler if he understood the instructions to which he stated Yes.  Balance and Counting Stage  0-10 Seconds: Put foot down: N/a Swayed: N/a Used Arms for balance: N/a Hops: N/a  11-20 Seconds: Put foot down: N/a Swayed: N/a Used Arms for balance: N/a Hops: N/a   21-30 Seconds: Put foot down: N/a Swayed: N/a Used Arms for balance: N/a Hops: N/a  Total Clues (0/4)  Preliminary Breath: preliminary breath test was not offered because I did not have one at the time of testing.   Arrest Due to my training of over 40 hours in DUI detection with live donors at the Maryland State Police Academy, being certified to conduct ARIDE testing through Baltimore County, as well as my Certification by the IACP (International Association of Chiefs of Police) to be a Drug Recognition Expert, and the observations of impairment made during the Field Sobriety testing; I determined I had probable cause to believe that Spangler was driving under the influence and unable to operate the vehicle safely. Due to the following:   Admission to drinking alcohol prior to driving   margin-left:8px"&gt;Clues of standardized field sobriety testing  I then placed Spangler under arrest fordriving or attempting to drive while under the influence of alcohol at 2326 hours.  Advice of Rights (DR-15) / Certified Breath Test (Accepted). I presented Spangler with the Advice of Rights form (DR-15) in English audio form prior to transporting him to the Northern Harford County Sheriff Precinct. Spangler accepted to submit to an intoximeter test at 2342 hours. After transporting Spangler to the Northern Precinct, First Class Deputy Gary #1287 conducted the intoximeter test. Spangler supplied a breath sample of .053 at 0020 hours on 08/06/2023. Spangler was charged with driving under the influence of alcohol and issued all pertinent paperwork.  Spangler was released to a license driver at approximately 0055 hours. Case Status- Closed due to arrest. All events occurred in Harford County Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 04:34:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 04:34:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Turner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6761</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allen</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7267</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stanley</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4849</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allen</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7267</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allen</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7267</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517210</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/05/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 01:45:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 01:55:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517210</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/05/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 01:45:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 01:55:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517210</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/05/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 01:45:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 01:56:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517210</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/05/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 01:45:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 01:57:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517210</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/05/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 01:45:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 01:52:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>23</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 01:45:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 01:57:50</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>384464</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Spangler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cole</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MONTGOMERY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/07/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/07/2023 00:32:41</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S152</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Spangler</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cole</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MONTGOMERY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/07/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S152</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/07/2023 00:32:41</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>109</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Theodora</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Forest Hill</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21050</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.376865</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.586226</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>987</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5236</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 01:57:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 01:57:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 01:57:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 01:45:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 01:45:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155843</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 01:45:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 01:45:29</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JN1FV7AR3LM660826</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>INFI</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1FG0833</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>