<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-029156</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/18/2023 02:01:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/18/2023 02:01:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/18/2023 01:41:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/18/2023 01:41:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI arrest of Dale M. Bowers</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 02:01:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/21/2023 00:52:20</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>FRIENDSHIP RD/ OCEAN GTWY</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>704170</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 02:01:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 00:41:25</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>704170</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Friendship</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>GTWY</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.19003</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.34335</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>9982-9985 FRIENDSHIP RD / 10623-10697 OCEAN GTWY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/18/2023 02:01:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/18/2023 02:01:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/21/2023 00:36:33</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 02:01:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:06:30</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police- Berlin Barrack V MSP Unmarked vehicle V-18 is equipped with a mobile recording device Trooper is also outfitted with a body worn camera (Videos are labeled: 23MSP029156)     Defendant: Dale Michael Bowers Jr. License #: MD B-620-135-603-450 Date of Birth: 06/16/1978 Date of Arrest: 08/18/2023 Times of Arrest: 0156 hrs. DUI #: 23-96-249 PBT Results: REFUSED Intox Results: REFUSED Subsequent Offender: NO Accident Involved: NO   CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING  - Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration  - Trained through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration as an SFST Instructor  - Trained by the Maryland State Police in Enhanced DUI Enforcement  -Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE)  - Distinguished graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)    On August 18, 2023, at approximately 0141 hrs., I, TFC Lane #6577 of the Maryland State Police-Berlin Barrack V, was on patrol in my unmarked patrol vehicle, V-18, in the area of Route 50 and Route 707, located in Ocean City, Worcester County, Maryland. At that time, I was traveling west on Route 50 when I began to observe a white Ford truck(MD: 7DW9310) traveling in front of me driving extremely erratic. While behind the truck, I observed it constantly swerving from the left to the right. On at least 11 occasions, I observed it swerved right over the white solid fog line. Each time, the entire right side tires were over the fog line. In between Riddle Lane and Route 589, half of the truck was over the solid white fog line. Upon turning right onto Friendship Road, I observed the truck take a wide turn, riding over the solid white lane marker, dividing the turn lane and northbound Friendship Road. After riding over the solid white line, I observed the Ford cross the center double yellow lines, and travel northbound in the southbound lane. After going into the opposite lane, it slowly corrected itself after I activated my emergency lights to conduct a traffic stop on it. Upon activating my emergency lights, I observed the Ford cross the double yellow center lines once again, and cut the turn into the Royal Farms short. When it did that, the Ford went into the opposite direction, once again. After turning into the Royal Farms, it came to a complete stop in the middle of the travel portion of the parking lot. It is to be noted there were many open parking spots where the truck could have pulled into.    PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)   I exited my patrol vehicle and approached the drivers side window. I introduced myself and advised the male driver the reason for the stop. While speaking with the driver, I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle and observed the drivers eyes to be extremely glassy and bloodshot with a gazed look. I asked the driver for his license and registration for the vehicle. The driver displayed a Maryland drivers license identifying him as, Dale Michael Bowers Jr.-DOB 06/16/1978.Speaking with Bowers, I observed him speak with a slurred speech and have slow and sluggish movements. When asked how many alcoholic beverages he had that night, Bowers stated, Probably about 4 or 5.After obtaining Bowers information, I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine MVA checks.   After conducting routine MVA checks, I returned to Bowerss vehicle. I then requested him to exit and walk to a level surface in the parking lot, to which he complied. While speaking with Bowers outside his vehicle, I continued to smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. Bowers openly stated, Im just gonna be completely honest, I have had drinks, my wife had more then me, so I drove, probably not the best decision in the world.I informed him that I wanted him to perform field sobriety tests, to which he consented. When asked if 4 or 5 was a good number, in reference to his alcohol consumption, Bowers stated, I think Its pretty close. When asked what kind of beer it was, Bowers stated, Bud Light.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   The evaluation was performed in the parking lot of the Royal Farms where Bowers had come to a complete stop at. The surface waslevel and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 80 degrees.Bowers appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlamps, parking lot lamps, and my flashlight. My front emergency lights were deactivated during all the tests.  I asked him the following questions:  Injuries  NO Medication  NO Medical Conditions  NO  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (_6_/_6_ clues observed)   The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. A silver pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12-15 inches from Bowerss eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Bowerss pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. He was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked him if he understood the instructions and he stated yes.  1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes   WALK AND TURN (_5_/_8_ clues observed)   Prior to Bowers performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Bowers was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Bowers was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Bowers was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Bowers was to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, I explained and demonstrated for Bowers to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. I again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Bowers was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Bowers if he understood the test and he stated, Yes.  Instructional Stage:  1.) Lost balance  Broke feet apart on three occasions  Walking Stage (1st Nine): 1.) Raised arms away from his side more than 6 inches 2.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 5, 7, and 9. After the 9th step, Bowers stopped and stated, Now I forgot what you told me. At that point, I had to advise him of the instructions once again. 3.).Stopped walking after step 9.   Walking Stage (2nd Nine):   1.) Raised arms away from his side more than 6 inches  2.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 1, 2, 5, and 7.  Turn:  1.) Improper- Didnt keep the front foot planted   ONE LEG STAND (_1_/_4_ clues observed)   Prior to Bowers performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Bowers was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, Bowerswas to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand-two), and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Bowersif he understood the test and he stated yes.   Seconds 0-10: 1.) Raised arms more than six inches from his body to maintain his balance.  Seconds 11-20:  1.) Raised arms more than six inches from his body to maintain his balance.  Seconds 21-30:  1.) Raised arms more than six inches from his body to maintain his balance.  Letter Test:   I asked Bowers how far he had gone in school, to which he stated, 11th grade. I asked him if he understood the English alphabet, to which he stated yes. I asked him to start at the letter F and stop at the letter T without singing it. He receipted it as follows:  F, G, A, B, C, D, E. After a long pause, I asked Bowers if he wanted to start over, to which he stated, Yea. At that point Bowers quickly stated the entire English alphabet from A-Z. When asked what I told him to end at, Bowers stated I dont know.  I asked Bowers if he wanted to consent to a Preliminary Breath Test(PBT). Bowers stated Im gonna go over an .08. After numerous attempts, and going back, Bowers stated, If I take that, Im gonna go over a .08. When asked why, he stated, Because Ive had 5 beers in the past hour. After going back and forth several more times, I determined he was going to be a refusal.  ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Bowers was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  *Swerving in and out of his lane on many occasions. *Going in the opposite lane of travel * Wide and cutting turns * Stopping in the middle of the parking lot *Odor of an alcoholic beverage off his breath and person * Admission to having alcohol * Eyes glassy and bloodshot * Slurred speech and slow and sluggish movements * My observed signs of impairment as he performed the psychophysical tests. * Inability to recite the English alphabet as explained * Stating he was going to blow over a .08 on the PBT * Inability to decide whether to take the PBT test or not   I arrested Bowers for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0156 hrs. Bowers then was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle.While still on scene, I played the English audio version of the DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Bowers via the MVAs official website. The copy of the DR-15 was placed in front of Bowers to which he advised he could read. At the conclusion of the DR-15 audio, I verbally repeated and reviewed the possible suspensions and sanctions that can be imposed by the MVA per the DR-15 form. Bowers refused to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the same at approximately 0215 hrs.    While en route to the Barrack, Bowers openly stated, I get it, I probably made a mistake tonight by having a couple of drinks and driving.   INTOXIMETER RESULT:  REFUSED.  Bowers was later released to his sober friend from the Barrack. Bowers was polite and cooperative throughout the entire process.   All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.   Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 01:24:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 03:54:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7062</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lane</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6577</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518603</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/18/2023 01:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 01:03:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 01:03:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518603</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/18/2023 01:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 01:03:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 01:03:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518603</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/18/2023 01:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 01:03:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 01:03:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518603</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/18/2023 01:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 01:03:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 01:03:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518603</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/18/2023 01:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 01:03:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 01:03:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 01:14:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 04:01:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>385554</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bowers Jr</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dale</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/16/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/20/2023 01:12:53</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bowers Jr</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dale</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/16/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/20/2023 01:12:53</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1912</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Arundel</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Pasadena</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21122</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.479601</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.152653</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>867</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0302</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 04:01:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 04:01:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 01:03:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 01:03:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>