<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-019701</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/02/2023 00:32:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/02/2023 00:32:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/02/2023 00:18:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/02/2023 00:18:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Check Welfare with a male operator slumped over the wheel while vehicle is running.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 00:32:49</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5162</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/14/2023 11:48:47</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>484810</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 00:32:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/03/2023 03:05:08</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>484810</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>13400</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>H G Trueman</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Solomons</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20688</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.459991</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.346242</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/02/2023 00:32:47</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/02/2023 00:32:47</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/11/2023 13:47:08</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 00:32:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:05</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This stop was audibly and visually recorded using the Axon Digital Video Camera System installed in Maryland State Police Unit, U-6 and also TFC Marschs issued Axon body worn camera.  DUI# 23-048 Maryland Drivers License # D-520-441-302-765  PHASE ONE- Vehicle in Motion   OnFriday, June 2nd,2023, atapproximately 0019hours, I, TFC R. Marsch #6850, was patrolling Solomons Island, Solomons, Calvert County, Maryland in my unmarked Maryland State Police car, U-6. Calvert County Emergency Communications dispatched a check welfare at Taco Bell located at 13400 H.G. Trueman Road, Solomons, for a subject slumped over the wheel. Once on scene I observed a white Nissan Maxima displaying Maryland registration 2AC8813, running with the lights on, covering two parking spaces in front of Taco Bell. I approached the drivers side of the vehicle and observed a middle-aged white male slumped over the steering wheel with his face facing the driver side window. The air conditioner was at full blast, with the windows fogged.  PHASE TWO  Personal Contact  I immediately contacted the driver. I identifiedthe driver byhis Maryland drivers license as Joseph Herman Downs(White/Male,DOB:10/04/1972), and explained the reason for making contact with him. Downs was nodded off on the steering wheel. I tapped Downs left upper arm and he immediately sat up in the driver seat. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Downss breath and person. His eyes were glassy and bloodshot.I asked him to retrieve hislicense and registration.I then asked Downs what he was doing, and he stated he was just sleeping. He stated he was waiting on his girlfriend to come pick him up. I then asked Downs if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages and he stated, Yes, I had a couple early. When Downs was speaking with me, I could hear him slurring his speech. He stated he wasnt driving and was waiting for his girlfriend to come get him.   PHASE THREE  Based on my observations and the statements of Downs, I asked him to perform voluntary Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs). Downs complied with my request and opened his drivers side door.I asked Downs to go behind his vehicle. When I asked Downs if there were any medical conditions that would affect his eyes, prevent himfrom walking a straight line, or prevent him from standing on one leg, Downs stated, NO  the SFSTs were performed on the asphalt parking lot to Taco Bell. The asphalt was a non-slippery surface. It was flat, hard, level, and was free of debris or obstructions. The weather was clear with no wind or varying environmental conditions. The SFSTs were performed with the following results:   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN)- An involuntary jerking of the eyes occurring as the eyes gaze side to side. Total of six of a possible six clues were present. Downs was instructed to stand with his feet together, hands at his sides and to look straight ahead. He was instructed to hold his head still during the test and to follow the stimulus with his eyes only. Downs was then asked if he understood the instructions and he acknowledged by saying, Yes. Placing my stimulus approximately 12-15 inches away from Downs, I then checked Downss eyes for equal pupil size, equal tracking and any signs of resting nystagmus. This is done to check for any kind of medical disorder or injury that might exhibit a form of nystagmus. I observed none of these signs or symptoms when checking Downss eyes.    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;I observed lack of smooth pursuit in both of Downss eyes as I administered HGN.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;I observed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both of Downss eyes as I administered HGN.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;I observed onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes (approximately 40 degrees) as I administered HGN.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Vertical gaze nystagmus was not observed as I administered HGN.  WALK AND TURN (WAT) - A divided attention Field Sobriety test consisting of two stages. Total of four out of a possible eight clues were present. Downs was then given the following instructions for the Instructional Stage of the Walk and Turn test:  I instructed Downs to place his foot on the white line in front of him. Then I instructedDownsto place the heel of his right foot against the toe of his left foot. I instructed Downsto place his arms at hissides and to maintain that position while the rest of the test was explained. As these test procedures were explained, I was demonstrating it in front of Downs and then paused so he could understand my movements. Downs was then asked if he understood everything that I had demonstrated and explained so far and he stated,Yes. Downswas given the following instructions for the Walking stage of the Walk and Turn test: I instructed Downs that whenI tell him tostart, hewill take nine heel-to-toe steps, turn, and then take nine heel-to-toe steps back Downs the same line. I instructed Downs that when you turn, keep the heel of your foot on the line and turn to your left, taking series of small steps with your opposite foot. I instructed Downs that while heswalking, keep hisarms at hissides and watch hisfeet as hewalked. I instructed Downs tocount each step out loud. I then instructed Downs that once you start the test,do not stop until you havecompleted the test. I asked Downs if heunderstood my instructions? Downs stated, Yes, but I had eight surgeries on my foot and I might not be able to do the test. As these test procedures were explained, I was demonstrating it in front of Downs and then pausing so he could mimic my movements. Downswas then asked if he understood, Downs stated, Yes. Instructional stage: 1. Downs stepped out of position to regain his balance. Walking Stage:     margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Downs missed heel-to-toe for the first nine steps on steps 2 and 9.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Downs stepped offline on step on steps 3,5,6 and 7 on the first series.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Downs had his left arm more than six inches from his waistband on step 2.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Downs missed heel-to-toe on the second series of steps on step 2.    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Downs stepped offline on the second series of steps on step 3 and 8.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Downs had his right arm out more than sixes inches from his waistband on the second series of steps on step 8 before loosing his balance and going completely off the line.    ONE LEG STAND (OLS) - - A divided attention Field Sobriety test consisting of two stages. Total of threeclues were present out of four clues. Instructional Stage:  I explained to Downs the test as I demonstrated it. I instructed Downs to stand with your feet togetherandarms at yoursides. I instructed Downs tonot start the test until I tell himto do so. I asked Downs if heunderstood? Downs stated, Yes. I then instructed Downs that when I tell himto, you will raise one leg approximately six inches off the ground, keeping your toe pointed so that the raised foot is parallel to the ground. I instructed Downs to keep your legs straight with your arms down at your side. While maintaining that position, you will count out loud, One thousand one, one thousand two,one thousand three, and so on, until I tell you to stop. I instructed Downs to keep hisarms at hissides and continue to watch hisraised foot while hecounts. I asked Downs ifheunderstood? Downs stated, Yes. As these test procedures were explained, I was demonstrating it in front of Downs and then pausedso he could understand my movements as I narrated. Balance and counting stage:     margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Downs puts his foot down with in the first five seconds   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Downs puts his arms out more than six inches from his waist within the first ten seconds.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Downs started swaying side to side to try and maintain balance within the first fifteen seconds.   Downs refused to a Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) while on the roadside.  ARREST DECISION (Probable Cause):  Based on my observations, I determined Downs was unable to operate his vehicle safely. This is based on the totality of the circumstances from my initial observation ofpersonal contact with the driver, and the clues from the field sobriety test. All the evidence, takentogether,establishedprobable cause for me to believe Downs was driving while impaired and Downs was placed under arrest at 0109 hours for driving under the influence of alcohol and transported to the Maryland State Police Prince Frederick Barrack for processing.   TRANSPORT  While in my vehicle, the odor of an alcoholic beverage was evident. Downs was played the audio version of the DR-15 Advice of rights on the way to the barrack.   BARRACK  Downs signed his DR-15 Advice of Rights at 0050 hours and refused the intoximeter test. Downs was provided signed copies of the DR-15, Dr-15A, and citations. Downs received Maryland Uniform Citations for the following offenses: *TA 21-902 (a1i): Driving Vehicle While under the Influence of Alcohol. *TA 21-902(b1i): Driving Vehicle Impaired by Alcohol.  An MSP Field Arrest form was completed and filed.  Downs was released to his son Kyle Joseph Downs at 0145 hours.  The appropriate DR-15, and DR-15A were mailed to the Maryland Motor Vehicle Administration (MVA).  Case Closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Calvert County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6850</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 04:06:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6850</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 14:12:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pilkerton</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4319</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Marsch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6850</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509135</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>18</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/02/2023 00:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6850</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 02:16:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6850</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 02:16:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>50</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6850</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 02:10:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:59</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378723</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Downs</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Herman</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/04/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.20826748E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>06/02/2023 01:41:30</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J210</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Downs</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Herman</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/04/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.20826748E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>D520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J210</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/02/2023 01:41:30</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>39011</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>New Market Turner</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Mechanicsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20659</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.725963</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.467208</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>672</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3678</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6850</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 02:17:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6850</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 02:17:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6850</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 02:17:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6850</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 02:16:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6850</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 02:16:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153684</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6850</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 01:43:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6850</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 01:43:28</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1N4AA5AP1DC817899</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MAX</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2AC8813</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>