<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-034754</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/03/2023 18:45:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/03/2023 18:45:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/03/2023 18:04:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/03/2023 18:04:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Kidnapping</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 18:45:24</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6166</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 01:18:10</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>KD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>103405</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 18:45:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 21:00:15</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>103405</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>101</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Beech</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>North East</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21901</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.943951</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.594834</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/03/2023 18:45:18</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/03/2023 18:45:18</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>Y</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/19/2023 01:18:10</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 18:45:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6166</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 01:18:10</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP ISSUED BODY CAMERA WAS ACTIVE DURING THIS INCIDENT.  Scene processing:  No scene processing was conducted due to the nature of the incident.  Neighborhood checks:   North East Dominos Pizza.  North East Maintenance Garage.  North East Pats Pizza.  100 W Beech Street.   margin-left:8px"&gt;104 W Beech Street.  Attachments:    Copy of chain of custody log.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Copy of witness statement.  Narrative:  On Tuesday October 3, 2023 at approximately 1804 hours I, Trooper Starr #7289 responded to the North East Car Wash in North East for a report of a kidnapping.  Upon my arrival I made contact with a female identified as Beatrice J Squires (W/F DOB 6/29/1978). Squires stated a juvenile male identified as Kamryn D Johnson (B/M DOB 10/12/2012) approached her at the car wash hysterically crying and stating that he had been kidnapped. Squires son subsequently called 911. Johnsons grandmother, identified as Teresa Lynn Ditchfield (W/F DOB 03/08/1965) arrived on scene shortly after.  I then made contact with Johnson. Johnson stated that he was riding his bicycle out front of his house located at 7 W Beech Street in North East and in the area of 100 W Beech Street. He stated that a newer model white Subaru sedan then parked in front of 104 W Beech Street and a white male wearing blue jeans and a white t-shirt exited the vehicle. Johnson stated that this male, approximately 30 years old with long brown hair and a silver ring on his left hand, then forced him and his bike into the back seat of the vehicle against Johnsons will. He stated there was no other individual in the vehicle with him and the male, and described that there was an empty plastic Dollar General shopping bag on the floor of the vehicle. Johnson then stated that the male drove him west on W Beech Street, turned south onto 3rd Street, turned east onto W Walnut Street, turned north onto Mauldin Avenue, and then turned east onto Pulaski Highway. Johnson said that the male then stopped the vehicle on the right shoulder of eastbound Pulaski Highway in front of the North East Car Wash located at 2376 Pulaski Highway.  Johnson stated at this time he exited the vehicle with his bike. He stated he placed his bike on the ground and ran to the carwash where he requested help from Squires. He stated that the male driver exited his vehicle, picked up Johnsons bike, and placed it in the bushes outside of Bombas Barbeque Restaurant located at 2360 Pulaski Highway. Johnson stated that the male then reentered his vehicle and continued eastbound on Pulaski Highway.  I obtained a written witness statement from Squires, and then transported Johnson back to the MSP North East Barrack to be interviewed. Assisting Troopers responded to the North East Dominos Pizza, North East Maintenance Garage, and to the area of 100 W Beech Street for video surveillance footage. Johnsons bicycle was also recovered and transported to the North East Barrack for processing.  Johnsons bicycle was placed on a chain of custody log, and later released to his grandmother.  Master Trooper Hagan #5497 from the MSP Northern Region Criminal Enforcement Division responded to the barrack to conduct the interview of Johnson. Reference Master Trooper Hagans supplement narrative for the details of the interview and disposition of this case.  On October 3, 2023 at approximately 2358 hours I notified Cecil County CPS after hours line (410-996-5350) and spoke to Catherine Harris and advised them of the incident.  I request this case be closed due to it being unfounded.  All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7289</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 23:45:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7289</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 00:02:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pepe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7054</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mott</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kenneth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7053</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kim</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6166</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Starr</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dalton</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7289</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>10</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7289</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 21:04:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 21:04:18</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389481</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kamryn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>D</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/12/2012 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/03/2023 21:04:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K565</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kamryn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>D</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/12/2012 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K565</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/03/2023 21:04:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>BEECH</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>NORTH EAST</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.94155816291094</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.59451106056133</Latitude>
               <SubBeat>552</SubBeat>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7289</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 21:04:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>58</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7289</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 21:06:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 21:06:42</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389482</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ditchfield</LastName>
               <FirstName>Teresa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/08/1965 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/03/2023 21:06:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D321</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ditchfield</LastName>
               <FirstName>Teresa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/08/1965 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D321</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/03/2023 21:06:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>207</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9992</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>207</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6555</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7289</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 21:06:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7289</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 22:00:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 22:01:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389490</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Squires</LastName>
               <FirstName>Beatrice</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>J</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/29/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/03/2023 22:00:46</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B362</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Squires</LastName>
               <FirstName>Beatrice</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>J</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/29/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B362</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/03/2023 22:00:46</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>945</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6259</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7289</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 22:01:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7289</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 21:08:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7289</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 21:08:15</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>480</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>254863</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>TEA</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>No Ruler</Make>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/05/2023 12:46:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/05/2023 12:46:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/05/2023 13:17:41</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5497</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 12:46:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6166</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 01:18:10</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On October 3rd, 2023, at approximately 1831 hours, the Maryland State Police North East Barrack received a 911 call for a juvenile abduction. The caller stated that a 10 year old black male ran up to her while she was in the area of the Dominoes at 2328 Pulaski Hwy, North East, Cecil County, Maryland, claiming that he had been taken but was able to get away by jumping out of the suspects vehicle. Initial investigation by Troopers revealed that the 10 year old juvenile advised he was riding his bike in the town of North East in the area of Beech Street and Third Street when a white, newer model Subaru sedan pulled up next to the juvenile. The juvenile went on to say the driver got out of the vehicle and forcefully pushed him along with his bicycle into the back seat of the Subaru and drove away. For unknown reasons, the driver/abductor stopped in the area of 2376 Pulaski Highway (Eastbound US Route 40) on the right shoulder. At this point, the juvenile advised he attempted to get out of the car but ultimately was pushed out of the vehicle by the abductor.  The juvenile ran to the Dominoes, leaving his bicycle to which the abductor threw the bicycle into bushes of the business in that area and fled the scene. The driver/suspect was described as a 30 year old white male, with long brown hair, no facial hair and a silver ring on his left hand.  A BOLO for the vehicle and driver were put out to the agencies in the area. The vehicle/suspect were not located. More than a dozen law enforcement officers from Maryland State Police (FOB and CED), North East Police Department and Cecil County Sheriffs Office were involved in the multi-jurisdictional investigation.  Master Trooper Hagan from MSP CED Northern Investigators was called and responded to assume the investigation. Upon arrival at the North East Barrack, Master Trooper Hagan was briefed by Cpl. Kim. Cpl. Kim advised troopers were able to locate video footage of the juvenile in the area of the Dominos Pizza for 20 minutes prior to the report of the crime. The juvenile was riding his bike around with 10 to 15 other youths. Additionally, Sgt. Cox, MSP SOG, spoke with Troy Preston of Preston Lawn Care. This location is equipped with video surveillance systems pointed in the direction of the kidnapping. Nothing was recorded showing the juvenile or the suspect vehicle in the area.  Master Trooper Hagan spoke with Sgt. M. Cox of MSP SOG. Sgt. Cox provided the following statement:  Sir, on todays date M/T Pettit and myselfassisted the North East Barrack Uniformed Patrol with a call for service regarding an abducted juvenile from Beech Street, North East. M/T Pettit and myself went to Beech Street to check for video surveillance of the incident. We arrived to 20 Beech Street where we observed numerous surveillance cameras posted on all the corners of the home. We made contact with the homeowners (The Prestons) who were more than happy to let us view the video footage from 1740 hours to 1804 hours (The video footage and playback was correct with the date and time). One of the camera angles shows the front of the house and looks down towards the end of Beech Street (Well past 100 Beech Street where the juvenile said he was abducted from). During this time frame, we did not see any juvenile on foot or on a bike in the area and certainly didnt see a white Subaru passenger car stop in the area and abduct anyone. There were two white cars, neither of which were Subarus, that had driven through the area during that time frame. It should also be noted that during this time frame, neighborswere in and out of their homes and there was a woman power walking up and down Beech Street. Once back at the barrack, it was relayed to us that the child had already been observed on surveillance by the Dominos peddling his bike.  Based on the totality of the situation, the contradictions between the physical evidence and the story of events from the juvenile, Master Trooper Hagan conducted an interview with the juvenile and his grandparents, who are his legal guardians. This case met the exemption to the Child Interrogation Act and the Office of the Public Defender was not consulted in this matter. Per MSP rules and regulations, Troopers will only conduct a custodial interrogation of a child outside of the above requirements if 1) there is reasonable belief that the information sought is necessary to protect against a threat to public safety; and 2) questions are limited to information necessary to protect against the threat to public safety. During the interview, the juvenile provided the same timeline of events as provided to initial troopers. The juvenile provided extremely specific descriptions of the suspect and the vehicle. The juvenile was confronted with the contradictory evidence and eventually admitted he fabricated the events because he was playing in an area he should not have been playing. The juvenile eventually gave a story of him riding his bike from his home and making it to the Dominos and riding with friends.  Case Closed as unfounded.   This report will be forwarded to Cecil County CPS and Juvenile Services for review and to provide the family resources and services. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5497</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 12:47:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5497</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 12:49:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Donald</LastName>
            <FirstName>Frank</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6049</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hagan</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5497</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>