<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-034781</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/04/2023 00:44:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/04/2023 00:44:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/04/2023 00:26:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/04/2023 00:26:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI Dolan</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 00:44:07</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 10:44:37</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>BALTIMORE BLVD/ OLD WESTMINSTER PIKE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>530038</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 00:44:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 10:16:57</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>530038</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Baltimore</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Finksburg</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>PIKE</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.90909</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.51355</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3125-3201 BALTIMORE BLVD / 3268-3357 OLD WESTMINSTER PIKE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2450-2508 BALTIMORE BLVD / 0-0 OLD WESTMINSTER PIKE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 BALTIMORE BLVD / 2816-2819 OLD WESTMINSTER PIKE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2801-2847 BALTIMORE BLVD / 0-0 OLD WESTMINSTER PIKE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3125-3249 BALTIMORE BLVD / 3268-3357 OLD WESTMINSTER PKE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2400-2448 BALTIMORE BLVD / 0-0 OLD WESTMINSTER PIKE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2510-2536 BALTIMORE BLVD / 0-0 OLD WESTMINSTER PIKE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/04/2023 00:44:03</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/04/2023 00:44:03</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/18/2023 02:27:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 00:44:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:49</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>G-13isequipped with a mobile recording device. BWC was activated for this incident  23-158   Defendant: Daniel Charles Dolan  Date of Birth: 7/18/1983  Date of Arrest: 10/4/2023  Times of Arrest: 0043 hours  MD DL #:MD10273890158    TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:    * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Trained and certified by the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration in operations of Radar and LIDAR. * Certified Preliminary Breath Test operator by the Office of the Chief Medical Examiner Incident Organizations. * ARIDE (Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement) certified through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.   VEHICLE IN MOTION    On Wednesday, October 11, 2023, at approximately 0030 hours, I Trooper First Class Petry #6426 of the Maryland State Police Westminster barrack was on patrol, traveling eastbound on Baltimore Boulevard east of Green Mill Road, Finksburg, Carroll County, Maryland 21048.  At this time, UHaul box truck bearing Arizona registration AJ40830 traveling in lane 1 eastbound on Baltimore Boulevard. While following the vehicle, I observed the vehicle travel over the dotted white line by approximately a full tire width. As we continued, the vehicle again crossed the dotted white line into lane 2 as a vehicle was traveling in lane 2. Immediately after crossing through the intersection with Dede Road, the vehicle traveled across the solid yellow line by a full vehicle width. The vehicle moved back into lane 1 and then crossed back across the solid yellow line by one tire width. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle on Baltimore Boulevard just prior to the Baltimore County Line.   PERSONAL CONTACT    I approached the vehicle on the driver side and made contact with the male operator and sole occupant of the vehicle. He was identified by his Maryland Drivers License as Daniel Charles Dolan (2/m 7/18/1983). While speaking with Dolan, I observed his eyes to be bloodshot and detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. Dolan advised that he did not have anything to drink.  Due to the observations made, I asked Dolan to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Testing and had Dolan move to the front of his vehicle. While exiting the vehicle, I observed a yellow can on the floor that appeared to be an alcoholic beverage container with a 99 on the can. It appeared that Dolan was attempting to hide the can from my view by placing his foot next to the can as he exited the vehicle.      PRE-ARREST SCREENING    The evaluation was performed in front of his vehicle on the right shoulder of the roadway. The surface was dry and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and his vehicle headlights. Dolan appeared to be in good physical condition. While speaking with Dolan, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.  Glasses - None  Dolan advised that he does not have any medical conditions or any injuries that would prevent him from completing any tests.  Dolan stated that he takes anxiety medication.   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)    The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from Dolans eyes and just above eye level. Dolan was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Dolanspupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking.    1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes  2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes  3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes  Vertical Nystagmus was also present in both eyes.    WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)    Prior to Dolan performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Dolan was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Dolan was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Dolan was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Dolanwas instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Dolan was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to the left to turn completely around. Dolan was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Dolan was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud.    Instructional Stage:   1.) Lost balance during instruction and moved from instructional position. 2.) Started the test prior to being told and began with his feet side by side and not in the instructional position.    Walking Stage (1st Nine):  1.) Did not start from the instructional position. Did still take 9 steps    Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  1.) Missed touching heel to toe on step 6. Left foot crossed over to the right of his right foot 2.) Stepped offline on step 6. Left foot was placed offline to the right while making step.  Turn:  Completed Satisfactorily    ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)    Prior to Dolan performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Dolan was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Dolan stated he understood the instructions for the test. Dolan raised his rightfoot.    Instructional Stage:  Nothing to Report .  Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 1-30:  1.) Placed foot on ground multiple times. 2.) Raised arms to assist in balancing. 3.) Swayed during the test.  After completing the test Dolan stated and showed an obvious injury to his right ear. Dolan advised that he was struck days prior by his son and his balance was off.    LACK OF CONVERGENCE  Nothing to Report   MODIFIED ROMBERG  Nothing to Report    ARREST    Based on the following, I had reason to believe Dolan was driving a motor vehicle under the influence:    * Failure to maintain lane * Failure to drive right of center * Odor of an alcoholic beverage * Clues during standardized field sobriety testing.  Due to the number of observations, I concluded Dolan was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At 0043 hours, I placed Dolan under arrest for driving while under the influence.  Because the vehicle was a rental vehicle, a tow truck responded to remove the vehicle from the roadway. After entering the vehicle, i observed a 99 Brand wild cherry acholic beverage that was not opened. I also observed a opened can on the floorboard behind to drivers seat within reach of Dolan. There was also a bottle of vodka in a book bag on the passenger floorboard.  I transported Dolan to the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack for processing. At the Westminster Barrack, I read and provided Dolan with a DR-15 Advise of Rights. Dolan refused to submit to the test at 0124 hours.  Dolan was placed in a holding cell while awaiting a ride. Once Dolans ride arrived, I removed Dolan from the cell and observed a large puddle on the cell floor. There was a strong odor of urine and I observed the front of Dolans pants, and it appeared that he had urinated himself while in the cell that was also equipped with a toilet.  Dolan was provided with copies of all pertinent paperwork and was released to a sober driver at the Westminster Barrack.  I request this case be closed.  All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6426</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 10:26:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6426</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 11:30:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Keller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brady</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7360</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dale</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2927</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Petry</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colton</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6426</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524239</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/04/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6426</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6426</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524239</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/04/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6426</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6426</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524239</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/04/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6426</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6426</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524239</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/04/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6426</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6426</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524239</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/04/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6426</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6426</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524239</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15558</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/04/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15558</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6426</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6426</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6426</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 10:22:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6426</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 10:22:31</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390338</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dolan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/18/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/14/2023 09:42:24</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D450</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dolan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/18/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D450</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/14/2023 09:42:24</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>978</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Shore Acres</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Arnold</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21012</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1728</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.462397</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.055021</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6426</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 10:22:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6426</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 10:22:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6426</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 10:22:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6426</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6426</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 10:19:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158043</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6426</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 10:24:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6426</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 10:24:23</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SAV3500CGO</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>AZ</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>AJ40830</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>