<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-015879</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/04/2023 13:15:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/04/2023 13:15:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/04/2023 13:15:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/04/2023 13:15:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>05/04/2023 13:55:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>Assist Out-of-State Agency With Sexual Assault</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/04/2023 13:16:02</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6761</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/05/2023 09:05:18</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SAS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>1401 BELAIR ROAD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>692879</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/04/2023 13:16:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/04/2023 15:08:25</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>692879</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1401</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Belair</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/04/2023 13:15:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/04/2023 13:15:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>Y</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/05/2023 09:05:17</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/04/2023 13:16:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6761</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/05/2023 09:05:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Complainant/Victim Information:  1. Paige Alexandria Hartlove, White Female, D.O.B. 04/21/1996, 709 Millwood Drive, Fallston, Maryland 21074, Phone No. 443-904-1995.  Witness Information:  1. Unknown at this time.  Suspect Information:  1. Unknown Male Subject, Hispanic/Middle Eastern, Possible Height Of 510, Possible Weight Of 180 lbs., One Dangling Earring, Red Bumps (Acne) On His Back, Brown Eyes With Very Dilated Pupils, Wearing Cowboy Hat  Louis Vuitton Underwear.  Attachments:  1. MSP 076-Victims Written Statement  2. Photocopy of Victims License Information  Narrative:  On May 4, 2023, at approximately 1315 hours, a female subject entered the front lobby of the Bel Air Barrack to report a sexual assault that occurred out-of-state, identifying herself as Paige Alexandria Hartlove, White Female, D.O.B. 04/21/1996. Hartlove began by stating on April 28, 2023, while in Houston (Texas) attending a bachlorette party with twelve other females, they arrived at a male review show sometime between 2000-2100 hours, titled, Hunk-O-Mania, located at the Henke  Pillot Building, 809 Congress Street, Houston, Texas 77002. Aside from their bachlorette party, there were reportedly four other women in attendance. Shortly thereafter, at approximately 2250 hours, various members of the bachlorette party, to include Hartlove, split from the group for the purpose of paying for their own private dances, which Hartlove advised was located in a dark corner of the club. After the unknown male dancer performed for Hartlove for 60-90 seconds, that is when he reportedly began to choke her, followed by licking her vagina through her underwear, and then attempted to digitally-penetrate her vagina. Hartlove then stated she pushed the male dancer away from her, grabbed her bag, and ran to the bathroom. The male dancer was then observed running out of the building by Hartloves friends. He was described as either Hispanic or Middle Eastern, 510, 180 lbs., dangling earring in one ear, red bumps (possibly acne) on his back, brown eyes with very dilated pupils, wearing a cowboy hat, and Louis Vuitton underwear. She left with her three close friends in an Uber and returned to their Airbnb, only identified by Hartlove as Paige Wyckoff, Allie Wyckoff, and Athena Randall. The next morning, Hartlove told the other portion of the bachlorette party about the incident. Hartlove returned to Maryland on Monday, May 1, 2023. The following day on Tuesday, after a complaint was filed with the business, she received a call from a male subject claiming to be the manager out of New York, who Hartlove suspected to be the CEO Armand Perri. He repeatedly advised Hartlove that she couldnt go to the police since she has no proof. On May 3, 2023, when Hartlove contacted the Houston Police Department to report the incident, she was advised to contact her local police department, who would then forward a copy of the report to them to investigate. Hartlove did not sustain any physical injuries during this incident and advised she was wearing a black halter dress with thong underwear. Furthermore, Hartlove was not provided with a Maryland Crime Victim and Witness pamphlet, since this incident occurred outside of Maryland. However, she was provided with the case number, along with my contact information. Finally, I contacted the Houston Police Department and received the contact information for the appropriate personnel this report will be forwarded to once it has been approved through the appropriate internal channels. The number for their Sex Crimes Unit is: 713-308-1180, and the employee the report will be forwarded to by fax is Desirea Molett: 713-308-1181. That information was also provided to Hartlove later that afternoon by email.   Scene Processing: Due to the nature of this out-of-state incident and how it was reported, scene processing was not conducted.   Neighborhood Check: Due to the nature of this out-of-state incident and how it was reported, a neighborhood check was not conducted.   Based on the above stated facts, I respectfully request this case be forwarded to the Houston Police Department Adult Sex Crimes Unit, for further investigation.   While the initial incident occurred in Houston, it was reported by the victim in Harford County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4849</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/04/2023 14:58:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4849</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/04/2023 16:39:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Turner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6761</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stanley</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4849</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4849</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/04/2023 15:15:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:17</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>376100</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hartlove</LastName>
               <FirstName>Paige</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alexandria</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/21/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/04/2023 15:13:32</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H634</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hartlove</LastName>
               <FirstName>Paige</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alexandria</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/21/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H634</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/04/2023 15:13:32</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>904</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1995</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/04/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4849</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/04/2023 15:15:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4849</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/04/2023 15:15:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>