<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-033498</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/23/2023 19:48:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/23/2023 19:48:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/23/2023 19:21:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/23/2023 19:21:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Troopers dispatched to 10-50 / driver was 10-55.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:48:41</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4792</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 15:49:52</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN HWY/ DAVIS STORE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>547204</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:48:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/27/2023 09:46:43</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>547204</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Pocomoke City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.60721</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.08728</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>7437-7548 OCEAN HWY / 33081-33207 DAVIS STORE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>7549-7734 OCEAN HWY / 33081-33207 DAVIS STORE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 OCEAN HWY / 33100-33199 DAVIS STORE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/23/2023 19:48:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/23/2023 19:48:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/04/2023 15:42:13</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:48:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI ARREST X-13 does not have an in car camera. Body worn camera was operational.   Defendant:Vanessa Ann Handy Date of Birth: 01/20/1961 Date of Arrest:09/23/2023 Time of Arrest:1947 hours MD License #:H-530-839-067-055 DUI #:23-95-051 /23MSP033498   TRAINING/CERTIFICATES    margin-left:8px"&gt;Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration 2017.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Police officer from May 2017 with the Salisbury City Police Department located in Wicomico County, Maryland, until June 2022 for five years.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Maryland State Trooper since June 2022 where I was retrained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.   VEHICLE IN MOTION/ CRASH OBSERVATIONS (PHASE 1) On September 23, 2023, at approximately 1923 hours, I, Trooper Dean #7572 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack was operating marked Maryland State Police vehicle X13 in the area of Route 13/ Perry Road when I was dispatched to the area of northbound Route 13/ Davis Store Road, in reference to a motor vehicle collision. Upon arrival, I observed a silver Subaru Outback bearing Maryland Registration number 9FE0872 with front end damage and a white Ford Van bearing Maryland Registration number 5CL6776 with front end damage. Thesilver Subaru Outback bearing Maryland Registration number 9FE0872 was the at fault vehicle and crashed into the white Ford Van in lane number one at northbound Route 13/ Davis Store Road.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)   I approached the silver Subaru Outback bearing Maryland Registration number 9FE0872 on the drivers side and made contact with the female operator and sole occupant of the vehicle. I informed the operator that I would be investigating the accident. I immediately detected a strongodor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and/or person.I requested her drivers license, which she presented. The driver was identified by her Maryland license as Vanessa Ann Handy (B/F/M DOB 01/20/1961). While speaking with Handy, I observed Handy, had glassy, watery and bloodshot eyes and her voice was difficult to understand due to slurred speech.  A check through MVA revealed that Handys license was valid, and she had no open warrants.  I requested that Handy exit the vehicle. Handy struggled to open the driver side door prior to exiting her vehicle. As I communicated with Handy outside the vehicle, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. I asked Handy to perform standardized field sobriety tests, to confirm that she was okay to drive, and she agreed.    PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   The evaluation was performed on the shoulder of Davis Store Road. The surface was damp from the rain, level, and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlights, my vehicles headlights, my flashlight, Handy appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. Prior to beginning the test, I deactivated my vehicles forward facing emergency lights.   I asked Handy the following questions:  Glasses or Contacts  Glasses. Medical Conditions  Diabetic / Handy was checked by EMS prior to being administered tests. Injuries  None Medication  None   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)   The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus. It was held approximately 12-15 inches from Handys eyes, slightly above her eye level. Handy was instructed to look straight ahead, keep her head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with her eyes. Handy was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. Handys pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. It should be noted throughout the test Handy had to be instructed multiple times to follow the tip of my pen with her eyes only. I asked Handy multiple times if she understood the test, Handy replied I understand. Handy continued to move her head multiple times throughout the test despite advising she understood the instructions.      Lack of Smooth Pursuit  (PRESENT) in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  (PRESENT) in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees (PRESENT) in both eyes     (RESTING NYSTAGMUS / NOT PRESENT). (VERTICAL NYSTAGMUS PRESENT).   WALK AND TURN (5/8 clues observed)   The test was explained and demonstrated. Handy was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Handy was then instructed to place her hands flat at her sides and remain in that position until told to begin. Handy was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, she was instructed to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Handy was instructed to complete the second series of nine (9) steps in the same heel to toe fashion. Handy was instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, count every step aloud, and once she began the test she was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Handy if she understood the test, and she confirmed that she did.   Handy performed this test wearing shoes.    Instructional Stage:    (Did not remain in the instructional phase position).  (Handy was also swaying back and forth while test was being explained).      Walking Stage (1st Nine)    (Did not walk heel-toe for any of the first nine steps).  (Handy proceeded to lift her arms to keep balance).  (Handy proceeded to step off the line multiple times throughout the test).     Turn:    (Improper turn-lifted foot up and proceeded to walk backwards even though sheadvisedshe understood the instructions).    Walking Stage (2nd Nine)    (Raised arms while walking despite being instructed to keep arms down by herside).  (Did not walk heel-toe for any of the nine steps).  (Proceeded to walk backwards and did not complete test proper).    ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)   The test was explained and demonstrated. Handy was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, watch the raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, etc) and to not put her foot down until the end of the test. I asked Handy if she understood the test, and she confirmed that she did.   Instructional Stage:    Handy advised she understood the instructions. Handy proceeded to walk towards the Trooper and did not perform the test properly. I explained the test multiple times to Handy and ultimately stopped the test for safety purposes.     Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10:    Trooper stopped test.  Seconds 11-20:    Trooper stopped test.   Seconds 21-30:    Trooper stopped test.    While on scene, I informed Handy of her Preliminary Breath Test Rights. Handy was offered a PBT, to which she refused. At this time, the test was documented as refusal.  ARREST   Based on the totality of circumstances, I had reason to believe Handy was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:      Silver Subaru Outback bearing Maryland Registration number 9FE0872 front end damage from accident.  Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle/breath/person.  Clues during Standardized Field Sobriety Testing.   Handy admitting to drinking prior to operating the vehicle.    Due to the number of observations, I concluded Handy was driving under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a vehicle safely. On September 23, 2023, at approximately 1947 hours, I placed Handy under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack, and searched her person for weapons and contraband, both with negative results. Handy was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy. Handy was read her DR-15 Advice of Rights in English. At approximately 2034 hours Handy agreed to take an alcohol concentration test.   20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD  I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Handy beginning with her arrest. A preliminary search of Handy was conducted on scene, and it revealed that she had nothing in her mouth at approximately 1947 hours. I observed Handy from the time of arrest until the time she submitted to the test, and she did not put anything in her mouth.The test was conducted by Sgt Barkley of the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrackon a certified instrument. Handy had a result of (.14) grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at approximately 2040 hours.   INTOXIMETER RESULT  (.14)BrAC  I processed Handy and released her to Jeremy Jamar Dennis (DOB: 12/17/1993) her family member from the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack. It should be noted that Handy was released at approximately 2100 hours. Handys eyes were still glassy, watery and bloodshot. Handy was provided her citations and walked through each citation individually.    The defendant was issued copies of the following documents: -Citations -DR-15 Advice of Rights. -DR-15a Order of Suspension. -MSP 033  All documents were forwarded to the Somerset County, States Attorney Office.  The vehicle was secured on scene and towed by Superior Towing.  All events occurred in Somerset County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7572</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 22:23:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7572</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 23:04:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Salgueiro</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7370</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dean</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7572</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522953</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/23/2023 19:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7572</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 10:32:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7572</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/28/2023 21:54:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522953</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/23/2023 19:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7572</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 10:32:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7572</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/28/2023 21:54:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522953</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/23/2023 19:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7572</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 21:55:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7572</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/28/2023 21:55:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522953</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/23/2023 19:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7572</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 21:56:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7572</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/28/2023 21:56:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522953</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/23/2023 19:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7572</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 21:57:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7572</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/28/2023 21:57:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>62</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7572</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 10:32:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7572</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 03:54:13</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388585</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Handy</LastName>
               <FirstName>Vanessa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/20/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16761229E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 21:33:18</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>V520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Handy</LastName>
               <FirstName>Vanessa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/20/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16761229E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>H530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>V520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 21:33:18</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>30970</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>REHOBETH</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>WESTOVER</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.68144577596337</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.04589826221963</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>251</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2966</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7572</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 03:54:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7572</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 03:54:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7572</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 03:54:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7572</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 03:54:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7572</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 10:32:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7572</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/27/2023 10:32:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>