<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-028300</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/10/2023 19:09:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/10/2023 19:09:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/10/2023 19:01:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/10/2023 19:01:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/10/2023 19:09:27</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/28/2023 06:48:09</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MD-100 / CATHERINE AVE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>640488</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/10/2023 19:09:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 01:29:39</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>640488</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Md-100</StreetName>
         <City>Glen Burnie</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>AVE</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.54851</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.12008</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>19802-20551 MD-100 / 8131-8142 CATHERINE AVE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/10/2023 19:09:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/10/2023 19:09:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/27/2023 08:54:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/10/2023 19:09:27</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:06:42</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI #: P-23-105  CASE #: 23-MSP-028300  DEFENDANT: Nelson Antonio Olivio Ramirez (Soundex) MD10272194451 (H/M) DOB 07-16-2001  *THIS INCIDENT WAS RECORDED ON MY IN-CAR AND BODY WORN CAMERA SYSTEMS*  NARRATIVE:  On 08-10-2023, at approximately 1902 hours I, Senior Trooper D. Bartch #5301 was in marked patrol unit P-24, on patrol in the area of Eastbound Route 100 West of Catherine Ave, Anne Arundel County, Maryland. I was traveling in lane #1 directly behind a green BMW bearing Maryland registration 8FF3285. The BMW caught my attention when I observed the vehicle to be following another vehicle to close. The BMW was less than 6 feet away from the vehicle that was in front of the BMW. I also observed both of the drivers hands outside the sunroof for approximately 5 seconds. I then observed the BMW to cross the solid yellow line to the left more than a tire width for about 25 yards. The BMW then came back into lane #1 and then started to cross the dotted white line into lane #2. The BMW crossed the dotted white line more than a tire width for about 15 yards and then back into lane #1. I then activated my emergency equipment and stopped the vehicle on the right shoulder at Eastbound Route 100 just prior to Catherine Ave, Anne Arundel County, Maryland.    I exited my patrol vehicle and made contact with the driver and I identified myself. I advised him that the traffic stop was being visually and audibly recorded, reason for the stop and asked for his license and registration to the vehicle. The driver was identified by his Maryland driver license as Nelson Antonio Olivio Ramirez (H/M) DOB 07-16-2001. While speaking with Ramirez, I detected a moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. I observed thatRamirez eyes were blood shot red and very glassy.Ramirez kept drinking Gatorade to try and mask the odor of alcoholic beverages. I askedRamirez if he had any alcoholic beverages, and he stated 2 alcoholic beverages. Based on the odor of alcohol, I askedRamirez to exit and come to the rear of his vehicle.  Based on my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, I suspectedRamirez was impaired by alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. Ramirez agreed to submit to standardized field sobriety testing. The tests were performed on the right shoulder of Eastbound Route 100 just prior to Catherine Ave in an area that was level and free of debris and weather was clear.Ramirezadvised me that he had no present injuries, and did not wear glasses or contacts.Ramirez also confirmed that he could see my stimulus (pen) in front of his face.   STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS  Instructions: Ramirez was told to stand with his feet together and his arms down at his side. A stimulus (ink pen) was held approximately twelve to fifteen inches fromRamirez face, and he was asked to follow the stimulus with his eyes only and to not move his head. Prior to beginning the test, I askedRamirez if he understood the instructions.Ramirezanswered yes, I initially checked for equal pupil size, resting nystagmus, and equal tracking. I, next checked for lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees. Lastly, I checked for vertical gaze nystagmus. Both eyes were checked twice for each clue.  6/6. VGN present. Both pupils were equal in size and equally tracking the stimulus. Resting nystagmus was not present. Nystagmus was observed in each eye during all three observations.Ramirez eyes were blood shot red and both were very glassy.  WALK AND TURN  Instructions:Ramirez was told to stand with his right foot in front of his left foot in a heel to toe manner. He was told to stay in that position and keep his arms at his side until being told to begin the test. I askedRamirez if he understood, and he answered yes. I began explaining and demonstrating the test. Ramirez was instructed to take nine heel to toe steps on a straight line. On the ninth step, he was instructed to leave his lead foot planted and take a series of small steps to turn 180 degrees.Ramirezwas told to then take an additional nine heel to toe steps back down the same line. He was told to gaze down at his feet, count the steps out loud, keep his hands at his side, touch heel to toe on every step, and to not stop walking until the test is complete. I askedRamirezif he understood the instructions before beginning and Ramirez answered yes.  At the beginning of the test he could not stay in the instructional phase. On the first series of nine steps,Ramirez lost balance and stepped off-line to his left on step number 2.Ramirez again on the 4th step lost balanced and stepped off-line to the right.Ramirez took 10 steps on the first series of 9 heel to toe steps. Ramirez did not complete the turn as instructed and turned to his right.Ramirez then looked at me and stated to the other side? I explained toRamirez to complete the test as instructed. On the second series of nine stepsRamirez did not complete any step heel to toe.   ONE LEG STAND  Instructions: Ramirez was instructed to stand with his feet together and his hands at his side while I explained the instructions and demonstrated the test. Ramirez was told to raise either foot of his choice approximately six inches off the ground while keeping it parallel to the ground. He was told to begin to count, one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-threeetc.Ramirezwas instructed to continue counting until I told him to stop. He was told to gaze down at his feet, to count out loud, to keep his arms at his side, and to not put his foot down. I then asked if he understood the instructions.Ramirez answered yes.   While I was explaining the test I had to stopRamirez from starting and again advise him to stay in the instructional phase. After count 1002 I had to advise Ramirez again to keep his foot off the ground 6 inches. Ramirez then put his foot down.Ramirez then continued to count but again dropped his foot at count 10 and stopped the test. I then had to adviseRamirez to keep going.Ramirez started the count over, I then stop the test.    Ramirez was offered a preliminary breath test andRamirez did agree to take it. Ramirezs results were a .13 blood alcohol level.  Based on my observations and my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper,Ramirez was placed under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol at approximately 1909 hours. I securedRamirez in my patrol vehicle and transported him to the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie barrack for processing. We arrived at the barrack at approximately 1925 hours. I escortedRamirez into the barracks Troopers room, and he was provided a copy of his DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along as a spanish audio version was played to him out loud in its entirety. A spanish speaking Anne Arundel County officer responded to the barrack. A. A. County Officer made sureRamirez completely understood the DR-15 Advice of Right.Ramirez advise he understood the form, and he answered yes. At approximately 1952 hours, Ramirez refused to submit to the intoximeter test.    Ramirez was provided with all appropriate paperwork and citations. Ramirez drivers license was confiscated and submitted to the MVA along with a DR-15A form.Ramirez was released to Carlos Alberto at 2030 hours.  All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 09:57:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 08:51:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wiest</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4939</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bartch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5301</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517744</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/10/2023 19:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 10:01:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 10:02:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 01:22:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 01:29:39</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>385486</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ramirez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nelson</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Antonio olivio</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/16/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/19/2023 01:19:26</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R562</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N425</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ramirez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nelson</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Antonio olivio</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/16/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R562</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N425</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/19/2023 01:19:26</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7767</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Tick Neck</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Pasadena</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21122</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2202</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.528027</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.139021</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 01:22:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 01:22:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 01:22:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 01:22:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 10:02:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 10:02:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>