<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013592</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/17/2023 00:37:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/17/2023 00:37:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/16/2023 00:13:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/16/2023 00:13:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect was arrested for DUI following a traffic stop.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 00:38:01</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4913</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/08/2023 12:32:37</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>US-50 / CAPE SAINT CLAIRE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>568352</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 00:38:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/01/2023 19:27:43</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>568352</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>E/B</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>US Route 50 @ Cape St Claire Road</StreetName>
         <City>Annapolis</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21409</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-76.4471757</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0267246666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM MDT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/17/2023 00:37:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/17/2023 00:37:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/02/2023 20:53:29</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 00:38:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:43</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> Maryland State Police Annapolis Barrack.  This incident was captured on an in-car camera, J-8.  Body-worn camera not operational.  Defendant: Dawn Mcmanus Maltese  Date of Birth: 09/02/1967  Date of Arrest: 04/17/2023  Time of Arrest: 0036  Maryland Drivers License: M-432-135-597-684  DUI# J-23-057   Training and Certification:  *I am trained by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Transportation Safety Administration to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  *I am a certified Preliminary Breath Test operator.    VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On 04/17/2023 at approximately 0002 hours, I, Trooper Baker #7430, was in full uniform and operating marked Maryland State Police vehicle J-8 when I received a call from the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack dispatcher. The dispatcher advised a caller was on the line and stated they were following behind a Toyota SUV that was swerving all over the road in the area of southbound Interstate 97 prior to eastbound US-50, Anne Arundel County, Maryland. The caller believed the driver was impaired and advised the Toyota SUV was displaying Maryland registration 5CP5391. The caller advised the Toyota SUV was now driving eastbound on US-50, and the caller soon disconnected from the dispatcher and did not provide additional information. I then positioned my vehicle on the shoulder of eastbound US-50 prior to the Severn River Bridge on the right shoulder.  I saw a Toyota SUV displaying Maryland registration in Lane 1, matching the suspect vehicle description, appearing to be traveling above the posted speed limit of 55 miles per hour. I caught up to the Toyota SUV when it crossed the Severn River Bridge on eastbound US-50. The Toyota SUV was now in lane 3. I observed the vehicle swerve across the right solid white fog line twice with the front and back tires crossing the line. I also observed the vehicle swerve across the left broken white line twice with the front and back tires crossing the line. The Toyota SUV was swerving consistently within and out of its lane. The Toyota SUV turned on its right blinker while still in lane 3 and started driving partially on the right shoulder. The Toyota SUV then positioned itself back in lane 3 and appeared to forget to turn off the blinker. I followed the vehicle for approximately 2.1 miles, and the vehicles speed fluctuated between 70 and 80 mph in a posted 55 mph zone. For approximately 0.3 miles, I paced the vehicles speed at 70 mph in a posted 55 mph zone. The distance between my patrol vehicle and the Toyota SUV did not change during the pace. The Toyota SUV took exit 29A and crossed the right solid white line. I activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop. The Toyota SUV was stopped at the Exxon gas station at 317 Buschs Frontage Rd, Annapolis, MD 21409. The suspect vehicle was positively identified as a silver Toyota Highlander displaying Maryland registration 5CP5391.    PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I made contact with the operator via the drivers side front window. Upon making contact, I immediately smelled the very strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicles interior and the drivers breath. I advised the driver of the reason for the traffic stop and requested her drivers license, registration, and proof of insurance. The driver was identified by her Maryland drivers license as Dawn Mcmanus Maltese (W/F DOB: 09/02/1967). I asked Maltese when she had her last alcoholic beverage, and Maltese advised about one hour ago. Maltese then began to stumble over her words and advised she didnt want to tell me what alcoholic drink she had and how many. After Maltese recovered the documents I requested, I also asked where she was coming from and where she was headed. Maltese advised that she was coming from hanging out with friends in Annapolis and was headed home to 1585 Secretariat Dr, Annapolis, MD 21409. Maltese would not advise where exactly she was with friends. As I spoke with Maltese, I observed Malteses speech to be slowed and slurred. Maltese appeared to be staring at me and not blinking her eyes. I also observed Maltese eyes to be watery and glassy. I asked Maltese if she would conduct a Standardized Field Sobriety Test (SFST) to ensure she could drive safely, and Maltese responded by saying you dont have to do this. Maltese requested I drive her to her residence because her residence is close. I advised Maltese I couldnt do that, and Maltese ultimately agreed to Standardized Field Sobriety Test (SFST).  Trooper First Class Hill #6278 arrived on the scene and had an operational body-worn camera prior to any testing.    PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3  Maltese exited her vehicle and walked to the front of her vehicle. Maltese leaned on the front of her vehicle, which appeared to help her balance. The evaluation was performed in the parking lot of the Exxon gas station at 317 Buschs Frontage Rd, Annapolis, MD 21409. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all tests. Maltese informed me that she did not have any injuries that would prevent her from walking or standing and did not display any visible injuries.  I asked Maltese the following questions:  Medical Conditions  No.  Injuries  No.  Medication  No.  Contacts  No.  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my fingertip was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Maltese eyes. Maltese advised she could see my fingertip. Maltese was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of my fingertip with her eyes until told to stop. Maltese pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Maltese was asked if she understood the directions, and she stated yes.    HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes  2. Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes  3. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both    Other observations:  1. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus observed.  2. Maltese had to be reminded to keep her head still multiple times and to follow my fingertip with her eyes multiple times.    WALK AND TURN (Refused)  Prior to Maltese performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Maltese removed her footwear before testing. Maltese was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Maltese was instructed to place her hands flat at her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Maltese was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. Maltese was told to keep her hands flat at her side, keeping her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. Maltese was demonstrated and explained to keep her lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Maltese was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. After explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked Maltese if she completely understood the instructions, and she stated yes.    Other observations:  1. Maltese failed to keep balance while listening to the instructions multiple times and began to lean on her car. Maltese was told to stop leaning on her car, but she did not listen.  2. I demonstrated and explained the test multiple times because Maltese advised me to repeat the directions.  3. Maltese later advised that she couldnt do that regarding the walk and turn test.  4. Maltese refused to submit to this test.    ONE LEG STAND (Refused)  Prior to performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Maltese was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her side while the instructions were given. Maltese was instructed not to begin the test until she was told to start, and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, keep her hands down by her side, count out loud by thousands (one thousand - one, one thousand - two), and continue the test until told to stop. Maltese was asked if she understood the test and the instructions, to which she stated yes.    Other observations:  1. Maltese advised that she understood the directions but continually asked me to repeat the tests.  2. Maltese refused to submit to this test.    PBT refused.    ARREST:  Based on the following:  *Swerving across the solid right white fog line three times.  *Swerving across the left broken white line twice.  *Driving on the roadway and forgetting to turn off her right blinker.  *Fluctuating speed between 70mph and 80mph.  *Exceeding the speed limit (70mph in a 55mph zone).  *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicles interior.  *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Maltese breath.  *Slurred speech.  *Watery and glassy eyes.  *Thousand-yard stare. *Admission to consuming an alcoholic drink. *Unable to keep balance and consistently learning on the front of her car.  *Observations during Standardized Field Sobriety Test and while giving the instructions regarding the test.    Given the aforementioned observations, I determined Maltese could not operate a motor vehicle safely. She was arrested at approximately 0036 hours on 04/17/2023 for driving under the influence of alcohol.   Search incident to arrest of Maltese person was conducted, and located in her right front pocket was one vape pen containing suspected marijuana. Maltese possessed a valid Maryland Medical Cannabis Commission card (MMCC). A search of the vehicle yielded negative results.   One handle of Deep Eddys Lemon Vodka was located in the front right passenger side floorboard in a brown paper bag.The bottle was closed, but the seal was broken and was half empty.  Maltese was transported to the Maryland State Police Annapolis Barrack for processing. While at the Annapolis Barrack, a mouth check was conducted with a 20-minute observation period. I played the MVA English version of the Dr-15 Advice of Rights to her in its entirety, and Maltese was given a copy of the Dr-15 to follow along. At the conclusion of the form, Maltese advised she wanted a lawyer and didnt know if she should take the test. Maltese discussed her rights with Sgt Graves #1405, who had an operational body camera. Maltese was given opportunities to make phone calls.    Other observations:  While Maltese was speaking to a friend on her cellphone, Maltese advised that she was drunk and wasnt sure if she should take the test. This moment was captured on Sgt Graves #1405 body-worn camera.    Maltese was brought into the intoximeter room, and the intoximeter ran through its test runs and was deemed to be working correctly. Maltese advised she didnt know if she wanted to take the test, and the intoximeter eventually timed out.  Maltese was again given multiple opportunities to complete all field sobriety tests, submit to a PBT, and complete the intoximeter test.  Maltese refused to sign the DR-15 (0154 hours).    INTOXIMETER RESULT:  *** MALTESE INTOXIMETER TEST RESULTS. REFUSED***  Maltese was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to a sober driver.  I continued to detect an odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Maltese breath and person throughout her time in custody and release.   Case closed by arrest.   All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7430</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 00:22:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7430</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 06:39:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6278</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Engleman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jonathon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5835</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Baker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Drew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7430</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503000</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 00:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7430</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 23:20:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7430</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 23:20:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503000</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 00:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7430</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 23:21:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7430</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 23:23:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503000</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 00:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7430</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 23:22:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7430</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 23:23:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503000</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 00:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7430</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 23:22:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7430</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 23:23:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503000</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 00:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7430</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 23:24:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7430</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 23:24:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>55</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7430</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 23:40:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374611</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Maltese</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dawn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Mcmanus</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/02/1967 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 23:40:09</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M432</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Maltese</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dawn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Mcmanus</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/02/1967 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M432</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 23:40:09</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1585</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Secretariat</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Annapolis</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21409</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.434907</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.029702</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>562</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9786</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7430</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 03:36:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7430</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 03:36:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7430</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 23:20:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7430</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 23:20:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152085</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7430</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 23:48:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7430</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 23:48:23</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/25/2023 15:07:17</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JTEEP21A160170652</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2009</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CIV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4D</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLU</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>951BLP</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>10</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehConditionCode>F</VehConditionCode>
         <VehDamageCode>12</VehDamageCode>
         <VehDamageDesc>Rear left tire damage and front left/right bumper damage. </VehDamageDesc>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>