<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-024500</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/08/2023 21:23:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/08/2023 21:23:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/08/2023 20:58:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/08/2023 20:58:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The unknown male caused a disturbance in the store and assaulted customers</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 21:23:15</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5367</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/07/2023 15:01:11</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DIS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>5121</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>569</SubBeat>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 21:23:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/26/2023 12:49:42</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>5121</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>25</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>LIBERTY</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>SYKESVILLE</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>569</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-76.9959240369229</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.42274602265764</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>HIGHS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>GOURMET WINE AND SPIRITS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/08/2023 21:23:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/08/2023 21:23:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/07/2023 15:01:13</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 21:23:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was audibly and visually recorded with my body-worn camera (BWC).   LIST OF ATTCHMENTS  Copy of BOLO Form 76 (Witness Statement) from Jacob Myrick  VICTIM/COMPLAINANT STATEMENT  Nicholas Light DOB: 07/27/95 9921 McKinstry Mill Road New Windsor, MD 21776 PH: 443-280-2989  Light stated on 7/08/23 at approximately 2045 hours he and his wife, Kara Lycliter, pulled up to the Highs while there was an argument going on between an unknown white male and other people. Light stated he got out of his vehicle and stepped up onto the curb when the unknown male stepped into his face. Light stated the unknown male started yelling and cussing at him. Light proceeded into Highs to purchase items. Light noticed the unknown male came into the store and started acting up, causing a scene. Light advised he approached the unknown male to tell him to calm down and leave the store but the unknown male because irate. Light advised the unknown male swung at him approximately nine times, hitting him in five times. Light put his hands up to block the unknown male instead of hitting him back. Light advised the unknown male ran out of the store, got in his truck and left in a hurry.  WITNESS STATEMENT  Kelly Pare DOB: 8/4/78 6800 Rustling Breeze Drive Sykesville, MD 21784 PH: 410-984-8420  Pare stated her and her husband were driving westbound on Liberty Road (MD. 26) at Linton Road, when a white van flew by them. Pare stated when they approached the entrance ramp for Highs, the white van was blocking the entrance. Pare and her husband tried to go around the white van when an unknown white male gets out of the white van and starts yelling at them. Pare stated her husband drove past and used the entrance off Klee Mill Road to get to Highs. Pare advised once she and her husband parked and walked into the store, she noticed the unknown male was already in there.  WITNESS STATEMENT  Kara Lycliter DOB: 11/10/95 9921 McKinstry Mill Road New Windsor, MD 21776 PH: 443-280-7372  Lycliter stated she stayed in the vehicle while Light got out and went into the Highs. Lycliter observed Light was having issues with an unknown white male but was able to go into the store. Lycliter stated she didnt get out until she noticed the unknown male was swing at Light and was hitting him. Lycliter and Pare attempted to get the tag of the unknown male as he ran to the white van and sped out of the parking lot. Lycliter believed the unknown male attempted to run her over with the van.  WITNESS STATEMENT  Jacob Myrick DOB: 12/14/98 10 Liberty Road Sykesville, MD 21784 PH: 410-708-1147  Myrick stated the aggressive customer, suspect, walked into the store shoving the victim/complainant. Myrick stated the suspect proceeded to buy cigarettes but he was a dollar short. Myrick stated the suspect walked out the store to retrieve another dollar. Myrick stated the suspect returned into the store, shoving the line of people, who were purchasing items, so that he could purchase his cigarettes. Myrick advised the suspect handed him a dollar in quarters for the cigarettes. Myrick stated, shortly after, the suspect started shouting and got into a physical altercation with the victim/complainant. Myrick attempted to deescalate the conflict, but the suspect took off in a hurry, driving dangerously in the process of leaving.   SCENE PROCESSING  A copy of the recorded video was obtained and will have to be compressed and uploaded to a thumbdrive at a later date to be stored as evidence.I obtained a still shot of the suspect and the vehicle, which were uploaded to VeriPic.  NEIGHBORHOOD CHECK  Due to the nature and circumstances surrounding the crime, no neighborhood check was performed.  NARRATIVE  On 7/08/23 at 2058 hours, I responded to Highs, 10 Liberty Road, Sykesville, MD 21784 for a reported assault. Upon arrival, I contacted the victim/complainant, Nicholas Light and witnesses, Kara Lycliter and Kelly Pare. See Victim/Complainant and Witness Statements above.  Light described the unknown male as a white male, approximately 511, heavy set, approximately late 30s or early 40s, brownish grey colored hair, wearing a blue shirt with blue jeans and boots.  I noted that the unknown white male hit Light on the right side of his face three (3) times and two (2) times on the left side. I checked Lights face for any signs of visible physical injuries but didnt observe any.  I observed the video recorded by Lycliters phone. Initially you can see the unknown male exit the store yelling and going to his vehicle. At some point, while the camera wasnt focused on the front door, the unknown male returned into the store. Then you see Light trying to enter the store and the unknown male shoves him. One of the other customers in the store attempts to stop the situation and gets shoved by the unknown male. Light tries to have the unknown male walk away from the counter area, where the other people are, but the unknown male walks back over to the counter and shoves the same customer again. Then you see customers standing around and Light trying to reason with the unknown male but the unknown male says something and is being disorderly, which Light tries to shove the unknown male out of the way. This starts the physical altercation between the unknown male and Light, where the unknown male starts to swing at Light but Light stands his ground. Then you see the unknown male throw a punch with his left hand, hitting Light on the right side of his face and knocking off his hat. Light continues you square up to the unknown male, while the unknown male throws punches at him, and Light blocks most of his punches. Light tells the unknown male he needs to stop but the unknown male proceeds to take his shirt off and get in Lights face. The employee of Highs, Jason Myrick, tries to step in to defuse the situation, but the unknown male swings his shirt with his right hand, hitting Light in the face. Myrick continues to stand in between Light and the unknown male, with his hands up to separate them. Light and the unknown male continue to yell back and forth, which the unknown male decides to leave the store. The unknown male gets into a white van, as the driver, and had a white female sitting in the passenger seat. Lycliter attempts to go to the back of the van to record the registration plate but the unknown male starts to back up, which his tires were canted towards the crowd. Lyclister goes into the lot to get a clearer shot, which the unknown male starts to drive forward to speed off. Due to the unknown males tires being turned towards the crowd he started driving towards them but quickly corrected the tires and sped off out of the parking lot towards Klees Mill Road. See Scene Processing above.  I noted that the vehicle was a white Ford Transit Van, with a MD temporary registration, with a Younger sign posted for the front plate. Possibly belonging to Younger Nissan in Frederick, MD.  While contacting Light, Lycliter and Pare, another unit went inside to contact the employee, Myrick, to obtain a witness statement. See Witness Statement above.  After contacting Light, Lycliter and Pare, I went inside the Highs to contact Myrick to see if I could view video footage to obtain further information, but he didnt know how to operate the system. Myrick advised he would contact his manager to view the footage and obtain a copy for me at a later date.  A BOLO was sent out with photos of the suspect, the vehicle and description of the incident.  Due to the facts above, I request this case remain open pending further investigation.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 13:12:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5123</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/26/2023 14:55:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Snedeker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5367</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thompson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Chymere</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5123</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513940</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>07</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/08/2023 20:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 12:52:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5123</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/26/2023 12:52:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513940</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0060</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>07</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/08/2023 20:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 0060</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 12:53:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5123</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/26/2023 12:53:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 12:56:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383527</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 12:56:10</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 12:56:10</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 12:56:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:16</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 13:01:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383528</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Light</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nicolas</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>William Moreland</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/27/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 13:00:01</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L230</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N242</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Light</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nicolas</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>William Moreland</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/27/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L230</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N242</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 13:00:01</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9921</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>McKinstry Mill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>New Windsor</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21776</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>280</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2989</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>280</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2989</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 13:01:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 13:01:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 13:04:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:21</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383530</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lycliter</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kara</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/10/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 13:03:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L243</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lycliter</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kara</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/10/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L243</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 13:03:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9921</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>McKinstry Mill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>New Windsor</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21776</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>280</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7372</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>332</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>280</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7372</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 13:04:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:12</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>44</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 13:07:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:21</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383532</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Pare</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kelly</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/04/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 13:07:09</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Pare</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kelly</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/04/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 13:07:09</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6800</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Rustling Breeze</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Sykesville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21784</Zip5>
               <Zip4>8044</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.971945</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.388252</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>984</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8420</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>984</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8420</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 13:07:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:12</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 13:10:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:07</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383533</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Myrick</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jacob</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/04/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 13:10:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J210</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Myrick</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jacob</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/04/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J210</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 13:10:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>10</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>LIBERTY</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>SYKESVILLE</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.99669398522909</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.42330302785824</Latitude>
               <SubBeat>569</SubBeat>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>708</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1147</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>708</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1147</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 13:10:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/26/2023 12:53:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5123</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/26/2023 12:53:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/03/2023 20:38:35</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/03/2023 20:38:35</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/07/2023 15:01:13</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/03/2023 20:38:35</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>LIST OF ATTACHMENTS  None.  NARRATIVE  On 7/26/23 I created a BOLO to be disseminated for other agencies to help identify the unknown suspect.   On 8/9/23 at 0140 hours, Sgt. Snedecker #5367 submitted my BOLO to MCAC to have disseminated.  On 12/5/23 at approximately 1900 hours, I contacted the victim, Nicholas Light, to see if he had any further information as far as the unknown male suspect, which he advised he hadnt.  Since the Transit Van was possibly purchased at Younger Nissan in Frederick, MD, contact with the dealership could provide further information of the unknown suspect.  Due to the facts above, I request this case remain open pending further investigation.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5123</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 19:26:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5123</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 19:27:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Snedeker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5367</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thompson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Chymere</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5123</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>