<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-027808</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/06/2023 06:52:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/06/2023 06:52:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/06/2023 06:19:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/06/2023 06:19:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/06/2023 06:52:48</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5948</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 12:24:55</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>1893 W GROVE AVE,FALLSTON</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>703074</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/06/2023 06:52:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 10:22:26</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>703074</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1893</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Grove</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.3891030833333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.4984552166667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/06/2023 06:52:44</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/06/2023 06:52:44</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/22/2023 01:31:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/06/2023 06:52:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:02:32</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The incident was audibly and visually recorded from my BWC. MSP unmarked unit D-24 is equipped with MVR equipment. DEFENDANT: SIMPSON, MARK Date of Birth: 10/17/1988 (33 years old) Date of Arrest: 8/06/2023 Time of Arrest: 06:51 hours DUI #: 23-197 (Bel Air Barrack, Harford County) Subsequent Offender: No Minor in the vehicle: No FL-DL. # FL-29240654 CDL: No Certificate and Training: *I am a certified police officer in the state of Maryland with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with participants at the Maryland State Police Academy and prior DUI/DWI arrests and convictions. *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *RADAR / LIDAR Certified 2019. *Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator Certified. *Advance Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement Certified (ARIDE): Attended ARIDE with the Maryland State Police in January 2021 *UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND DUI INSTITUTE: I attended the University of Maryland DUI Institute, and I completed the course with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with live participants (From June 5 to June 10, 2022) *Certified as SFST witness expert by Honorable Judge Martin H. Schreiber II in Baltimore City Circuit Court on September 27, 2022. *Certified SFST witness expert by Honorable Judge David E. Carey in Harford County District Court on October 11, 2022. *I have apprehended more than 170 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On August 06, 2023, at approximately 0619 hours, I, Trooper First Class Reckeweg #7214 of the Maryland State Police currently assigned to the Bel Air Barrack (unmarked MSP patrol vehicle D-24), was traveling in lane two (2) on northbound Route 1 prior to Reckord Road, Fallston, Maryland. At this time, I observed a white BMW sedan ahead of my patrol vehicle traveling in lane (1). The BMW swerved two times to the right and went over the dotted line dividing lane one (1) from lane two (2) by its tire width. The BMW regained control and returned to lane one (1). I then observed the BMW make a sharp left turn into Milton Avenue, crossing into the opposite lane by half length of the vehicle. I pulled behind the BMW, and a traffic stop was initiated as I activated my emergency equipment. The BMW did not stop for approximately 30 seconds and then stopped in the parking lot of 1893 West Grove Avenue, Fallston, Harford County. I then observed the BMW bearing Pennsylvania registration MCB1992. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the BMW via the drivers side window, made contact with the driver (only occupant), and explained to the driver the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver for his drivers license and registration. The driver handed me a Pennsylvania Department of Transportation paper containing his drivers license information (see attachment). I identified the driver as SIMPSON, MARK (B/M, DOB 10/17/1988, Pennsylvania Soundex 29240654) by his Pennsylvania MVA photo record. SIMPSON told me that he was coming from Annapolis and he was going to his job. While talking to SIMPSON, I instantly noticed his eyes were glassy and bloodshot. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from inside the BMW. The drivers speech was slurred. I asked the driver how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed that morning, and he stated, I had nothing to drink. I asked SIMPSON when the last time he had consumed alcoholic beverages was. He said yesterday he smoked cigarettes and weed. I asked SIMPSON to exit and walk to the front of my patrol vehicle. At the front of my patrol vehicle, I could detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on SIMPSONs breath and person. I observed SIMPSON having difficulty keeping his balance as he swayed from left to right and leaned against my patrol vehicle for balance. I advised SIMPSON that I would perform standardized field sobriety test on him, which he agreed to submit. The summary of the first contact is as follows: Attitude: cooperative Eye Condition: Glassy/bloodshot Mental State: Normal. Walk: Normal. Speech: Slurred. I asked SIMPSON the following questions: Medication- No Medical Conditions- No Glasses: No Any pain in the body- No PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The below standardized field sobriety tests were performed in the parking lot of 1893 West Grove Avenue, Fallston, Harford County. That area of the driveway was level and free of debris. I turned off my front emergency lights before beginning the standardized field sobriety tests below. The weather conditions were clear. Lighting conditions consisted of my patrol vehicle headlights and daylight. SIMPSON appeared in good physical condition and displayed no visible signs of injury. I explained and demonstrated the standardized field sobriety tests below to SIMPSON. SIMPSON stated he understood my instructions and had no questions about the standardized field sobriety tests. -HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN) / (6/6 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: YES) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my index finger from my right hand was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from SIMPSONs eyes, slightly above his eyebrows. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. SIMPSONs pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I observed his eyes to be red. SIMPSON was positioned to ensure passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked SIMPSON if he understood the instructions, and he stated, Yes. The following clues and observations were made during the test: Lack of Smooth Pursuit- Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation- Present in both eyes The onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 Degrees- Present in both eyes Additional test Vertical Gaze Nystagmus- Present in both eyes -WALK AND TURN (WAT) / (3/8 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: Yes) Before SIMPSON performed the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. SIMPSON was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. SIMPSON was instructed and demonstrated to put his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until instructed to begin. SIMPSON was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on each step. SIMPSON was asked to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count each step out loud. On the ninth step, SIMPSON was explained, and I demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and planted and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around to his left. SIMPSON was again explained, and I demonstrated that the second series of nine (9) steps were to be completed identically to the first. Keep his hands by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. I asked SIMPSON if he understood the test. SIMPSON stated, Yes. SIMPSON was instructed to begin the test. Instructional Stage: N/A Walking Stage (1st Nine) SIMPSON stepped offline on steps 4 and 5. SIMPSON missed heel to toe by approximately 2 inches on steps 6 and 8. Walking Stage (2nd nine): SIMPSON stepped offline on steps 3 and 4. SIMPSON missed heel to toe by approximately 2 inches on steps 2 and 6. Turn: Completed Unsatisfactory. SIMPSON did not leave his front foot planted and used both feet to walk in a circle. -ONE LEG STAND (OLS) (LEFT LEG) (1/4 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: Yes) Before SIMPSON performed the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. SIMPSON was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given during the test. SIMPSON was instructed to begin the test when he was asked to start and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to watch his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (thousand-one, thousand-two), and continue the test until told to stop. I asked SIMPSON if he had any questions about the test (OLS) which he replied, No. SIMPSON raised his left foot. Instructional Stage: Nothing to report. Balance and Count Stage: 1. Raise arms: SIMPSON raised arms on the 01 and 7-second mark -PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT) (AGREED)- The final test offered to SIMPSON was the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT). SIMPSON agreed to submit to the PBT test with a result of .14 ARREST Based on my knowledge, training, experience as an MSP Trooper, previous DUI arrests, and clues gathered thus far, I had reason to believe SIMPSON was driving a motor vehicle while impaired (under the influence of Alcohol). *Swerving on the roadway. * Physical control of a motor vehicle. *admission of consumption of alcoholic beverages. *Odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. *Bloodshot eyes. *Slurred speech. *Watery eyes. * My observed signs of impairment as he performed the standardized field sobriety. ARREST / ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) / CERTIFIED BREATH TEST (AGREED)/ SGT. Behringer #0257 (Maryland State Police). I arrested SIMPSON for driving under the influence of Alcohol at approximately 0651 hours. SIMPSON was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. He was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along with as the DR-15 Advice of Rights was played to him from the official MVA website from inside my patrol vehicle. At the conclusion of the DR-15, SIMPSON agreed to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the DR-15, indicating the same at approximately 0722 hours. SIMPSON was transported to Maryland State Police JFK Memorial Highway Barrack for processing, where a mouth check was performed 20 minutes before his submission to the breath test. SIMPSON provided two breath examples with positive results of .09 BRAC (0821 hours). SIMPSON was transported to the Bel Air Barrack and was given all copies of pertinent paperwork. SIMPSON was released to a sober adult that came to Bel Air Barrack. INTOXIMETER RESULT: Results of .09 BRAC (0821 hours) SIMPSON was uncooperative during the processing. Case Status  Closed by arrest. All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 20:35:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 01:24:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sander</LastName>
            <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5948</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517252</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/06/2023 06:51:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/06/2023 13:36:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 10:28:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/06/2023 13:36:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 18:46:31</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>384413</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Simpson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/17/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S512</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Simpson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>NMN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/17/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/06/2023 13:22:39</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S512</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Simpson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/17/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S512</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Simpson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>NMN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/17/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S512</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/06/2023 13:22:39</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1136</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Riverboat</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Annapolis</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21409</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.48046</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.030535</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>929</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>219</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2112</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 10:31:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 10:31:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 10:31:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/06/2023 13:36:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/06/2023 13:36:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155866</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 10:33:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 10:33:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <DateOfInfo>08/26/2023 19:32:09</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WBA4A7C54FD413908</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>BMW</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>6SERIES</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>PA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>PA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>MCB1992</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicNumber>MCB1992</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>