<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-029893</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/24/2023 16:00:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/24/2023 16:00:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/24/2023 15:26:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/24/2023 15:26:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/ Accident</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/24/2023 16:00:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6495</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 12:38:56</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>692610</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7580</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 14:24:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 14:24:46</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>692610</AddressId>
         <StreetName>CRAIN HWY @ TIMOTHY BRANCH DRIVE</StreetName>
         <City>BRANDYWINE</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20613</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.8761211209988</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.6746682696243</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/24/2023 16:00:00</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/24/2023 16:00:00</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/11/2023 12:38:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/24/2023 16:00:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:04:39</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Marked Car L-22: Dashcam unavailable.  Body Worn Camera: Body-worn camera operational.  Assisting Troopers/Officers: S/T Ortiz #5858  Defendant: Dana Chevonne Bussey  Date of Birth: 03/02/1980  Case Number: 23-MSP-029893       CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING  * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On 08/24/2023 at approximately 1526 hours I, Trooper Murray, was on routine patrol in my marked MSP patrol vehicle L-22, when I was traveling S/B RT 301 at Brandywine Rd. in Prince Georges County, Maryland. As I traveled S/B, I observed a truck pulling a trailer to the right shoulder. The driver of the vehicle waved his hand out of the window in an attempt to flag me down. I pulled in front of the vehicle and stepped out of my patrol vehicle. The driver informed me that if I picked up enough speed, I would be able to catch up to a tan Chevrolet Suburban. The driver informed me that he observed the above vehicle cutting other vehicles off, swerving and slamming on their brakes in front of other vehicles. I returned to my patrol vehicle in an attempt to investigate further. As I attempted to catch the vehicle the College Park duty officer came over the radio and stated that there was a lookout for a gold or tan Suburban, in the area of Brandywine. I informed him over the radio that I was in the area looking for that vehicle. At the intersection of S/B RT 301 at Timothy Branch I located a tan Chevrolet Suburban, bearing the Maryland registration 8BY0581. The vehicle was stopped in lane 1. The tan Chevrolet Suburban was approximately 30 feet behind the vehicle in front of it. I activated my emergency equipment and got behind the vehicle. After moving behind the tan Suburban, the driver stepped off the brake and drove forward approximately 30 feet. The driver of the tan Suburban had difficulty staying in the same lane of travel. The tan Suburbans right wheels crossed into lane 2 once, and nearly struck the curb on the left side of the roadway twice. The tan Suburban finally came to a stop at the intersection of S/B Rt 301 at Timothy Branch, due to traffic coming to a halt in front of it.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I made contact with the driver, who I later identified as Dana Chevonne Bussey (DOB 03/02/1980, B/F). I explained the reason for the stop, and requested Busseys drivers license and registration. Bussey began to look for her drivers license, and only produced it after several minutes of searching. She had to be reminded several times to retrieve her license. Bussey never produced a registration for the vehicle. While speaking with me, I noted that Busseys speech was slurred, and there was a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. I also noted that Busseys movements were slow and lethargic. In order to move Bussey safely out of the road, I requested that she drive to a nearby 7-Eleven parking lot. After Bussey had moved to the vehicle into a parking space, I positioned my vehicle behind the tan Suburban again. I approached the vehicle a second time and questioned the driver as to where exactly she was coming from.Bussey initially stated that she did not have any alcohol to drink when I questioned her, although I never asked whether she had consumed any alcohol. I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct a routine METERS/NCIC check. While I was seated in my patrol vehicle, Bussey exited her vehicle several times. She asked me Why is this necessary. several times. I asked her to return to her vehicle. When Bussey attempted to enter her vehicle, I observed that she had trouble standing on both feet.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed in the parking lot of the 7-Eleven located at the corner of RT 301 and Timothy Branch. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and the temperature was approximately 75 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of my patrol vehicles headlamps and my flashlight. Bussey appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries.  Injuries  None.  Glasses  Glasses, were not worn at the time of the evaluation.  Medical Conditions  None.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Busseys eyes. Bussey was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Busseys pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Bussey was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Bussey if she understood the instructions and she stated yes. During the course of the test, Bussey had to be reminded multiple times to keep her head straight, and to focus her eyes only on the stimulus.   1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes   2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes   3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes  VGN - Present in both eyes.  WALK AND TURN - REFUSED Prior to Bussey performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Bussey was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Bussey was unable to conduct the test due to being unable to place her feet in the required position for the instructional phase. While attempting to place her feet in the required position, Bussey was unable to touch her left and right foot heel to toe. Bussey nearly fell over several times. While attempting to assume the position required for the walk and turn, Bussey grabbed on to my wrist to help herself balance. After several minutes of trying, I told Bussey that we would move on to the next test.  ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed) Prior to Bussey performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Bussey was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised he was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Bussey if she understood the test and she indicated that she did. Instructional Stage:  1.) No clues observed.  Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10:  1.) Put foot down.  2.) Sways.  3.) Raises arms.   Seconds 11-20:  1.) Put foot down.  2.) Sways.  3.) Raises arms.    Seconds 21-30:  1.) Put foot down.  2.) Sways.  3.) Raises arms.  Bussey refused to submit to a PBT..  ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Bussey was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Observed driving.  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person.  * Statements from other witnesses as to the driving of a tan Suburban  * Difficulty locating requested documentation and needed to be reminded to provide me with her drivers license.  * My observed signs of impairment as she performed field sobriety tests.  * Slurred speech.  * Stated that she was sober on two separate occasions before I inquired as to whether she had been drinking  I arrested Bussey for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 1558 hours and she was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Forestville Barrack for processing. While attempting to place Bussey in the front passenger seat of my vehicle, Bussey resisted myself and S/T Ortiz. Bussey eventually sat in the vehicle after S/T Ortiz called her husband on her phone. While returning to the Forestville barrack, I played the DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Bussey in English. Bussey agreed to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the DR-15 indicating the same at approximately 1622 hours.   The intoximeter test was performed by Sgt. Landis #5082.  While in the process of taking the test, Bussey stated to myself and Sgt. Landis that she had drunk, and on one occasion that she had too much.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: *** 0.25 BrAC ***  Bussey was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released from to the custody of a sober individual. Bussey was polite and cooperative for the entirety of our interaction.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7580</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 14:49:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7580</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/09/2023 09:08:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ortiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Angel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5858</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oleyar</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6495</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Murray</LastName>
            <FirstName>Niall</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7580</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519342</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/24/2023 15:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7580</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 15:33:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7580</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 15:33:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519342</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/24/2023 15:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7580</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 15:34:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7580</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 15:34:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>43</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7580</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 14:39:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7580</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 09:35:27</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386199</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bussey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dana</FirstName>
               <DOB>03/02/1980 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/26/2023 14:38:11</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bussey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dana</FirstName>
               <DOB>03/02/1980 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/26/2023 14:38:11</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4959</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Morraine</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Waldorf</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20602</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5180</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.911659</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.576262</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7580</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 09:35:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7580</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 09:35:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7580</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 09:35:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7580</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 15:33:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7580</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 15:33:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156479</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7580</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 14:44:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7580</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 14:44:48</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3GNFK16337G210357</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2007</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SUB</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>TAN</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>TAN</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8BY0581</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>6</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>