<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-030997</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/03/2023 03:15:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/03/2023 03:15:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/03/2023 02:45:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/03/2023 02:45:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>09/03/2023 04:45:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>Robert George Garcoa was arrested for DUI/DWI. DUI folder # 23-96-268</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/03/2023 03:15:53</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 22:45:37</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>RACETRACK RD/ TAYLORVILLE LN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>671490</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/03/2023 03:15:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/08/2023 10:58:44</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>671490</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Racetrack</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.16608</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.365968</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10637-10945 RACETRACK RD / 10616-10725 TAYLORVILLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10520-10636 RACETRACK RD / 10616-10725 TAYLORVILLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/03/2023 03:15:52</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/03/2023 03:15:52</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/13/2023 07:46:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/03/2023 03:15:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI Folder # 23-96-268 SUSPECT: Robert George Garcia LICENSE #MD/ G-620-745-275-080 DUI CITATION # 3TM0VPH SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER: No ACCIDENT INVOLVED: No VIDEO: Maryland State Police; Axon Evidence Video ID #: 23MSP030997. BWC Utilized.  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:   I am trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).  I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of 2021.  I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of 2020.  I have apprehended more than 90 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.   Phase #1 - Vehicle in Motion:  On September 3, 2023, at approximately 0245 hours, I, TFC Pinto #7212, was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating unmarked MSP vehicle V-9 at westbound Ocean City Expressway near Mile Maker 8. I was stationary off the right side of the roadway when I observed the following on a white sports utility vehicle traveling westbound on Ocean City Expressway near Mile Marker 8:  OCEAN CITY EXPRESSWAY NEAR MILE MAKE 8:  1. The white sports utility vehicle pulled off the roadway into the right shoulder and remained stationary for approximately two minutes.  I safely pulled into the westbound Ocean City Expressway near Mile Maker 8 and closed in on the same white sports utility vehicle near Mile Marker 7.  OCEAN CITY EXPRESSWAY FROM MILE MARKER 7 TO RACETRACK ROAD: 2. The white sports utility vehicles left tires traveleddirectly on topof the left solid yellow center line on one (1) occasions. The vehicle abruptly weaved back into the westbound lane. 3. The white sports utility vehicles right tirescrossed(by at least one (1) tires width) the solid white shoulder line ontwo (2) occasions. The vehicleabruptly weaved back into the westbound lane each time. The white sports utility vehicle took the southbound Racetrack Road exit.   RACETRACK ROAD EXIT RAMP ONTO SOUTHBOUND RACETRACK ROAD : 4. The white sports utility vehicle failed to stop at the circular red traffic control device from the exit ramp onto southbound Racetrack Road.   RACETRACK ROAD TO TAYLORVILLE LANE: 5. The white sports utility vehicle crossed (approximately one (1) tires width) the solid double yellow center road lines on one (1) occasion. The vehicle drifted back into the southbound lane.  6. The white sports utility vehicle was exceeded the maximum posted speed limit traveling 63 MPH in a of 40 MPH zone using front same direction radar beam. The radar unit was tested before and after my tour of duty. 7. The white sports utility vehicle crossed the solid white line into the shoulder or right turn lane on two (2) occasions. The vehicle abruptly weaved back into the southbound lane each time.   ADDITIONAL OBSERVATIONS: 8. The vehicle failed to maintain proper lane position due to pronounced and excessive weaving (alternately moving toward one side of the lane and then the other) during the entire duration of my observations. 9. Total distance traveled was approximately 3.7 miles.  DWI INDICATORS / REASON FOR STOP 1. Weaving across lane lines 2. Drifting 3. Weaving 4. Failure to stop at circular red traffic control device 5. Exceeding the maximum posted speed limit  All of the above DWI indicators were exhibited by the same vehicle prior to my initiating a traffic stop.  TRAFFIC STOP  I activated the emergency lights to my patrol vehicle, initiating a traffic stop on the white sports utility vehicle at southbound Racetrack Road at Taylorville Lane.The vehicle came to a stop at southbound Racetrack Road at Taylorville Lane. The vehicle was a white GMC Yukon, bearing Maryland registration 7EX6244.  -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT-   I made contact with the driver via the drivers side door open window, and I immediately detectedthe strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop. I asked the driver for his license and registration. While speaking with the driver, I observed two passengers in the back seats of the vehicle and no one in the front passenger seat. I asked the driver where he was traveling, and he replied,I was going to take them to the casino.I asked the driver where he was traveling from and he stated, Uh this place called Spain, we had dinner. The driver provided his license and the driver was identified as Robert George Garcia (H/M 01/30/1970), by his Maryland drivers license. I asked Garcia how many alcoholic beverages he consumed before driving and advised him that I was detecting the odor of an alcoholic beverage, and he stated, Probably about two hours ago. I asked Garcia what alcoholic beverage he consumed, and he replied, Uh I just had a beer two hours ago. Garcia was unbale to locate his registration card. I advised him once he found it to hold it out his drivers side window.    As Garcia spoke, I made the following observations:  1. I intentionally observed his eyes to beglassy and bloodshot. 2. Garcia admitted consuming one alcoholic beverages before operating the motor vehicle. 3. I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the passenger compartment of the vehicle. 4. Garcia was wearing ablue bandand a purple band that read Fagers Island on his right wrist (consistent with wristbands provided to bar patrons to indicate that the patron is at least 21 years old).  I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Garcia.  I later returned to the white GMC and requested Garcia exit the vehicle, walk to the front of it, and he complied. While at the front of the vehicle, I advised Garcia that I was going to put him through some tests to make sure he can operate his vehicle safely. I advised Garcia I was going to ask him some questions and requested he stand with his feet together, hands by his side, and to remain in that position, and he complied.     I asked Garcia how many alcoholic beverages he consumed before operating the motor vehicle, and he stated,I just told you I just had one.   I asked Garcia where he consumed the alcoholic beverages, and he replied, Just at, just at Fagers.  I asked Garcia what type of alcoholic beverages he consumed, and he responded,Uh I remember a club soda, but club soda, a club, club soda and, and maybe I dont, I dont know what he got me, but just a club soda.  I asked Garcia what time he consumed his last alcoholic beverage, and he replied,2 hours ago. I advised Garcia it was currently 0255 hours and asked if he consumed his last alcoholic beverage around midnight, and he responded, That sounds right.  During my second interaction with Garcia, I observed the following: 5. I detected thestrong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. 6. I continued to observe Garcias eyes to beblood shot and glassy.  -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING-  STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder area. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight, vehicle headlamps, and street lamps. Weather was clear. I asked Garcia if he has any physical disabilities, and he stated,Uh, I mean, I got a bad knee, but its, its fine. I asked Garcia if is physical disability affects his daily walking, and he replied, Little bit, but its, its fine. I asked Garcia what was wrong with his knee, and he responded, Uh, just left knee over time. Running a lot of marathons. I asked Garcia if he has any medical disabilities, and he stated,No.I asked Garcia if he has any recent injuries, and he replied,No.I asked Garcia if he is currently on any medications, and he responded,Lipitor.I asked Garcia what Lipitor is for and he stated, Its for cholesterol. I asked Garcia if it states on his Lipitor prescription if he should not take it and drive, and he replied, No. I advised Garcia I observed he wears glasses. I asked Garcia if I hold a pen approximately 12 inches from his face if he could follow and pen, and he responded, I think so.   Garcia was wearing a brown button up shirt, white pants, and brown scandals.  **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. A pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from eyes, slightly above eye level. Garcia was instructed to look straight ahead at my pen, instructed to follow the pen with his eyes and eyes only, and keep his head and shoulders still. When asked if he understood the instructions, Garcia replied,Yupp.Garcia eyes were brown, were equal in size, and showed equal tracking. I observed there was no resting nystagmus.  1. Garcia displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  2. Garcia displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  3. Garcia displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.  **WALK AND TURN: 5 of 8 clues**  Before the test, I asked Garcia if he wanted to conduct the test in his sandals or wanted to take them off and he decided to keep them on. I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Garcia was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot, touching heel to toe. Garcia was instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. I asked Garcia if he understood to remain in the starting position, and he stated,Yea sure.Garcia was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step. Garcia was told to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Garcia was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Garcia was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. I advised Garcia I was taking three (3) steps for instructional purposes, but he was to take nine (9) steps. Garcia was explained he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keeping his hands down by his sides, looking down at his feet, and to count every step out loud. When Garcia was asked if he understood the test he stated,Yea. I asked Garcia if he had any questions and he stated, I think so.  Instructional Stage:  1. Garcia failed to remain in starting position by losing balance and place his left foot next to his right.  First 9 Steps: 2. Garciastepped off the lineon step: 8 3. Garcia missed heal to toe on step: 9  Turn Stage:  4. Improper turn - Garcia pivoted both feet in place at the same time to turn around.   Second 9 Steps: 5. Garcia raised arms for balanceon steps: 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9 6. Garcia stopped walking on step: 1  While Garcia performed the test, I observed the following observations: 1. Garcia started with his left foot in front of his right when he was instructed multiple times to start with his left foot on the line and his right foot in front.  2. Garcia stopped after conducting the turn improperly and asked if he walks back.   **ONE LEG STAND: 3 out of 4 clues**  Prior to Garcia performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his foot, keep his toe pointed forward, keep his hands at his sides, to count out loud by thousands (one-one thousand, two- one thousand, three- one thousand), and to continue the test until told to stop. When Garcia was asked if he understood the instructions he replied,yea.When told to begin Garcia lifted his right leg.     GarciaSwayedfrom left to right and right to left: 1 to 10 seconds and 11 to 20 second.  Garcia hopped: 1 to 10 seconds, 11 to 20 seconds, and 21 to 30 seconds.  Garciaused his arms for balance: 1 to 10 seconds, 11 to 20 seconds, and 21 to 30 seconds.   ADDITIONAL TESTING  **ALPHABET TEST**:  Garcia advised that he was a high school graduate and that he was capable of reciting the English alphabet and numbers. I instructed Garcia to recite from the letter F to the letter T.  -Garcia recited in the following manner:F-G-H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P. Garcia then asked, When did you say stop? I advised Garcia T and he then recited, E-F-G-H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P-Q-R-S-T.  **COUNT TEST**:  I instructed Garcia to count backwards from 59 to 36.  -Garcia counted in the following manner:59-58-57-56-55-54-53-52-51-50-49-48-47-47-46-40-45-44-43-44-42-41, 40, 39, 38, 37, 36, 35, 34, 33, 32, 31 30. I know I, I went more you ask me to.  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)  After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Garcia the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Garcia refused to submit to a PBT. Upon placing Garcia under arrest, Garcia advised he wanted to submit to the PBT. Garcia submitted to a PBT with a reading of0.11BrAC.   ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Garcia was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: * Driving vehicle in a negligent manner which caused it to commit 6 lane violations in addition to excessive weaving DRIVING SKILLS IMPAIRED. * Driving vehicle above the posted speed limit and failed to stop a red traffic control device. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot. * Admission to consuming at least one (1) alcoholic beverage prior to operating a motor vehicle. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. * I observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests.  I determined that Garcia was under the influence an alcoholic beverage that adversely affected his ability to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests properly can also adversely affect the persons ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. I placed Garcia under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0315 hours on September 3, 2023.  TRANSPORT  Garcia was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. Garcia was transported to the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack for processing. During transport, the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Garcia continued to be strong.  ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)  Upon arrival at the barrack, Garcia was given his Advice of Rights via the audio version of the DR-15 Form (played through speakers of a computer). A copy of the DR-15 Form was given to Garcia, and he was asked to follow along. At the conclusion of the audio version, Garcia was asked if he wanted to submit to the intoximeter test, and he refused to submit to a breath test at approximately 0356 hours on September 3, 2023. Garcia changed his mind and at 0357 hours advised he agreed to a breath test. While Corporal Snell was entering information into the intoximeter instrument for Garcia to submit to the test, Garcia changed his mind a third time and at 0412 hours refused the test. This time, Garcia was asked if he was sure he did not want to submit to the test, told this was his last opportunity, and he advised he was sure he did not want to submit to the test.   After the refusal was submitted into the intoximeter instrument, Garcia advised he wanted to submit to the test. Garcia was advised that the refusal was already submitted into the instrument, and it was too late.   RELEASE  Garcia was released to a valid sober driver and advised not to drive for 12 hours.  CHARGES  Garcia was charged with the following citations:    Driving Vehicle While Under the Influence of Alcohol (3TM0VPH)  Driving Vehicle While Impaired by Alcohol (3TN0VPH)  Negligent Driving (3TP0VPH)  Reckless Driving (3TQ0VPH)  Driver Failure to Obey Properly Placed Traffic Control Device Instructions (3TR0VPH)  Driver Failure to Stop at Steady Circular Red Signal (3TS0VPH)  Exceeding Posted Maximum Speed Limit: 63 MPH in a Posted 40 MPH Zone (3TT0VPH)   Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/10/2023 08:14:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/10/2023 10:27:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Benjamin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7043</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Drew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>520446</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/03/2023 03:15:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/08/2023 10:56:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/08/2023 11:00:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>53</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/08/2023 10:56:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/08/2023 11:01:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>325021</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Garcia</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>George</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/30/1970 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/31/2021 13:41:50</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Garcia</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>George</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/30/1970 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/31/2021 13:41:50</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1502</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Park Hill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Fallston</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21047</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2136</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.4377992</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.5087348</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>286</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0296</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/08/2023 11:01:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/08/2023 11:01:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/08/2023 10:58:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/08/2023 10:58:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156891</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/08/2023 11:03:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/08/2023 11:03:53</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>G62074525080</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>YUK</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7EX6244</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>12</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>