<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025256</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/15/2023 01:42:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/15/2023 01:42:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/15/2023 01:23:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/15/2023 01:23:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>OLUGBADE "P" 23-087</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 01:42:57</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 10:45:53</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>JESSUP RD/ MD-295 SB TO JESSUP EB</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>700955</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 01:42:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/16/2023 09:42:17</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>700955</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Jessup</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Jessup</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2808-2816 JESSUP RD / 1-170 MD-295 SB TO JESSUP EB</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/15/2023 01:42:53</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/15/2023 01:42:53</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/01/2023 10:45:55</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 01:42:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:29:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E) TEAM* MVR Statement: The following incident was captured on in-car and Body camera. Title: OLUGBADE P 23-087. ID: 23-MSP-025256.  Arrested: Olugbade, Adewale Ismail. Certification and training  -Trained in Field Sobriety Test through Maryland State Police Academy.  -Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E)  -Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  - Graduated from The Institute of Advanced Law Enforcement Studies Driving Under the Influence Institute-University of Maryland.  - I have apprehended more than 240 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On July 15, 2023, at approximately 0121 hours, I, TFC. I. Riba Tankari # 7058 with Maryland State Police was traveling westbound MD-175 (Annapolis Road) east of Disney Road, Anne Arundel County, Maryland in lane #2 (middle lane). My issued patrol vehicle is Maryland State Police marked unit DUI-3. At that time, I observed a black Maserati SUV bearing Maryland registration 8EY8309 traveling westbound MD-175 in lane #3 (right lane) unable to stay within a single lane. I observed the Maserati had crossed the solid white line from lane #3 into the bike lane by one tire width on one occasion. I changed lane into lane #3 and observed the Maserati had merged into lane #2 before changing lane into lane #1 (left lane). I followed the Maserati and observed the vehicle had crossed the dotted white line from lane #1 into lane #2 by one tire width on one occasion before coming to a stop at a red circular traffic light in the intersection of westbound MD-174 and Ridge Road passing the stop line by more than one tire length. After the light turned green, I observed the Maserati continued traveling westbound MD-175 in lane #1. I continued to follow the Maserati and observed the vehicle had swerved from lane #1 into lane #2 by one tire width, appeared to be traveling over the posted speed limit, and with my properly functioning patrol vehicle Golden Eagle II radar unit set activated, I obtained a speed reading of 57 in a posted 40 MPH zone. I initiated a traffic stop on the Maserati using my emergency equipment. The Maserati came to a stop in the area of westbound MD-175 and west of Parkside Blvd, Jessup, Maryland in lane #2. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the Maserati on the driver side and made contact with the driver and a female passenger sitting in the front passenger seat of the vehicle. I introduced myself and explained to him the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver where he was coming from, and he stated i am coming from picking her up. I again asked the driver where he was coming from, and he stated home. I requested his drivers license and registration card. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I observed that the driver had watery and glassy eyes. The driver was identified through his Maryland drivers license as Olugbade, Adewale Ismail. I returned to my patrol vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with. I returned to the Maserati and requested Olugbade to exit his vehicle and to walk to the front of his vehicle and he complied. I asked Olugbade how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed, and he stated I had like two beers I asked him what kind of beer, and he stated Heineken. I asked him is that a bottle or cup, and he stated a bottle. I asked him around what time, and he stated one thirty about twelve thirty, less two hours. While speaking with Olugbade outside his vehicle, I again detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I asked Olugbade to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and he agreed. The evaluation surface was dry, flat, and free of debris. No surface defects were observed. My patrol flashlight, his vehicle headlights, and surrounding lightning lit the area. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Olugbade appeared to be in good physical conditions and was wearing black sandals which he removed during the test. I asked Olugbade the following questions: Medical conditions: High blood pressure. Medications: High blood pressure medications. Anything that will prevent you from walking on straight line or standing on one leg: No Glasses or contact: I noticed, Olugbade was wearing glasses but denied wearing contacts. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: (6/6 clues observed). The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus - Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes - Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes - Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Notes: * During the HGN test, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Olugbades breath. WALK AND TURN: (5/8 clues observed). The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Olugbade stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage: Olugbade lost his balance to the right on three separate occasions then to the left on four separate occasions. I instructed Olugbade to return to the instructional position several times. Walking Stage (1st Nine): Raised his arms more than six (6) inches away from his body for balance on counts 1, 2, 3, and 4. Stepped completely offline by one shoe width on count 1. Took eight actual steps when instructed to take 9. Notes *Olugbade took eight steps but counted nine. He started counting prior to taking the first step. Turn: The turn was not completed correctly; instead Olugbade turned to his right failing to take a series of small steps as instructed and demonstrated. Walking Stage (2nd Nine Stepped completely offline by one shoe width on counts 1 and 8. Raised his arms more than six (6) inches away from his body for balance on counts 5, 6, and 8. One Leg Stand Test (2/4 observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Olugbade stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Left foot raised during the test. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: Swayed body to the right and left. Left foot hit ground two times. Seconds 11-20: Swayed body to the right and left. Left foot hit ground one time. Seconds 21-30: Swayed body to the right and left. Left foot hit ground three times. Preliminary Breath Test:  I explained and offered a PBT to Olugbade. Olugbade elected to consent to the PBT and results were .13 BAC. ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Olugbade was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a motor vehicle safely:  -Unable to stay within a single lane/driving patterns.  -Driving over the posted speed limit (57 Mph in 40 Mph speed limit zone)  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath as he conversed with me.  -Eyes watery and glassy.  -His admissions to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to driving.  -Observed signs of impairment as he performed the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  - Preliminary Breath Test result of .13 BrAC.  Olugbade was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a motor vehicle at 0142 hours and was transported to the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack. A search incident to arrest revealed no weapons or contraband. Upon arrival in the Barrack, Olugbade was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and it was read to him from the MVA website in English, and he refused to consent to the Intoximeter EC/IR II test at 0219 hours. A properly functioning instrument and operator where available. Olugbade was polite and cooperative during the encounter.  Olugbade was given pertinent paperwork, released from the barrack to his wife pending an appearance in the District Court of Maryland for Anne Arundel County at a later date.  All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 09:47:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/27/2023 11:52:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514698</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/15/2023 01:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 09:43:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/16/2023 09:44:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>53</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 09:43:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382667</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>OLUGBADE</LastName>
               <FirstName>ADEWALE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ISMAIL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/04/1970 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/16/2023 09:19:25</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>O421</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A340</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>OLUGBADE</LastName>
               <FirstName>ADEWALE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ISMAIL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/04/1970 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>O421</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A340</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/16/2023 09:19:25</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2243</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Brimstone</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hanover</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21076</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1871</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.743514</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.147907</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 09:46:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 09:46:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 09:46:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 09:43:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/16/2023 09:43:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155186</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 09:47:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/16/2023 09:47:04</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2ZN661XUS2HX220219</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MASE</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8EY8309</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>4</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleValue>1000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>