<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-024077</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/05/2023 09:28:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/05/2023 09:28:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/05/2023 08:50:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/05/2023 08:50:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Male subject stole the bucket to a skid-loader from a construction site utilizing a skid loader that was stolen from another location.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/05/2023 09:28:37</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5869</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/30/2023 12:07:29</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>STP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>THT</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>THVP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>50859</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/05/2023 09:28:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 03:33:50</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>50859</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>31997</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Beaver Run</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Salisbury</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21804</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.503091</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.376327</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/05/2023 09:28:34</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/05/2023 09:28:34</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/30/2023 12:07:30</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/05/2023 09:28:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>BWC Footage (On Scene):https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=9a5b314e45bf4949a7603b61d5b88312partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 BWC Footage (Property Recovery):https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=037157cc1feb45b0a1d248b24ca07535partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  Location: 31997 Beaver Run Drive Salisbury MD 21804  Scene Description: Construction site for future 7/11 Gas Station/Convenience Store  Scene Processing: I took Several Photographs of the scene and of the Bucket when I located it at the suspects property. I also obtained CCTV footage from a neighboring property showing the suspect vehicle, suspects and the theft of the property.  Narrative: On 7/5/2023 @ 0850 hrs, I S/Tpr Shelter responded to 31997 Beaver Run Rd Salisbury MD 21804 for the report of a theft. Upon my arrival, I contacted the complainant, Richard Reynolds, the owner of Reynolds Excavating. He advised me his company was contracted to do construction work at the property, and they have numerous pieces of equipment on the job site located at 31997 Beaver Run Rd. He said that upon arriving at the site around 6:30 am on todays date (7/5/2023), it was discovered that a black Caterpillar skid-loader bucket was missing from the job site. He told me that when he had left the job site on 6/30/23 around 5pm, the skid-loader bucket was on the property, and that none of his employees would have moved or picked it up after that point. No one was given permission to take or use the bucket at any time or remove it from the property. He said that no one was on the job site from 6/30/23 after 5pm through 7/5/23 at around 6:30am.  Reynolds told me that he was speaking with a friend over the weekend, a Jerry Bedsworth, owner of Bips Service Center in Princess Anne MD. Bedsworth told him that a Bobcat skid-loader had been stolen from him over the weekend, and that the State Police recovered it from an address in Parsonsburg Md. When Bedsworths Bobcat was recovered, he said that it was found with a Caterpillar skid-loader bucket attached to it, which Bedsworth noted was not his, and stated that the bucket was left at the property it was found at. Bedsworth also noted that his Bobcat had a badly leaking hydraulic cylinder. I did later contact Bedsworth via telephone to confirm that information.  When Reynolds arrived at the job-site this morning, he observed Bobcat skid loader tire tracks traveling from Beaver Run road onto the property in the loose dirt of the construction site. He also noted that he saw a trail of an oily fluid that was similar to hydraulic oil soaked into the pavement, in the path the Bobcat took onto the job site. The tire tracks went onto the property, to where his skid-loader bucket was located, and then lead away back to the property entrance in a similar path. At that time, he contacted the police about the theft, surmising that the skid-loader bucket that was attached to Bedsworths Bobcat when it was recovered was his.  While I was on the scene, I did observe hydraulic oil stains on Beaver Run Rd and the ingress and egress path tracks from the bobcat, which have a unique knobby and blocky pattern. The path led from the entrance into the property from Beaver Run Rd to where the skid loader bucket was previously placed in an open area. The property is an active construction site and is marked with visible No Trespassing signs. Reynolds stated that the skid-loader bucket is very heavy and would need a Bobcat or tracked loader to pick up and move. He advised that a replacement bucket would cost around $2,000 dollars. Reynolds later provided me with a price quote from Caterpillar pricing a similar bucket at $1,915.00.  Located across the street from the construction site is Salisbury Route 50 Self Storage, a self storage facility. The address is 32000 Beaver Run Rd Salisbury MD 21804. The facility is equipped with CCTV cameras. The cameras field of view includes the entrance and front parking lot, which captures the Beaver Run Rd entrance to 31997 Beaver Run Rd. I was able to obtain footage from the facility. The footage shows that on 7/1/2023 at around 0517hrs, a black Dodge pickup truck pulling an open utility trailer, parked on which, was a white Bobcat skid loader, pull up near the entrance to 31997 Beaver Run Rd. a man exits the pickup truck, and walks back to the trailer. The camera then cuts to 0521 hrs, showing the Bobcat driving back towards the trailer, with a Black bucket attached to the front of the unit. Someone was driving the machine, and another male subject was walking behind the machine as it drove onto the trailer. The men then drove away with the Bobcat and the stolen bucket. A second camera clip captures the entire event without interruption. I was able to obtain a digital copy of the footage, which was burned to a DVD. The DVD was stored on an MSP Form-67, Chain of Custody in the Barrack E Temp Storage.    I was able to learn via the MSP reporting system, the Caliber Public Safety Online RMS, that Bedsworth reported the Bobcat stolen on 7/1/23, with camera footage capturing the theft at around 0333hrs on 7/1/23. On 7/2/2023 at 1718hrs, during the course of the investigation, Troopers from the MSP Salisbury Barrack, assisting the Princess Anne Barrack, responded to 32472 Old Ocean City Rd Parsonsburg Md, where they located Bedsworths stolen bobcat, and came into contact with a Michael Stewart Matusky Jr. (DOB 12/17/1977), who was placed under arrest for the theft of the Bobcat. Tpr Wright of the MSP Princess Anne Barrack was the primary investigator in that case (23-MSP-023672) and the case was ultimately forwarded to S/Tpr Corron assigned to the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division (CED)-Lower Eastern Shore.    I then responded to 32472 Old Ocean City Rd Parsonsburg Md 21849. I was unable to locate Matusky at the property, but did contact a Susan Hutcherson (DOB 10-7-1950), who resides at the residence. She said she knew Matusky, but was un aware of any stolen property and advised me I could look around the yard. Located in plain view in the backyard of the property I located a black Caterpillar skid-loader bucket on the ground. I observed it had a data plate with serial # A4186BK20779. Contact was made with Reynolds, and he arrived to the property and identified the ski-loader bucket as belonging to him and his company. He was then able to recover it from that location and return it to service.  Based on the information provided to me by Reynolds, Bedsworth, the camera footage of the theft, as well as on-scene evidence and the investigation into the theft and recovery of the stolen Bobcat, the same piece of equipment was utilized to steal the skid-loader bucket from 31197 Beaver Run Rd Salisbury Maryland and bring it to Matuskys property, where it was found attached to the Bobcat Matusky stole on 7/2/23. Based on The timeline of events and the camera footage obtained from the Salisbury Route 50 Self Storage, a black Dodge pickup truck with an open utility trailer containing a white Bobcat Skid loader without an implement on the front was observed entering the 31997 Beaver Run Rd on 7/1/23 at 0517hrs, exiting the camera view before returning into the cameras field of view at 0521 hrs, with a black bucket attached to the front.Additionally, on 7/3/2023 @ 1233hrs, I responded to 32472 Old Ocean City Rd Parsonsburg assisting Tpr Bynum in an unrelated theft case, of which Matusky was a primary suspect. On that date in question, I observed a Black Dodge Pickup with black wheels parked on the property, displaying MD registration 5EH9091. An MVA search revealed that vehicle being registered to Matusky.   Based on my firsthand knowledge of Matuskys vehicle and information obtained and photographs taken in Tpr Wrights investigation, The black Dodge pickup truck as well as the open utility trailer and the stolen Bobcat located at Matuskys residence, 32472 Old Ocean City Rd Parsonsburg MD 21849, match the black Dodge pickup and the utility trailer observed in the obtained camera footage, notably the black rims on the Dodge and the Bobcat. The photos taken of the Bobcat in Tpr Wrights investigation depict the Bobcat with Reynolds Bucket still attached to the machine.  An application for charges was completed for Matusky and submitted to the Wicomico County District Court Commissioner. On 7/5/2023 the Commissioner returned a Criminal Summons for Matusky.  A copy of all related paperwork and documents are attached to this report. The DVD containing the recovered camera footage is stored in the MSP Barrack E Temp Storage as evidence. Photos taken of the scene and the recovered property will be uploaded to Veri-Pic.  Ref related MSP CC# 23-MSP-023672. (Tpr Wrights investigation), MSP CC# 23-MSP-023868 (Tpr Bynums investigation.)  At this time, I have been unable to locate Michael Matusky.  I request this case remain OPEN pending locating Matusky and serving him with his charges.  ALL EVENT OCCURRED IN WICOMICO COUNTY MD  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/21/2023 03:34:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5979</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/30/2023 11:25:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Weber</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5869</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shelter</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5979</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513516</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1136_23G</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>06</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/05/2023 08:50:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1136_23G</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/20/2023 04:40:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5979</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/20/2023 04:40:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513516</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 2210</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>06</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/05/2023 08:50:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 2210</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 09:22:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5979</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/30/2023 09:22:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>46</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/21/2023 03:38:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:15</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>92069</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Matusky</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Stewart</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/17/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.2019982E8</SSN>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>03/04/2016 10:09:06</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Matusky</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Stewart</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/17/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.2019982E8</SSN>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>M320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/04/2016 10:09:06</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>30069</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hudson Corner</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Marion Station</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21838</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.71223</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.048543</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>32472</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Old Ocean City</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21849</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.486164</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.386699</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/21/2023 03:38:22</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>74</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 07:07:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>6068</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Reynolds</LastName>
               <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Douglas</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/08/1948 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/03/2014 13:11:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R543</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R263</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Reynolds</LastName>
               <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Douglas</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/08/1948 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R543</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R263</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/03/2014 13:11:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetName>Loretta</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Princess Anne</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21853</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.693192</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.222231</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3659</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>ALLEN</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>EDEN</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21822</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.677119</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.294215</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>430</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8925</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/03/2014 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 07:07:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 07:07:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>64</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 07:23:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:11</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>225626</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bedsworth</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jerry</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Harold</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/15/1958 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/25/2019 15:06:58</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B326</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bedsworth</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jerry</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Harold</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/15/1958 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B326</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/25/2019 15:06:58</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11120</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Drawbridge</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Princess Anne</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.78500192629289</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.187724985464094</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>651</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3481</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/25/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 07:23:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>72</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 07:25:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:11</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383823</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hutcherson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Susan</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/07/1950 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/30/2023 07:25:25</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H326</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hutcherson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Susan</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/07/1950 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H326</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/30/2023 07:25:25</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>32472</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Old Ocean City</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Parsonsburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21849</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2006</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.485515</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.392342</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 07:25:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 09:22:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5979</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/30/2023 09:22:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>7</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 08:20:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5979</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/30/2023 08:20:34</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Black Caterpillar skid loader bucket.  </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>996</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>1915</PropertyValue>
         <Value>1915</Value>
         <SerialNumber>A4186BK20779</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>252404</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>Caterpillar</Make>
         <Model>279-5376</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>