<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-020881</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/11/2023 00:36:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/11/2023 00:36:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/11/2023 00:11:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/11/2023 00:11:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>06/11/2023 01:45:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>Valerie Kaye Grimes was arrested for DUI/ DWI. DUI Folder 23-96-157</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 00:36:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/28/2023 23:32:21</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY/ HERRING CREEK LN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>534329</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 00:36:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/23/2023 08:45:54</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>534329</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.136499</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.338015</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>RED LIGHT DISTRICT EB  50</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12026-12042 OCEAN GTWY / 9739-9940 HERRING CREEK LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12044-12156 OCEAN GTWY / 9739-9940 HERRING CREEK LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11851-11999 OCEAN GTWY / 9900-9999 HERRING CREEK LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12001-12099 OCEAN GTWY / 9900-9999 HERRING CREEK LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11851-11999 OCEAN GTWY / 0-0 HERRING CREEK LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/11/2023 00:36:01</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/11/2023 00:36:01</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/28/2023 11:39:51</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 00:36:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI Folder # 23-96-157 SUSPECT: Valerie Kaye Grimes LICENSE #MD/ G-652-839-461-138 DUI CITATION # 3KQ0VPH SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER: Yes ACCIDENT INVOLVED: No VIDEO: Maryland State Police; Axon Evidence Video ID #: 23MSP020881. BWC Utilized.  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:   I am trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).  I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of 2021.  I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of 2020.  I have apprehended more than 80 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.   Phase #1 - Vehicle In Motion:,  On June 11, 2023, at approximately 0011 hours, I, Tfc. Pinto #7212 was on duty, operating unmarked Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle V-9, patrolling in the area westbound Ocean Gateway east of Keyser Point Road, Ocean City, Worcester County Maryland in lane 2. At this time, I observed a black Ford passenger car bearing Pennsylvania registration, LRX 3231, that was traveling westbound on Ocean Gateway east of Kyser Point Road and crossed the dotted white line, with its passenger side tires, by approximately one (1) tire width from lane 2 into the right turn lane and slowly drift back into lane 2. I remained behind the black Ford in lane 2 at westbound Ocean Gateway east of Blue Marlin Drive when I observed the vehicle cross the white solid line, with its passenger side tires, from lane 2, into the right turn lane, by approximately one (1) tire width, and slowly drift into lane 2. While behind the black Ford in lane 2, at westbound Ocean Gateway east of Old Bridge Road when I observed the vehicle cross the dotted white line, with its passenger tires, by approximately a half (1/2) of tire width from lane 2, into the right turn lane, and drift back into lane 2. The black Ford continued westbound on Ocean Gateway east of Old Bridge Road in lane 2 when I observed the vehicle travel across the solid white line with its passenger side tires by approximately two (2) tires width, from lane 2, into the right shoulder area, and weave back into lane 2. I continue behind the black Ford, in lane 2, at westbound Ocean Gateway east of Man O War Lane when I observed the vehicle travel across the white dotted line with its passenger side tires, by a half (1/2) a tires width, and drift back into lane 2. I remained behind the black Ford at westbound Ocean Gateway east of Herring Creek Lane when I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the black Ford. The black Ford came to a stop in the right shoulder at westbound Ocean Gateway west of Herring Creek Lane.  Upon my approach to make contact with the driver on the passenger side of the vehicle, I observed the black Ford was drifting backwards toward my patrol vehicle. I ran to the back of the black Ford, yelled for the driver to put the vehicle in park, and pushed on the vehicle to see if the vehicle was in neutral. At this time, I noticed the black Ford was in reverse, continued to drift backwards, and I yelled at the driver to put the vehicle in park. The black Ford came to a stop approximately 2 feet from my patrol vehicle.   Phase 2 - Personal Contact  Upon contact with the driver of the vehicle, from the passenger side open window, I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the passenger compartment of the vehicle. I identified myself, and explained to the driver the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver for her license and her registration. The driver provided the registration and advised she dropped her license and needed to open the drivers door to get it. I advised the driver I that I would walk around to the drivers side of the vehicle to watch for other vehicles. Upon contact with the driver on the drivers side open window, she handed me her drivers license, and I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the passenger department of the vehicle. I identified the driver as Valerie Kaye Grimes (W/F 02/22/1979), by her Maryland Drivers license. I asked Grimes if she still resided at the Hagerstown address on her address and she stated, Yupp. I asked Grimes where she was traveling to and she stated, Hagerstown. I asked Grimes where she was traveling from and she stated, The Bar. I asked Grimes how many alcoholic beverages she consumed before driving and she stated, about two. I asked Grimes what time she consumed her last alcoholic beverage and she asked, What time is it. I advised Grimes it was currently 12:12 AM and she stated, 10:30. I asked Grimes if she was headed back home now and she stated, Yupp. I asked Grimes if she owned the black Ford or if it is a rental and she stated, Its a pay as you go car.While speaking with Grimes, I observed her eyes to be glassy.  I returned to my patrol vehicle, conducted routine checks on Grimes, and asked for back-up for Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  Phase #3 - Pre Arrest Screening    I deactivated my front emergency equipment. I approached the drivers window, advised Grimes I want to put her through some tests to make sure she is okay to drive, and asked Grimes to exit her vehicle to continue my investigation and she complied. While Grimes stepped out of the vehicle, Grimes stated, Yes Maam Sir.   While at the front of the black Ford, I observed was wearing a black t-shirt, blue jeans, and gray tennis shoes. I also detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Grimes breath and person.  I advised Grimes I was going to ask her some questions and while I did so I asked her to stand with her feet together and hands by her side and she complied. I asked Grimes how many alcoholic beverages she consumed this evening and she stated, Since six oclock probably about three and a half. I asked Grimes where she consumed the alcoholic beverages and she slurred her speck and I could not understand her. I asked Grimes which bar and stated, Pool Bar. Grimes then stated, Caribbean Bar is the name of it. I asked Grimes if she was staying in the location of the bar and she stated, No, I go down for my friends band playing and going back home. I asked Grimes what types of alcoholic beverages she consumed and she stated, They were mixed drinks. I asked Grimes what type of mixed drinks and she stated, Sex with an Alligator. I advised Grimes that I have not heard of that drink before and she stated, Jager, black rasmelon, and sour. I asked Grimes when she consumed her last alcoholic beverage and advised her it is currently 1219 hours, and she stated, Ten fifteen ten thirty. I asked Grimes if she has any physical disabilities and she stated, Nope. I asked Grimes if she has any medical disabilities and she stated, Nope. I asked Grimes if she has any recent injuries that would prevent her from walking in a straight line or standing on one leg and she stated, Nope. I asked Grimes if she was currently on any medications and she stated, Besides Benadryl for allergies then no. I asked Grimes if she wears glasses or contacts and she stated, Glasses. I observed Grimes did not have glasses on. I asked Grimes if I held a pen approximately twelve inches from her face if can follow the pen with her eyes and she stated, Yupp.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6 clues observed)     The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. Grimes was asked to stand with her feet together and hands by her side. A pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Grimes eyes, slightly above eye level. Grimes was instructed to look straight ahead at my pen and instructed to follow the pen with her eyes and eyes only. When asked if she understood the instructions, Grimes stated, Yes sir. Grimes pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I observed there was no resting nystagmus.  Lack of smooth pursuit: Present in both eyes  Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation: Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees: Present in both eyes  For information purposes, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Grimes breath and person while conducting the test. I also observed her eyes to be glassy.   Walk and Turn(3/8)  Weather: Clear and Dry Surface: Flat and free from debris   The next test was the Walk and Turn test, Grimes was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot, touching heel to toe. Grimes was instructed to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. When asked if she understood, Grimes stated, Yes sir.  Grimes was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step. Grimes was told to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Grimes was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Grimes was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. I advised Grimes I was taking three (3) steps for instructional purposes, but she was to take nine (9) steps. Grimes was instructed once she began the test keeping her hands down by her sides, looking down at her feet, and to count every step out loud. When Grimes was asked if she understood she stated, Yupp.   Instructional Stage:  No clues observed.   Walking Stage (1st Nine):   Stepped Off Line: Step 4 Missed Heal to Toe: Steps 5 and 9  Turn: Unsatisfactory. Grimes took kept both her feet on the line, pivoted both feet, and turned around without taking a series of small stops to turn around.   Walking State (2ndNine):  Missed Heel to Toe: Steps 3, 6, 7, 8, 9 Stepped Off Line: Steps 4   One Leg Stand(3/4 Clues)  Weather: Same as Above Surface: Same as Above  Prior to Grimes performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Grimes was instructed to stand with her feet together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, watch her foot, keep her toe pointed forward, keep her hands at his sides, to count out loud by thousands (one-one thousand, two- one thousand), and to continue the test until told to stop. Grimes was asked if she understood and she stated, yes.  Put Foot Down: 0-10 seconds, 11-20 seconds, 21-30 seconds Raised Arms for Balance: 0-10 seconds, 21-30 seconds Sways: 0-10 seconds, 11-20 seconds, 21-30 seconds For information purposes, once Grimes completed the test, she stated, Ill be honest with you, I should not be driving.   Alphabet Test (F to T):  I asked Grimes if she was familiar with the English alphabet and she stated, Yes. I asked Grimes if she graduated high school and she stated, Yea. I asked Grimes to say the Alphabet starting at F and end at T. Grimes stated, FGHIJKLMNOPQRST.  Count Backwards (59 to 36):  Grimes was asked to count backwards starting at 59 and end at 36.  Grimes stated, 59, 58, 57, 56, 55, 54, 53, 52, 51, 50, 49, 48, 47, 46, 45, 44, 42, 42, 41, 40, 39, 38, 36, Im sorry, 37, 36.   Preliminary Breath Test  I read Grimes her MSP Form 102 and explained the reasons for using a preliminary breath test and asked Grimes if she wanted to submit a breath sample. Grimes agreed to submit to the Preliminary Breath Test and submitted a breath sample of a 0.14 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  While interacting with Grimes during Standardized Field Sobriety I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. I also continued to observe her eyes to be glassy.  Arrest  Based on the following totality of circumstances, I had reason to believe Grimes was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:    Grimes failed to obey a properly placed traffic control device.  Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Grimes breath and person.  Grimes eyes were glassy.  Grimes completed Standardized Field Sobriety Test unsatisfactory.   At 0033 hours, I placed Grimes under arrest. I then placed Grimes into the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. I then entered my patrol vehicle and detected the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage that was not present prior to placing Grimes inside.  I transported Grimes to the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack V, located at 9758 Ocean Gateway, Berlin, Worcester County, Maryland.  DR-15 Advice of Rights  While at the Barrack, I placed a paper copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights in front of Grimes and I played the MVA Audio version of the DR-15 from the MVA website and asked Grimes to follow along.  After the DR-15 was completed, Grimes advised me at 0107 hours that she agreed to submit to take an intoximeter test, to measure herbreath alcohol concentration per 210 liters of breath.  Intoximeter Test  Corporal Snell #6171, a certified EC/IR II operator, checked Grimess mouth for foreign objects and nothing was located. At 0114 hours, Corporal Snell administered the breath testwith a result of 0.14 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  Grimes was processed and advised not to drive for 12 hours. Grimes was given her paperwork and citations and released to a valid sober driver from the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack.  Charges    Driving Vehicle While Under the Influence of Alcohol (3KQ0VPH)  Driving Vehicle While Under the Influence of Alcohol Per Se (3KR0VPH)  Driving Vehicle While Impaired by Alcohol (3KS0VPH)  Negligent Driving (3KT0VPH)  Reckless Driving (3KV0VPH)  Driver Fail To Obey a Properly Placed Traffic Control Device Instructions (3KW0VPH)  Person Driving Motor Vehicle on Highway or Public Use Property on Suspended License and Privilege (3KX0VPH)  Driving While License Suspended Under Special Section (3KY0VPH)  Driving Motor Vehicle on Highway Without Required License and Authorization (3KZ0VPH)   For information purposes, Grimes was polite and cooperative during the entire interaction.  Case Closed by Arrest.  All above events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/24/2023 10:24:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/24/2023 10:34:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7062</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Drew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510316</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/11/2023 00:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/23/2023 08:43:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/23/2023 08:46:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>44</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/23/2023 08:43:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:03</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>380605</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Grimes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Valerie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kaye</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/22/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/23/2023 08:26:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>V460</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Grimes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Valerie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kaye</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/22/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>V460</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/23/2023 08:26:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>16910</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Shadybrook</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>TER</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hagerstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21740</Zip5>
               <Zip4>6944</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.783261</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.62119</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>210</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>469</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1234</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/23/2023 08:47:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/23/2023 08:47:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/23/2023 08:45:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/23/2023 08:45:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240019877</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>Your Cause Auto</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>W</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/23/2023 08:50:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/23/2023 08:50:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154446</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/23/2023 08:52:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/23/2023 08:52:02</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FADP3E23EL319672</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FOC</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>PA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>LRX3231</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>5</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>