<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-027441</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/03/2023 11:05:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/03/2023 11:05:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/03/2023 09:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/03/2023 09:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Warrant Service - Suspect made suicidal statements - Emergency petition</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 11:05:28</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3355</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 09:17:15</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>EP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>702789</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 11:05:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 09:12:17</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>702789</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>4257</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Nicholas</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Baltimore</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21206</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.562822</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.327938</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/03/2023 11:05:26</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/03/2023 11:05:26</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40N</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/14/2023 09:16:43</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 11:05:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3355</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 09:16:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>***Incident Captured on Body Worn Camera***  Scene Processing: Digital photographs obtained and attached. Emergency petition paperwork completed and attached.  Narrative:  In July of 2023, Cpl. Tittle #6005 of the Maryland State Police - Maryland State Apprehension Team / U.S. Marshals - Capital Area Regional Fugitive Task Force, was requested by the Anne Arundel County Sheriffs Office to assist with locating and apprehending a fugitive, identified as Erica Chantavia Jennings, B/F, DOB: 7/28/1983. Jennings was wanted through the Anne Arundel County Sheriffs Office for Assault 1st Degree and related offenses (D-07-CR-23-017371), which was issued on 7/31/2023. The charges stem from an incident in which Jennings brutally assaulted a co-worker with a blunt object. Jennings has a violent criminal history to include Attempted 1st Degree Murder, Assault 1st Degree, Assault 2nd Degree, Dangerous Weapon Intent to Injure.  Upon being assigned the fugitive investigation, Cpl. Tittle conducted an in-depth background investigation into Jennings family, friends, associates, social media, and pattern of life. During the course of the investigation, Cpl. Tittle identified a current vehicle for Jennings, identified as a maroon 2016 Kia Sorento (Maryland registration 7FH0737). Cpl. Tittle obtained and analyzed LPR data for this vehicle, which consistently placed that vehicle parked stationary in the area the 4200blk of Nicholas Ave Baltimore, MD. During the background investigation, Cpl. Tittle identified that an address of 4257 Nicholas Ave Baltimore, MD for Jennings. In May of 2023, Jennings had a credit report through Experian with a listed address of 4257 Nicholas Ave Baltimore, MD.  On 8/2/2023, Cpl. Tittle conducted covert surveillance and located Jennings vehicle parked in the 4200blk of Nicholas Ave.  On 8/3/2023, Task Force members devised an operational plan to respond to this address to locate and apprehend Jennings. On 8/3/2023, at approximately 0823 hours, Task Force members arrived at this location. A perimeter was quickly established around the residence. Task Force members began knocking on the front entry door. After a period of time, Cpl. Tittle observed someone peak through the second floor middle window blinds. Task Force members continued to knock and announce their presence for a long period of time with no response.  A TFO from the Baltimore City Police Department made contact with police communications to inquire about any recent calls for service at this location. Communications advised on 7/6/2023 the fire department responded to this location for a 39-year-old female. This corroborated with Jennings age.  Task Force members continued to knock and announce their presence and provided their intent to force entry into the residence. After no response, Task Force members breached the front door. Upon the door being breached, Task Force members took a tactical position at the front door and continued to call out for Jennings to surrender. After no response, Task Force members tactically cleared the residence in search of Jennings.  Jennings was located hiding in the basement, with her five-year-old son, behind a closed door leading to a second closed exterior door. Jennings was immediately uncooperative. Task Force members attempted to deescalate Jennings and encouraged her to exit and surrender peacefully. Eventually Jennings exited and began walking towards the basement steps. Jennings cousin was now on scene and was going to take custody of her child. Task Force members continued to encourage Jennings to cooperate, however she refused.  Jennings was sat on the basement floor and leg irons placed on due to being uncooperative. During this time, Jennings attempted to kick Task Force members. A Baltimore City Police Department transport wagon was requested and responded. Jennings refused to walk to the wagon and had to be carried. While being transported, Jennings placed her hands to her front and unbuckled her seat belt and began banging inside the wagon. The wagon officer pulled over and requested assistance.  Jennings made suicidal statements and the decision was made to emergency petition her. EMS was requested to respond to the scene to assist with securing and transporting Jennings to the hospital. Heart to Heart EMS (private ambulance service contracted through the Baltimore City Dire Department) responded. Jennings was placed and secured on the stretcher. Jennings attempted to bite Task Force members while being secured. Jennings was transported to Johns Hopkins Bayview.  Upon arriving at the hospital, Jennings continued to be irate, agitated, and uncooperative. Jennings was subsequently sedated by medical staff.  Cpl. Tittle completed and submitted an emergency petition to hospital staff.  After being evaluated, Jennings was discharged at approximately 1600 hours. Jennings was released into the custody of Deputy England and Deputy Conover of the Anne Arundel County Sheriffs Office to be transported and processed at the Anne Arundel County Detention Center.  A USMS Tort Claim Form was provided.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 17:03:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6005</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 09:11:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Vanhoy</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3355</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tittle</LastName>
            <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6005</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 13:36:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 09:12:17</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>384165</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Jennings</LastName>
               <FirstName>Erica</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Chantavia</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/28/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/03/2023 13:35:55</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J552</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Jennings</LastName>
               <FirstName>Erica</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Chantavia</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/28/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J552</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/03/2023 13:35:55</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4257</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Nicholas</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21206</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.562822</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.327938</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 16:42:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 16:42:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>