<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-029561</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/21/2023 13:22:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/21/2023 13:22:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/21/2023 13:21:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/21/2023 13:21:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect was found to have had sexual contact with a minor in his care.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/21/2023 13:22:30</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/19/2023 11:23:50</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SAS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>685085</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/21/2023 13:22:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 08:13:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>685085</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1825</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>KINGSWOOD</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>PRINCE FREDERICK</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20678</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.564333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.559211</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/21/2023 13:22:28</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/21/2023 13:22:28</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/15/2023 11:15:56</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/21/2023 13:22:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:57</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On August 17, 2023, the Maryland State Police Internet Crimes Against Children (ICAC), Homeland Security Investigations and Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Central South, executed a Search Warrant signed by Honorable Judge Chandlee with the Calvert County District Court at 1825 Kingswood Drive, Prince Frederick, Maryland 20678 and the body of suspect, Hunter Lee Kirby (W/M, DOB: 6/24/1997.   During the course of the investigation, the suspect was found in possession of child pornography. Kirby voluntarily returned to the Maryland State Police Prince Frederick Barrack for a further interview and was also asked to participate in a polygraph examination administered by Cpl. F. Dollinger. Cpl. Dollinger read Kirby his Miranda Rights which he voluntarily waived. During the course of the subsequent interviews, Kirby disclosed he had inappropriate contact with his niece.  Due to these admissions, the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Central South was contacted. I, TFC Ruggles was assigned the investigation. On Friday August 18, 2023, I contacted ASA B. Cordero of the Calvert County States Attorneys Office and briefed her of the investigation. Additionally, I contacted Department of Social Services and advised them of the allegations. Further, I made contact with Kirbys Sister in Law, Brittany Michelle Kirby (W/F DOB: 08/28/1989). Brittany is married to Hunters brother. Brittany is also the mother of Cassidy Atlantis Millar (W/F DOB: 05/21/2009), Chloe Ann Marie Kirby (W/F DOB: 03/14/2012), Delany and Dallas. Due to the nature of the admissions by Hunter, I wanted to facilitate a Forensic Interview as soon as possible with Brittanys children. Brittany agreed and the interview was scheduled for Monday, August 21st, 2023.  On August 21, 2023, TFC Ruggles and Cpl C. Ditoto responded to the Calvert County Child Advocacy Center to observe two Forensic Interviews conducted by Jessica M. Jacobs of Maryland DHS CPS. Jessica conducted these with two of Kirbys nieces. Kirby had admitted to inappropriately touching one of the children as well as possibly illegal contact with the other.  The first interview conducted was with Cassidy Millar. Cassidy is a 14 year old Freshman at Calvert High School in Prince Frederick Maryland. During the interview, Cassidy was asked if there was any point in her life where anyone has done something that, might not be okay. Cassidy replied that something had happened. Cassidy was asked to explain. Cassidy replied by saying, So basically, it involves the person that we are here for. Cassidy went on to explain that at a previous house her family was living at, when she was six or seven years old, she was in the basement of the residence. Cassidy went into the bathroom with whom she later identified as Hunter Kirby. Hunter wanted Cassidy to take off her romper, lay down and spread her legs so that he could take pictures. Cassidy stated she took her romper off and Hunter took a photograph of her. In the interview, Cassidy would later clarify for this incident she was only wearing her bottom underwear at the time of the photograph and was unclothed from the waist up. Cassidy also recalled Hunter asking to her to take her underwear off and stating he would take his off too. Hunter then informs Cassidy that they would both, like it.  Following recalling this incident, Cassidy stated, That is one of the situations I fully remember. I remember that very distinctly. Cassidy then distinctly described the layout of the residence which investigators later identified as 622 Silver Rock Road, Lusby, MD 20657. Cassidy stated this incident occurred during the Thanksgiving/Christmas time and other family members were present. However, all other family members were upstairs at the time of the incident. Upon realizing Cassidy was not upstairs, Brittany came looking for her because no other family members, trusted Hunter. Cassidy continued to describe the incident in detail and reiterated that Hunter took her romper off, wanted her to lay down and spread her legs so that he could take a picture of her. Cassidy stated he took a picture of her in her underwear. Cassidy was asked to clarify if he assisted her in taking the romper off to which she clarified that Hunter physically took the romper off of her exposing her bare chest. Cassidy continued to describe the bathroom in which she was standing at the time. Cassidy described this incident in great detail. Cassidy also recalled Hunter utilizing a silver flip phone. It should be noted that although not located during the search warrant of the residence, TFC Ruggles contacted Hunters father to ask about the silver flip phone. Hunters father stated Hunter did have a silver flip phone but does not currently have the phone any longer. During this incident, Cassidy recalled being, frozen. After taking the photograph, Brittany located Cassidy and ended the situation.        As the interview continued, Cassidy recalled a second situation which had actually occurred prior to the incident in the basement. Cassidy recalled being in her bedroom, Hunter entered the bedroom and began talking, very nasty to Cassidy. Cassidy then recalled Hunter telling her to take her pants off.  Cassidy also recalled an incident, More recently where her family needed to get their refrigerator replaced. Hunter came to the house to help with the replacement. Cassidy stated her little sister, Delany, who is 8 currently, was on the tailgate of the truck. While Delany was on the tailgate, she was wearing a dress and Cassidy observed Hunter attempting to look up her dress. Cassidy described Hunter trying to put his head down to look up below Delanys dress.  Shortly after this, the interview with Cassidy was ended.  Following the interview with Cassidy, Chloe was interviewed.  During the interview with Chloe, Chloe appeared extremely guarded. Chloe was asked many of the same questions Cassidy was asked, however, it should be noted at the time of these incidents, Chloe would have been approximately 4 years old.  After the completion of the interview with Chloe, investigators made contact with Cassidy and Chloes mother, Brittany Michelle Kirby. Brittany is related to Hunter via marriage. Brittanys husband, CJ, is Hunters brother. Brittany stated she and CJ had been together for approximately 12 years, however, the situation with Hunter has caused what she believed to be irreparable damage in their relationship. Throughout their time together, Brittany had a bad feeling about Hunter. However, even following this, the family of Hunter took no steps to correct Hunters behavior and essentially pushed the behavior off to the side. Brittany recalled one other incident where Hunter was in a room with Cassidy. Brittany was positioned outside of the room. While outside the room, Brittany heard Hunter made very inappropriate comments to Cassidy. Brittany stated Hunter and Cassidy had intended on playing hide and seek prior to these comments being made. Brittany described these as requesting Cassidy to take her shorts off. Brittany recalled she was upstairs tending to her infant twins, when she came to the living room, she observed Hunters parents sitting on the couch. Brittany asked them where Hunter and Cassidy were before running to the basement. Brittany described Hunter as sitting on the couch by the time she got there and Cassidy was sitting on the floor. Brittany stated upon seeing this she stated, Get the fuck away from my kid.  Outside of these incidents, Brittany described Hunters behavior as, although not criminal, most definitely unsettling. Brittany stated as recently as spring of 2023. Brittany stated she does not allow her children alone with Hunter, nor does she particularly want Hunter around the children at all. Brittany admitted that family dynamics sometimes causes Hunter to be around the children. Brittany did not give Hunter the girls softball schedule. However, in spring of 2023, Hunter still showed up at the girls softball game. Brittany attributed this to Hunters mother, Dawn. Brittany described Dawn as an enabler. Brittany also told investigators about an incident where Hunter had stolen her underwear. Investigators were aware of Hunter stealing underwear in the past but were unaware Brittany had been a victim of this as well. Brittany stated she only learned this because Hunters mother, Dawn told her about it. Brittany also disclosed despite her not wanting Hunter around, Brittany and CJ allowed CJ and Hunters grandmother to live with them at the time of these alleged incidents. Hunter would come to the house periodically and at holidays. Hunters grandmother lived in the basement where these incidents occurred.  On Wednesday August 30th, 2023, a Forensic interview was conducted with Brittanys two younger children, Dallas and Delaney. Through the course of this interview, no nefarious behavior was uncovered.  On Friday September 1, 2023, I met with ASA B. Cordero of the Calvert County States Attorneys Office. After meeting with ASA Cordero, it was decided to apply for a warrant charging Hunter Kirby with multiple sex offenses. On September 1, 2023, I applied for a warrant requesting the charges of the following;  CR.11.207.(a)(1)- CHILD PORN SOLICIT SUBJECT CR.3.602.(b)(1)- SEX ABUSE MINOR CR.3.307- SEX OFFENSE THIRD DEGREE  On Friday September 1, 2023, the District Court Commissioner issued a summons charging Kirby with the aforementioned charges.  On September 5th, 2023, Hunter Kirby was served the summons without issue at the Calvert County Detention Center. Kirby made no comments pertinent to this investigation. However, Kirby appeared disgruntled upon learning the charges. Kirby was told he could read the statement of charges, however, immediately upon signing receipt of the document, Kirby requested a Correctional Officer place the paperwork in with his personal belongings.  This case is closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Calvert County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6923</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 09:02:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6923</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 13:18:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>DiToto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5815</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruggles</LastName>
            <FirstName>Evan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6923</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519009</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3 3600</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/21/2023 13:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3 3600</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6923</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 08:15:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6923</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 08:15:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519009</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0322</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/21/2023 13:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0322</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6923</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 08:16:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6923</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 08:16:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519009</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 3799</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/21/2023 13:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 3799</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6923</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 08:18:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6923</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 08:18:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6923</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 08:19:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 08:19:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383971</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Kirby</LastName>
               <FirstName>Hunter</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/24/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.20494753E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>08/01/2023 09:42:12</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K610</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H536</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Kirby</LastName>
               <FirstName>Hunter</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/24/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.20494753E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>K610</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H536</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/01/2023 09:42:12</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1825</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Kingswood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Prince Frederick</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20678</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.564333</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.559211</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>474</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2320</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6923</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 08:19:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>14</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6923</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 08:48:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 08:48:35</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>387527</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Millar</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cassidy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Atlantis</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/21/2009 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/11/2023 08:47:58</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C230</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Millar</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cassidy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Atlantis</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/21/2009 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C230</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/11/2023 08:47:58</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5022</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Timber View</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>St Leonard</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20685</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2104</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.522652</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.462387</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6923</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 08:48:36</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>11</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6923</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 08:50:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 08:50:17</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386075</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Kirby</LastName>
               <FirstName>Chloe</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/14/2012 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/25/2023 07:42:52</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K610</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Kirby</LastName>
               <FirstName>Chloe</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/14/2012 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>K610</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/25/2023 07:42:52</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6923</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 08:50:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP6923</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 08:52:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 08:52:14</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386077</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Kirby</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brittany</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/28/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/25/2023 07:46:06</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K610</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B635</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Kirby</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brittany</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/28/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>K610</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B635</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/25/2023 07:46:06</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>NOK</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6923</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 08:52:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>