<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-024507</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/08/2023 22:33:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/08/2023 22:33:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/08/2023 22:09:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/08/2023 22:09:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 22:33:54</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 12:36:21</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>700317</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 22:33:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/08/2023 22:33:58</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>700317</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>83.9</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I95 Sb</StreetName>
         <City>Aberdeen</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.200477</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.519064</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/08/2023 22:33:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/08/2023 22:33:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/22/2023 12:33:51</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 22:33:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:27:58</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police, Barrack D Marked MSP Vehicle D-17. In-Car Camera Operational.  Defendant: Hayward, Justin Lamar Date of Birth: 06/20/1997 Date of Arrest: 07/08/2023 Time of Arrest: 2232hours DUI #: 23-170(Bel Air) Blood test Result: .12 BrAC REPEAT OFFENDER  BEHAVIOR/CONDUCT:Hayward was cooperative.  CERTIFICATION  TRAINING NHTSA Trained/certified to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Test (SFST) Preliminary breath test operator certified Certified Radar/Laser Operator  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On July 8, 2023,at approximately 2140hours, I, Trooper Kumador #7052 of the Maryland State Police, Bel AirBarrack was traveling Southbound I-95 in the area of 107 Mile Marker in Cecil County, Maryland. I was operating an unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle, D-17 traveling to Harford County for the start of my night shift. Traffic conditions on the highway that Saturday night were moderate.  I observed a dark color vehicle also traveling southbound. The vehicle appeared to be traveling faster than normal traffic and kept changing lanes from lane 1 to 2 to 3 back and forth. Having noticed the unsafe manner of operation, I activated my forward facing camera to record the movement of the vehicle while following it closely into Harford County. The vehicle changes lanes into lane 1 and later into 2 and then to 3.  I followed the vehicle shortly in lane 3 and obtained a digital speed of 80 MPH in a posted of 65 MPH using the in-car mounted Golden Eagle II Radar. I activated my emergency lights and siren to initiate a traffic stop on the vehicle at approximately 2209 in the area of 83.9 Mile Marker in Aberdeen, Harford County, Maryland. I identified the vehicle after the stop as Black KIA KS displaying Delaware registration 519291. The radar unit was calibrated and tested and was found to be working properly.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) Prior to approaching the vehicle, I observed the driver spraying cologne into his clothing. I made a passenger side approachof the vehicleand made contact with the operator, a blackmale. I introduced myself and the reasonsfor the stop. The driver disputed my reasons. I requested his drivers license and the registration for the card. The driver displayed his United States Passport and said he did not have his license. He later displayed his registration. I detected the odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle.  Due to two other passengers in the vehicle, I requested the driver to exit the vehicle to speak with me outside. I asked the driver where he was traveling and he stated I was ready to go home and I was going to pull over because my friend is ready to drive, I cant drive As the driver spoke to me outside, I continued to detect a strong odor of alcoholic beverage on his breath. I asked the driver how much alcohol he had consumed and he stated I didnt have anything to drink. I also observed a bottle of alcohol on the floor of the rear passenger seat which was later concealed from my view.  Due to the overwhelming odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath, I asked the driver when was the last time he had any alcoholic beverage and he stated Yesterday. A quick check of his eyes shows the presence of Nystagmus. The driver later stated that he had Margarita about a couple of hours before the stop at his mothers birthday party and he was heading home in Baltimore with his friends. I later identified the driver by his vehicles registration and passport as Hayward, Justin Lamar, DOB: 06/20/1997. Haywards eyes were heavily bloodshot and glassy. His speech was slurred. He stated that he was previously arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol in Delaware and he had lost his license. While outside the vehicle seated on the guardrail, I observed Hayward dozing off. He was also seen dozing off while being transported to the barrack.      PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   Due to the overwhelming odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from Haywards breath, the admission to consuming alcoholic beverages before the traffic stop, and the unsafe manner of operating the vehicle on the highway, I had reasons to believe that he was driving under the influence of alcohol. I advised Hayward about my intention to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests to which he agreed. Upon the arrival of additional units, I requested Hayward to submit to the tests, to which he agreed. The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder in front of my patrol vehicle. The shoulderwasflat and free of any debris and the temperature was approximately 70 degrees.I asked Hayward the following questions: Contacts-Yes,Glasses-No, andAny Injuries-No.Any medication: No.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the Tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Haywards eyes. Hewas instructed to look straight ahead, keeping hishead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hiseyes until told to stop. I asked himif he understood the directions, and he advised yes. His pupils were equal in size and did show equal tracking.    Lack of Smooth Pursuit - present  The distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation  present  The onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  present.  Vertical-present   WALK AND TURN (7/8) Before Hayward performed the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. He was instructed to place hisright foot directly in front of hisleft foot and touch heel-to-toe. He was instructed to place hishands flat at hisside and to remain in the position until told to begin. Hewas advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. He was to keep his hands flat at hisside, keep hiseyes focused on hisfeet, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, he was demonstrated and explained to keep hislead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around to hisleft with hisrear foot to turn completely around. He was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. He was then instructed that once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep hishands down by hisside, look down at hisfeet, and count each step out loud.  During the instructional stage:I explained and demonstrated the starting position to Hayward andplaced him in thestarting position. He broke his feet while I was explaining the test to him. He was later placed back in the starting position.  Walking stage (1st Nine).    He took only 8 steps instead of 9 by counting from his right foot which placed in front of the left foot  Stepped offline during the teststeps.  Missed heel-to-toe by more than an inch  He stopped on the 8 step to ask questions.  He raised arms   Turn:  The turn was unsatisfactory. Haywardturned swiftly in one fluid motion, instead of taking a small series of steps toward his left as he was instructed.  Walking stage (2nd Nine).    Missed heel-to-toe by more than an inch   ONE LEG STAND (1/4) Prior to Haywardperforming the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. He was instructed to stand with hisheels together and hands down by hisside, while the instructions were given and during the test. He was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of hischoice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While hisleg was raised, he was to keep hisleg straight, watch hisraised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one thousand-two), and to continue the test until told to stop.    He did not raise his foot as instructed  He swayed side by side   PRELIMINARY BREATH A preliminary breath test was explained and offered to Hayward and he voluntarily accepted and submitted to the test with a result of .12 Br Ac.  ARREST Based on the following, I havereasons to believe that Haywardwas operating his vehicle while under the influence of alcoholand unable to operate safely    Extremely strong odor of alcoholic beverage on his breath  Admission to consuming alcoholic beverages few hoursbefore the traffic stop,  Unable to maintain lane discipline on the road way-swerving and speeding  Observed signs of impairment as he performedthe Standardized Field Sobriety Tests unsatisfactorily.  I arrested Haywardat 2232hours for driving his vehicle while under the influence of alcohol. Haywardlistened to the Englishaudio version of DR-15 Advice of Rights in its entiretyin my patrol vehicle and at the conclusion, he voluntarily agreedtosubmit to the test. Itransported himto the Maryland State Police, Bel Air barrack for processing where he signed the paper copy of the DR-15 at the barrack at 2330 hours.  20-MINUTES OBSERVATION PERIOD. Haywards observation started as soon as he was arrested and his oral cavity check was completed at 2233 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT:  Breath test was explained and offered to Hayward by Sgt. Stanley #5405 with a result of .12Br AC.  Hayward was charged with driving a vehicle while under the influence of alcohol and other DUI related charges.  Haywardwasgiven copies of all pertinent paperwork andlater released to a sober licensed driver at the barrack.  Closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/13/2023 01:52:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/13/2023 12:07:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Boniarski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6651</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Turner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6761</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kumador</LastName>
            <FirstName>Linford</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7052</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513947</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/08/2023 22:09:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/09/2023 00:55:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/09/2023 00:55:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/09/2023 00:56:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:11</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382016</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>HAYWARD</LastName>
               <FirstName>JUSTIN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LAMAR</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/20/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.08768601E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>07/09/2023 00:44:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J235</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>HAYWARD</LastName>
               <FirstName>JUSTIN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LAMAR</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/20/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.08768601E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>H630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J235</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/09/2023 00:44:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>300</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Cathedral</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21201</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4403</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.616992</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.293234</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>610</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>800</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9605</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/09/2023 00:56:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/09/2023 00:56:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/09/2023 00:56:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/09/2023 00:56:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/09/2023 00:55:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/09/2023 00:55:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154954</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/09/2023 00:56:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/09/2023 00:56:45</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5XXG64J26NG152486</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>KIA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>DE</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>519291</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>