<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-017768</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/19/2023 02:48:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/19/2023 02:48:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/19/2023 02:28:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/19/2023 02:28:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Vehicle was stopped for a moving violation. Upon contact with the driver, the odor of an alcoholic beverage was detected. SFST's was conducted and the driver was arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 02:48:46</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0104</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 10:06:09</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>3369 CRAIN,WALDORF</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>694456</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 02:48:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 03:33:41</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>694456</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Crain</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Waldorf</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20602</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>DR</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.917721</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.619686</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/19/2023 02:48:44</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/19/2023 02:48:44</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/08/2023 11:30:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 02:48:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:52:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car camera and body worn camera operational.  Defendant: Spinks, Kalen Rae  Date of Birth: 04/18/1995  Time of arrest: 0248 hours  Location: Southbound Route 301 in the area of St. Patricks Drive, Waldorf, Charles County Maryland, 20601.  North Carolina drivers license: 000038757902  DUI#: 23-093  1st DUI  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING  *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police.  *Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement through Charles County Sheriffs Office.  NARRATIVE/ VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1):  On 05/19/2023, at approximately 0228 hours, I, Tpr. Tripp #7333, with the Maryland State Police La Plata Barrack, was traveling southbound Route 301, in the area of Acton Lane, Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland 20601, in lane one, when I observed a white Hyundai Veloster, bearing North Carolina registration FMP1957, stopped approximately 200 feet before the intersection of southbound Route 301 and Acton Lane, Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland 20601, in lane two. The Hyundai then attempted to stay behind my vehicle from Acton Lane to Plaza Drive. Once my vehicle and the Hyundai approached Plaza Drive, the Hyundai merged into the right turn only lane and lowered their speed to approximately 20 MPH in a 45 MPH speed limit zone. I then merged over into the left turn only lane and stopped at the steady red arrow light. The Hyundai then increased their speed using the right turn lane to pass the intersection at Plaza Drive. I then activated my emergency equipment and stopped the Hyundai southbound Route 301, in the area of St. Patricks Drive, Waldorf, Charles County Maryland, 20601, in the right turn only lane.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):  I made contact with the driver and requested his drivers license and registration card, which he displayed. I was able to identify the driver through his North Carolina drivers license as Spinks, Kalen Rae (A.A/M, DOB: 04/18/1995). While speaking with Spinks, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle. I asked Spinks if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages, he advised no. While speaking with Spinks, I observed his eyes were glassy, andhis speech to be slurred and mumbled. I advised Spinks that I needed him to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) to which Spinks agreed.As Spinks approached the front of his vehicle, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):  Tpr. Fuller #7440 assisted with the traffic stop. While standing in front of Spinks vehicle, I asked Spinks if he is a diabetic or has high blood pressure, he advised no. I asked Spinks if he wears glasses or contacts, he advised he wears glasses. I asked Spinks does he need glasses to drive, he advised no. I asked Spinks if he had any head injuries or concussions, he advised no. I then asked Spinks is there any physical issues that I should be aware of before conducting the test, he advised no. I then asked Spinks if there are any medical conditions that I should be aware of, he advised no. I asked Spinks if he could perform the Walk and Turn (WAT) and the One Leg Stand (OLS) test, he advised yes. Spinks advised he is currently on medication (Amoxicillin) and the reason he shows signs of impairment is because of the medication. I then asked Spinks if he could visibly see my pen from the 12 to 15 inches distance from his face, he advised yes.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS TEST: (6/6 clues observed).  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Spinks eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping hishead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hiseyes until told to stop. Hispupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. Hewas positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results.Spinks was repeatedly instructed to follow the tip of the pen throughout the test.  Spinks displayed equal pupil size, equal tracking and no resting nystagmus in both eyes.  Spinks displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  Spinks displayed nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  Spinks displayed nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.  VERTICAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Spinks did not display vertical gaze nystagmus in both eyes.  WALK AND TURN: (4/8 clues observed).  Prior to Spinks performing the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Spinks was instructed to place hisright foot directly in front of hisleft foot and touch heel to toe. He was instructed and demonstrated to place hishands flat at hissides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Hewas advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. Hewas instructed to keep hishands flat at hissides, keep hiseyes focused on hisfeet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Spinks was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with hisrear foot to turn completely around. Spinks was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Hewas instructedonce he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep hishands down by hissides, look down at hisfeet, and count each step out loud. Spinks was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, Yes.   Spinks wore brown dress shoes for this test.  Spinks stepped off-line on his first, third, and ninth stepon his first set of nine steps.  Spinks missed heel-to-toe on his second and fourth step on his first set of nine steps.  Spinks stopped on his ninth step on his first set of nine steps.  Spinks performed an improper turn by performing a about face movement to turn around, instead of taking a series of small steps as instructed.  Spinks stepped off-line on his firstand ninth stepon his second set of nine steps.  Spinks missed heel-to-toe on his fourth step on his second set of nine steps.  ONE LEG STAND: (2/4 clues observed) font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Prior to Spinks performing the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Hewas instructed to stand with hisheels together and hands down by hissides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of hischoice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While hisleg was raised he was to keep hisleg straight, watch hisraised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Spinks was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, Yes.  Spinks raised his right foot for this test.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; 0-10  Spinks did not raise his foot for approximately two seconds  Spinks swayed at four seconds  21-30 seconds font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Spinks swayed at 23 and 28 seconds font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  Spinks was offered to take the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) and refused to take to the test.  Arrest: font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.  -Glassy eyes.  -Slurred and mumbled speech. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; -Admission to taking medication before driving  -Clues displayed from the Standardized Field Sobriety Test.  Spinks was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at 0248 hours.  Spinkswas read his DR-15 Advice of Rights, and he refused to take the Intoximeter test at 0341 hours. While Spinks was being processed he advised that the Amoxicillinmedication is the reason for his impairment. I researchedAmoxicillin, and it shows thatAmoxicillin does not cause impairment to drive a motor vehicle.Amoxicillin is an antibiotic that clears bacteria, for this case Spinks ear infection.  Spinks received the following citations: font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; TA-21-902(a1i) Driving vehicle while under the influence of alcohol  TA-21-902(b1i) Driving vehicle while impaired by alcohol  TA-21-901.1(b) Negligent driving  TA-21-901.1(a) Reckless driving  TA-21-201(a1) Driver failure to obey properly placed traffic control device instructions  TA-21-707(c) Failure to stop at stop sign at nearest point approaching traffic view  TA-21-202(m) Driver failed to make required stop at pavement mark  Spinks was rude and uncooperative throughout the entire process.  Spinks was released to a valid, sober driver. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; All events occurred in Charles County, Maryland.  Case closed. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 16:34:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/26/2023 11:27:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fuller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7440</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alphrin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5237</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Maszarose</LastName>
            <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6174</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tripp</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sedrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7333</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507200</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/19/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 04:50:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507200</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/19/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 04:50:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507200</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/19/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 04:51:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507200</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/19/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 04:51:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507200</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/19/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 04:51:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507200</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15642</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/19/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15642</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 04:52:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507200</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15535</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/19/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15535</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 04:52:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>28</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:46:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:13</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377410</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Spinks</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kalen</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Rae</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/18/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/19/2023 04:15:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S152</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K450</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Spinks</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kalen</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Rae</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/18/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S152</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K450</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/19/2023 04:15:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4801</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Kingwell</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>McLeansville</City>
               <StateCode>NC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>27301</Zip5>
               <Zip4>9268</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-79.68654</Longitude>
               <Latitude>36.063452</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 04:49:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153147</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 04:53:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 04:53:44</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>KMHT36AHXKU002793</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HYUN</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>VEL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>NC</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>FMP1957</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>6</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>