<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-020078</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/05/2023 00:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/05/2023 00:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/04/2023 23:52:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/04/2023 23:52:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>VOP</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 00:08:05</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2637</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/28/2023 16:36:41</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>VPO</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>696534</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 00:08:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP7053</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 03:12:44</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>696534</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>704</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mccauley</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Conowingo</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21918</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-76.11888</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.670669</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/05/2023 00:08:03</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/05/2023 00:08:03</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/18/2023 09:11:36</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 00:08:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Scene Processing: No scene processing was conducted Neighborhood Checks: No Neighborhood checks were completed. Attachments: No attachments Narrative: On 06/5/2023 at approximately 0001 hours, I TFC Mott #7053 of the Maryland State Police made contact with Emily Lauren Snyder (DOB 12/28/1998) on the phone in reference to a violation of protection order. Snyder advised that her ex-boyfriend who she has two kids with texted and called her on a different number. Snyder advised that her ex-boyfriend who she identified as Christopher Lee Paynter (DOB 5/23/1999). Snyder stated she obtained a protection order against Paynter due to him assaulting her in the first degree in May of 2023. Snyder advised that the text message she received at 2324 hours on 6/4/2023 listed both her address in Conowingo and her fathers address in Ohio. Snyder stated that only Paynter would know what her fathers address was in Ohio. Snyder then stated that a Facebook account sent her fathers Facebook multiple sexually explicit photographs of Snyder and stated sorry daddy your little daughter is a whore at 0011 hours on 6/5/2023. Snyder stated that only Paynter had these photographs of her. Snyder then stated that she was called twice by an anonymous number at 0019 hours and 0029 hours. Snyder has a final protection order against Paynter which is valid through 5/19/2024.  Snyder stated that on numerous other occasions that Paynter stated that he would kill her. An application for charges was completed and dropped off at the Cecil County Court Commissioners office.  While enroute to the commissioners office the North East barrack advised that a Griffin Barron (DOB 6/25/1998) contacted the barrack in reference to receiving threatening text messages. I made contact with Barron on the phone. Barron advised that he received numerous text message from the same number who was texting Snyder. Barron was referred to the commissioners office for a peace order.  All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7053</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 03:20:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7053</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 03:23:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kim</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6166</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mott</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kenneth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7053</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509512</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>15</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0254</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/04/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 0254</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7053</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 03:14:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7053</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 03:14:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7053</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 03:16:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>348719</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Snyder</LastName>
               <FirstName>Emily</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lauren</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/28/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/08/2022 15:19:03</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Snyder</LastName>
               <FirstName>Emily</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lauren</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/28/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/08/2022 15:19:03</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>704</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mccauley</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Conowingo</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21918</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.11888</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.670669</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <City>Conowingo</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21918</Zip5>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>350</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2917</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/08/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7053</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 03:16:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:12</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7053</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 03:16:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>91657</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Paynter</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/23/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/29/2016 10:54:09</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Paynter</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/23/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/29/2016 10:54:09</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>21</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Maple Hill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Port Deposit</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21904</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.083613</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.630306</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hillcrest</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Conowingo</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.18799117632433</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.68078748418389</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>993</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7112</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/29/2016 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7053</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/11/2023 16:27:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7053</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/11/2023 16:27:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/05/2023 12:13:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/05/2023 12:13:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/18/2023 09:11:36</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 12:13:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>SCENE PROCESSING:  I, Trooper First Class Scott (#7217), am equipped with a body-worn camera. My body-worn camera was active during my involvement in this incident.  CAD DISPATCH #:2023-00228945  NARRATIVE:  On June 5, 2023, at approximately 1031 hours, I, Trooper First Class Scott (#7217) of the Maryland State Police, was dispatched to 704 McCauley Road, Conowingo, Maryland in response to a violation of protective order. I arrived on scene at approximately 1123 hours.    Upon arrival, I made contact with EmilySnyder. Snyder was concerned Christopher Paynter may have placed something in her mailbox. However, she was also afraid to exit her home, because she was worried Paynter may ambush her. Snyder was with her two young children at the time I made contact with her.    As I conversed further with Snyder, I learned that she received more anonymous telephone contact that she suspects is Paynter. During my investigation, I became aware of this case number and briefly examined the contents of the initial narrative. I learned that Snyder already reported the protective order violation to Maryland State Police, specifically violations that occurred on June 4 and June 5, 2023. Snyder was reporting the new anonymous telephone contact occurred somewhere around 0800 hours on June 5. Considering a violation of the protective order was already reported regarding June 5, 2023 on this case number, I thought it prudent to note the additional contact she was reporting on this supplement as opposed to a new case number.    Considering her concerns, I escorted Snyder to her mailbox. Upon a check of the mailbox, it was found to be empty of mail. I also checked the foliage behind the mailbox and along her property line, as well as the woods extending behind her home. I did so considering her fear that she could be ambushed, coupled with her belief that Paynter is again attempting to contact her from anonymous telephone numbers. I also noticed the shed in her backyard appeared to be padlocked from the outside (and therefore unlikely to be used as a hiding spot), and she also informed me it was unlikely Paynter would hide in the outhouse on the property as the outhouse is full of various items. Overall, I did not detect any sign of Paynter waiting in ambush for Snyder at the property.    I instructed Snyder to keep her doors and windows locked. She said she does not have an alarm system on her home, but does have cameras. I told her to call for police assistance if anything suspicious occurs or an emergency arises. I also recommended she bring someone she trusts with her if she has to travel anywhere. I also asked that she contact police if she receives any packages she is not expecting.    Snyder also said it is possible that Paynter may be utilizing a gold Chevrolet Tahoe. I drove through the roadways immediately near her home checking for such a vehicle. I did not find Paynter or a gold Chevrolet Tahoe parked or traveling anywhere nearby.    After conducting checks of the area, I cleared the scene.    The dispatch number for my involvement in this case is included under SCENE PROCESSING.    The above events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland. This concludes my involvement in this case at this time.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 12:14:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 15:49:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Spayd</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5369</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Scott</LastName>
            <FirstName>Conor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7217</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/07/2023 15:39:54</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/07/2023 15:39:54</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/18/2023 09:11:36</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/07/2023 15:39:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>SCENE PROCESSING:   I, Trooper First Class Scott (#7217), am equipped with a body-worn camera, which was recording during interactions in the below dispatch number (i.e. the content of this narrative).    DISPATCH NUMBER:2023-00232202  NARRATIVE:   On June 7, 2023, at approximately 1034 hours, I, Trooper First Class Scott (#7217) of the Maryland State Police, was dispatched to 704 McCauley Road, Conowingo, Maryland in response to more developments in this case. I arrived on scene at approximately 1103 hours.    Upon arrival, I made contact with Emily Snyder. Emily informed me that she received notification on June 7, 2023 from her sister that her sisters fiance is now receiving lewd images of Emily. Emily said the lewd images were sent to her sisters fiance at approximately 0004 hours on June 7, 2023. In addition, a pornographic video of Emily was also sent to Emilys sisters fiance. The lewd content was sent by a Facebook account under the name of GOT CHA. Emily said the lewd content sent in this instance is very personal and claimed only Paynter would have access to the content.    Emily did briefly display some of the new content she was referencing. I recommended she retain the copies of the content she possessed, and also later recommended via telephone that she reach out to Trooper First Class Mott regarding whether she should send the content for inclusion here or retain it pending contact with the Cecil County States Attorneys Office.    Emily also expressed interest in filing for additional charges. However, I recommended she allow the Cecil County States Attorneys Office to examine this case first and possibly amend the current charges if necessary, as the content of the complaint is in proximity to the original complaint in this case, all regarding the same protective order. In other words, I explained to her that the States Attorneys Office may see fit to simply add additional charges to this case.    I also learned that Emily has joint custody of her children with Paynter. June 7, 2023, is a day in which Paynter was scheduled to have the children.    I determined via conversation with Emily that the most likely location to find Paynter was at 5 Hillcrest Drive, Conowingo, Maryland. I made my way to that address after speaking to her, arriving at approximately 1148 hours. My initial attempts at contact did not garner a response from Paynter. However, as I was preparing to leave to check another address, a citizen drove by and advised that Paynter would be at the residence shortly. I made contact with Paynter at 5 Hillcrest Drive moments later, at approximately 1210 hours. At this time, I placed Paynter under arrest in accordance with the active arrest warrant for him in this case.    Paynter was transported to the Cecil County Commissioners Office for his initial appearance. As a result of his initial appearance, Paynter was held without bond on the arrest warrant for this case.    After the initial appearance, Paynter was transported to Cecil County Detention Center. We arrived there at approximately 1354 hours. While there, custody of Paynter was transferred from myself to corrections personnel at Cecil County Detention Center.    I made a telephone call to Emily after custody of Paynter was transferred to Cecil County Detention Center. I also learned from discussing their childrens situation with Paynter that Paynter wanted Emilys mother to pick up their children from his brother and bring them to Emily (the children were left in the custody of his brother while the warrant was served). When I contacted Emily, she advised she made arrangements to have the children picked up and brought to her as planned.    I request this case remain open pending any closing remarks from Trooper First Class Mott. This concludes my involvement in this case for the time being.    All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/07/2023 15:41:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/07/2023 16:02:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Spayd</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5369</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Scott</LastName>
            <FirstName>Conor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7217</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>