<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-032317</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/14/2023 16:10:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/14/2023 16:10:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/14/2023 15:40:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/14/2023 15:40:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>MSP BK G DUI 23-150, TA 21-902D1 (GINA GAY DOYLE)</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/14/2023 16:10:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 09:31:21</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>NEW WASHINGTON RD/ SYKESVILLE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>613307</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/14/2023 16:10:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 10:20:41</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>613307</AddressId>
         <StreetName>New Washington</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westminster</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.989371</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.522551</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3572-3729 NEW WASHINGTON RD / 1762-1775 SYKESVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3572-3729 NEW WASHINGTON RD / 1800-1817 SYKESVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/14/2023 16:10:41</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/14/2023 16:10:41</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/27/2023 13:25:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/14/2023 16:10:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:49</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23-MSP-032317  Incident: MSP Barrack G DUI 23-150 (GINA GAY DOYLE)  TA 21-902(D)(1)  Date  Time: 09/14/2023, 1540 hours  Location of Offense: N/B MD 97, S/O MD 32, Westminster, Carroll County, MD.  My investigation was recorded on AXON digital recording system assigned to G-39 and AXON body camera assigned to M/Tpr Fair.  Minors in Vehicle:NO  PBT: 0.00 BrAC at 1610 hours  EVIDENTIARY TEST:three insufficient samples/ Refusal at 1726 hours on 09/14/2023  DRE (Drug Recognition Expert): N/A  Weather: clear, sunny, approximately 78 degrees Fahrenheit  Qualifications:  -Maryland State Police Academy (June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007)  -I am trained to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through NHTSA and the Maryland State Police (MSP Academy, June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007).  -I have attended and graduated from the University of Maryland University College Advanced DUI College (UMUC January 7-11, 2013).  -I have attended and completed training Enhanced DUI Enforcement: The Complete Arrest (MPCTC, 05/11/2016).  -A.R.I.D.E.: Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (MPCTC, 03/29-03/30/2017)  -Cannabis Impairment Detection Workshop (MPCTC, 09/29/2021)  -Preliminary Breath Test Instructor (MSP CTAU, 09/11-09/12/2023)  Driver:   MD DL D-400-279-271-037 GINA GAY DOYLE 309 WEST MAIN ST WESTMINSTER, MD 21158 2/F, DOB 01/13/1968  Witness:  JEFFREY WAYNE CARR  The witness (Jeffrey Carr) followed the vehicle driven by the defendant (a gray Honda CRV, MD tag 6ED5211) N/B on MD 97 from the area of MD 26. Carr advised he observed the vehicle swerve/ drift within the lane several times, and cross the double yellow center lines, into the travel portion of S/B MD 97. The witness advised he saw the passenger side tires of the defendants vehicle strike the curb/ entrance to the Park  Ride, located on MD 97, just S/O MD 32. Instead of stopping, the witness observed the vehicle continue N/B MD 97, then made an abrupt right turn, leaving the roadway, crossing the grass shoulder, and enter the Northern most point of the Park  Ride. The witness stated he believed the passenger side tires were flattened from striking the curb at the entrance to the Park  Ride. The witness turned back and parked in the Park  Ride, and awaited our (the Polices) arrival.  Phase I: Reason for Stop  On 09/14/2023 at approximately 1540 hours, I was on duty, in uniform, operating a marked MSP patrol vehicle: G-39. I responded to the area of Park  Ride, located on MD 97 at MD 32, Westminster, Carroll County, MD, for a report of a possible impaired driver. The witness (Jeffrey Carr) followed the vehicle driven by the defendant (a gray Honda CRV, MD tag 6ED5211) N/B on MD 97 from the area of MD 26. Carr advised he observed the vehicle swerve/ drift within the lane several times, and cross the double yellow center lines, into the travel portion of S/B MD 97. The witness advised he saw the passenger side tires of the defendants vehicle strike the curb/ entrance to the Park  Ride, located on MD 97, just S/O MD 32. Instead of stopping, the witness observed the vehicle continue N/B MD 97, then made an abrupt right turn, leaving the roadway, crossing the grass shoulder, and enter the Northern most point of the Park  Ride. The witness stated he believed the passenger side tires were flattened from striking the curb at the entrance to the Park  Ride. The witness turned back and parked in the Park  Ride, and awaited our (the Polices) arrival. I responded to the area to check the welfare of the driver of the Honda CRV. The weather was clear and approximately 78 degrees Fahrenheit. Upon my arrival, the driver/ defendant was standing outside the witness vehicle.  Phase II: Contact  I made contact with the witness, I identified myself, and stated the reason for the contact. The witness provided me with his above listed statement. TFC Poff was on scene and had obtained the drivers identification. The driver, who was identified by her Maryland Drivers License to be GINA GAY DOYLE, was standing in the parking lot of the Park  Ride, swaying side to side. The driver was wearing a black shirt, plaid leggings, and boots. I made contact with the driver and asked her several questions regarding her wellbeing, health, medications taken, drug use, and alcohol consumption. The driver denied any illegal/ street drug use, denied alcohol consumption, and advised she is currently in chemotherapy for cancer, and is prescribed (and taking) gabapentin for nerve damage/ nerve pain. The driver did advise she had difficulty walking due to possibly having low blood oxygen. The driver was wearing prescription transition sunglasses, but was able to see my pen 12-14 inches in front of her face without them. The driver advise she is not on pain management medications, and is not taking any anti-depressant/ anxiety medications.  While speaking with the driver, I made the following observations:  -slow, slurred speech -side to side sway -dilated pupils  Based on my observations and the statement of the witness, I made the decision to administer the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  Phase III: Pre-Arrest Screening  All tests were explained and demonstrated prior to asking the driver to attempt them. The tests were conducted in a flat, well-lit area, free of debris.  SFSTs:  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus:  The drivers eyes displayed equal pupil size (dilated), tracking, and reaction. I was able to observe 6 clues out of the 6 potential clues:  -both eyes lacked smooth pursuit -distinct nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes -onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degree deviation in both eyes  Additional observations:  -eyes bloodshot -had to be reminded to keep her head still and to keep looking at/ for the stimulus (pen) -slight side to side sway  Vertical Nystagmus was not observed.   Walk  Turn:  The driver conducted this test with her shoes off. I observed 6 clues out of the potential 8 clues:  -side stepped out the instructional position twice (unable/ difficulty maintaining balance) -raised arms approximately 6 inches (and more) for balance -incorrect number of steps (8 on first set of steps, not the 9 as instructed) -missed heel to toe on both sets of steps: side stepped for balance during the walking portion -incorrect turn: turned to the right, not left as instructed and demonstrated -stopped walking after the turn, until I reminded her of the instructions  Additional observations:  -slurred speech  One Leg Stand:  The driver conducted this test with her shoes on. The driver indicated she understood my instructions. The driver stood on her left foot and raised her right. I observed 3 out of the 4 potential clues:  -put foot down 6 times -swayed side to side throughout the test -raised arms approximately 6 inches away from her body for balance  Additional observations:  -slurred speech  Additional Tests: A.R.I.D.E.  Lack of Convergence:  The lack of convergence was observed: left eye diverged from center  Additional observations:  -slurred speech -sway side to side -dilated pupils -bloodshot eyes  Finger To Nose:  The driver was placed in the instructional position: arms down to their side, heels together, hands in fists with index fingers extended and wrists rotated outward. The driver was instructed, when told to do so, to close their eyes and tilt their head backward. I would then give the command, either right or left, and the driver is to touch the tip of their nose with the tip of their index finger, then immediately bring their arm back down to their side. I provided the following commands: left, right, left, right, right, left.  Observations:  -used pad of finger, not finer tip as instructed and demonstrated -body tremors -eyes bloodshot -pupils dilated -sway -missed tip of nose 5 out of the 6 attempts (touching nostrils)  Modified Romberg:  The driver was placed in the instructional position: arms down to their side and heels together. The driver was instructed when I would tell them to do so, to close their eyes, tilt their head back and estimate the passage of 30 seconds by counting quietly to themselves. After the passage of 30 seconds, the driver was instructed to bring their head down, open their eyes and say done.  Observations:  -initially the driver started talking to me during the test and opened her eyes, so I had her stop and begin againafter I gave the instructions again -during the test, the driver swayed front to back approximately 1 inch -the driver took 11 seconds (according to the digital recording) to estimate the passage of 30 seconds  The driver was offered a Preliminary Breath Test, which she submitted to with a result of 0.00 BrAC. Based on my observations of the driver during contact and the SFSTs, I made the decision to place the driver under arrest for DUI. The specific observations that drove my decision were the following:  -slurred speech -dilated pupils -bloodshot eyes -constant swaying throughout contact -impaired balance -the observations of the WT and OLS -impaired time perception -impaired control of her body/ depth perception (Finger To Nose) -overall inability to follow instructions provided  The driver was advised she was under arrest for DUI and handcuffed. The driver was placed in my patrol vehicle. I then went to the drivers vehicle and made the following observations: fresh damage to the passenger side tires, and flat front passenger side tire. The vehicle was secured, and the driver was transported to the MSP Westminster Barrack for further processing.  The driver was transported to the MSP Westminster Barrack, where she was read the DR15 Advice of Rights at 1647 hours on 09/14/2023. During the reading of the DR15, the driver nodded off. The driver signed the DR15 at 1709 hours, agreeing to submit to the intoximeter. The intoximeter was administered by Cpl McCarty. The driver was given the opportunity to provide two valid breath samples. The driver was not able to provide 2 valid samples in 3 attempts (insufficient samples). The intoximeter was marked as a / insufficient breath/ sample/ refusal at1726 hours. The intoximeter was found to be in working order and a successful simulation test was completed at 1743 hours. The driver was issued the DR15, DR15A, the Notice to Right of Counsel, the Notice to Appear, and traffic citations M6R0DJH-M6Y0DJH. The driver was advised not to drive for 12 hours from the time of arrest (1610 hours). The driver was released to her daughter.  While I was explaining the Notice to Appear and the other paperwork, the driver did appear to nod off.  The driver was polite and respectful at all times.  All events did occur in Carroll County, MD.  Case closed on arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 10:54:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 12:37:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>FAIR</LastName>
            <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5334</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>521770</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/14/2023 15:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 10:21:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 10:21:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>55</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 10:48:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 10:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389320</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>DOYLE</LastName>
               <FirstName>GINA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>GAY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/13/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 10:48:02</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>DOYLE</LastName>
               <FirstName>GINA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>GAY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/13/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 10:48:02</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>309</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Main</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Westminster</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21158</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.013474</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.585006</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 10:48:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 10:48:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 10:48:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 10:48:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>42</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 12:31:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 12:31:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389330</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>CARR</LastName>
               <FirstName>JEFFREY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>WAYNE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/28/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 12:30:40</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J160</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>CARR</LastName>
               <FirstName>JEFFREY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>WAYNE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/28/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J160</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 12:30:40</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>882</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Gaming</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>SQ</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hampstead</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21074</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2024</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.837781</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.599261</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>667</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>701</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5083</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 12:31:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 12:31:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 10:22:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 10:22:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157657</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 10:54:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 10:54:44</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>7FARW2H82LE011202</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CR-V</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>LL</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6ED5211</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>