<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-017668</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/18/2023 14:02:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/18/2023 14:02:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/22/2023 21:52:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/22/2023 21:52:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Distribution of child pornography. Cybertip #160824548</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/18/2023 14:02:18</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 09:00:50</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>CAC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>694887</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/18/2023 14:02:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 10:13:12</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>694887</AddressId>
         <City>Great Mills</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.496791</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.261608</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/18/2023 14:02:14</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/18/2023 14:02:14</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>05/23/2023 11:49:44</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/18/2023 14:02:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 09:00:36</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments -NCMEC Cybertip # 160824548  Narrative On May 15, 2023, the Maryland State Police Computer Crimes Section /Maryland Internet Crimes Against Children Task Force received NCMEC CyberTip # 160824548. The CyberTip, generated by Snapchat, indicated that a subject uploading/possessing/distributing child pornography through the internet. The CyberTip was assigned to TFC Burnett for investigation.   The CyberTip provided the following information pertaining to the suspect: Date of Birth: 02-06-2009 Screen/User Name: cutie_kylene22 IP Address: 216.36.6.149 04-23-2023 06:50:42 UTC Additional Information: The account identifier provided is a username which should be provided when seeking data.  TFC Burnett reviewed this CyberTip and observed it to contain three video files depicting child pornography as it is defined by Maryland Law. The file is described below:  Filename #1: q0_XeTNXQ2mmn_BuGu221wAAAZGxmamR0dGtmAYesonX3AYesofYy AAAAAA~web.mp4 (uploaded twice)  Description: This file is a nineteen second colored video of a nude African American female child in a bathtub, exposing her breasts. Based on the size and physical development, the child appears to be between 10-13 years of age. These files appear to be self-produced.  Filename #2: q0_XeTNXQ2mmn_BuGu221wAAAZ2NoeHVsanV2AYeq9D9eAYeq9DRp AAAAAA~web.mp4  Description: This file is a nine second colored video of a nude African American female child in a bathtub, exposing her breasts. Based on the size and physical development, the child appears to be between 10-13 years of age. These files appear to be self-produced and is the same female as Filename #1.  TFC Burnett conducted a query of the IP address 216.36.6.149 through an open source database and observed it to be registered through Breezeline and geo-locates to Great Mills, Md.   TFC Burnett authored a subpoena request for the IP address through Breezeline which was submitted to the Howard County States Attorneys Office for endorsement.  Based on the content, a knock and talk will be conducted in the future.   Case Status OPEN / PENDING ADDITIONAL INVESTIGATION</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6764</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/22/2023 10:13:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6764</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 10:13:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burnett</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kelsey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6764</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/31/2023 06:29:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/31/2023 06:29:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/09/2023 09:00:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6764</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 06:29:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 09:00:36</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments:    -Signed Breezeline subpoena   -Breezeline subscriber information   -Breezeline declaration of authenticity   -Breezeline records release cover  Narrative:    On 5/25/2023, I received the signed Breezeline subpoena from the Howard County States Attorneys Office and submitted it to Breezeline.    On 5/30/2023, I received the Breezeline subpoena return with the below information:   Target Details IP Address 216.36.6.149 on 04/23/2023 06:50:42 (UTC) Subscriber Name: CHARLES WISE JR Subscriber Address: 19986 PINEY POINT RD, CALLAWAY, MD 20620 Billing Address: PO BOX 91, CALLAWAY, MD 20620-0091 Account Activation Date: 03/29/2007 Account Deactivation Date: Account is active. Associated Email Addresses: WISECT2002@AOL.COM Associated Phone Numbers: 301-481-4848 IP Address History: 216.36.6.149  A law enforcement search revealed the name ofCharles Edward Wise Jr. (W/M, DOB: 9/20/1972), located at 45055 Lady Lane, Callaway, MD since 7/21/2021. The name Catherine Theresa Andrews (W/F, DOB: 3/20/1975) is associated to Charles and has the same address as the subpoena return 19986 Piney Point Rd, POB 91, Callaway, MD. Also Catherine has the same phone number and email address as the subpoena, Charles does not.  A knock and talk will be conducted on 6/2/2023.    On 6/2/2023, at approximately 0614 hours, Sgt. Pitcher and I responded to 19986 Piney Point Rd, Callaway, Maryland to conduct a knock and talk. Upon arrival, we made contact with Catherine Andrews and showed her a photograph of the females face that was in the video, which she could not identify. Catherine retrieved her daughter who was able to identify the child as Kylene, Aden Jones ex-girlfriend and they go to Leonardtown Middle School. I later sent the Chief, Safety and Security of the St. Marys County Public Schools, Frederick Wyant about identifying the child in the video.    Wyant provided the name ofKylene Syreniti Tudder, DOB. 02-09-10, address: 24111 Speith Road, Hollywood, MD 20636. The listed guardianfor the studentis Leigha Tudder, same address with a contact telephonenumber of 240-431-6591. I also received a call from School Resource Officer, Cpl. Carbarry with the St. Marys Sheriffs Office in reference to this case.  On 6/7/2023, I made contact with Cpl. Carbarry about this case and he explained that this incident was previously reported by Kylenes mother/grandmother that her account was hacked in April 2023. Cpl. Carbarry advised he had talked to the guardians and the issue was resolved. He advised he will reach back out to the guardians and explained that the Snapchat account did not appear to be hacked.  Case closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6764</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 06:33:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6764</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/07/2023 09:03:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burnett</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kelsey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6764</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>