<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-027280</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/01/2023 20:28:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/01/2023 20:28:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/01/2023 20:04:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/01/2023 20:04:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI Crash</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/01/2023 20:28:17</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 13:23:46</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>GREENSBORO RD/ N MAIN ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>642527</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/01/2023 20:28:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:33:38</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>642527</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Greensboro</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Greensboro</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21639</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>N</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-75.799226</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.984922</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/01/2023 20:28:15</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/01/2023 20:28:15</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/20/2023 10:34:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/01/2023 20:28:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:04:28</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Benson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Benson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fisher</LastName>
            <FirstName>Rodney</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516724</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/01/2023 20:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:35:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:35:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516724</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/01/2023 20:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:35:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:35:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>28</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:43:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:43:21</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>385578</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Garrett</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Douglas</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/19/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14433942E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>08/20/2023 07:42:17</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Garrett</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Douglas</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/19/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14433942E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>G630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/20/2023 07:42:17</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7070</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Statum</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Denton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21629</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2559</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.8407083</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.801759</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>208</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Academy</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Greensboro</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21639</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.806758</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.976769</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>463</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5268</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:43:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:43:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:43:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:43:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:35:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:35:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/20/2023 10:22:16</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/20/2023 10:22:16</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/20/2023 10:34:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 10:22:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:04:28</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23-MSP-027280 DUI #23-58-155 Greensboro Road @ N Main Street, Greensboro, Caroline County, MD TROOPER T. BENSON #7099 MARYLAND STATE POLICE - EASTON BARRACK  Maryland State Police (MSP) unmarked patrol vehicle I-5 is equipped with a mobile video recording device. Body Worn Camera was operational. Incident recorded.  Defendant: Name: Robert Douglas Garrett Date of Birth: 10/16/1994 MD SDX#: MD-10273297655 Date of Arrest: 08/01/2023 Time of Arrest: 2039 hours DUI #: 23-58-155 (Easton Barrack)  Training  Certificates: * I am trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA). * I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training. * I have successfully completed Enhanced DUI Enforcement Training through the Maryland State Police SPIDRE Team. * I have successfully completed Cannabis Impaired Detection Workshop through the Maryland State Police.  Narrative: On Tuesday, August 1, 2023, at approximately 2004 hours, I, TFC. Benson #7099, was dispatched to the area of Greensboro Road and N Main Street in Greensboro, Caroline County, MD for the report of a single vehicle, rollover motor vehicle collision. The MSP Easton Barrack advised that the Greensboro Fire Department and Caroline County Emergency Medical Services were being dispatched as it was unknown on injuries.   Phase 2  Personal Contact: Upon my arrival, Greensboro Fire Department and Caroline County EMS Paramedic 17 (Run #: 27899) were on scene treating the driver, and sole occupant of the vehicle, for possible injuries. I observed a single vehicle, a black Ford Fusion bearing MD registration 6BTF76, resting on its roof approximately 10 yards off the shoulder of northbound Greensboro Road north of N Marin Street in Greensboro, Caroline County, MD. I also observed one (1) telephone pole snapped in half from the collision. The driver, identified as Robert Douglas Garrett, DOB: 10/16/1994, 2/M, refused medical treatment. At this time, I made contact with Garrett in the back of Caroline County EMS Paramedic 17. I observed Garrett to have red, bloodshot eyes. Garrett spoke with a slur as he answered questions. I also observed Garrett nodding out, having difficulty staying awake, while EMS personnel spoke to him. Garrett also displayed a thousand-yard stare and his movements were slow and lethargic. As he spoke, I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his person.   I asked where Garrett was heading to which he stated he was heading to a girls house in Goldsboro. Garrett stated he was coming form his sisters house, located at 208 Academy Street, Greensboro, MD. He stated he had been at his sisters house since approximately 3:30pm. Garrett stated he went to his sisters hose after he got off work. Garrett went on to state that as he was coming around the bend on Greensboro Road the steering in the vehicle got hard, he heard something snap, and the steering wheel began spinning freely.   Phase 3  Pre-Arrest Screening: At this time, I asked Garrett to submit to a series of Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs), to which he agreed.  Medical Pre-Screening: Garrett appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any physical injuries. Garrett was wearing a black t-shirt, red shorts, and gray New Balance tennis shoes. I asked Garrett the following questions:  Doctor and/or Physical Therapist  No. Physical Injuries No. Medical Conditions No. Medication Gabapentin, 400mg. Glasses and/or contacts Yes, glasses. Garrett did not have his glasses and was unsure where they were located.  I asked Garrett if he could walk in a straight line, turn around, and walk back, to which he stated he could. I asked Garrett if he could balance on one (1) foot to which he stated I cant do it sober. Garrett stated he has bad balance due to a right knee surgery from approximately three (3) years prior due to a motorcycle crash in Ocean City, MD. I asked Garrett again if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages, to which he stated he had NOT consumed any alcoholic beverages. I asked Garrett is had consumed medication or any other substances, to which he stated he had taken his Gabapentin (400mg) as prescribed earlier that morning at approximately 0630 hours. Garrett later stated he also consumed Ibuprofen.   HGN was conducted in the rear, treatment compartment of Caroline County EMS Paramedic 17. The treatment area of Paramedic 17 was flat and free of debris. Lighting conditions consisted of the interior lights of Paramedic 17.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) Test: Prior to beginning the test, I instructed Garrett to stand with his feet together and his arms down at his sides. I explained the test to Garrett. Garrett advised he understood and did not have any questions. Prior to beginning the test, I held my pen twelve (12) to fifteen (15) inches from Garretts nose, slightly above eye level. His pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present. 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present. 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present.  Vertical Gaze Nystagmus (VGN) was not conducted.  A total of six (6) clues were observed during this test.  Walk and Turn (WAT) Test: Prior to conducting the Walk and Turn Test I asked Garrett to exit Paramedic 17 to conduct the remainder of the test on the shoulder of Greensboro Road. The shoulder of Greensboro Road was flat and free of debris.  Prior to beginning the test, I instructed Garrett to stand on the white line, on the shoulder of Greensboro Road, with his right foot directly in front of his left foot touching heel to toe and to place his arms down by his sides. At this time, I demonstrated and explained the test to Garrett. Garrett advised he understood and did not have any questions.   Instructional Stage: 1.) Lost Balance two (2) times.   Walking Stage (1st Nine): 1.) Stepped Off-Line 2,) Stops Walking  At this time, I allowed Garrett to restart the test a second time.   Instructional Stage: 1.) Lost Balance one (1) time.  Walking Stage (1st Nine): 1.) Missed Heel to Toe on step 5 2.) Stepped Off-Line on step 6 3.) Stops Walking on Step 6  Turn: Performed satisfactorily and as instructed.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): 1.) Stepped Off-Line step 2 and 4 2.) Stops Walking on step 4  A total of four (4) clues were observed during this test.  One Leg Stand (OLS): Prior to Garrett performing the test, I demonstrated and instructed him to stand with his feet together and arms down by his sides. I explained and demonstrated the test to Garrett. Upon completion of my explanation and demonstration, Garrett advised he understood and did not have any questions. Garrett stated he was going to balance on his right foot, raising his left foot off the ground.   Instructional Stage: Nothing observed.  Balance and Counting Stage: Seconds 0-10: 1.) Sways left to right.  Seconds 11-20: 1.) Sways left to right. 2.) Put foot down one (1) time.  Seconds 21-30: 1.) Sways left to right. 2.) Arms more than six (6) inches.  While counting, Garrett missed the number 3, counting the number 4 twice. Garrett also counted the number 7 two (2) times. Garrett counted 20 seconds in a total of 30 seconds. I observed Garretts right leg shaking aggressively throughout the entirety of the test.   A total of three (3) clues were observed during this test.  At this time, Garrett stated he had consumed one (1) shot at approximately 1530 hours (3:30pm).  Lack of Convergence: Prior to beginning the test, I instructed Garrett to stand with his feet together and arms down at his sides. I explained the test to Garrett. Garrett advised he understood and did not have any questions. Prior to beginning the test, I held my pen twelve (12) to fifteen (15) inches from Garrett nose and instructed him to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus (black pen) with his eyes and eyes only.  Lack of Convergence was NOT PRESENT.  Modified Romberg Balance: Prior to beginning the test, I instructed Garrett to stand with his feet together and arms down at his sides. I explained the test to Garrett. Garrett was instructed to tilt his head back, close his eyes, and estimate the passage of thirty (30) seconds. Garrett advised he understood and did not have any questions.   Garrett swayed, in circular motion, throughout the entirety of the test.  Garrett estimated the passage of thirty (30) seconds in twenty-two (22) seconds. When asked how long he thought it was Garrett state 40 seconds. When asked how he got there he stated went a little bit past 40.   Finger to Nose: Prior to beginning the test, I instructed Garrett to stand with his feet together and his arms down at his sides. I explained the test to Garrett. I instructed Garrett to make a fist and point his index finger out. Garrett was instructed that when advised he would tilt his head backwards and close his eyes. Garrett was instructed that he would bring the tip of his index finger that I instructed to the tip of the nose and directly back down. I demonstrated to Garrett how the test was to be performed. Garrett advised he understood and did not have any questions.  1.) Left Finger  performed as instructed 2.) Right Finger  performed as instructed 3.) Left Finger  performed as instructed 4.) Right Finger  performed as instructed 5.) Right Finger  Initially brought tip of left finger to the tip of his nose, but corrected and brought the tip of right finger to the tip of his nose. 6.) Left Finger  performed as instructed  Preliminary Breath Test (PBT): Garrett was offered a Preliminary Breath Test roadside. Garrett refused to submit to the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT).   Conclusion: Based on my observations, the results of the Standardized Field Sobriety, along with my training, knowledge, and experience Garrett was placed under arrest at approximately 2039 hours. Garrett was read the English audio version of the Advice of Rights form (DR-15) and an English copy was placed on his lap to read along. Garrett agreed to refused to an intoximeter test at approximately 2056 hours. Garrett was transported to the Maryland State Police Denton Detachment, located at 207 South Third Street, Denton, MD 21629. Garrett was issued the appropriate paperwork and released to a sober ride, Catherine Ann Bergholz, DOB: 01/16/1991, 2/F at approximately 2135 hours.  Knotts Towing was contacted and removed the vehicle from the scene. An ACRS report was completed and is uploaded to this report.Delmarva Power Company was contacted and arrived on scene to repair the damaged pole.  CASE CLOSED BY ARREST.  ALL EVENTS OCCURRED IN CAROLINE COUNTY, MARYLAND.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 10:23:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 10:31:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bringman</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5204</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Benson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>