<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013976</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/20/2023 01:18:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/20/2023 01:18:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/20/2023 01:01:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/20/2023 01:01:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>MSP BK G DUI 23-059, TA 21-902D1 (JAVIER ANTONIO GOMEZ)</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 01:18:50</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 11:13:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>BALTIMORE BLVD/ DEDE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>3167</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 01:18:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 12:24:44</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>3167</AddressId>
         <StreetName>BALTIMORE</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>FINKSBURG</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.884344</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.491197</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3125-3201 BALTIMORE BLVD / 0-0 DEDE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3101-3101 BALTIMORE BLVD / 0-0 DEDE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3140-3400 BALTIMORE BLVD / 2900-2999 DEDE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3090-3120 BALTIMORE BLVD / 0-0 DEDE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3320-3499 BALTIMORE BLVD / 2800-2999 DEDE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3000-3123 BALTIMORE BLVD / 2800-2999 DEDE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3090-3120 BALTIMORE BLVD / 2900-2999 DEDE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3124-3319 BALTIMORE BLVD / 2800-2999 DEDE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/20/2023 01:18:47</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/20/2023 01:18:47</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:15:13</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 01:18:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23MSP013976  Incident: MSP Barrack G DUI 23-059  TA 21-902(D)(1)i Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol  Date/ Time: 04/20/2023, 0058 hours  Location of Offense: W/B MD 140, W/O Baltimore/ Carroll County line, Finksburg, Carroll County, MD.  Incident recorded on AXON digital recording system assigned to G-39 and AXON body camera assigned to M/Tpr Fair.  Minors in Vehicle:NO  PBT: 0.00 BrAC at 0118 hours on 04/20/2023  EVIDENTIARY TEST:0.00 BrAC at 0209 hours on 04/20/2023   DRE (Drug Recognition Expert): TFC Eckhardt (IBM 6469)  Blood Drawn at 0403 hours on 04/20/2023 at Carroll Hospital Center Emergency Department, located at 200 Memorial Ave, Westminster, Carroll County, MD 21157.  Weather: clear, approximately 46 degrees Fahrenheit  Prior Offense: NO  Qualifications:  -Maryland State Police Academy (June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007)  -I am trained to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through NHTSA and the Maryland State Police (MSP Academy, June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007).  -I am trained and certified to operate a Kustom ProLaser III, set # 5. All records are kept on file at the MSP Electronic Services Division and Westminster Barrack, the unit was found to be in working order prior to and following the stop, and was used in accordance with MSP policy, my training, and the manufacturers guidelines. My certificate is kept on file with the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack and the Education and Training Division. My training, certification, and the Certificate of Accuracy for the LIDAR unit is non-expiring.  -I have attended and graduated from the University of Maryland University College Advanced DUI College (UMUC January 7-11, 2013). -Street Narcotics Investigation for Road Patrol (MPCTC, 05/22/2015)  -I have attended and completed training Enhanced DUI Enforcement: The Complete Arrest (MPCTC, 05/11/2016).  -A.R.I.D.E.: Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (MPCTC, 03/29-03/30/2017)  -Cannabis Impairment Detection Workshop (MPCTC, 09/29/2021)  Driver: MD DL MD10273864091 JAVIER ANTONIO GOMEZ 8403 SAINT REGIS WAY MONTGOMERY VILLIAGE, MD 20886 5/M, DOB 05/24/2004 301-318-0313 Javiergomez17777@gmail.com  Phase I:  Reason for Contact:  On 04/20/2023 at approximately 0058 hours I was on duty, in uniform, operating a marked Maryland State Police Patrol vehicle, G-39. I was stationary on the right shoulder of E/B MD 140, W/O the Baltimore/ Carroll County line, inside Carroll County, MD, monitoring traffic. I was also utilizing a Kustom ProLaser III, set # 5 (see above listed training and qualifications). I observed a vehicle, described as a gray 2015 Infiniti passenger vehicle (displaying Maryland registration 1ET6764) traveling W/B MD 140 in the left lane of travel (lane 1) at what appeared to be above the posted speed limit of 50 mph. After the vehicle entered Carroll County an passed my location, I was able to activate the LIDAR unit, obtain a solid visual lock, which was accompanied by an audible tone. The LIDAR unit displayed a speed reading of 68 mph in the posted 50 zone, at a distance of 259.3 feet. Also observed the vehicle drive with the passenger side tires over the lane dividing line between lane 1 and lane 2. As I got behind the vehicle, I also observed the vehicle drift side to side, and the driver side tires on the yellow center line. I initiated a traffic stop by activating my emergency equipment (specifically my overhead red and blue lights). The vehicle merged to the left, and came to a stop in the roadway in the center median alternating turn lane. I ordered the driver over the patrol vehicles PA system to move the vehicle out of the roadway. The driver moved the vehicle to parking lot of the Jiffy Mart, located at 3137 Baltimore Blvd, Finksburg, Carroll County, MD. I was able to observe the driver was the only occupant of the vehicle. The weather was clear and approximately 46 degrees Fahrenheit.  Phase II: Contact:  I approached the vehicle on the drivers side of the vehicle. The window was already down and I immediately detected a strong odor of burnt marijuana emanating from the vehicles passenger compartment. I recognized the odor to be that of marijuana (a Controlled Dangerous Substance of Schedule 1) through my knowledge, training, and experience gained with the Maryland State Police. I identified myself, advised the stop was being recorded, and stated the reasons for the traffic stop. The driver already had the vehicles registration card and his identification in his hands and presented them immediately upon request. The driver confirmed his home address and advised he was returning to McDaniel College, where he is a student. The driver was identified as JAVIER ANOTNIO GOMEZ. As I was speaking with the driver, I made the following observations:  -moderate to strong odor of burnt marijuana on exhaled breath -eyes bloodshot in appearance  I returned to my patrol vehicle to enter the drivers information for the business needs of the traffic stop.  I made contact with the driver again. I continued to detect the strong odor of burnt marijuana emanating from the passenger compartment of the vehicle. I asked the driver to exit the vehicle, so I could separate him from the odor of the alcoholic beverage that was emanating from the vehicle. The driver complied. I asked the driver the following questions:  Q. How long ago did you last smoke marijuana? A. Uhhhhhhhhh, ... The driver indicated he last smoked marijuana in the afternoon of 04/19/2023, after 12 or 1pm.  Q. If I was marijuana, where would I be in the vehicle? A. Uhhhhhhhh, the driver admitted to having a little bag of marijuana in the vehicle.  Q. Are you in the medical marijuana program? A. No, I am not.  Q. Do you where contacts or glasses? A. No.  Q. Do you have any physical issues that would prevent you from standing on one leg for approximately 30 seconds or walking a straight line heel touching toe? A. No. The answer was given before I finished asking the question.  Q. Other than marijuana, have you consumed anything that would be considered a Controlled Substance in the State of Maryland, including (but not be limited to) heroin, methamphetamine, cocaine, or anything like that? A. No, sir.  Q. How often do you smoke marijuana? A. Pretty often. The driver clarified this answer to once or twice a week.  Q. How much did you smoke today? A. Not much, just a little bit. I asked if the driver meant a grams worth of marijuana, and he responded yeah.   While speaking with the driver, I continuously made the following observations:  -moderate to strong odor burnt marijuana on breath and person -eyes bloodshot -white dried spittle on the corners of his mouth  Based on my observations of the driver, I made the decision to administer the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  Phase III: Pre-Arrest Screening:  SFSTs:  All tests were explained and demonstrated prior to me asking the driver to attempt them. The driver was wearing a black sweatshirt, black sweat pants, and gray slip on flat soled shoes. The tests were conducted a well lit and level area of the parking lot, free of debris.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus:  The drivers eyes displayed equal pupil size, tracking, and reaction. I was able to observe 0 out of the 6 potential clues.  Additional observations:  -slight sway side to side approximately  inch -eyes bloodshot -body tremors -moderate to strong odor of burnt marijuana on breath and person  Vertical Nystagmus was not observed.   Walk  Turn:  The driver conducted this test with his shoes off. I observed 6 clues out of the potential 8 clues:  -stepped out the instructional position 1 time -stopped walking during the first set of steps -took 8 steps on the first set of steps, stopped walking then took one more step -incorrect turn: pivoted on both heels, not completed as instructed or demonstrated -missed heel to toe (side stepped slightly) on step # 2 and step 6 and -those steps were not in-line with the previous step (not heel touching toe in direct line)  Additional observations:  -strong odor of burnt marijuana breath and person -eyes bloodshot -body tremors  One Leg Stand:  The driver conducted this test with his shoes off. The driver indicated he understood my instructions. The driver stood on his right foot and raised his left. I observed 2 out of the 4 potential clues:  -the driver swayed side to side during the test 2 inches or more -raised arms approximately 6 inches away from body for balance  Additional observations:  -strong odor of burnt marijuana breath and person -eyes bloodshot in appearance -body tremors observed  Additional Tests: A.R.I.D.E.  Lack of Convergence:  The lack of convergence was observed: left eye diverged from center.  Additional observations:  -eyes bloodshot -strong odor of burnt marijuana on the drivers breath and person -body tremors  Finger To Nose:  The driver was placed in the instructional position: arms down to their side, heels together, hands in fists with index fingers extended and wrists rotated outward. The driver was instructed, when told to do so, to close their eyes and tilt their head backward. I would then give the command, either right or left, and the driver is to touch the tip of their nose with the tip of their index finger, then immediately bring their arm back down to their side. I provided the following commands: left, right, left, right, right, left.  Observations:  -on every command of right: touched left nostril -used pad of finger, not finer tip as instructed and demonstrated, on every try -eyelid tremors observed -strong odor of burnt marijuana on the drivers breath and person -eyes bloodshot  Modified Romberg:  The driver was placed in the instructional position: arms down to their side and heels together. The driver was instructed when I would tell them to do so, to close their eyes, tilt their head back and estimate the passage of 30 seconds by counting quietly to themselves. After the passage of 30 seconds, the driver was instructed to bring their head down, open their eyes and say done.  Observations:  -during the test, the driver swayed front to back and side to side approximately 1 inch -the driver took 22 seconds (according to the digital recording) to estimate the passage of 30 seconds -eyelid and body tremors observed -strong odor of burnt marijuana on the drivers breath and person -eyes bloodshot  The driver was offered a Preliminary Breath Test, which he accepted. The result of the PBT was 0.00 BrAC. Based on my observations of the driver during contact and the SFSTs, I made the decision to place the driver under arrest for DUI. The driver was advised he was under arrest and handcuffed.  I conducted a search of the vehicle incident to arrest, and because the driver admitted that marijuana was present within the vehicle. The following items were located and seized:  A. one clear plastic baggie containing green plant matter, suspected CDS marijuana, 61.0 grams (including baggie), 2.15 ounces B. two plastic baggie containing green plant matter, suspected CDS marijuana, 28.4 grams (including baggies), 1.00 ounces C. one black digital scale w/ green plant matter residue, suspected CDS marijuana, trace D. green plant matter, suspected CDS marijuana, 0.9 grams E. one gray colored grinder, formerly containing item D F. one blue colored grinder w/ green plant matter residue, suspected CDS marijuana, trace  All items were located in a black bag, located behind the front passenger seat. All plant matter was recognized through my knowledge, training, and experience gained with the MSP to be CDS of Schedule 1: marijuana. All seized property was seized, captured on MSP form 67 and 63 (P-323273) and submitted to the MSP Westminster Barrack evidence locker in compliance with MSP policy and procedure. Per the agreement with the Carroll County States Attorneys Office, the driver was not charged with the CDS (marijuana) violation.  Located in the trunk of the vehicle, were two cans of an alcoholic beverage (Cutwater Mango Margaritas, 12.5 % alcohol by volume). These were emptied on scene, as the driver was 18 years old and not authorized to possess any alcoholic beverages.  The vehicle was secured in a parking spot and the driver was transported to the MSP Westminster Barrack, where he was read the DR15 Advice of Rights at 0159 hours on 04/20/2023. The drier signed the DR15 at 0200 hours, submitting to the intoximeter. The intoximeter was administered by Sgt Gibson at 0209 hours, with a result of 0.00 BrAC per 210 liters of breath. This reading did not correspond with the impairment I had observed. TFC Eckhardt, a certified Drug Recognition Expert, responded to the MSP Westminster Barrack upon my request and conducted a 12-step IACP/ NHTSA approved Drug Influence Evaluation of the driver, JAVIER GOMEZ. At the conclusion of the evaluation, TFC Eckhardt found GOMEZ to be under the influence of cannabis, impaired, and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At 0338 hours, GOMEZ signed the DR15, submitting to a blood draw and analysis. The driver was transported Carroll Hospital Center Emergency Department, located at 200 Memorial Ave, Westminster, Carroll County, MD 21157, where his blood was drawn at 0403 hours.  The blood sample was packaged according to MSP policy and procedure and sent off for analysis. The driver was released to a sober family member. The driver was polite, respectful, and cooperative at all times.  I request this case remain open, pending service of the blood analysis results and appropriate citations.  All events occurred in Carroll County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 18:18:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 20:37:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>FAIR</LastName>
            <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5334</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503390</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/20/2023 01:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 12:30:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 12:30:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 18:11:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:06</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377304</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>GOMEZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>JAVIER</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ANTONIO</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/24/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/17/2023 18:09:50</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J160</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>GOMEZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>JAVIER</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ANTONIO</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/24/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J160</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/17/2023 18:09:50</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>8403</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>SAINT REGIS</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>MONTGOMERY VILLAGE</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20886</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5603</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.172803</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.182458</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>318</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0313</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 18:11:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 18:11:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 18:11:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 12:30:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 12:30:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153105</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 20:48:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 20:48:30</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>INFI</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>CP</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1ET6764</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 20:43:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 20:43:14</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Baggie w/ green plant matter</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>248821</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>61</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 20:44:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 20:44:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Two plastic baggies w/ green plant matter</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>248822</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>28.4</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 20:45:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 20:45:30</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Digital scale w/ marijuana residue</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>248823</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.001</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 20:46:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 20:46:15</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Green plant matter</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>248824</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.9</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 20:46:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 20:46:54</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Two grinders w/ green plant matter residue</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>248825</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.001</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/18/2023 20:52:44</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/18/2023 20:52:44</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:15:13</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6469</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/18/2023 20:52:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>DRE Report</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Date and time of evaluation: 04/20/2023 0232 hours MSP Case number: 23-MSP-013976 Other Agency Case Number: N/A Rolling log number: 23-003-0087 Location of evaluation: Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack Suspect: Gomez, Javier Antonio Date of birth: 05/24/2004  1. Breath Alcohol Test The suspect agreed to the breath alcohol test with the arresting officer. The test was conducted on instrument #011733 with a result of 0.00 BrAC at 0209 hours. 2. Interview of Arresting Officer On April 20, 2023, M/Tpr. Fair #5334 of the Maryland State Police contacted me and advised that he had a subject at Westminster Barrack who had agreed to the breath test and the breath test results were not consistent with the level of impairment.  I spoke with M/Tpr. Fair who explained that he was on duty and patrolling the Finksburg area on Route 140 when he observed a vehicle that was traveling above the posted speed limit of 50 miles per hour. He explained that he obtained a confirmed speed of 68 miles per hour. He also observed the vehicle to cross over the solid yellow center line. He conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle and made contact with the male operator who was identified as Javier Gomez.  While speaking with Gomez, M/Tpr Fair explained that he detected a moderate to strong odor of brunt marijuana coming from the breath, and person of Gomez. He observed Gomezs eyes to be bloodshot and Gomez to sway and display body tremors while standing outside of the vehicle. Based on his observations, M/Tpr. Fair placed Gomez through Standardized Field Sobriety Testing. M/Tpr. Fair observed 0 out of 6 clues on the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test, 6 out of 8 clues on the Walk and Turn Test, and 2 out of 4 clues on the One Leg Stand Test. M/Tpr. Fair then placed Gomez under arrest for DUI.  A search of the vehicle revealed raw marijuana, a grinder and scale.  3. Preliminary Evaluation  I met with Gomez in the DUI Room of the Westminster Barrack. I identified myself and asked if he would be willing to speak with me. I explained my position, and what my evaluation would entail. He advised that he would be willing to speak with me and go through the evaluation. I produced an MSP Form 180 Advice of Miranda Rights. I read the form 180 to Gomez and asked if he understood his rights, which he advised yes. I asked Gomez to write his initials next to each of the rights if he understood them, which he did. He then signed his name on the acknowledgement line. I advised Gomez to sign the waiver of rights line if he wishes to waive his rights and continue with my evaluation. I further explained that he can invoke his rights at any time and stop the evaluation. Gomez advised that he understood and signed the wavier.  I immediately detected a moderate odor of burnt marijuana emanating from Gomez.  I asked Gomez if he had eaten today, and if so what; Gomez explained that he had a 10 piece wings around 8 or 9 p.m. I asked if he had anything to drink today. He advised that he had water, with his last drink being around the same time he ate.  I asked Gomez to estimate the current time and he stated, 2:00 a.m. (0200 hours). The actual time being 2:34 a.m. (0234 hours). I asked Gomez when he last slept and for how long. Gomez stated last night and he estimated that he went to bed around 2:00 a.m. and woke up around 11:00 a.m.  I asked him if he was sick or injured, which he replied, No. I asked Gomez if he is a diabetic or an epileptic, which he stated, No. When asked if he takes insulin he stated, No.  I asked if he had any physical defects, which he stated that he does not.  I asked if he is under the care of a doctor or dentist, and he stated no.  I asked Gomez if he had taken, or is currently taking, any medications or drugs. Gomez stated that he smokes marijuana.  While speaking with Gomez I observed his speech to be normal. Gomez was cooperative.  Pulse check: 108 bpm at 0242 hours. (ELEVATED)(Average range 60-90 bpm)  4. Examination of the eyes Gomez was advised to sit upright, look at me, and keep his head still. I asked if he wears contacts or glasses, and he advised that he does not. When asked, he denied blindness in either eye. I utilized a penlight with a steady illuminated green light for the stimulus. I advised him to look at the stimulus and to follow it with his eyes only, keeping his head still. I asked him if he understood my instructions, and he explained that he did.  While holding the stylus steady, I observed his eyelids to be normal. Resting nystagmus was not observed.  I was able to observe that he had equal tracking of both eyes and the following:     margin-left:8px"&gt;Lack of smooth pursuit: Not Present.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Maximum Deviation: Not Present.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Angle of Onset: Not Present.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Vertical Gaze Nystagmus: Not Present.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Lack of Convergence: Eyes converged.  5. Divided Attention Tests All of the following divided attention tests were conducted in the DUI Room of the Westminster Barrack, with the exception of the Walk and Turn test, which was conducted in the hallway outside of the room. The floor was level and free from any debris in both locations. All of the tests were explained and demonstrated to Gomez. Prior to asking Gomez to perform the tests, I asked if he understood my instructions and would clarify any questions.   Modified Romberg  I observed Gomez to have no sway from front to back or side to side. I observed very distinct eyelid tremors.  Gomez estimated 30 seconds of time in 18 seconds. This indicates a fast internal clock.  Walk and Turn Test  Instructional Phase: Nothing to report.  Walking Phase (1st Nine): Took a total of 8 steps. Raised arms more than 6 inches for balance.  Turn: Turned incorrectly.  Walking Phase (2nd Nine): Took 9 steps.  One Leg Stand (Raised Right Foot) Swayed from side to side while balancing. Raised arms more than 6 inches for balance. Hopped. Counted to 28 in the allotted 30 seconds.  One Leg Stand (Raised Left Foot) Left foot hit the ground on count 4. Raised arms more than 6 inches from body to maintain balance. Counted to 29 in the allotted 30 seconds.  Finger to Nose   border:none"&gt;          border-left:1px solid #999999; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:1px solid #999999; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Hand Told to Use     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:1px solid #999999; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Spot on Face Touched     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:1px solid #999999; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Portion of Finger Used     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:1px solid #999999; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Miscellaneous           border-left:1px solid #999999; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Left     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Just above the tip     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;N/A           border-left:1px solid #999999; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Right     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Just above the tip     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;N/A           border-left:1px solid #999999; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Left     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Tip of nose     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;N/A           border-left:1px solid #999999; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Right     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Tip of nose     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;N/A           border-left:1px solid #999999; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Right     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Tip of nose     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;N/A           border-left:1px solid #999999; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Left     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Tip of nose     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px" valign="top"&gt;N/A        6. Vital Signs     margin-left:8px"&gt;Blood Pressure: 150/74 mmHg (ELEVATED)(Average range is 120-140 / 70-90 mmHg)   margin-left:8px"&gt;Pulse #2: 108 bpm at 0259 hours (ELEVATED)(Average range is 60-90 bpm)   margin-left:8px"&gt;Temperature: 98.6 (Average range is 98.6 +/- 1 degree Fahrenheit)  7. Dark Room Examination    border:none"&gt;          border-left:1px solid #999999; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:1px solid #999999; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px"&gt;Pupil     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:1px solid #999999; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px"&gt;Room Light    (2.5  5.0)     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:1px solid #999999; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px"&gt;Near Total Darkness    (5.0  8.5)     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:1px solid #999999; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px"&gt;Direct Light    (2.0  4.5)           border-left:1px solid #999999; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; height:26px; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px"&gt;Left     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; height:26px; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px"&gt;5.5 mm     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; height:26px; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px"&gt;8.0 mm     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; height:26px; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px"&gt;5.5  6.0 mm           border-left:1px solid #999999; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; height:23px; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px"&gt;Right     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; height:23px; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px"&gt;5.5 mm     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; height:23px; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px"&gt;8.0 mm     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid #999999; border-top:none; height:23px; padding:0in 7px 0in 7px; width:156px"&gt;5.5  6.0 mm        Rebound Dilation: Present Pupillary Reaction to Light: Normal  Nasal Area Observations: Clear. Oral Cavity Observations: Clear.  8. Muscle Tone Examination Gomezs muscle tone was normal.  9. Injection Site Examination Nothing notable.  Pulse #3: 108 bpm at 0309 hours (ELEVATED)(Average range 60-90 bpm).  10. Observations and Subject Statements Throughout my evaluation of Gomez, I observed him to remain cooperative. Gomezs balance was poor during the one leg stand test. He had an altered time perception.  I asked Gomez if he had taken any medications or drugs and he stated that he smoked marijuana (approximately 1 gram) around noon time.  11. Opinion of Evaluator  My opinion, as a certified Drug Recognition Expert, is that Javier Antonio Gomez is under the influence of Cannabis, is impaired, and is unable to operate a vehicle safely.  My opinion is based on the following signs of impairment:     margin-left:32px"&gt;The noticeable indicators to drug use and impairment are:       margin-left:8px"&gt;The noticeable signs of impairment during the Modified Romberg, Walk and Turn, One Leg Stand, and Finger to Nose.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Cannabis        margin-left:8px"&gt;Dilated pupils     margin-left:8px"&gt;Altered time and distance perception     margin-left:8px"&gt;Bloodshot eyes     margin-left:8px"&gt;Eyelid tremors     margin-left:8px"&gt;Odor of Marijuana     margin-left:8px"&gt;Rebound dilation     margin-left:8px"&gt;Relaxed Inhibitions     margin-left:8px"&gt;Admission to Cannabis use             12. Toxicology Exam I asked Gomez if he would consent to a blood test. Gomez agreed to the blood test and was transported to Carroll Hospital Center by M/Tpr. Fair. ER Tech Ramirez Abuzov (100069483) drew Gomezs blood from his left A.C. at 0403 hours, using MSP Blood Kit G-449. I witnessed the entire blood draw and sealed the blood kit.  13. Miscellaneous The full DRE exam was recorded on body won camera.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6469</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/18/2023 20:53:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6469</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/20/2023 19:28:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Snedeker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5367</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckhardt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derek</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6469</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/07/2023 06:53:30</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/07/2023 06:53:30</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:15:13</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 06:53:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23-MSP-013976  Incident: MSP Barrack G DUI 23-059  TA 21-902(D)(1)i Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol  Date/ Time: 04/20/2023, 0058 hours  Location of Offense: W/B MD 140, W/O Baltimore/ Carroll County line, Finksburg, Carroll County, MD.  Driver:  MD DL MD10273864091 JAVIER ANTONIO GOMEZ 8403 SAINT REGIS WAY MONTGOMERY VILLIAGE, MD 20886 5/M, DOB 05/24/2004 301-318-0313  text-decoration:underline"&gt;Javiergomez17777@gmail.com  Narrative:  On 08/04/2023 I received the blood analysis results for this incident. The results have been attached to this report. The blood tested positive for Carboxy THC and Delta 9 THC. On 08/06/2023 at approximately 1515 hours, I made contact with the driver, JAVIER GOMEZ, at his residence. GOMEZ was served a copy of the test results, Civil Citation 2Z46653903 for the under 21 alcohol violation, and traffic citations M1H0DJH-M1N0DJH. The driver was issued the Notice to Appear and the Notice to Right of Counsel. The driver was not asked any questions regarding the incident, and did not make any statements. Per the agreement with the Carroll County States Attorneys Office, the driver was not charged with any marijuana/ cannabis violations.  I request the case be closed on citations. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/07/2023 06:53:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 07:30:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>FAIR</LastName>
            <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5334</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503390</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>2</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/17/2023 12:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 12:30:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/17/2023 12:30:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>