<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-040381</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/14/2023 21:49:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/14/2023 21:49:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/14/2023 21:17:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/14/2023 21:17:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The victim alleged the suspect threatened him with a knife.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 21:49:54</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1865</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/08/2023 13:04:39</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>713156</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 21:49:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/19/2023 04:25:44</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>713156</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>43029</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Megan</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Leonardtown</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20650</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.585858</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.274775</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/14/2023 21:49:52</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/14/2023 21:49:52</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/08/2023 13:04:02</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 21:49:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-car and body worn camera operational T-22.  SCENE PROCESSING:   One MSP Form 76, Written Statement, from victim Gene Alan Haigh. One MSP Form 76, from witness Stephanie Rena Haigh. Five digital photographs of the victim. One digital photograph of the suspect.  PHYSICAL EVIDENCE:   Two (2) Written Statements.   Five (5) digital photographs of victim.  One (1) digital photograph of suspect.  NARRATIVE:   On November 14, 2023 at 2117 hours, while on duty, I responded to 43029 Megan Ln Leonardtown, St. Marys County, Maryland 20650 for a reported assault. The St. Marys County Emergency Communications Center (ECC) dispatched the call and advised they took multiple 911 calls for people yelling and fighting outside. They advised one person possibly has a knife.   Upon my arrival, I made contact with the complainant, who was identified by her Maryland Drivers License as Stephanie Rena Haigh (W/F DOB 09/15/1972). Stephanie advised she was outside with her husband, who would later be identified as the victim, by his Maryland Drivers License as Gene Alan Haigh (W/M DOB 05/27/1971). They were yelling at their German Shepard to go back inside their residence. Stephanie advised that is when a white male from down the street started yelling at them to shut up because his mom was trying to sleep. Stephanie advised Gene yelled back at the white male to be quiet and mind his own business. Stephanie advised Gene and the white male, continued to yell back and forth at each other. Stephanie told Gene to go back inside the residence, which Gene did. Stephanie advised she went down the drive to tell the white male to mind his own business. Stephanie advised the white male yelled I will kill you bitch. Stephanie advised Gene came back out of the residence and confronted the white male in the street. Stephanie advised the white male lunged at Gene with a knife. Stephanie advised she only saw the blade of the knife. Stephanie advised she saw Gene take a step back, however she did not see the white male touch Gene with the knife. Stephanie advised she then went back into her residence and called 911. Stephanie completed an MSP Form 76, Written Statement.   I made contact with Gene. He advised he was outside with Stephanie trying to get their German Shepard back inside their residence. Gene advised while trying to get their dog back inside, a white male yelled at them stating shut the fuck up several times. Gene advised they replied back to him, telling him to mind his own business. Gene advised he got the dog back inside the residence and Stephanie went down the drive. Gene advised that is when he heard the white male threaten to kill Stephanie. Gene advised he came back outside the residence and confronted the white male, asking him what his problem was. Gene advised the white male stated are you ready for this and began running towards him with a knife. Gene advised the white male lunged at him with the knife and held the knife to his stomach. Gene advised the tip of the knife touched his stomach. Gene advised the knife did not penetrate his skin. Gene advised that he froze and stated are you fucking crazy is that a knife? Gene advised the white male stated I told you I was gonna kill you. Gene advised that he could only see the blade of the knife and could not tell if it was a switch blade or a fixed blade. Gene described the white male as holding the knife in his right hand, winding his arm back, and then bringing the knife under hand and lunging forward towards him.   Gene described the white male, as possibly in his 30s, with brown hair, and little bit of facial hair. Gene was not able to provide a clothing description. Gene advised the male lives down the street and pointed to two different trailers located at 43013 and 43015 Megan Ln Leonardtown, St. Marys County, Maryland 20650. Gene advised he does not know the males name; however, he knows he lives in the neighborhood. Gene advised approximately a week ago, Gene and his next-door neighbor got into a verbal argument about dog poop being in the neighbors yard. Gene advised that during the verbal argument, the same white male from tonight approached them and interjected him self into the argument. Gene advised that he could call his landlord, and he would know who the white male is. Gene completed an MSP Form 76, Written Statement. I also obtained five digital photographs of Gene. I did not observe any physical injuries. I also did not observe Genes shirt to be cut or any holes where the knife made contact with his body.   Myself, Deputy Bud #325 and Deputy Henry #333 conducted neighborhood checks at the following addresses: 43031, 43032, 43027, 43025, 43023, 43013, 43015, and 43017 Megan Ln Leonardtown, St. Marys County, Maryland 20650. All neighbors that we made contact with, all advised the could hear yelling outside, however they did not witness any physical altercation or witness anyone with a knife.    Gene contacted his landlord, who would later be identified as James Calvin Washington (B/M DOB 11/26/1961). Washington responded to the scene and made contact with me. Washington advised that the white male Gene is referring to resides at 43013 Megan Ln, and goes by the name of Shane. I asked Washington how he knew Gene was referring to Shane. Washington advised because Shane is the same subject the interjected himself into the argument that occurred approximately a week ago.    I responded to 43013 Megan Ln to make contact with Shane. Upon my arrival, an elderly female opened the door, who was identified as Deborah Elizabeth Underwood (W/F DOB 01/02/1954). I asked Deborah if her son was home, to which replied yes. I asked Deborah what he sons name was and she advised David. I asked Deborah if Shane was home and Deborah advised Shane is Davids middle name. Deborahs sons would later be identified as David Shane Underwood (W/M DOB 07/01/1979). Deborah advised David is in bed sleeping and has been home the entire time. I asked Deborah to go get David for me, she replied back you want me to wake him up? Deborah appeared to be hesitant to go get David. I asked Deborah again to go get him to which she complied.   I made contact with David and advised him we were investigating an argument between neighbors. David advised he heard some yelling earlier approximately an hour ago. I advised David of his Advice of Miranda Rights which he knowingly and intelligently understood. I asked David if got into an argument with his neighbors tonight. David denied any involvement. David admitted to intervening in the argument approximately week ago, between Gene and his next-door neighbor. David advised that he left Ledos Pizza located at 25460 Point Lookout Rd Leonardtown Maryland, 20650 at approximately 2030 hours. David advised he brought food home for Deborah. David advised that he was probably home before 2100 hours. David advised he then went down the street to a trailer located towards the entrance of the neighborhood, to help take care of an elderly male. David advised he left there and got home around 2130 hours. David advised on his way home, he heard yelling between a male and female, however he did not witness any fighting. I asked David multiple times throughout the interview if he had an argument with his neighbors tonight and he denied any involvement. During the course of the interview, I conducted a wanted check on David. PCO T. Smale from the Leonardtown Barrack T advised David had an active arrest warrant (#67223) through the Calvert County Sheriffs Office.   David was placed under arrest for the arrest warrant at 2241 hours. David was placed in the front seat of my patrol vehicle. David was transported to the St. Marys County Detention and Rehabilitation Center, pending a bond review with the District Court Commissioner.   I request this case to remain open, pending further investigation.  All events occurred in St. Marys County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:55:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/19/2023 04:30:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5920</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckrich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7350</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529849</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/14/2023 21:17:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:28:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 01:28:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529849</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1420</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/14/2023 21:17:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1420</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:29:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 01:29:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>44</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:31:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/19/2023 04:25:44</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>221255</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Underwood</LastName>
               <FirstName>David</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shane</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/01/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14196631E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2019 22:41:49</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>U536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Underwood</LastName>
               <FirstName>David</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shane</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/01/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14196631E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>U536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2019 22:41:49</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>43013</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Megan</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Leonardtown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20650</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.586264</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.274215</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>237</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0267</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:31:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:31:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:31:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>52</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:43:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/19/2023 04:25:44</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393022</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Haigh</LastName>
               <FirstName>Gene</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/27/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 01:42:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Haigh</LastName>
               <FirstName>Gene</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/27/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 01:42:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>43029</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Megan</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Leonardtown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20650</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.585858</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.274775</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>572</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0328</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:43:24</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:43:24</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>51</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:45:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/19/2023 04:25:44</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393023</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Haigh</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stephanie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Rena</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/15/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 01:45:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Haigh</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stephanie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Rena</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/15/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 01:45:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>43029</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Megan</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Leonardtown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20650</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.585858</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.274775</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>572</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0330</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:45:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:45:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>61</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:51:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/19/2023 04:25:44</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393024</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Washington</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Calvin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/26/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 01:51:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Washington</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Calvin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/26/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 01:51:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>587</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9935</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:51:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>69</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:53:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/19/2023 04:25:44</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393026</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Underwood</LastName>
               <FirstName>Deborah</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elizabeth</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/02/1954 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 01:53:24</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>U536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D160</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Underwood</LastName>
               <FirstName>Deborah</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elizabeth</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/02/1954 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>U536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D160</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 01:53:24</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>43013</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Megan</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Leonardtown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20650</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.586264</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.274215</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>237</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0267</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 01:53:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/08/2023 07:20:52</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/08/2023 07:20:52</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/08/2023 13:04:02</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/08/2023 07:20:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Body Worn Camera Operational T-12.  NARRATIVE:   On December 5, 2023, I created a photo lineup containing a picture of Underwood with five other people with similar physical features as Underwood. Tpr Hersh #7443 presented the photo lineup to Haigh in the lobby of the Leonardtown Barrack T located at 23200 Leonard Hall Dr Leonardtown, St. Marys County, Maryland 20650. Haigh was unable to positively identify Underwood as the suspect. On December 8, 2023, I contacted Haigh and informed him that I will be closing the case due to a lack of evidence.  The Photo lineup was captured on an MSP Form 67, Chain of Custody.  Due to a lack of evidence and lack of a positive identification of the suspect, I request this case to be closed.  All events occurred in St. Marys County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7350</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/08/2023 07:21:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7350</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/08/2023 12:43:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Laney</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1865</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Marquis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6369</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckrich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7350</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>