<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-042671</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/02/2023 19:10:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/02/2023 19:10:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/02/2023 19:08:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/02/2023 19:08:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Suicidal Subject - Exigent Request</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 19:10:19</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 09:40:43</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ASD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>Baltimore, Maryland</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>714871</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 19:10:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 07:35:14</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>714871</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Hanover Ccu</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/02/2023 19:10:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/02/2023 19:10:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>12/05/2023 09:40:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 19:10:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 09:40:27</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments - Facebook Records - Instagram Records  Narrative  On 12/02/2023, at approximately 06:37 PM, TFC Crowe was assigned as the On Call CCU Investigator when he was notified of an individual making suicidal claims via social media. TFC Crowe contacted the Maryland State Police Headquarters Duty Officer who stated they were contacted related to a video of a young man laying on a set of railroad tracks claiming he intended to kill himself. The Duty Officer then provided the following information:  IP Address: 2600:0387:0015:0917:0000:0000:0000:0006 Phone Number: (443) 621-3740 Instagram Username: bando_ru101 Facebook Username: Rando Ru DOB: 12/22/2001 Reporting Party: Kiki White (Phone: 650-486-3101)  TFC Crowe was also provided with a link to the video posted by the reported user. TFC Crowe observed the 16 second color video and observed a black male, approximately 20-25 years old, wearing a dark sweatshirt and reflective vest, laying between a set of railroad tracks and saying Today, I will be killing myself, before asking everyone to repos while he waited for the subway to come.  By 07:17 PM, a Pen Register Trap and Trace was put in place for the reported Facebook and Instagram accounts. TFC Crowe conducted a query of the phone number associated with the reported Facebook account and observed it to belong to ATT. An additional Pen Register Trap and Trace for the phone number was put in place shortly thereafter.  TFC Crowe attempted to contact the reported phone number numerous times with no answer. Eventually, TFC Crowe received location data from ATT placing the cell phone in Baltimore City on North Mount Street between Riggs Avenue and Lauren Street. TFC Crowe observed there to be a set of railroad tracks near this location. Baltimore City Police Department was contacted and units were sent to the area, however, the individual was not located.  At 09:23 PM, TFC Crowe again attempted the reported phone number and was successful. TFC Crowe instantly recognized the voice on the phone as the voice from the reported video. After stating the words Maryland State Police, the call went dead. At 09:26 PM, TFC Crowe again connected with the reported phone number and assured the user he was not in any trouble. Loud music and several voices could be heard in the background of the call. TFC Crowe asked the individual if he was Bando, to which he responded, Yeah, bando_ru101. TFC Crowe advised the male of the reason for the call, to which the male responded, Oh, I was just making content for my pages. TFC Crowe then asked if the male was safe from harm, to which he responded, Yeah, Id never really do that. Throughout the conversation it became evident the male was significantly impaired, but surrounded by other people. Though he was hesitant to provide identifiable information, the unidentified male positively identified himself as the account owner and claimed production of the reported video.  After disconnecting the call, TFC Crowe located several social media pages utilizing the username Bando_Ru101, with ties to social media content creation, and hip hop music. TFC Crowe matched an image of Bando Ru to the individual in the reported video. Subsequent logins to the reported Instagram account continued for the next 24 hours before the PRTT was withdrawn.  Case Status Closed by Exception</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/04/2023 07:36:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6726</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 08:02:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Crowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6726</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>