<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-036781</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40I</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/19/2023 20:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/19/2023 20:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/19/2023 19:19:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/19/2023 19:19:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Possession CDS</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/19/2023 20:54:23</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6037</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 02:19:55</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>EASTERN BLVD S / MOUNT AETNA RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>709051</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/19/2023 20:54:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 20:54:24</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>709051</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Eastern</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <StreetSuffixCode>S</StreetSuffixCode>
         <City>Hagerstown</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-77.71114</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.63122</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>450-498 EASTERN BLVD S / 900-959 MOUNT AETNA RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 EASTERN BLVD S / 900-959 MOUNT AETNA RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/19/2023 20:54:19</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/19/2023 20:54:19</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40I</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>12/06/2023 02:19:55</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/19/2023 20:54:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6037</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 02:19:55</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 10/19/2023 at approximately 1930 hours, M/Tpr. Hood and Cpl. Buck were patrolling in the area of Dual Highway near the Days Inn motel when a white VW SUV bearing Maryland temporary tag T1543080 was observed. During the observation, the right rear taillight was displaying white lighting due to a faulty rear taillight lens. The VW was observed pulling into the parking lot of the Days Inn and out of the sight of M/Tpr. Hood for approximately 5 minutes. The white VW was then observed pulling back out of the parking lot and a traffic stop was conducted due to the equipment violation. Upon making contact with the female driver she was identified by her Maryland drivers license as Brooke D. Shilling DOB 8-17-1988. M/Tpr. Hood advised Shilling the reason for the traffic stop and asked for her license and registration for the vehicle. Shilling stated she had just purchased the car and provided a registration card with a third partys name on it. While Shilling was getting the necessary paperwork, M/Tpr. Hood asked Shilling where she was coming from, and she stated a friends house. M/Tpr. Hood knows this was not correct due to the prior observations made. The right front male passenger of the vehicle was avoiding eye contact and also appeared to be very nervous. M/Tpr. Hood was also able to observe several scabs on Shillings arms, and it appeared she was previously or currently a CDS user. Due to several observations made, M/Tpr. Hood called for a K-9 to the scene to conduct a free air scan of the vehicle. M/Tpr. Thompson and his K-9 partner arrived at the scene and completed a free air scan of the vehicle. The K-9 gave a positive alert for the odor of illegal narcotics.  During the search of the vehicle no items were located. Shilling was then searched by a female Hagerstown City Officer and the CDS was located in the front of Shillings pants. One of the items was a rubber container with a white rock substance inside. The other item located was a clear plastic bag containing the same white substance. Due to M/Tpr. Hoods training and experience as a Maryland State Trooper he was able to identify the substance as suspected crack cocaine. Shilling was then advised of her Miranda rights and waived her right to COUNSEL. Shilling advised she had gone to the Days Inn Hotel and met with a male that sold her the suspected crack cocaine. Shilling was given Cpl, Wests contact information pertaining to the suspected drug dealer. Shilling and West will be in contact on a later date and time. Shilling was not charged at the scene and an application will be completed on a later date and time for the possession of CDS not marijuana.  The identity of the male passenger was later determined by his name and date of birth as Jon Eugene Barth DOB 8-4-1988. Barth has a current open warrant in PA however the warrant was not extraditable.  Barth and Shilling were released from the scene.  All the above events occurred in Washington County Maryland.  I request this case be closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/23/2023 11:31:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 13:32:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>64</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thompson</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3053</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40I</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>West</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5950</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40I</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Buck</LastName>
            <FirstName>Theodore</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6037</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40I</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hood</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daryl</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5345</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>