<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-038371</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/31/2023 13:17:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/31/2023 13:17:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/31/2023 13:17:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/31/2023 13:17:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Telephone Misuse.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/31/2023 13:17:28</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0486</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 04:17:33</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>HMP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>33453</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>510</SubBeat>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/31/2023 13:17:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/31/2023 14:13:12</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>33453</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>110</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>AIRPORT</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <StreetSuffixCode>E</StreetSuffixCode>
         <City>FREDERICK</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>510</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-77.37710064842739</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.40483954714474</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MSP FREDERICK /  AT GAS PUMPS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MSP FREDERICK / @ PUMPS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FREDERICK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MSP FREDERICK/ @ PUMPS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FREDERICK COUNTY LAW ENFORCEMENT CENTER</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FREDERICK CITY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MSP FREDERICK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/31/2023 13:17:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/31/2023 13:17:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/02/2024 04:17:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/31/2023 13:17:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 04:17:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>OFFICERS ON SCENE: Cpl. Rishell #5730 (duty officer)   Case Number: 23-MSP-038371  Date: 10/31/2023  Time: 1245 hours  Location: MSP Frederick 110 Airport Drive. Frederick MD, 21701  Narrative:    On 10/31/2023 at approximately 1105 hours, a citizen made a call to the Frederick County 911 center and wished to make a complaint about an MSP Patrol Vehicle. The citizen, later identified as Joshua Cropper, was forwarded to MSP Frederick who spoke with Emergency Dispatcher (ED) Murphy. Due to several ongoing calls the duty officer, Sgt. Kulina was unable to take the call and Cropper was advised that a supervisor would return his call. A short time later, Sgt. Kulina was able to return Croppers phone call. Cropper advised Sgt. Kulina that he wished to make a complaint against a Trooper and his driving. Cropper advised that the Trooper was tailgating him, then went around him and flashed his emergency lights at him, got in front of him, and then brake-checked him before getting off on an exit. Cropper was unable to get a tag but advised that it was in the area of Westbound Route 340 near Virginia. Sgt. Kulina advised Cropper that they did have a Trooper in that area, and he was responding to a call for service with a male who was overdosing. Cropper immediately became aggressive and began using profanity towards Sgt. Kulina and stated that he was trying to cover for the Trooper. Sgt. Kulina advised the process of how to make a complaint. Due to several other calls coming in at the same time, Sgt. Kulina advised Cropper that he was going to place him on a brief hold and that other calls were coming in. When Sgt. Kulina handled the other calls that had come in, he attempted to pick up the call from Cropper and realized that he had hung up. Cropper called back into MSP Frederick and again began a profanity-laced tirade and hurled insults at Sgt. Kulina. Sgt. Kulina calmly explained the process for a complaint, provided his own name and ID number, and told Cropper that if he continued to use profanity and speak in that manner the conversation would be over. Cropper advised that he could speak however he wanted, Sgt. Kulina worked for the public and it was within his First Amendment right to speak however he wanted to. Cropper continued to call back six more times. Sgt. Kulina advised him that he had already provided him with all the information for how to file a complaint and his own name and ID number. At 1300 hours, Sgt. Kulina gave Cropper a lawful order to stop calling. Sgt. Kulina advised him that he was calling an emergency number during the middle of a busy workday, that he had already been provided all the information he needed and he was currently tying up a phone line that is used by the public for multiple different reasons.   The MSP phone line is a recorded emergency line that is used by MSP Duty officers to facilitate multiple different facets of enforcement. Local and non-local Police agencies routinely call the MSP phone to confirm warrants, get copies of police reports, and check the status of prisoners. The general public also routinely calls the MSP phone line to give information for active dangerous drivers that is then given as general broadcasts to Troopers on the road. On-duty Troopers also use the MSP phone line to make contact with the duty officer to give updates for active calls for service and other pending calls for service.   After being lawfully told to stop calling the MSP Frederick phone line, Cropper called back again. Sgt. Kulina advised Cropper that if he continued to call the line he could be charged with telephone misuse. Cropper then became more agitated and stated that he could not be charged for calling a public number. He advised that his questions were not being answered and he kept getting hung up on in the middle of his sentences. Sgt. Kulina again advised that he was not to call this number again and that his calls would not be answered. Over the next thirty minutes, Cropper continuously called the MSP Frederick line over twenty (20) times.   At approximately 1330 hours, I, Cpl. Rishell, relieved Sgt. Kulina and took over as duty officer. Sgt. Kulina advised me of the situation and Cropper had been verbally aggressive while calling over 20 times. At approximately 1345 hours, Cropper called the 911 center and was transferred to ED Murphy. He advised ED Murphy that he wished to file harassment charges against a Trooper and wanted to speak with someone. I advised ED Murphy to transfer Croppers call to me. I then spoke with Cropper. I introduced myself and advised that the phone call was being recorded. Cropper spoke very fast and I could hear the agitation in his voice. He stated that he wanted to file harassment charges and that he was being threatened by a member of the Maryland State Police. I asked how he was being threatened and he stated that the person he had just spoken with on the phone had advised him that he was going to be charged with a crime. He could not remember the name of the person but advised it was something like Sgt. King or similar. I advised that he had just spoken with Sgt. Kulina and that he had left for the day. He advised that Sgt. Kulina had threatened him with a crime and he had been harassing him. He stated that his questions were not being answered and that he had been hung up on several times. I asked him what questions he had and that maybe I could answer them for him. He stated that he had called in earlier about the way a Trooper had been driving. He gave me a brief summary of the Troopers driving and asked what the rules were regarding emergency response. He advised that where he was from the police had to travel with lights and sirens on when responding to a call. I explained the MSP policy for emergency response and explained the difference between Code 1, Code 2, and Code 3 response. I then asked for Croppers Information. He advised that his name was Joshua Leigh Cropper (DOB 2/7/81) with an address in Alaska. He stated that his mailing address was in Alaska and he was traveling through the area. I explained to Cropper that Sgt. Kulina was trying to advise him that he could be charged with a crime and not that he was going to be charged. I explained to Cropper that I believed it to be a misunderstanding but he was adamant that Sgt. Kulina had told him that he was being charged with a crime. I explained to Cropper that as of this moment, he was not being charged with a crime and if that changed he would be contacted. I again explained the process of how to file a complaint through the MSP website and gave him the information for Sgt. Kulina and TFC Silver. Cropper thanked me and our conversation ended.   On 11/1/2023, I contacted Barry Williams the Frederick County 911 center supervisor, and forwarded him a FOIA request for all the phone calls made by Cropper.  I request this case remain open pending further investigation.     CASE OPEN.      </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5730</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/31/2023 14:25:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5730</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/08/2023 07:16:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cain</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kenneth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0486</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rishell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5730</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>527835</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0340</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>05</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/31/2023 13:17:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0340</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5730</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/31/2023 14:15:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5730</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/31/2023 14:15:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5730</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/31/2023 14:16:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/31/2023 14:24:16</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>391713</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Kulina</LastName>
               <FirstName>Sgt.</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/31/2023 14:15:56</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K450</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Kulina</LastName>
               <FirstName>Sgt.</FirstName>
               <SLastName>K450</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/31/2023 14:15:56</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>110</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>AIRPORT</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>FREDERICK</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.37642185238832</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.40685872653754</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5730</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/31/2023 14:24:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5730</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/31/2023 14:24:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>42</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5730</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/31/2023 14:24:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/31/2023 14:24:04</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>391715</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cropper</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leigh</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/07/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/31/2023 14:23:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C616</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cropper</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leigh</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/07/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C616</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/31/2023 14:23:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3102</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Carney</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Wasilla</City>
               <StateCode>AK</StateCode>
               <Zip5>99654</Zip5>
               <Zip4>9009</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-149.371911</Longitude>
               <Latitude>61.649202</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>907</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>351</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1771</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5730</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/31/2023 14:24:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/18/2023 08:41:27</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/18/2023 08:41:27</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/02/2024 04:17:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5730</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 08:41:27</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 04:17:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>NARRATIVE:    On 11/28/2023, at D/SGT Stein contacted the Frederick County States Attorneys office in reference to this case. Mr. McLaughlin and Mr. Moore were contacted and asked to review the case and if their office would pursue charges. As of 12/27/2023, they have not responded. The suspect has made no further contact to MSP Frederick about this incident or any other.    I request this case be suspended.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5730</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 08:42:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5730</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 16:51:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cain</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kenneth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0486</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rishell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5730</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>