<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-040329</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/14/2023 14:42:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/14/2023 14:42:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/14/2023 14:28:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/14/2023 14:28:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Check Fraud</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 14:42:10</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2735</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 07:35:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FRD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>2215</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>961</SubBeat>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 14:42:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 05:57:11</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>2215</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>9758</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>OCEAN</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>BERLIN</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>961</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-75.22930642777145</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.34673126782248</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MSP BERLIN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IN FRONT OF BK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50  IN FRONT OF THE  BERLIN BARRACK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>34778 LINCOLN DR, FRANKFORD DE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>50 WB/BK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>50 EB/ BERLIN BARRACK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>50 PRIOR TO BERLIN BARRACK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50 / BERLIN BARRACK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>BERLIN BARRACK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/14/2023 14:42:06</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/14/2023 14:42:06</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 07:35:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 14:42:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 07:35:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>CASE#: 23-MSP-040329 DATE: 11/6/2023-11/7/2023 SUSPECT: Donovan C Harper VICTIM: David Franklin Shockley and Sandra Rothenstein Shockley TOTAL AMOUNT FOR RESTITUTION: $2,340 SUMMARY:   A fraudulent check was cashed at a PNC Bank in Kent Island on 11/6/2023 in the amount of $2,340 paid to Donovan C Harper. An attempt was made at cashing another fraudulent check on 11/7/2023 at a PNC Bank in Easton, however this check was identified as a fraudulent check and the owners of the bank account were notified. The victims reported the fraud to PNC Bank and froze their account. They discovered a third name added to their bank account when they filled out the paperwork to report the fraud and are unsure when, why, or how this third name was added. The victims advised that they are not missing any checks, and the number on the fraudulently cashed check matches a check that they filled out and sent through the mail to a company that repairs their farm equipment.  NARRATIVE:  On 11/14/2023 at 1428 hours, I, Trooper ODonald #7667, responded to the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack in reference to a report of check fraud. Upon my arrival, I made contact with the complainants David Franklin Shockley (DOB: 09/25/0947) and Sandra Rothenstein Shockley (DOB: 11/29/1947), both of whom were identified by their Maryland Drivers Licenses. Sandra advised that on 11/6/2023, a fraudulent check drawing money from their account was cashed at the PNC Bank located on Kent Island. The total amount of money cashed was $2,340. Sandra stated that on 11/7/2023, an individual attempted to cash another check at the PNC Bank located in Easton, however the bank teller became suspicious of the individual and refused to cash the check. Upon the individual leaving the bank, the teller, identified as Lisa, called David and Sandra and explained what occurred. Lisa originally asked Sandra and David to drive to Easton in order to complete paperwork reporting the fraudulent activity, however upon informing her that they lived too far away to make the drive, she recommended they respond to a PNC location in Salisbury. Before ending the phone call, Lisa advised Sandra that she sent the fraudulent check to PNCs loss prevention personnel. Sandra advised that Lisa called them to report the activity sometime in the early afternoon. Sandra advised that she did not know exactly what time the attempted fraud occurred.   On 11/8/2023, Sandra and David responded to the PNC location in Salisbury to sign paperwork in order to report the fraudulent activity and have their account frozen. As they were going through this process, David discovered that a third name had been added to their bank account. To Davids knowledge, only his name and Sandras name was on the account. However, they discovered that one Daniel Shockley had been added to the account. Furthermore, Daniel Shockley used Davids social security number with a different birth date. David advised that they are not related to anyone named Daniel. David advised that he and Sandra have a son, however their sons name is Phillip. I asked David if anyone other than Sandra has access to his social security number, and he advised that no one else does. I asked if he or Sandra had recently received any phone calls, text messages, or emails asking for their social security numbers or other personal identifying information, and they advised that they did not. David further advised that PNC Bank was unable to inform him of when Daniels name was added to their account. Sandra and David further stated that they do not employ anyone else to work on the farm and that no one has access to their checkbook.      Sandra was able to provide me with a photocopy of the check that was cashed in Kent Island. It appears to be one of their checks, complete with their company name, Indiantown Farms, and the number on top of the check is 17386. Sandra advised that they were not missing that check, and in fact they had used that check on 11/4/2023 in order to pay a company that does repair work on some of their farm equipment. Sandra stated that she mailed the check either on the fourth, or the next day on 11/5/2023 to HD Tire Service and Sales in Laurel, Delaware. Sandra advised that she drove the check to the post office and mailed it directly from there. The check was written for $860. Sandra further stated that they are not missing any other checks in their checkbook and that both she and David are unaware of how anyone could have gotten access to that check. Sandra stated that after PNC contacted her about the fraudulent check on 11/7/2023, she contacted the owner of HD Tire Service and Sales, who she identified as Harry, and told him not to cash the check. Sandra stated that Harry told her he had not received the check in the mail yet. Sandra further advised that Harry did not receive the check until approximately 11/9/2023 or 11/10/2023. Upon receiving the check, Harry sent Sandra a picture of it. Sandra printed this picture out and provided me with a copy of it.      The fraudulent check that was cashed on 11/6/2023 is dated 11/1/2023, and the signature on the bottom of the check reads Sandra L Shockley. Sandra advised that her middle initial is R, not L, and that whoever forged the signature did not do it properly. Additionally, Sandra advised that after they discovered the fraudulent check, they noted that Sandras middle initial on the account was incorrectly listed as L instead of R. Sandra advised that she was unaware that her middle initial was incorrect on the account and that she is unsure when this change was made. However, the signature on the fraudulent check looks very similar to Sandras actual signature. Furthermore, the check is written out to Donovan C Harper. The handwriting for this portion of the check is clearly different from that of the signature. Neither Sandra nor David stated that they do not know anyone named Donovan C Harper.      I ran the name Donovan C Harper which returned to a Donovan Charles Harper (DOB: 06/05/1990) who lives at 8113 Timberbrooke Road Rosedale. Maryland 21237. I ran a criminal history on Harper which returned that he was arrested on 11/9/2023 in Harford County for possessing of a forged private document and theft between $1,500 and $25,000. Harper was released on personal recognizance the same day that he was arrested. I called the Havre de Grace Police Department on 11/15/2023 at 0717 hours and made contact with the duty officer. The duty officer forwarded me a copy of the arresting officers report which stated that Harper attempted to cash a check at the MT Bank in Havre de Grace. The teller at the bank recognized that the check was fraudulent because a check bearing that number had been previously cashed and reported it to the police. The fraudulent check was written to an amount of approximately $1,700.      I request that this case be forwarded to the Criminal Enforcement DivisIon for further investigation.  All the above events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7667</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 06:33:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7667</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 08:22:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gordy</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kendrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4879</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Snell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6191</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Odonald</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jameson</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7667</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529797</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1361</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>02</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/14/2023 14:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1361</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7667</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 06:20:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7667</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 06:20:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>75</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7667</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 06:29:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 06:29:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393032</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Shockley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Sandra</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Rothenstein</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/29/1947 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 06:29:34</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S536</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Shockley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Sandra</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Rothenstein</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/29/1947 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S536</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 06:29:34</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6631</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Whiton</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Snow Hill</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21863</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3119</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.382525</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.234667</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>632</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0641</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7667</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 06:29:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>76</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7667</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 06:31:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 06:31:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393033</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Shockley</LastName>
               <FirstName>David</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Franklin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/25/1947 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 06:31:41</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Shockley</LastName>
               <FirstName>David</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Franklin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/25/1947 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 06:31:41</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6631</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Whiton</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Snow Hill</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21863</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3119</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.382525</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.234667</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>422</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2165</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7667</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 06:31:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/29/2023 13:12:28</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/29/2023 13:12:28</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 07:35:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5640</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 13:12:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 07:35:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Initial Report</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report:   Initial Report  Victim(s)   Name: Sandra Rothenstein Shockley   Race: White Sex: Female   Date of Birth: 11-29-1947   6631 Whiton Road, Snow Hill, Maryland 21863   Phone: 410-632-0641    Name: David Franklin Shockley   Race: White Sex: Male   Date of Birth: 9-25-1947   6631 Whiton Road, Snow Hill, Maryland 21863   Phone: 410-632-0641  Suspect:   Name: Donovan Charles Harper   Race: Black Sex: Male   Date of Birth: 6-5-1990   Address: 8113 Timberbrooke Road, Rosedale, Maryland 21237   Phone: 410-663-4702  Evidence:   One (1) bank check in the amount of $860.00 made payable to HD Tire Service and Sales, check #17386 stored in MSP Berlin Barrack property room   One (1) open envelope addressed to HD Tire Service and Sales stored in MSP Berlin Barrack property room  Narrative:  On November 27, 2023, I Sgt. Donna Radcliff, #5640 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region received the following items from Sandra Shockley [hereinafter referred to as Sandra] pertinent to the investigation:   One (1) bank check in the amount of $860.00 made payable to HD Tire Service and Sales, check #17386  One (1) open envelope addressed to HD Tire Service and Sales  According to Sandra, she mailed the aforementioned check in the aforementioned envelope on Saturday, November 4, 2023, at the Snow Hill Post Office in Snow Hill, Maryland. A duplicate of the aforementioned check, (check #17386), was cashed in the amount of $2,340 at PNC Bank located at 120 S. Piney Road, Chester, Maryland 21619 on November 6, 2023. This check was made payable to Donovan C.Harper with a signed name of Sandra L. Shockley. An unauthorized check return was issued by PNC Bank for the aforementioned amount to Sandras bank account. Sandra further advised that HD Tire Service received the original check of $860.00 on or about November 9 or 10, 2023. Upon inspecting the envelope, I observed a bar code and a Delaware zip code across the top of the envelope. The envelope appeared to have been opened once. According to Sandra she placed a sticker on the back of the envelope and two pieces of tape to ensure that the envelope stayed sealed. The tape and sticker were visible and in place, and it appeared that the envelope had been opened with a letter opener across the top. I made contact with Snow Hill Post Office who advised that when mail leaves their office it is routed to Salisbury, Easton and Baltimore before it reaches its final destination. The postal clerk could not advise as to why there were no additional post markings from either aforementioned post office.  Sandra provided me with a photocopy of a voided check made out to Donovan C. Harper in the amount of $2340, dated November 1, 2023, signed as Sandra L. Shockley, check #17392. It should be noted that Sandras middle initial is R, not L. An attempt to cash this check was made at PNC Bank located at 104 Marlboro Avenue, Easton, Maryland 21601. The attempt was haulted by the bank teller and no funds were received by the suspect.  A Maryland Judiciary Case Search for Donovan Charles Harper yielded the following results:   District Court for Harford County - Criminal      Harper, Donovan Charles   Black, Male, 506. 165lbs.   8113 Timberbrooke Road, Rosedale, Maryland 21237   DOB: 6-5-1990   Charge 1: Forgery/Priv Document/Possess - 11-9-2023   Charge 2: Att-Theft: $1500 to UND $25K - 11-9-2023   11-9-2023   Released on Recognizance      District Court for Somerset County - Criminal     Harper, Donovan Charles   Black, Male, 506, 165 lbs   8113 Timberbrooke Road, Rosedale, Maryland 21237   DOB: 6-5-1990   Charge 1: Theft: $1500 To Under $25,000 - 11-6-2023   Charge 2: Issue False Document - 11-6-2023   Charge 3: Forgery-Priv Documents - 11-6-2023   Charge 4: Forgery/Priv Document/Possess - 11-6-2023   Summons Issued: 11-16-2023      District Court for Queen Annes County - Criminal     Harper, Donovan Charles   Black, Male, 506 165 lbs.   8113 Timberbrooke Road, Rosedale, Maryland 21237   DOB: 6-5-1990   Charge 1: Forgery-Priv Documents - 11-21-2023   Charge 2: Forgery/Priv Document/Possess - 11-21-2023   Charge 3: Issue False Document - 11-21-2023   Summons Issued: 11-22-2023      District Court for Talbot County - Criminal     Harper, Donovan Charles   Black, Male, 506, 165 lbs   8113 Timberbrooke Road, Rosedale, Maryland 21237   DOB: 6-5-1990   Charge 1: Theft: $1500 To Under $25,000 - 11-7-2023   Charge 2: Forgery-Priv Documents - 11-7-2023   Charge 3: Forgery/Priv Document/Possess - 11-7-2023   Charge 4: Issue False Document - 11-7-2023   Summons Issued: 11-28-2023      It should be noted that Donovan Harper [hereinafter referred to as Harper] has not been served in three of the aforementioned cases. There is an open case with Queen Annes County Sheriffs Office, lead detective, Chase Arrington [hereinafter referred to as Det. Arrington] regarding Harper and same theft/fraud scheme at banks in Det. Arringtons jurisdiction. I have been in contact with Det. Arrington regarding this investigation as well as other law enforcement from the aforementioned jurisdictions. Harper has not been formally interviewed by law enforcement regarding the above listed cases.  I learned that the Worcester County Sheriffs Office recently (within the last two months) investigated a similar case in which the suspects were employed at a post office in Baltimore County. Their case was turned over to the post master in Baltimore County for further investigation. Follow up with the post master in Baltimore County will take place in the coming days to ascertain whether the cases are related.  Case open     </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5640</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 13:26:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5640</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 13:45:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ramey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2735</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Radcliff</LastName>
            <FirstName>Donna</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5640</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5640</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 13:22:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 13:22:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>394129</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Harper</LastName>
               <FirstName>Donovan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/05/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/29/2023 13:18:25</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H616</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D515</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Harper</LastName>
               <FirstName>Donovan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/05/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H616</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D515</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/29/2023 13:18:25</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>663</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4702</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5640</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 13:22:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/29/2023 15:16:49</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/29/2023 15:16:49</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 07:35:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5640</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 15:16:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 07:35:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Subpoena Service</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report:   Subpoena Service  Narrative:  On November 27, 2023, I Sgt. Donna Radcliff, #5640 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region issued a subpoena to PNC Bank, 104 Marlboro Avenue, Easton, Maryland 21601 via email address surveillanceprocessing@pnc.com requesting video surveillance for November 7, 2023. I was advised by the victims in this case that an actual person entered the bank and attempted to cash a check in the amount of $2,340.  On the same date I issued a subpoena to PNC Bank, 120 S. Piney Road, Chester, Maryland 21619 via email addresssurveillanceprocessing@pnc.com requesting video surveillance from November 6, 2023. I was advised by the victims in this case that an actual person entered the bank and cashed a check in the amount of $2.340.  To date I have not been given a description of the individual that entered the bank with fraudulent checks from the victims bank account. Upon receipt of the video surveillance I hope to obtain suspect identification in an effort to further this investigation.  Case open</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5640</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 15:17:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5640</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 15:26:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ramey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2735</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Radcliff</LastName>
            <FirstName>Donna</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5640</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/13/2023 14:12:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/13/2023 14:12:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 07:35:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5640</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 14:12:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 07:35:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Receipt of Video Surveillance PNC Bank Easton</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report:   Receipt of Video Surveillance PNC Bank Easton  Suspect:   Name: Donovan Charles Harper   Race: Black Sex: Male   Date of Birth: 6-5-1990   Address: 8113 Timberbrooke Road, Rosedale, Maryland 21237   Phone: 410-663-4702  Evidence:   One (1) thumb drive containing video surveillance from PNC Bank in Easton, MD stored in agency case file.   Six (6) still shots from video surveillance of suspect, Donovan Harper, stored in RMS attachment section of this report.  Narrative:  On December 6, 2023, I Sgt. Donna Radcliff, #5640 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region received video surveillance via email link from PNC Bank,104 Marlboro Avenue, Easton, Maryland 21601. Upon download of the video surveillance, it was determined that the format in which it was sent was not compatible with my MSP agency issued laptop. I contacted investigators with the Homicide Unit who utilized Axon Investigative software to aid in opening the video surveillance in a format which can be viewed. The attempt was a success and still shots of the suspect were extracted from the video. The video showed suspect, Donovan Harper, [hereinafter referred to as Harper] enter the bank during the time frame provided in the subpoena, with what appeared to be a check in his hands. Harper is a black male, wearing a blue colored polo type shirt, blue jeans and light colored tennis shoes. Harper is bald and has a full beard and mustache.  I forwarded the still photographs to Det. Tunney of the Somerset County Sheriffs Office who recently charged Donovan Harper with the same modus operandi. Det. Tunney viewed the photographs and stated, The still-shots you provided appear to be Donovan Harper. The still-shots are consistent with the still-shots I obtained from different Hebron Savings Bank locations as well as Harpers MVA photo.  I forwarded the still photographs to Det. Arrington of the Queen Annes County Sheriffs Office who has an open case with Harper for the same modus operandi. Det. Arrington confirmed that these photographs match the description of Harper as depicted in video surveillance in his investigation. I compared the still photographs to Harpers MVA photo which matched the description of Harper.  Case open pending video surveillance from PNC Bank in Chester, MD </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5640</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 14:12:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5640</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 14:39:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pruitt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jonathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4927</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ramey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2735</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Radcliff</LastName>
            <FirstName>Donna</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5640</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/18/2023 12:39:33</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/18/2023 12:39:33</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 07:35:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5640</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 12:39:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 07:35:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Receipt of Video Surveillance PNC Bank Chester, MD</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report:   Receipt of Video Surveillance from PNC Bank Chester, MD  Suspect:   Name: Donovan Charles Harper   Race: Black Sex: Male   Date of Birth: 6-5-1990   Address: 8113 Timberbrooke Road, Rosedale, Maryland 21237   Phone: 410-663-4702  Evidence:   Video surveillance procured from PNC Bank in Chester, MD stored on Seagate external hard drive   Thirteen (13) still photographs extracted from video surveillance of suspect entering and leaving bank attached to this report  Narrative:  On December 18, 2023, I Sgt. Donna Radcliff, #5640 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region received video surveillance via Federal Express from PNC Bank in Chester, Maryland. Upon receipt of the video, I observed the following:   11-6-2023 at 1306:31 hours a subject matching the description of Donovan Harper [hereinafter referred to as Harper], black male, wearing blue jeans a light colored t-shirt, a ball cap, light colored tennis shoes, is observed walking in the bank driveway toward the bank.  11-6-2023 at 1306:56 hours Harper enters the bank.  11-6-2023 at 1300 hours Harper is observed walking past bank teller #1  11-6-2023 at 1307:12 hours Harper makes contact with bank teller #3. Harper has a full beard and mustache and is wearing a light color Lucky Brandt-shirt and a ball cap with a Ralph Lauren logo on the front.  After making contact with the bank teller, Harper presents what appears to be a drivers license to the teller and proceeds to endorse the back of a check that he entered the bank with.  The bank teller takes the check, leaves her post momentarily and then returns with US Currency in her hands.  She counts the US Currency and then gives it to Harper.  Harper folds the US Currency, puts it in his back pocket and exits the bank at 1312 hours.  There is no vehicle observed in the video surveillance. It appears that Harper walks from an adjacent parking lot into the cameras view when he is observed on bank surveillance in the bank driveway.  On December 18, 2023, I was provided a booking photograph of Harper from Detective Arrington of the Queen Annes County Sheriffs Office. The booking photo was taken on 11-9-2023 at the Harford County Detention Center.  The video footage of Harper and still photographs captured match the description of Harper as depicted in the aforementioned booking photo, Harpers MVA photo and video footage and still photographs I received from PNC Bank in Easton, Maryland.  Case open pending criminal charges   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5640</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 12:40:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5640</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:17:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pruitt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jonathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4927</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Radcliff</LastName>
            <FirstName>Donna</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5640</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>5</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/18/2023 14:39:00</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/18/2023 14:39:00</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 07:35:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5640</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 14:39:00</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 07:35:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Case Summary</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report:   Case Summary  Suspect:   Name: Donovan Charles Harper   Race: Black Sex: Male   Date of Birth: 6-5-1990   Address: 8113 Timberbrooke Road, Rosedale, Maryland 21237   Phone: 410-663-4702  Narrative:  Case Summary:   11-6-2023 - Fraudulent checked cashed in the amount of $2340.00, check #17386 dated November 4, 2023, at PNC Bank, Chester Maryland. (original check already written and mailed)  11-7-2023 - Attempt to cash an additional fraudulent check for $2340.00, check #17392 dated November 1, 2023, at PNC Bank in Easton, Maryland. (original check still in check book)  Check made payable to Donovan C. Harper  MVA check of Harper revealed Donovan Charles Harper, DOB: 6-5-1990, 8113 Timberbrooke Road, Rosedale, MD, black male, bald with a beard and mustache.  Maryland Judiciary Case Search Revealed that Donovan Charles Harper of the same aforementioned DOB and address was charged in Harford County, MD, Somerset County, MD, Queen Annes County, MD and Talbot County, MD for Theft, Forgery and Issuing False Documents between November 9, and November 28, 2023.  Subpoenas issued for video surveillance from PNC Bank in Chester and Easton, MD for time frames given by bank employees of when Donovan Charles Harper entered the bank(s).  Video surveillance received and a subject matching Donovan Charles Harpers description is observed during the time frames requested. Additionally, the subjectmatches the description of Donovan Charles Harpers MVA photo, booking photo from 11-9-2023 and video surveillance from other law enforcement agencies who have charged Donovan Charles Harper for the same modus operandi.  Case open pending criminal charges   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5640</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 14:40:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5640</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 15:07:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ramey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2735</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Radcliff</LastName>
            <FirstName>Donna</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5640</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>