<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-044592</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/17/2023 13:12:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/17/2023 13:12:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/17/2023 12:17:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/17/2023 12:17:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Domestic Dispute / Emergency Petition</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 13:12:54</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5549</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 10:52:56</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>EP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>435962</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 13:12:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 07:31:50</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>435962</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>305</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Braeburn</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Walkersville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.32968728384748</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.483420619635496</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/17/2023 13:12:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/17/2023 13:12:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/27/2023 10:52:56</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 13:12:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5549</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 10:52:56</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>B60 is equipped with an in car-camera and body worn camera, both cameras were activated.  Case Number: 23-MSP-044592 Date: 12/17/2023 Time: 1217 hours Location: 305 Braeburn Dr, Walkersville, Maryland.                                                                                            Victim / Complainant: -Richard Anthony Keller (W/M DOB 07/06/1967)  Suspect: Joshua Hudson Keller (W/M DOB 10/25/1998)  Scene Processing: - Information was gathered from the victim at the scene. Joshua was transport to Frederick Health Hospital for an Emergency Petition. Richard received a witness victim form to assist in receiving help in the future with the mental health of his son, and applying for a protective order.  Attactments: - Meters/NCIC printouts -Emergency Petition - 214 Domestic Violence Screening  Narrative: On 12/17/2023, at approximately 1217 hours, I, TFC Nolf #7209 of the Maryland State Police Frederick Barrack, was dispatched to a report of a mental patient, located at the 305 Braeburn Dr, Walkersville, Maryland. While en route I requested further details on the call, and dispatch advised the son was beating the dad.  When I arrived on scene, I observed male with no shirt striking an older male in the face with his fist multiple times over. While exiting my patrol car, I requested additional units to assist for a fight in progress. I immediately approached the male with no shirt, later identified by name and date of birth asJoshua Hudson Keller (W/M DOB 10/25/1998),and was able to get him to stop striking his father, also later identified by his Maryland Drivers license asRichard Anthony Keller (W/M DOB 07/06/1967). When Joshua stopped striking his father, he looked at me with rage, and told me to get the f**ck off his shit. TFC Ingram arrived on the scene and asked Joshua to come with her, to separate him from his dad. Joshua complied with all TFC Ingrams verbal commands, and laid down on the grass.  Once separated, I was able to talk to Richard and assess the injuries to his nose, from Joshuas fist. I requested two ambulances to the scene to check out both Joshua and Richard. Richard advised that he was going to go the hospital later, and he did not want to go in the ambulance. While being checked Richard stated that Joshua has been agitated the last couple of days, and he suffers from schizophrenia, and has not been taking his medicine. Richard advised he went into Joshuas room to check on him, and he was laying face down on the bed. When Joshua woke up, he attacked Richard with his fists, and an exercise weight. Richard ran out the front door and down the street, calling 911 emergency services, while still being chased by Joshua. Joshua caught up to Richard again, and started striking him in the face again, which is when I arrived on scene.  When EMS took over care of Richard, I went over to assist TFC Ingram with Joshua. Joshua would not agree to go to the hospital by ambulance, but did agree to let TFC Ingram transport him. TFC Ingram was able to transport Joshua to Frederick Health Hospital without incident, where he was admitted for an Emergency Petition.  After leaving the hospital, I spoke with Richard, who advised he would let me know at a later date if he wanted to press charges against Joshua.  On December 19, 2023, I received an email from Richard stating that he does not want to press charges against Joshua. He advised his main concern at this point is getting Joshuas mental health in order.  Case Status: I request this case be closed.  All events occurred in Frederick County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7209</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 14:46:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7209</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 08:07:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Carter</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6361</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rishell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5730</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ingram</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jasmine </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6663</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Conklin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5549</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nolf Jr.</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gregory</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7209</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>25</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7209</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 15:34:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 08:18:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>222136</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Keller</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Hudson</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/25/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/20/2019 01:10:23</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Keller</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Hudson</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/25/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>K460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/20/2019 01:10:23</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>305</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Braeburn</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Walkersville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.32968728384748</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.483420619635496</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7209</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/20/2023 08:18:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7209</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 08:18:47</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>56</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7209</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 15:41:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 07:31:50</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>395530</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Keller</LastName>
               <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ANTHONY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/09/1967 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/17/2023 15:41:18</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R263</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Keller</LastName>
               <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ANTHONY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/09/1967 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>K460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R263</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/17/2023 15:41:18</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>305</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Braeburn</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Walkersville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.32968728384748</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.483420619635496</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>610</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>999</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8962</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7209</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 15:41:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7209</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/17/2023 15:41:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7209</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 15:41:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7209</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/17/2023 15:41:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/17/2023 14:18:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/17/2023 14:18:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/19/2023 06:46:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5730</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 14:18:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5549</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 10:52:56</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>VICTIM:   Richard Anthony Keller (w/m 7/9/67)  NARRATIVE:    On 12/17/23 at 1218 hours, MSP dispatch advised TFC Nolf to respond to 305 Braeburn Drive for a domestic in progress. TFC Nolf arrived on the scene and immediately advised that there was a fight in progress and to start more units. TFC Carter and I started in that direction from the barrack. When I arrived on the scene several minutes later, the victim was in the ambulance and TFC Ingram was speaking with the suspect, who was seated on the curb. The suspect, later to be identified as Joshua Hudson Keller, had blood on both of his hands and his elbow. TFC Nolf advised me that it was a father and son issue and the son had assaulted the father, potentially breaking his nose. TFC Ingram convinced Joshua Keller to go with her to the hospital. He was placed into custody and put into TFC Ingrams patrol vehicle. TFC Nolf and TFC Carter followed TFC Ingram to the hospital while I remained on the scene with the victim. The victim, who was identified as Richard Anthony Keller, was being treated in the ambulance. He refused medical treatment and I contacted him at his residence. Richard Keller advised me that Joshua had just attacked him without provocation when Richard had woken him up that morning. Richard showed me Joshuas room inside the residence. The Room was in complete disarray. The TV and dresser supporting it had been knocked over and broken. White baby powder covered most of the room. Richard advised that he walked into the room that morning to check on Joshua. He advised that there was very strange music playing that he described as scrib music. He advised that music was on a loop and the words, Son, once you commit to it there no going back, playing over and over. He stated that as soon as he asked Joshua if he was ok, Joshua woke and immediately started to attack him. He stated that Joshua was punching him as hard as he could in the face and head. Richard was able to get away and ran downstairs. As he was running he heard a loud thud hit the ground behind him. After the incident when he walked back upstairs, he noticed an adjustable dumbbell on the ground and stated that must have been what Joshua had thrown. Joshua then chased him out of the house and down the street still attacking him. Joshua caught up and hit him several times again in the face and head. They continued to fight on the ground until the police arrived. Richard stated that he is convinced that if he had not been able to get out of the house Joshua would have killed him.   Richard advised that just a week ago, Joshua had been completely normal. He stated that it was just as if Joshua had been normal. Thursday, December 14th, Richard and his wife left town to visit their daughter. He arrived back on Saturday and could tell that Joshua had changed. Joshua told Richard that he had smoked 7 packs of cigarettes in two days. Richard stated that he and Joshua had a good conversation on Saturday evening about going to get some mental help and the conversation felt productive. Joshua went to the room that evening and Richard did not see him again until the following morning when he was attacked. Richard stated that Joshua had been previously diagnosed with schizophrenia and had seen a doctor. Joshua had not been taking his medication. He stated that Joshua had recently broken up with his girlfriend and his body cannot handle the stress. Throughout his statement, Richard was visibly upset and had to stop several times to hold back tears.   I completed the domestic violence supplement report with Richard and he screened in based on his answers. I spoke with a counselor at the Frederick County Heartly House and they advised they only handle cases involving intimate partners. I explained the process of peace and protective orders to Richard and he advised that he would probably do that. He advised that he did not feel safe having Joshua come back into the house.   Refer to TFC Nolf report for further. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5730</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 14:19:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5730</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 07:47:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cain</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kenneth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0486</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rishell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5730</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>