<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-035523</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/10/2023 02:40:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/10/2023 02:40:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/10/2023 02:25:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/10/2023 02:25:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 02:40:28</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3258</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/02/2023 02:52:01</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MINEOLA AVE/ MOHAWK AVE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>709471</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 02:40:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 02:40:29</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>709471</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Mineola</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Salisbury</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>AVE</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.613884</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.379218</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>917-999 MINEOLA AVE / 800-803 MOHAWK AVE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/10/2023 02:40:26</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/10/2023 02:40:26</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/02/2023 02:52:03</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 02:40:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 16:26:58</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Subsequent offender: No  In-car camera mounted inside E-45 used for this stop.   Front- N/A for this incident due to my patrol vehicle not being in the area the arrest was made.   Rear-https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=3cdfe4889c4446e1aa2fba215bfc3a84partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1   Rear-https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=d6873e03e9f34dc6a6dc70d84ba3fc19partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1   Body- https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=09feeed842b04996bde347367e586a8bpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  MD Drivers License: G660560003002 Suspect: Luclerson Guerrier 01-01-1978 DUI #: 23-54-203  Phase One - Vehicle in Motion:        On 10-10-2023 at 0225 hours I, TFC. Norfolk 7120 did not see this vehicle in motion. Troopers on the scene advised that a vehicle drove up to an active crime scene that was blocking the road on Mineola Ave @ Mohawk Ave Salisbury MD 21801. Troopers on the scene attempted to knock on the window of the vehicle to speak to the driver and let him knowthe roadway was closed due to an active crime scene and the driver would have to find an alternate route. The driver was not rolling the window down or even looking at the Troopers at first. Eventually, the driver rolled the window down and was observed to be under the influence of alcohol. As an available trooper, I was requested by the initial trooper to contact the driver of the vehicle. Phase Two - Personal Contact:        I identified the driver and sole occupant of the vehicle to beLuclerson Guerrier 01-01-1978.Guerrier was advised of the reason for the road being blocked. Guerrier was advised that everything was being audibly and usually recorded by my body warn camera. I was able to observeGuerrier to have extremely red shot and glassy eyes. After speaking withGuerrier, I was able to detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from inside the vehicle.Guerrier was asked if he had been drinking any alcohol, tonight before driving to which he advised that he did. I askedGuerrier if he could read and write the English language and if he could understand what I was saying.Guerrier said, You are asking me questions, and I am answering them so yes I understand you.Guerrier was asked where he was coming from, he said work and that he was on his way home. Guerrier was asked if he knew what time it was currently without looking at his watch, he believed it to be around 2200 hours. I askedGuerrier to step out of the vehicle to perform SFSTs which he complied by saying 10-04 multiple times.  Phase Three - Pre-Arrest Screening:  OnceGuerrier was out of the vehicle I was able to smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming fromGuerriers breath and person. Guerrier was observed to have trouble walking to the front of his vehicle and staggered from side to side while walking.Guerrier also had difficulty standing upright without swaying from side to side.At the time of testing, Guerrier was wearing no shoes and only socks, I asked if he wanted to put shoes on for more favorable testing for him to which he refused to put shoes on.Guerrier was also wearing appropriate clothing for the season, more specifically a loose shirt and shorts. The area where the testing was completed was flat level and free from debris. The testing area was lit by my patrol vehicles headlights.  Before administering the tests, I asked Guerrier if he had any medical conditions or physical issues that would keep him from completing any of the tests today to which he advised no. Guerrier was asked if he wore contacts and or glasses he advised no.  The first test administered was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test:  I explained the test to Guerrier. Headvised that he understood my instructions and did not have any questions.   Displayed the lack of smooth pursuit and equal tracking in both eyes.  Displayed the Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  Displayed the Onset of Nystagmus before 45 degrees in both eyes.  A check for Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was conducted with negative results.    Guerrier had an extremely difficult time completing this test. He kept moving his head to the side and raising his left hand in attempt to touch the pen I was holding and then his own face.Guerrier tried to say that he did not speak English at this time, I reminded him that I have already established that he does speak English due to his response to my earlier question.Guerrier no longer tried to say he could not speak English after this point. A total of (six) clues were observed during this test.  The second test administered was the Walk and walk-and-turn test:  I explained the test to Guerrier. Headvised that he understood my instructions and did not have any questions.    Started the test beforeinstructed to do so and was reset into the starting position.  Had to movefeet from heel to toe contact and had to move hisfeet on multiple occasions to maintainbalance.  Completed multiple steps during thetest witharms raised more than 6 inches from hisbody.  Stopped walking after first set of steps and asked for further instruction.  Completed an improper turn by turning to the right while not using a series of steps.  Missed heel-to-toe on all steps during the test.  Stepped offline on all steps during the test.  Took approximately 20steps on the first set of steps instead of the instructed nine steps and approximately 20steps on the second set of steps.  A total of (8) clues were observed during this test.  The third test administered was the One Leg Stand Test:  I explained the test to Guerrier. Headvised that he understood my instructions and did not have any questions.    Put hisfoot down repeatedly during the test in an attempt to keep from falling.  Swaying from side to side by approximately three inches during the test.  Raised arms approximately 18 to 20 inches from the side of hisbody to maintainbalance.    Guerrier struggled with the one-leg stand and the test was finished early due to his inability to complete it. A total of two (3) clues were observed during this test.  Guerrier was offered the roadside PBT which he agreed to take with a result of .33 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  Based on observations of Guerriersdriving, physical appearance, and performance of SFST he was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at 0240hrs He was seated in my patrol vehicle. When I entered my vehicle, I could smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage that was not present before him being seated in it. Guerrier was transported to the Salisbury Barrack for processing. While on the way to the Salisbury State Police Barrack Guerrier was read and allowed to read his DR-15 advice of rights. After completing the DR-15, he agreed to submit to the intoximeter at 0301 hrs. Guerrier submitted a sample of .29 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. Guerrier Was provided with all copies of the paperwork and released.   Based on all the above facts, I request that the case be closed by arrest. CASE CLOSED.  All events occurred in Wicomico County, MD.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7120</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 09:15:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7120</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/31/2023 23:58:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckrich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Long</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tabitha</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4993</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norfolk</LastName>
            <FirstName>Wyatt</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7120</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mareck</LastName>
            <FirstName>Keven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3258</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norfolk</LastName>
            <FirstName>Wyatt</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7120</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norfolk</LastName>
            <FirstName>Wyatt</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7120</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524983</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/10/2023 02:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7120</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 04:52:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7120</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 04:58:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7120</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 04:52:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7120</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 04:59:16</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>215366</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Guerrier</LastName>
               <FirstName>Luclerson</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>none</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/01/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/16/2018 04:42:11</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G660</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L246</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Guerrier</LastName>
               <FirstName>Luclerson</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>none</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/01/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G660</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L246</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/16/2018 04:42:11</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1114</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Nokomis</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21801</Zip5>
               <Zip4>8915</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.6122518</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.38363</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>603</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5450</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/16/2018 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7120</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 04:59:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7120</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 04:59:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7120</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 04:59:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7120</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 04:52:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7120</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 04:52:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>