<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>24-MSP-000429</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/05/2024 02:41:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/05/2024 02:41:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/05/2024 02:14:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/05/2024 02:14:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The driver was stopped for an inoperable registration lamp. The driver was placed under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol. DUI#: 24-004.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 02:41:50</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2362</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/15/2024 09:17:21</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>21350 MD-246,LEXINGTON PARK</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>718841</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 02:41:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/15/2024 06:13:38</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>718841</AddressId>
         <StreetName>MD-246</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Lexington Park</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
         <Zip4>1204</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>DR</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.452282</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.265839</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/05/2024 02:41:47</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/05/2024 02:41:47</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/15/2024 09:17:22</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE PROCESSED-ORIGINAL</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 02:41:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>BWC  In-car camera operational, T-25. DUI#: 24-002 Suspect: Keith Xavier Hagens (05/24/1992) OLS: MD10273087414 // Maryland Date of Arrest: 01/05/2024 Time of Arrest: 0235 hours  NARRATIVE: VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1):  On January 5, 2024 at approximately 0214 hours, I, Trooper Lewis #7660, was on duty, on patrol, in uniform, operating marked patrol vehicle T-25, when I observed a silver 2014Lincoln MKS passenger car bearing a, Temporary Maryland registration T1637812 in the area of Great Mills Road at Lexwood Drive with an inoperable passenger side registration lamp rendering the registration plate illegible from a distance of 50 feet to the rear. The vehicle was swerving back and forth in between the travel lane and, a lawful traffic stop was initiated. When my emergency equipment was activated, the vehicle made an abrupt stop in the middle turn lane of Great Mills Road at Forest Run Drive, and was parked on the double solid yellow line.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):  I contacted the operator, and sole occupant, of the vehicle, later identified by his Maryland drivers license as Keith Xavier Hagens (B/M, DOB: 05/24/1992). I asked Hagens for his drivers license and registration and he questioned why. While speaking with Hagens, his speech was slurred, and I detected the very strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Hagens breathe and person. Hagans was stalling to display his license and asked do I have to tell you, that Im recording you? After multiple orders, Hagens handed me his drivers license and proceeded to look on his phone for his registration after I told him it would not be on his phone.   While Hagens was still fumbling with his phone, trying to find his registration, I asked him how much he had to drink? Hagens replied he did not have anything to drink and that he had friends in the vehicle previously and they were drinking. Hagens then retrieved his registration and at the time, I requested Trooper Black to respond to my location. When Trooper Black #7094 arrived on-scene, I ordered Hagens to exit his vehicle so I could administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3): The tests were conducted roadside. The surface was composed of dry pavement, and it was free of any obvious signs of debris. My vehicles head lamps were on and front facing emergency equipment was off. Lighting consisted of my vehicles head lamps and my flashlight. Prior to administering the tests, I asked Hagens the following questions: Glasses or Contacts - No. Injuries - No. Medical Conditions - No. Medications - No.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 Clues Observed): The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus. I held it approximately 12 to 15 inches from Hagens face and slightly above eye level. Hagens was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still, while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes only. I asked Hagens if he understood the instructions, and he indicated he did. Hagens pupils were equal in size and displayed equal tracking. I observed no resting nystagmus in either eye. After Hagens stated he understood, Hagens questioned multiple times if he could turn his head, and kept looking at me instead of the tip of the stimulus. Hagens failed to keep his head still.    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Vertical Nystagmus was not observed during the administration of this test.   WALK AND TURN (6/8 Clues Observed): Prior to performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Hagens was instructed to imagine a straight line on the ground in front of him, and to place his left foot on said, imaginary line. Hagens was then instructed to place his right foot on the line, directly in front of his left foot, touching heel to toe. Hagens was questioning why and how he had to stand in the instructional position multiple times. Hagens was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Hagens stated he understood. Hagens was instructed to take nine (9) steps in a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step. Hagens was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead, left foot on the line and to take a series of small steps with his right foot to complete his turn. Hagens was explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Hagens was instructed, once he began the test, he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keeping his hands down by his sides, looking down at his feet, and counting each step out loud. I asked Hagens if he understood the test, and he advised he understood the test.    Instructional Stage:  Broke Instruction Position (2 Times)      Walking Stage (First Nine):  Steps Off Line  Step: 9 (Left)  Turning Stage:   Improper Turn (Hagens did not keep his lead foot (left) still and spun around on his right foot)      margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Walking Stage (Second Nine):   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Stops Walking (Before starting second series of nine (9) steps)   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Missed Heel to Toe by More Than Half an Inch: 1 (Right)   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Steps Off Line - Step: 1 (Right),   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Inaccurate Number of Steps: 10   ONE LEG STAND: (3/4 Clues Observed): Prior to Hagens performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Hagens was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, Hagens was instructed to raise the foot of his choice approximately 6 inches off the ground, keeping the raised foot parallel to the ground. While his leg was raised, he was to keep both legs straight, watch his foot, keep his hands at his sides, count out loud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one thousand-two), and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Hagens if he understood the test, and he stated yes. Hayes balanced on his right foot, while raising his left foot.       margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Balance and Counting Stage   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Seconds 1-10:   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Nothing Observed      margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Seconds 11-20:   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Uses Arms for Balance   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Puts Foot Down (1 Time)   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Swaying       margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Seconds 21-30   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Swaying    Hagens was offered a Preliminary Breath Test at 0233 hours, which Hagens refused, Hagens was then placed under arrest. Hagens then proceeded to explain he would take the Preliminary Breath Test, because he did not want to be arrested. Hagens then stated he only had one sip of his beer and had smoked medical cannabis earlier.  ARREST:  On Janurary 05, 2024 at 0235 hours, Hagens was placed under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol, based on the following: Extremely slow lethargic movements. Slurred speech, bloodshot and glassy eyes. The drivers own admission to drinking alcoholic beverages, and smoking cannabis, and the observed clues and observations while performing the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  A mouth check was completed at approximately 0240 hours and nothing was observed. Hagens was transported to the Maryland State Police Leonardtown Barrack. Hagens was played the digital audio version the of DR-15 Advice of Rights in English, with an electronic copy to view. I also read the DR-15 Advice of Rights in person to Hagens. Hagens advised he understood his rights. Hagens submitted to the intoximeter test at 0345 hours, yielding the results of 0.06. Hagens was issued the appropriate paperwork and released to a sober, valid driver.  All events occurred in St. Marys County, Maryland.  Case Closed by Arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7660</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 04:42:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7660</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/15/2024 06:31:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Black</LastName>
            <FirstName>Darren</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7094</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Murphy</LastName>
            <FirstName>Shawn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2362</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lewis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7660</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>536106</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/05/2024 02:14:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7660</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 04:29:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7660</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/05/2024 04:29:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>536106</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/05/2024 02:14:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7660</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 04:30:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7660</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/05/2024 04:30:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>536106</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/05/2024 02:14:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7660</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 04:31:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7660</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/05/2024 04:31:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>536106</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/05/2024 02:14:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7660</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 04:32:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7660</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/05/2024 04:32:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>536106</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17053</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/05/2024 02:14:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17053</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7660</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 04:33:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7660</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/05/2024 04:33:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7660</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 04:22:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/15/2024 06:13:38</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>355973</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hagens</LastName>
               <FirstName>Keith</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Xavier</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/24/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.18353067E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>09/19/2022 05:03:05</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hagens</LastName>
               <FirstName>Keith</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Xavier</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/24/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.18353067E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>H252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/19/2022 05:03:05</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>46563</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Valley</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>7004</SubNumber>
               <City>Lexington Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.464578</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.267916</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>855</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9257</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/19/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7660</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 04:34:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7660</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/05/2024 04:34:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7660</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 04:34:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7660</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/05/2024 04:34:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7660</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 04:34:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7660</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/05/2024 04:34:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7660</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 04:34:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7660</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/05/2024 04:34:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7660</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 04:29:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7660</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/05/2024 04:29:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>