<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-044849</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/19/2023 13:09:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/19/2023 13:09:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/12/2023 22:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/12/2023 22:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Distribution of child pornography. Cybertip #182367642</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/19/2023 13:09:32</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:51:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>CAC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>716739</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/19/2023 13:09:34</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 10:31:10</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>716739</AddressId>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.641271</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.045754</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/19/2023 13:09:30</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/19/2023 13:09:30</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>12/27/2023 09:49:59</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/19/2023 13:09:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:51:31</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments -NCMEC Cybertip # 182367642   -Suspects possible Instagram  Narrative On December 14, 2023, the Maryland State Police Computer Crimes Section /Maryland Internet Crimes Against Children Task Force received NCMEC CyberTip # 182367642. The CyberTip, generated by the victim, indicated that a subject was he was dating sent his nude images to an adult. CyberTip was assigned to TFC Burnett for investigation.   The CyberTip provided the following information pertaining to the suspect: Relationship to Reporter: Ex-Boyfriend Gender: Male Race: Black or African American Disability: Anger Issues Additional Disability Information: I think he may live somewhere in Maryland Approximate Age: 15 Relationship To Child Victim: Online Partner / Boyfriend / Girlfriend (Have never met in person) Screen/User Name: realifemenaceonthenet Platform: instagram Screen/User Name: Baltowulf Platform: xboxLive Screen/User Name: baltothawulf Platform: twitch Screen/User Name: u/InnerMembership5285 Platform: reddit Profile URL: https://www.instagram.com/realifemenaceonthenet Additional Information: I dont know exactly but possibly those photos are on a hidden folder or linked to one of his online accounts. Please check I dont want that video being seen anymore. He remembers me by Lemon  The CyberTip provided the following information pertaining to the victim: Joseph Esparza Preferred Name: Alex Gender: Non-binary/third gender Preferred Pronouns: She/He/They Race: Hispanic or Latino/a Race: White Home Email: nerdshadow158@gmail.com Keep me fully anonymous Im trying to push this out of my life and make sure my family doesnt worry. Only email please IP Address: 172.223.113.72  TFC Burnett reviewed this CyberTip and observed a description of the incident: I lost chat logs. But a use who goes by Balto. Hes 15 my age and he wanted nudes of mewhich i didnt think would be bad at the time but once me and him got in a fight he sent them toa grown adult. And told me the adult liked it. He had then proceeded to blame me for gettinggroomed by others. He also has a boyfriend who may also be a victim of this I dont know hisname. Incident Date Range: Between 6 months and 1 year ago  TFC Burnett conducted an open source search of the victims IP address (172.223.113.72) through an open source database. The IP address returns to Spectrum and geo-locates to Waxahachie, TX.  Based on the context of the issue, I emailed the victim, Joseph and they preferred to contacted only by email. I sent Joseph a list of questions which they responded to. -Do you know their name? - I unfortunately dont know their name. -How do you know they might be 15 years old? -From what I can gather that they are 15 years old is they had two boyfriends around the age range which I dont know if that could help. -Do you have a picture of the person so I can identify them? -He had sent a picture of his face at one point. Problem is I deleted the chats as I hated looking at them also the constant harassment he kept doing when I never had him blocked. -What exact chatting platforms did you both chat on, where the files would have been sent through? -The chatting platform was Instagram primarily where the few videos and photos were taken. -Do you know where they might live, an area or anything that they might have mentioned to help locate the area?     -The only assumption I can give is near Maryland and Maybe in Baltimore? He never gave me a location. -What exactly did you send to them and how much? (describe)     -The video(s) were of me using a sex toy. I wanna say I think I was wearing a spider-man shirt in that video from what I remember. -Do you have any chat logs that you could share with me? that would not contain any inappropriate files.     -I have chatlogs from the xbox app but I dont know how much of that can help. -Do you know what they sent to the adult?     -From what he had told me it was the video or videos I think I sent him more Im not sure -Do you know who the adult was?     -No I do not. -Do you know when they sent the files to the adult?     -I would say perhaps September or August around that time. -Do you know how many videos you might have sent?  -Likely 1-2  Joseph also provided an ex-friend (zahirbuckingham@gmail.com)of the suspect that Joseph reached out to during the incident that might have more information on the suspect whos name is Tiyon. On 12/22/2023, I sent an email to ( text-decoration:underline"&gt;zahirbuckingham@gmail.com) to acquire any further identifying information for the suspect.  TFC Burnett authored a subpoena request for the suspects accounts through (Instagram, Twitch, Reddit), which were submitted to the Howard County States Attorneys Office for endorsement.  Case Status Open, investigation ongoing.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6764</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/22/2023 10:32:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6764</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 10:34:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burnett</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kelsey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6764</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/19/2024 07:43:34</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/19/2024 07:43:34</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/19/2024 12:51:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6764</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/19/2024 07:43:34</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:51:31</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>ATTACHMENTS:    -Signed Twitch subpoena   -Signed Reddit subpoena   -Signed Instagram subpoena   -Twitch account information   -Twitch authenticity   -Two images of the subject  NARRATIVE:    On 12/29/2023, I received the signed Twitch and Reddit subpoenas from the States Attorneys Office. I also received a response from Zahir Buckingham advising the subjects real name is Tiyon,xbox usernameis BaltoWulf and he is dark skinned. They also provided two images of the subject.    On 1/2/2024, I submitted the Twitch subpoena with the reference #CRIM1301559 2024 ds. I sent the Reddit subpoena by email.    On 1/3/2024, I received the Twitch return with the below information:  Login/Display Name: baltothawulf Email: baltowulf@icloud.com Created on: 2023-04-24 02:53:18    On 1/8/2024, I received the signed Instagram subpoena from the States Attorneys Office, it was submitted through the portal with the reference #8360737.    Case open, investigation ongoing.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6764</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/19/2024 07:44:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6764</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 07:54:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burnett</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kelsey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6764</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>