<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-040440</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/15/2023 11:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/15/2023 11:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/15/2023 11:03:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/15/2023 11:03:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>2nd Degree Assault Reported</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 11:56:10</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5926</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/20/2024 02:42:55</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>719292</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 11:56:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/20/2024 02:40:47</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>719292</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>9700</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Old Harford</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Parkville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21234</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.51905</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.423395</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/15/2023 11:56:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/15/2023 11:56:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/20/2024 02:42:56</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE PROCESSED-ORIGINAL</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 11:56:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5926</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/20/2024 02:42:56</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On November 15, 2023 at approximately 1103 hours, the Maryland State Police, Golden Ring Barrack received a phone call from the Chesapeake Treatment Center (CTC) located at the Charles H. Hickey Jr. School regarding a 2nd Degree Assault. I responded to the CTC at approximately 1211 hours to investigate the assault.  Upon my arrival, I contacted Clinical Director, Caryn Gates, at the CTC Admin Building. Gates provided me with the Incident Report (IR) which included a hand-written note from the victim to his therapist which alerted staff to the incident. This note from the victim to his therapist was passed along on November 14, 2023. After a brief review of the IR, I wanted to confirm some of the details with Gates regarding the sequence of events. When asked, Gates advised that the incident was reported on November 14, 2023 at 1744 hours and the IR was filed approximately one hour later. The incident occurred on November 11, 2023 at approximately 2136 hours. Confirming with Gates, there were five staff members involved, including the alleged aggressor, Kennah Buba and therapist, Jessica Yingling. I also confirmed with Gates if there was a video of the incident and she advised, yes.  After further review of the IR, the victim involved was identified as Amir Rashad Rich (1/M, DOB 3/25/2008), a resident of the CTC. The alleged suspect/staff member involved was identified as Kennah Buba (1/M, DOB 8/271963). According to the written statement provided by Rich, Buba placed his arm on Richs neck while being restrained and taken to the floor. Rich stated that he couldnt breathe so he bit Buba in attempts to be released by Buba so Rich could get some air. Buba then let go and placed his forearm or fist by his neck and jaw so he couldnt breathe again. Rich began crying and screaming that he couldnt breathe. Rich stated that he told the nurse to tell the other staff members to get off of his neck while repositioning himself in the restraint to get some air. Rich stated that the nurse just watched. On November 13, 2023, Rich stated that he heard about staff members joking around and telling other youth about Rich crying and screaming during the incident.  At which time, I was escorted to CTC Residential Building by Milieu Director, Lazarus Eluagu, to review the video of the incident.   When asked while reviewing the video, Eluagu identified staff member, Buba in the video and that the nurse was signaled to give Rich a shot of medication. When asked if Rich was refusing, Eluagu stated and demonstrated that Rich has a history of being uncooperative when given this medication. Eluagu never stated that Rich refused. Eluagu stated that due to Richs history, the nurse ordered staff members to restrain Rich while given the medication. After a brief review of the video, I asked Eluagu to provide me with a copy so I could review it more carefully. At one point while watching video, I observed Rich point to his left arm/shoulder area as he anticipated his medication in the form of an injection. The video later shows Rich standing in the doorway of the quiet room talking with a female staff member at approximately 2122 hours on November 11, 2023. While still conversing with one another, Buba enters the area. Buba then signals other staff members to enter area after being signaled to give Rich his injection. Several staff members enter the Time Out Room to restrain Rich, including the nurse administering the injection. Once the injection is administered, the nurse exits the room. Soon after, the other staff members in the room take Rich down to the floor while being restrained by them. During this process of gaining compliance of Rich on the floor, Buba is bitten on his arm by Rich. Buba then releases Rich before standing up and exiting the room while checking his arm. After reviewing the video with Eluagu, I requested to meet with, and interview Rich.   At this time, I was escorted to Gates office to await the arrival of Rich. Upon the arrival of Rich, I identified myself and advised him the nature of my visit. I also advised that our interaction was being recorded. When asked, Rich and I read over his written statement together as I was not able to understand some of his writing. After review of his written statement, Rich advised that he did not want to add anything involving the incident and he advised, no.  When asked to walk me through the incident on November 11, 2023, Rich began explaining that they cant be threatened with needles. There were a few verbal exchanges with Buba throughout that day where Buba was accused of threatening to put Rich down and give him a needle. When asked about the sequence of events leading to the incident earlier that day, Rich stated he was placed in the Quiet Room the day prior to and was given a safety plan for arguing with another youth. Rich stated that he had a plastic container that he pulled out of his pocket which damaged a mirror and smoke detector. A staff member then came to his room and called for staff support. After explaining that staff support would not be needed and he would clean up the mess, Buba stated that if you dont want to walk down to the Quiet Room, youll be walked down by force. Later, Rich walked to the Quiet Room on his own. Staff members advised they would be removing all items from his room to prevent Rich from harming himself. Rich later asked if he could call his Parole Officer due to the staff abusing their power. After Rich made his phone call, the nurse ordered the injection for Rich. Once back into the Quiet Room, Rich was restrained by staff members for the injection. While being restrained, Buba placed his arm against Richs neck. Rich then bit Buba to release Bubas arm off of his neck. Rich continued to reposition himself to get some air. When asked, Rich advised he did not lose consciousness but he did get light-headed. I did not observe any injuries to Richs neck or face area. The interview with Rich was soon after concluded.  At this time, I respectfully request this case remain open pending interviews with involved staff members. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/30/2023 04:10:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5163</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/20/2024 02:27:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Crump</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7571</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fike</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5926</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Hasim</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5163</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529908</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>15</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/15/2023 11:03:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/29/2023 01:53:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5163</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/29/2023 01:53:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>15</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/29/2023 02:00:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/20/2024 02:40:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>357675</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Rich</LastName>
               <FirstName>Amir</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Rashad</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/25/2008 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/07/2022 23:17:48</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A560</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Rich</LastName>
               <FirstName>Amir</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Rashad</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/25/2008 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A560</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/07/2022 23:17:48</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>46357</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Columbus</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>605</SubNumber>
               <City>Lexington Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9700</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Old Harford</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Parkville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21234</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.52149</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.418921</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5163</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/29/2023 02:00:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5163</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/29/2023 02:00:44</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5163</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/29/2023 02:00:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5163</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/29/2023 02:00:44</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>60</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/29/2023 02:13:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/20/2024 02:40:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>396332</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>BUBA</LastName>
               <FirstName>KENNAH</FirstName>
               <DOB>08/27/1963 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/29/2023 02:11:53</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>BUBA</LastName>
               <FirstName>KENNAH</FirstName>
               <DOB>08/27/1963 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/29/2023 02:11:53</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9700</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>OLD HARFORD</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>PARKVILLE</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.519898</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.41992</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5163</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/29/2023 02:13:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5163</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/29/2023 02:13:40</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>