<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-036148</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/14/2023 20:31:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/14/2023 20:31:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/14/2023 20:18:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/14/2023 20:18:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 20:31:59</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5099</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/17/2023 01:08:39</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>SHORE HWY/ N SIXTH ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>285028</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 20:32:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 07:09:49</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>285028</AddressId>
         <StreetName>SHORE</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Denton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21629</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>N</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.80194027</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.89485976</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>700-799 SHORE HWY / 600-699 N SIXTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>800-899 SHORE HWY / 600-699 N SIXTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 SHORE HWY / 600-699 N SIXTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>700-799 SHORE HWY / 522-599 N SIXTH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/14/2023 20:31:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/14/2023 20:31:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/17/2023 01:08:40</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 20:32:00</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 20:22:15</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23-MSP-036148 DUI #23-58-218 North Sixth Street @ Shore Highway, Denton, Caroline County, MD TROOPER T. BENSON #7099 MARYLAND STATE POLICE - EASTON BARRACK   Maryland State Police (MSP) unmarked patrol vehicle I-5 is equipped with a mobile video recording device. Body Worn Camera was not operational. Stop recorded.  Defendant: Name: Shafqat Ali Date of Birth: 11/20/1966 MD SDX#: MD-10272359353 Date of Arrest: 10/14/2023 Time of Arrest: 2028 hours DUI #: 23-58-218 (Easton Barrack)  Training  Certificates: * I am trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA). * I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training. * I have successfully completed Enhanced DUI Enforcement Training through the Maryland State Police SPIDRE Team. * I have successfully completed Cannabis Impaired Detection Workshop through the Maryland State Police.  Narrative: On Saturday, October 14, 2023, at approximately 2016 hours, I, TFC. Benson #7099, was operating Maryland State Police (MSP) unmarked patrol vehicle I-5 in the area of Denton, Caroline County, MD. At this time, Caroline County broadcast a Be On the Lookout Out (BOLO) for a champagne or tan Honda passenger vehicle traveling southbound on Greensboro Road toward Shore Highway. The complainant stated that the vehicle was all over the roadway, crossing the solid white edge line and solid double yellow center line. The vehicle had also possibly struck a mailbox. The complainant advised Caroline County that the vehicle had pulled into McDonalds and parked on the backside of the building. The complainant observed the driver stumble out of the vehicle, look at the damage, and walk inside McDonalds.  Phase 1  Vehicle in Motion: At approximately 2018 hours, I located the vehicle, a bronze Honda Civic bearing MD registration 37096K, exiting the McDonalds parking lot traveling eastbound on Fleetwood Road towards N Sixth Street in Denton, Caroline County, MD. At this time, I observed the vehicle apply its brakes and come to a stop at the stop sign at the intersection of Fleetwood Road and N Sixth Street. I observed the vehicle, accelerate, enter the intersection, make a left turn onto N Sixth Street from Fleetwood Road heading northbound towards Shore Highway, and fail to yield the right of way to a white hatchback passenger vehicle that was traveling northbound on N Sixth Street towards Shore Highway. I observed the vehicle fail to turn into the northbound travel lane of N Sixth Street as the vehicle traveled northbound in the southbound lane of N Sixth Street. At this time, I activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle activated its four way flashers/hazard lights and made a right turn onto the eastbound on ramp of Shore Highway. The vehicle continued, slowly being approximately 5 mph to 10 mph on the eastbound on ramp as my emergency equipment was activated, failing to come to a stop. The vehicle finally came to a stop on the shoulder of eastbound Shore Highway at the 15.0 mile marker prior to the Camp Road overpass.  Phase 2  Personal Contact: I made contact with the driver of the vehicle who was identified by his MD drivers license Shafqat Ali, DOB: 11/20/1966, 5/M. When I made contact with Ali he was unable to find the button to roll down the driver side window and instead opened the driver side door. At this time, I observed Alis eyes to be red, bloodshot, and glassy. I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. At this time, I asked Ali for his drivers license and registration card for the vehicle. Ali fumbled around the vehicle for several minutes looking for his drivers license and the registration card as requested. Ali spoke with slurred speech as he answered questions. Ali stated he was driving home from the bar in Greensboro (313 Roadhouse) when he stopped at McDonalds for food. Ali state he had consumed three (3) alcoholic beverages at 313 Roadhouse and all three (3) drinks were Johnny Walker Black Label. Ali did not remember hitting anything while driving from 313 Roadhouse in Greensboro to McDonalds in Denton. It should be noted that there was visible damage to the passenger side of the vehicle (see attached photographs). There were several long silver scraps down the entirety of the passenger side, which appear to be from striking a guardrail, along with damage to the plastic wheel cover on the front passenger wheel.  Phase 3  Pre-Arrest Screening: At this time, I asked Ali to submit to a series of Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs), to which he agreed.  Medical Pre-Screening: Ali appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any physical injuries. Ali was wearing a gray polo, blue khakis style shorts and tennis shoes. Prior to beginning the tests I asked Ali the following questions:  Doctor and/or Physical Therapist No Physical Injuries No. Medical Conditions No Medication No Glasses and/or contacts No  I asked Ali if he could walk in a straight line, turn around, and walk back, to which he stated he could. I asked Ali if he could balance on one (1) foot to which he stated he could. At this time, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his person.  Standardized Field Sobriety Testing was conducted on the shoulder of Shore Highway. The shoulder was flat and free of debris. The weather was dark and raining with an approximate temperature of 50 degrees.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) Test: Prior to beginning the test, I instructed Ali to stand with his feet together and his arms down at his sides. I explained the test to Ali. Prior to beginning the test, I held my pen twelve (12) to fifteen (15) inches from Alis nose, slightly above eye level. His pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present. 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present. 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Test not conducted as Ali continued to move his head left to right following the stimulus, failing to keep his head still, looking straight ahead, and following the stimulus with his eyes and his eyes only as instructed. Not Present.  Vertical Gaze Nystagmus (VGN) was not conducted and NOT present.  A total of four (4) clues were observed during this test.  Walk and Turn (WAT) Test: I attempted to explain the test to Ali several times. Ali had a difficult time understanding the instructions. At one point, Ali almost walked out into traffic. Test not conducted.  A total of zero (0) clues were observed during this test.  One Leg Stand (OLS): Test not conducted.  A total of zero (0) clues were observed during this test.  Preliminary Breath Test (PBT): Ali was not offered a Preliminary Breath Test on the roadside.  Conclusion: Based on my observations, the results of the Standardized Field Sobriety, along with my training, knowledge, and experience Ali was placed under arrest at approximately 2028 hours. Ali was read the English audio version of the Advice of Rights form (DR-15) and an English copy was placed in front of him, on his lap to read along. Ali agreed to an intoximeter test at approximately 2045 hours. Ali was transported to the Caroline County Sheriff Office, located at 9305 Double Hills Road, Denton, Caroline County, MD 21601. Upon arrival at the Caroline Sheriff Office, a chemical breath test was administered, at approximately 2116 hours, by breath test operator Cpl. Bringman #5204. The chemical breath test yielded a result of 0.16 breath alcohol content (BrAC). Ali was issued the appropriate paperwork and released to a sober ride, Asim Sharif, DOB: 10/06/1975, 5/M at approximately 2146 hours.  CASE CLOSED BY ARREST.  ALL EVENTS OCCURRED IN CAROLINE COUNTY, MARYLAND. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 17:23:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/11/2023 17:23:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bringman</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5204</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Goldman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stansbury</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Benson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525609</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 20:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 07:11:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 07:11:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525609</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 20:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 07:11:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 07:11:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525609</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 20:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 07:11:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 07:11:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>56</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 07:23:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 07:23:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>391625</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>M</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>A</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ali</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shafqat</FirstName>
               <DOB>11/20/1966 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 07:22:32</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S123</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ali</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shafqat</FirstName>
               <DOB>11/20/1966 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>A400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S123</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 07:22:32</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>25875</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sennett</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Denton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21629</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.80436</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.853603</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 07:23:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 07:23:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 07:23:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 07:23:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7099</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 07:11:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7099</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 07:11:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>