<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-036048</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/14/2023 04:05:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/14/2023 04:05:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/14/2023 03:50:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/14/2023 03:50:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>MSP Barrack G DUI 23-162, TA 21-902(A)(1) DUI (SCOTTY WILLIAM BAILEY)</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 04:05:40</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/24/2023 11:15:32</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>BALTIMORE BLVD/ MALCOLM DR</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>7450</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 04:05:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/23/2023 09:45:41</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>7450</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>576</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>JERMOR</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>WESTMINSTER</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>565</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-76.97631548950504</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.56438274852493</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>DUNKIN DOUGHNUTS PARKING LOT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OLD CACTUS WILLIES PARKING LOT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/14/2023 04:05:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/14/2023 04:05:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 07:18:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 04:05:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:47</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23-MSP-036048  Incident: MSP Barrack G DUI 23-162 (SCOTTY WILLIAM BAILEY)  TA 21-902(A)(1) DUI  Date  Time: 10/14/2023, 0349 hours  Location of Offense: 576 JERMOR LANE, WESTMINSTER, CARROLL COUNTY, MD.  My investigation was recorded on AXON digital recording system assigned to G-39 and AXON body camera assigned to M/Tpr Fair.  Minors in Vehicle:NO  PBT: 0.00 BrAC at 0405 hours  EVIDENTIARY TEST:Insufficient/ refusal at 0452 hours  DRE (Drug Recognition Expert): N/A  Weather: clear, approximately 51 degrees Fahrenheit  Qualifications:  -Maryland State Police Academy (June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007)  -I am trained to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through NHTSA and the Maryland State Police (MSP Academy, June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007).  -I have attended and graduated from the University of Maryland University College Advanced DUI College (UMUC January 7-11, 2013).  -I have attended and completed training Enhanced DUI Enforcement: The Complete Arrest (MPCTC, 05/11/2016).  -A.R.I.D.E.: Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (MPCTC, 03/29-03/30/2017)  -Cannabis Impairment Detection Workshop (MPCTC, 09/29/2021)  -Preliminary Breath Test Instructor (MSP CTAU, 09/11-09/12/2023)  Driver:  MD MD10272790624 SCOTTY WILLIAM BAILEY 37 WEBSTER ST, APT A WESTMINSTER, MD 21157 2/M, DOB 06/21/1971  Phase I: Reason for Stop  On 10/14/2023 at approximately 0349 hours I was on duty, in uniform, operating a marked Maryland State Police Patrol vehicle, G-39. I was patrolling E/B MD 140, E/O Gorsuch Rd, Westminster, Carroll County, MD. I observed a gray Subaru Forester stopped in the drive-thru of the Dunkin, located at 576 Jermor Dr, Westminster, Carroll County, MD. I observed the male driver to be slumped forward, head on the steering wheel. I circled around and pulled into the Dunkin parking lot, facing the rear driver side of the vehicle. As I passed the vehicle again, and was pulling around, I observed the male driver still slumped forward on the steering wheel, eyes closed. At this time the business was not open. I observed the headlights to be on, and the engine running (sound and exhaust observed). The vehicle was displaying Maryland tag 1ES0700. The driver was the lone occupant of the vehicle. I activated my AXON dash camera in my patrol vehicle and BWC. As I opened my patrol vehicle door, I observed the driver sit up, look at me in his side mirror, and turn his head to look at me, and immediately light a cigarette. The weather was clear and approximately 51 degrees Fahrenheit.  Phase II: Contact  I made contact with the driver, identified myself, and advised the contact was being recorded. The driver indicated he was waiting to get coffee (Dunkin opens at 0400 hours). I asked the driver for his identification. The driver provided me his MD DL, which identified him as SCOTTY WILLIAM BAILEY. As I was approaching the vehicle, and standing at the drivers door, I detected the strong odors of raw and freshly burnt marijuana emanating from the open drivers window. I advised I was checking his welfare, as I saw him passed out. The driver said he was not and had a cigarette. I advised he was not initially, and I saw him light the cigarette. I asked the driver exit the vehicle to separate him from the odors emanating from the passenger compartment. The driver complied. I also asked the driver to put the cigarette down. The driver stepped out, still holding the cigarette. I had to repeat my instructions to put down the cigarette several times before he finally did so. I had the driver step away from his vehicle to further separate him from the odors. I asked the driver the following questions:  Q. Are you on any medications? A. No, sir.  Q. Have you consumed anything that would be considered a Controlled Dangerous Substance, to include (but not be limited to) heroin, marijuana, cocaine, methamphetamine, or anything like that? A. Not today, I just woke up.  Q. Have you had anything to drink as far as alcohol is concerned in the last 12 hours? A. No, sir.  Q. Do you have any physical issues that would prevent you from standing on one leg for approximately 30 seconds or walking a straight line heel touching toe? A. No, sir.  Q. How often do you smoke marijuana? A. Every other couple of days.  I made the following observations of the driver:  While seated in vehicle:  -eyes bloodshot -strong odor of freshly burnt marijuana on breath  While standing outside the vehicle:  -eyes bloodshot -strong odor of freshly burnt marijuana on breath and person -swaying as he stood  Based on my observations, I made the decision to administer the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The driver consented.  Phase III: Pre-Arrest Screening  All tests were explained and demonstrated prior to asking the driver to attempt them. The tests were conducted in a flat, well-lit area, free of debris. The driver was wearing a gray hooded sweatshirt, blue jeans, and sneakers.  SFSTs:All tests were explained and demonstrated prior to me asking the driver to attempt them.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus:  The drivers eyes displayed equal pupil size (pinpoint), tracking, and reaction. I was able to observe 2 clues out of the 6 potential clues:  -both eyes lacked smooth pursuit  Additional observations:  -eyes bloodshot -had to be reminded to keep his head still and to keep looking at/ for the stimulus (pen) -had to be reminded to keep his arms down to his sides -side to side sway, 1-2 inches -strong odor of brunt marijuana on breath and person  Vertical Nystagmus was not observed.   Walk  Turn:  The driver conducted this test with his shoes on. I observed 6 clues out of the potential 8 clues:  -incorrect turn: turned to the right, not left as instructed and demonstrated -stepped out of instructional position -stepped offline: walked in tangent to his left on both sets of steps, not in a straight light toward where I instructed him to do so -missed heel to toe twice on first set of steps -raised arms/ moved arms for balance during the test -incorrect number of steps: only took 8 steps prior to the turn on first set of steps  Additional observations:  -bloodshot eyes -strong odor of burnt marijuana on breath and person  One Leg Stand:  The driver conducted this test with his shoes on. The driver indicated he understood my instructions. The driver stood on his left foot and raised his right. I observed 4 out of the 4 potential clues:  -driver put his right foot down after approximately 4 seconds, then raised his left foot (I did provide correction to this)  The driver resumed, standing on his right foot and raising his left.  -the driver hopped -put his foot down twice -swayed front to back for balance -raised his arms for than 6 inches away from his body for balance as he put his foot down for the last time  Additional observations:  -bloodshot eyes -strong odor of burnt marijuana on breath and person -inability to follow instructions: switched feet during the test  Additional Tests: A.R.I.D.E.  Lack of Convergence:  The lack of convergence was observed: neither eye converged to center  Additional observations:  -bloodshot eyes -strong odor of burnt marijuana on breath and person -the driver had to be reminded to follow the stimulus with his eyes only  Finger To Nose:  The driver was placed in the instructional position: arms down to their side, heels together, hands in fists with index fingers extended and wrists rotated outward. The driver was instructed, when told to do so, to close their eyes and tilt their head backward. I would then give the command, either right or left, and the driver is to touch the tip of their nose with the tip of their index finger, then immediately bring their arm back down to their side. I provided the following commands: left, right, left, right, right, left.  Observations:  -bloodshot eyes -strong odor of burnt marijuana on breath and person -had to be reminded to put his hand down immediately -missed the tip of his nose, touching nostrils and bridge of his nose -swaying side to side -used the finger pad, not the fingertip as instructed and demonstrated -body and eyelid tremors observed  Modified Romberg:  The driver was placed in the instructional position: arms down to their side and heels together. The driver was instructed when I would tell them to do so, to close their eyes, tilt their head back and estimate the passage of 30 seconds by counting quietly to themselves. After the passage of 30 seconds, the driver was instructed to bring their head down, open their eyes and say done.  Observations:  -during the test, the driver swayed front to back approximately 1 inch -the driver took 25 seconds (according to the digital recording) to estimate the passage of 30 seconds -body tremors observed -bloodshot eyes -strong odor of burnt marijuana on breath and person -body and eyelid tremors observed  The driver was offered a Preliminary Breath Test, which he submitted to with a result of 0.00 BrAC. Based on my observations of the driver during contact and the SFSTs, I made the decision to place the driver under arrest. The specific observations that drove my decision were the following:  -bloodshot eyes -impaired balance throughout the contact (swaying) -the observations of the WT and OLS -impaired control of his body/ depth perception (Finger To Nose) -overall inability to follow instructions provided (specifically during the OLS) -body and eyelid tremors observed, potentially indicative of recent marijuana use -strong odor of freshly burnt marijuana on breath and person, indicative of recent marijuana use  The driver was advised he was under arrest for DUI, handcuffed, and placed in my patrol vehicle. The driver was handcuffed and placed in my patrol vehicle. A search incident to arrest of the vehicle uncovered a large amount of raw marijuana and several smoking devices w/ burnt plant matter (marijuana) in the vehicle (see BWC). Due to the nature of the items observed and located, none were seized.  The vehicle was secured in the parking lot of Dunkin. I transported the driver to the MSP Westminster Barrack for further processing. The driver was read the DR15 Advice of Rights and signed it at 0438 hours, submitting to the intoximeter. The intoximeter was administered by Sgt Gibson. The driver was provided three opportunities to provide a valid breath sample. The driver did not provide a valid sample, stopping his breath early on each attempt. The intoximeter was found to be in working order immediately after the insufficient sample/ refusal was logged. The driver was issued the DR15, DR15A, Notice to Appear, Notice of Right to Counsel, and traffic citations M9B0DJH-M9J0DJH. The driver was transported to his residence and released into the care of a sober family member. The driver was advised several times not to drive within 12 hours of the time of arrest.  The driver was respectful at all times.  Closed on arrest.  All events occurred in Carroll County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/23/2023 09:31:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/23/2023 09:31:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>FAIR</LastName>
            <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5334</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525509</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 03:50:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/23/2023 09:38:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/23/2023 09:38:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>52</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/23/2023 09:44:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/23/2023 10:07:28</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>391046</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>BAILEY</LastName>
               <FirstName>SCOTTY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>WILLIAM</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/21/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/23/2023 09:43:24</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>BAILEY</LastName>
               <FirstName>SCOTTY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>WILLIAM</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/21/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/23/2023 09:43:24</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>37</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Webster</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>A</SubNumber>
               <City>Westminster</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21157</Zip5>
               <Zip4>6782</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.984715</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.566059</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/23/2023 10:07:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/23/2023 10:07:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/23/2023 10:07:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/23/2023 10:07:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/23/2023 09:38:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/23/2023 09:38:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158311</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/23/2023 09:48:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/23/2023 09:48:44</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JF1SG65647H725719</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2007</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>SUBA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>LL</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1ES0700</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>