<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-044609</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/17/2023 17:46:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/17/2023 17:46:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/17/2023 14:56:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/17/2023 14:56:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Assist Montgomery County with a police impersonator.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 17:46:21</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4714</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/24/2023 02:40:41</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>716319</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 17:46:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/17/2023 17:46:22</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>716319</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>7117</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Arlington</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Bethesda</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20814</Zip5>
         <Zip4>2908</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.09821</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.981096</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>NIKE STORE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/17/2023 17:46:18</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/17/2023 17:46:18</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>12/24/2023 02:40:40</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 17:46:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4714</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/24/2023 02:40:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 12/17/2023 at approximately 1457 the Maryland State Police Rockville Barracks received a call from Montgomery County Police Department Sergeant Marshall #2302 in regards to Maryland State Police Impersonator. I, TFC Seidl #7061, responded to 7117 Arlington Rd Bethesda, MD (NIKE Store) in order to make contact with Sgt Marshall. Upon my arrival I made contact with Sgt. Marshall, he advised that the suspect was apprehended and taken to MCPD 2nd District station for processing. At the MCPD 2nd District I asked Sgt. Marshall what had occurred, he stated that approximately 2-3 weeks ago he was working an Overtime Detail in Silver Spring, Maryland, when he observed the suspect working a part time security detail at a store in Silver Spring. Sgt. Marshall advised that he made contact with him. He asked the suspect at the time what agency he worked with, the suspect advised that he worked with MSP. Sgt. Marshall observed that the suspect was wearing multiple PVC tactical patches on his vest as well as a Police patch on the back of his vest. On 12/17/2023, Sgt. Marshall was again working Overtime Detail this time in the area of Bethesda, when he observed the same individual working part time security at the Nike store located at 7117 Arlington Rd Bethesda, MD. He did not observe any police vehicles in the area. He observed that the suspect was wearing the same attire as his last encounter. He made contact with the suspect and asked what barracks did he work for. The suspect advised that he worked for the Pikesville barracks. Sgt. Marshall then asked the suspect why he didnt drive his state vehicle to the part time. The suspect replied that he didnt feel like it. Sgt. Marshall observed his demeanor as strange and peculiar in regards to how he answered his questions. Sgt Marshall then contacted the barracks and asked if any Troopers had secondary employment authorization submitted for the location of that NIKE store. Cpl. Thomas #4714 contacted Lt. Upole #4264 to see if anybody applied for secondary employment in the area. Lt. Upole stated that no secondary employment authorizations were filed for that location. Cpl. Thomas advised Sgt. Marshall that the barrack had no record of secondary employment filed for that area. Sgt Marshall made contact with the suspect and asked him to step outside of the NIKE store in order for them to talk away from the business. As the suspect approached him, Sgt. Marshall observed a firearm and a badge. He observed that the badge was not a Maryland State Police badge based on his 20 years of law enforcement experience. He then advised the suspect, who was later identified as Marshall Charles Edwards (MD SDX: E363585115207), to turn around in order to detain him for proper identification. Edwards stepped back and refused to place his hands behind his back. Sgt. Marshall told him to turn around, Edwards refused to cooperate. He was placed under arrest by Montgomery County Police Department. Upon further investigation, Edwards to found to be active law enforcement through Morgan State University. All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7061</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 17:48:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7061</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/17/2023 17:48:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stafford</LastName>
            <FirstName>Keifer</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7377</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thomas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4714</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Seidl</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brendon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7061</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>