<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-036804</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/20/2023 00:51:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/20/2023 00:51:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/20/2023 00:35:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/20/2023 00:35:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>23-558 "R" NELSON</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 01:06:50</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6354</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/04/2023 21:50:27</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MARTIN BLVD / WINDLASS DR</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>710467</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 01:06:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/20/2023 01:30:06</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>710467</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Martin</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>DR</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/20/2023 01:06:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/20/2023 01:06:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/04/2023 21:50:27</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 01:06:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 16:27:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E.) TEAM* The following incident was captured on in-car and body camera Defendant: Jason Christopher Nelson  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: * I am trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (March 2013 SFST NHTSA Manual). * I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor as of February 2016. * I am a Certified Breath Test Operator by the Toxicologist of the State of Maryland as of March 2016. * I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of March 2016. * I am a distinguished graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute as of June 2015 * I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of May 2014. * I am a Preliminary Breath Test Instructor as of May 2019. * I am a RADAR and LIDAR Instructor as of October 2019. * I have apprehended more than 1,100 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On October 20, 2023 at approximately 0035 hours, I (Cpl. Wallace #6323) was on patrol in unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle DUI-1 on westbound Eastern prior to Martin Blvd, Baltimore County, Maryland. I observed a black Jeep Wrangler continued to accelerate towards the rear of the vehicle in front, brake and swerve. The Jeep took the ramp for Martin Blvd. The Jeep was following the vehicle in front of it very close, swerved left onto the solid white line and immediately right. The Jeep swerved right into the bike lane towards the curb prior to jerking left. The Jeep accelerated away from my patrol vehicle and towards the rear of the vehicle in front. The Jeep was bearing Florida registration QMTH40, swerved right over the fog line and onto the shoulder with  the vehicle width. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the Jeep.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Jeep on the driver side and made contact with the male operator of the vehicle. There was a male in the front passenger seat. I explained the reason for the stop and requested his drivers license and vehicle registration. He was holing a cigarette in his left fingers, but it was not lit. He was identified by his Maryland drivers license as Jason Christopher Nelson. While speaking with Nelson, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I deliberately observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. He continued to tell me that he was taking the passenger home because him and his girlfriend were arguing. I returned to my patrol vehicle to notify the barrack who I was out with.  I returned to the Jeep and requested Nelson to exit his vehicle and walk to the rear He complied and exited his vehicle. While speaking with Nelson outside the vehicle, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. When asked about alcohol consumption prior to driving, he stated that he had a beer and a half or two beers earlier, then he went to sleep. He stated that he went to pick the passenger up. I informed Nelson that I wanted him to perform standardized field sobriety tests, to which he agreed to the tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests.  I asked Nelson the following questions:  Glasses or contacts  No Head Injuries - No Medication  No Problems with knees or ankles  No  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus   Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes     Looked away when instructed to follow the stimulus.  WALK AND TURN (5/8 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage:    Lost balance stepped completely offline to the right 2 times.  Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Missed touching heel to toe by more than  inch on steps 5 and 9.  Stepped completely offline on steps 8 and 9.  Stopped after steps 8 and 9 to gain balance  Turn: Turned left using both feet  Walking Stage (2nd Nine):    Stepped completely offline on steps 2 and 7.  ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed.  Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10:    Swayed body to the left and right.  Seconds 11-20:    Swayed body to the left and right.  Left foot hit the ground 1 time  Seconds 21-30:    Swayed body to the left and right.  Right foot hit the ground 1 time  Raised arms more than 6 inches from side for balance.      Stated that he chugged the beers  PBT #209455 with a result of .09 BrAC.  ARREST Due to the number of observations, I concluded Nelson was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0051 hours, I placed Nelson under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. He was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack for processing.  Upon arrival at the barrack, I provided Nelson with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Nelson listened to the DR-15 Advice of Rights from the MVA website. At 0117hours, Nelson agreed to take a breath test.  20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Nelson beginning at 0052 hours. A search revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. Nelson was observed from that time until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by TFC Riba Tankari of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Nelson had a result of .09 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 0132 hours. **False teeth  INTOXIMETER RESULT: ****.09 grams of alcohol****  Nelson was polite and cooperative during the encounter. Nelson was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 01:34:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/04/2023 19:39:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>526266</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/20/2023 00:51:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 01:30:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/20/2023 01:32:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 01:30:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/20/2023 01:33:06</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390795</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Nelson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christopher</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/14/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/20/2023 01:21:06</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Nelson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christopher</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/14/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>N425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/20/2023 01:21:06</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2517</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mountain</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Joppa</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.359593</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.456926</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 01:33:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 01:33:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 01:30:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/20/2023 01:30:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158214</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 01:33:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/20/2023 01:33:50</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2021</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>WRG</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>FL</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>QMTH40</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>