<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-004661</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/06/2023 09:49:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/06/2023 09:49:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/06/2023 08:16:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/06/2023 08:16:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Attempt to locate for a wanted subject. The wrong person was arrested and transported to the barrack. Once identified, he was immediately taken out of restraints and provided transportation back to his residence.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 09:49:18</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6661</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 20:45:34</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>676341</AddressId>
      <City>MDC574</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 09:49:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 12:33:43</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>676341</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>3495</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Promenade</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Waldorf</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20603</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.935478</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.614784</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/06/2023 09:49:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/06/2023 09:49:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/08/2023 13:25:38</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 09:49:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6661</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 20:45:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On February 6, 2023, at approximately 0819 hours, I, Cpl. B. Meurrens #6372, was working as the La Plata Barrack Duty Officer when I received a phone call from Tpr. Barlow #7186, assigned to the Forestville Barrack. Tpr. Barlow advised he was assigned a warrant for Brandon Andrew Lee DOB: 1/9/1996, that originated from the La Plata Barrack and the subject was located at a residence in Waldorf, Maryland. Tpr. Barlow advised he spoke with Lee on the phone who advised he was located at 3495 Promenade Pl. Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland. Tpr. Barlow advised Lee was notified he had a warrant and was cooperative.  I checked the La Plata Barrack Warrant Ledger and located the warrant folder for Brandon Andrew Lee. I then checked Judiciary Case Search and verified the case was still active with a warrant issued. After verifying the warrant, I called TFC Howard #6842, who was field training Tpr. Shank #7507, and dispatch them for the Attempt to Locate Brandon Andrew Lee, who had an active arrest warrant for Failure to Appear - Driving Without a License. I notified TFC Howard of the circumstances of the call and requested for him to contact Tpr. Gardner # 7503 to assist as a back-up trooper. I then generated a CAD incident and entered Brandon Lees information into the card.  Once all units were on-scene, TFC Howard called the Barrack and asked which apartment they were supposed to check. I called Tpr. Barlow again and he advised apartment number 315. I notified the on-scene units of the apartment number and also told TFC Howard that Tpr. Gardner was going to be the assigned unit for the warrant. The units called out the subject was in custody at 0833 hours, approximately 10 minutes after being notified of the apartment number. Tpr. Gardner left the residence with a subject in custody at 0840 hours and transported him to the barrack to pick up the warrant. At 0856 hours, Tpr. Gardner was provided a copy of the warrant, and he entered Brandon Aleyander Lee DOB: 6/29/1995 into CAD. That name was obtained from the license of the subject in custody and was different from the subject on the warrant. Tpr. Gardner then asked for my assistance and I went outside and spoke to him. After looking at the license of the subject in custody and the name on the warrant, I instructed Tpr. Gardner to remove the handcuffs from Brandon Lee and transport him back to his residence because he was not the subject on the warrant. Tpr. Gardner transported Brandon Aleyander Lee back to his residence and he was released without charges.  I notified D/SGT Barth #0104 and Cpl. Rogers #5660 of the incident.  Case Close, Non-Criminal </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6372</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 12:50:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6372</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 13:47:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Howard</LastName>
            <FirstName>Travis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6842</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gardner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Hunter</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7503</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shank</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7587</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barth</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0104</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Meurrens</LastName>
            <FirstName>Blake</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6372</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494044</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>09</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>MSP1002</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/06/2023 08:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6372</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 14:15:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6372</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 14:15:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6372</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 13:48:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>284706</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lee</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Andrew</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/01/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.1847783E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>09/30/2020 22:18:11</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lee</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Andrew</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/01/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.1847783E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>L000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/30/2020 22:18:11</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6811</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Meteor</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Springfield</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>22150</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.1732263</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.7704671</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>423</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4310</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/30/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6372</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 13:48:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:52</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6372</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 14:17:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:25</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368282</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lee</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Aleyander</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/29/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/06/2023 10:03:18</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lee</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Aleyander</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/29/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/06/2023 10:03:18</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6372</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 14:17:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/06/2023 15:02:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/06/2023 15:02:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/08/2023 13:26:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6842</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:02:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6661</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 20:45:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On February 6, 2023, at approximately 0819 hours, I TFC Howard #6842, was on duty working in the area of Crain Highway and Smallwood Drive, Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland. I received a phone call from Cpl. Meurrens #6372 dispatching Tpr. Gardner, Tpr. Shank (Field Training) and I for an Attempt to Locate of a subject, Brandon Lee, who had an active arrest warrant for Failure to Appear - Driving Without a License. Cpl. Meurrens advised that Tpr. Barlow, assigned to the MSP Forestville Barrack contacted the La Plata barrack and advised he was assigned a warrant for Brandon Lee, that originated from the La Plata Barrack and the subject was located at a residence in Waldorf, Maryland. Tpr. Barlow advised he spoke with Lee on the phone who advised he was located at 3495 Promenade Pl. Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland. Tpr. Barlow advised Lee was notified he had a warrant and was cooperative.  Upon arrival at 3495 Promenade Place, Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland, I contacted the barrack to locate the apartment number. Cpl. Meurrens contacted me via telephone advising Tpr. Barlow called Lee back and was advised apartment 315. Tpr Gardner, Tpr .Shank (Field Training) and I arrived at the apartment and Tpr. Shank knocked on the apartment door. Lee answered the door with his house key and jacket in hand. I asked Lee if he was aware why we were there. Lee advised Yes, as if he were ready to go and stated that he had just gotten off the phone with Tpr. Barlow. I asked Lee if he knew what the warrant was for and he stated he did not because it was from 2020. I advised Lee the warrant was for driving without a license. Lee stated he was working on getting into the Virginia State Police and thought they would have told him that this was on his record. I asked Lee where he was in the process and he stated he was going to take the physical fitness test in May. Lee was cooperative through the entire event and stated he did not remember getting stopped.  Lee was placed into handcuffs by Tpr. Shank, per his field training instructions and was transported to the Maryland State Police La Plata Barack by Tpr. Gardner at 0840 hours.  All events occurred in Charles County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6842</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 15:02:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6842</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/08/2023 13:12:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barth</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0104</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Howard</LastName>
            <FirstName>Travis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6842</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/08/2023 10:46:53</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/08/2023 10:46:53</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/13/2023 20:45:34</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 10:46:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6661</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 20:45:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car (L-42) and Body Worn Camera Operational, but did not capture this incident.   Narrative: On February 6, 2023, at approximately 0750 hours, I, Trooper J. Barlow #7186, of the Maryland State Police, currently assigned to the Forestville Barrack, was on duty in my marked patrol vehicle, when I responded to 5612 Helmont Drive, Oxon Hill, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20744, to attempt to locate a Brandon Andrew Lee (B/M DOB: 09/01/1996) who had an open warrant through Maryland State Police La Plata Barrack, driving without a license.   Upon my arrival, I contacted a resident of the residence who advised Brandon Lee does not live at this address. At approximately 0755 hours, I contacted the Police Communication Operator (PCO) to locate a phone number of Lee through the TLO database. The PCO sent me approximately 5 possible numbers which belonged to the Lee, one of which had an 86% accuracy of being connected to Lee. At approximately 0801 hours, I called Lee on the number which was 202-749-0253, to which a male answered where I advised him who I was and asked if this was Brandon Lee to which he advised he was. I advised Lee I was calling to locate him for a warrant he had for his arrest. I asked Lee if he still lives in Prince Georges County to which he stated, No I do not, I moved to Virginia, but I am currently at my girlfriends house in Waldorf, Maryland. I asked Lee what is the address of his girlfriends house in Waldorf to which he advised 3495 Promenade Place, Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland 20603. I advised Lee the warrant was for driving without a license, and he needed to be taken into custody to see the Commissioner to receive a new court date for missing the initial date. Lee advised he had a valid drivers license for a few years. I advised Lee the last time he was stopped for this reason was in 2020.  At approximately 0805 hours, I contacted the Maryland State Police La Plata Barrack, and advised the Duty Officer, Corporal B. Meurrens #6372 of the active warrant and I had contacted Lee via phone. I advised Cpl Meurrens Lee is aware of the warrant and was cooperative. I advised Cpl Meurrens if he could send a trooper to the address to take him into custody. Cpl Meurrens advised he would get someone to the address to contact Lee.  At approximately 0904 hours, I received a phone call from Cpl Meurrens advising after the trooper transported Brandon Lee to Charles County Detention Center (CCDC) it was revealed they had arrested the wrong Brandon Lee.   All events Prince Georges/Charles County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 10:48:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/08/2023 10:48:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Heun</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mason </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6661</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>