<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-043686</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/10/2023 20:26:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/10/2023 20:26:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/10/2023 20:06:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/10/2023 20:06:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>ACRS DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 20:26:24</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1114</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 05:42:27</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>US-50 EB EXIT 38A / DUKE ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>607114</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 20:26:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 01:42:00</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>607114</AddressId>
         <StreetName>W/B Rt 50 W/O Castle Marina Rd</StreetName>
         <City>Chester</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21619</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.291743</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.975893</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/10/2023 20:26:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/10/2023 20:26:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>80</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 18:44:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 20:26:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:13</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Patrol Vehicle S-22 is Equipped with an in-car camera/recorder and body cam.  Weather:Raining/57degrees  Defendant: Puher, Jonathan, Michael Date of Birth: 02/20/1993 Date of Arrest: 12/10/23 Time of Arrest: 2033                                                     License#: Md 9EL2989 DUI #S-23-167 Centreville  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) Vehicle was involved in a three vehicle collision.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) On Sunday, Dec 10, 2023 at approximately 2006 hours, I was dispatched to a multi-vehicle collision in the area of W/B Rt 50 W/O Castle Marina Rd, Queen Anne County, Stevensville Md 21666. Upon arrival, I observed three vehicles into the guardrail. A gray 2017 Ram 1500 bearing MD registration 9EL2989, and black 2017 Toyota Tacoma bearing Md registration 5FJ5179 with left front damage, and a white 2019 BMW X1 bearing VA registration UPF8418. I exited my vehicle, and made contact with the individuals to assess their conditions. First was the driver of the white BMW X1, Jennie Rose Cavallaro, (W/F 5/24/75) who advised she was okay, and was the caller. I then made contact with the operator of the black Toyota Tacoma, Alexis Brooke Marconi, (W/F 11/06/96) who did not appear injured. I then made contact with the operator of the gray Ram 1500, who had already been identified as the at fault driver, Jonathan Michael Puher, (W/M 2/20/93) who advised that he had just come off of Castle Marina Rd, and encountered road spray. He advised that his rear tires drifted out, and he struck the Tacoma, which then struck the BMW. As Puher was detailing what occurred I observed a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath. He had advised that he had been at a Christmas party. When I asked Puher if he had been drinking he said, Not tonight. I told him his speech was slurred and I was going put him through SFSTs which he agreed. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed on the roadway on the shoulder in front of Puhers Ram 1500. The surface was wet, level and free of any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight, and overhead street lighting, and passing vehicles. Puher was wearing shoes, jacket, and pants. Puher appeared in good physical health, and advised he had no injuries preventing him from taking SFSTs    HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  HGN was conducted using my index finger as a stimulus. The stimulus was passed horizontally at a distance of 12-15 inches and slightly above eye level across Puhers face. During the instructions I made it clear to Puher to keep his head still and to only follow the stimulus with his eyes. During the test, I instructed him to only follow with his eyes. I then checked for equal tracking and equal pupil size. During the test, Puher failed demonstrate smooth pursuit and equal tracking. He demonstrated distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and an onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees. During the test there was an odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath.  WALK AND TURN (3/8 clues observed)  Prior to Puher performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. I placed Puher into the instructional position. Puher was then instructed to place his right foot in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. I demonstrated and instructed Puher to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Puher had to be placed in the instructional position twice, as he attempted to start before instructions were given. Puher was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Puher was to keep his hands flat to his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, I demonstrated and explained to Puher to keep his lead foot on the line, and make a series of small steps around his lead foot with his rear foot to turn completely around and begin the second series of nine steps. I again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be identical to the first series. Puher was instructed that once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Puher if he understood the test, and he explained the instructions back to me. No discrepancies were observed on the initial 9 steps.ed heel to toe on steps. Puher then performed the turn unsatisfactory by turning to his right side without walking around the lead foot. Puher then continued his second series of nine steps by missed heel to toe on step 5.  Instructional Stage: Started too soon  Walking Stage (1st Nine):  Turn: 1.) Turned by pivoting around to the right side. (unsatisfactory)  Walking Stage (2nd Nine) 1.) Missed Heel to toe on step 5   ONE LEG STAND (OLS) (3/4 clues)  Prior to Puher performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Puher was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Puher was asked if there was anything medically that would prevent him from performing this test, to which he indicated that his hip was sore a little bit. Puher was asked if he understood the test and the instructions which he indicated he did. Puher then lifted his left foot and put it back down on the count of 10. He then picked up his left foot again and restarted. Puher displayed a lack of balance, by holding arms out to his side as he started to sway back and forth. Puher then put his foot down again. Puher attempted the test multiple times, and was stopped after real time of 54 seconds.  Instructional Stage: 1.) Swayed 2.) Hands out  Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: foot down, swayed, hands out Seconds 10-20: foot down, swayed, hands out Seconds 20-30: foot down, swayed, hands out, and stopped test  1.) Puher attempted multiple times, but was stopped after 54 seconds.   PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT) Puher was offered a PBT, but refused  ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Puher was driving a motor vehicle while impaired. * Performance on SFSTs * Strong odor of alcohol on breath * Admission to drinking after initially denying  Puher was placed under arrest for Driving While Impaired at 20:33 hours. Puher was given the DR-15 via MVA website in English. Puher refused intoximeter, and was provided all his citations, and paperwork then released to his family on scene of the collision.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: Refusal  I request this case closed by citations and arrest  All events occurred in Queen Anne County Maryland</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6379</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 00:45:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6379</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 04:15:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hendrick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Graham</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7300</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Golladay</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jerry</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1114</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Strange</LastName>
            <FirstName>Wendell</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6379</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533161</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/10/2023 20:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6379</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 02:13:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6379</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 02:13:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533161</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/10/2023 20:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6379</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 02:14:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6379</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 02:14:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533161</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21329</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/10/2023 20:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21329</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6379</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 02:17:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6379</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 02:17:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533161</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/10/2023 20:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6379</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 02:18:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6379</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 02:18:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>30</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6379</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 02:28:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6379</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 02:28:55</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>395262</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Puher</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jonathan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MICHAEL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/20/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/14/2023 02:26:58</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J535</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Puher</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jonathan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MICHAEL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/20/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J535</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/14/2023 02:26:58</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1053</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hampton</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Crownsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21032</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1315</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.581445</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.059404</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>995</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9562</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6379</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 02:28:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6379</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 02:28:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6379</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 02:28:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6379</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 02:28:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6379</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 02:28:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6379</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 02:28:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6379</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 02:13:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6379</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 02:13:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>