<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011477</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/31/2023 10:22:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/31/2023 10:22:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/31/2023 09:37:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/31/2023 09:37:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>ACRS that resulted in a DWI arrest where the driver is suspected of being under the influence of cds</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/31/2023 10:22:13</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/13/2023 11:34:02</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>81795</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>531</SubBeat>
      <City>MDC407</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/31/2023 10:22:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 01:20:17</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>81795</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1520</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>ROCK SPRING</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>FOREST HILL</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>531</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-76.37069480348141</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.558745120639294</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>RITE AID</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/31/2023 10:22:08</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/31/2023 10:22:08</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/13/2023 07:51:37</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE PROCESSED-ORIGINAL</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/31/2023 10:22:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6761</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/13/2023 07:51:37</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-car camera and body worn camera operational, Marked Car D25.  Maryland State Police, Bel Air Barrack DWI #23-087 23-MSP-011477  Defendant: Tana Marie Dunn Defendant Address: 2710 Park Heights Dr, Baldwin MD 21013 DOB: 12/31/1969 Date of Arrest: 03/31/2023 Time of Arrest: 1019 hours Subsequent Offender: No Minor in the vehicle: No Driver License Number: MD DL MD-10272599248 CDL: No  First Observation:  On 03/31/2023 at approximately 0937 hours, I, Trooper Allen #7267, was dispatched to a two vehicle motor vehicle accident located at 1520 Rock Spring Rd, Forest Hill. Upon my arrival I witnessed two vehicles in the Rite Aide parking lot both with damage to their side. I then saw the driver of the a gray Toyota Avalon Andrew Hensler (W/M DOB 02/13/1987) standing near his vehicle which had heavy front driver side damage to his vehicle. Hensler advised that the other driver was currently inside the Rite Aide. I then asked Hensler how the accident occurred, he advised that while traveling south on Rock Spring Rd in lane 3 the other vehicle was to his left and they merged into his lane side swiping his vehicle. I took note to the other vehicle which was a silver Honda Accord which had heavy front passenger side damage. It was at this time that the driver of the Honda Tana Dunn (W/F DOB 12/31/1969) walked out of the Rite Aide and approached the Accord.  Phase Two- Personal Contact:  I then met with Dunn and asked her what happened to cause the accident. Dunn stated she was traveling south on Rock Spring Rd in lane two and then stated that she attempted to turn into the Rite Aide. Dunn state that she then merged into the other vehicle and that the accident was her fault. While speaking with Dunn, I noticed that she was acting very lethargic and sluggish. I did not detect any odor of an alcoholic beverage on Dunns breath, but her behavior was that of an intoxicated person. Dunn also slurred her speech while I spoke with her. I then noticed that in her front sweatshirt pocket, I saw a small 1.7 ounce bottle of Smirnoff Vodka. I then requested that Dunn partake in field sobriety testing due to possessing the alcohol beverage on her and due to her behavior. Dunn stated that the Smirnof bottle was discarded in the parking lot and that she picked it up. However, Dunn agreed to partake in field sobriety testing.     Phase Three- Prearrest Screening  Standardized Field Sobriety Test:  The evaluation administered to Dunn was in the paved parking lot of 1520 Rock Spring Rd during the daytime hours. Emergency lights were deactivated and Dunn was tested facing away from any emergency equipment. The parking lot was also free of debris and deformities. When I asked Dunn if she had anything to drink or if she used any substances, Dunn denied consuming alcohol or CDS.  Questions: Glasses or contacts: None Medical conditions: None  Injuries: None.  Medications: None at the time of testing.   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) (5/6 Clues observed) (Instructed and Understood/ Defendants Response: YES) The first test administered was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. A stimulus pen was used and held approximately 12 inches from Dunns face. I instructed Dunn to follow the stimulus with her eyes and eyes only. She was also instructed to stand with her feet together and hands to her side. I asked Dunn if she understood the instructions which she stated she did.The following observations were made:  Lack of smooth pursuit: 2 clues observed Distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation: 2 clues observed Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees: 1 clue observed Vertical Nystagmus: not present. Total Observed Clues: 5/6  Other: Dunn also had resting nystagmus which was noticeable at the time of testing and later while at the barrack.  Walk and Turn Test (6/8 Clues Observed) (Instructed and Understood/ Defendants Response: Yes) The second test offered to Dunn was the Walk and Turn. I instructed Dunn to stand in the starting position by placing her right foot in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe.I then instructed Dunn to remain in that position and that she was not to begin the test until told to do so. I then explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. I instructed Dunn to take 9 heel to toe steps while keeping her hands to her side, and continuously look at her feet while counting aloud. On the ninth step, I explained that Dunn was to keep her lead foot planted, while she took a series of small steps around her lead foot with her rear foot to turn completely around and take an additional 9 steps in the same manner. I then reminded Dunn that she was not to start or stop the test until it was completed. I then asked Dunn if she understood the instructions, which she stated that she did. It should be noted that Dunn performed two additional set of 9 steps despite being instructed to only perform two. Dunn performed a total of 4 sets of steps.   Instructional stage:  Stepped out of the starting position.  Walking stage:   First Nine Steps:  Toe to Heel:missed on 0 steps Stepped off line: on 0 steps  Used arms for balance: on step 2 Second set of nine steps:  Toe to Heel: missed on steps 1, 3  Stepped off line: on steps 1, 3, 5 Used arms for balance: on steps 1, and 3 to 10 Third set Toe to Heel:missed on step 6 Stepped off line: on steps 6 an 7  Used arms for balance: on steps 1 to 10 Fourth set Toe to Heel:missed on step 3 Stepped off line: on steps 1, 3, and 4  Used arms for balance: on steps 2 to 10 Number of steps:In correct number of steps on all 4 sets. Due to not beginning in the starting position, Dunn would end her 9th step with her right foot, then take a 10th step to plant her left foot to perform the turn. Dunn also did two additional sets.  Started too soon: No Stopped during the test: Yes. However, Dunn believed she was following the instruction of Cpl. Atkinson #5623. Cpl. Atkinson arrived on scene to assist me during my field sobriety testing. While I administered the test, Dunns mother arrived on scene and approached Dunn during the WAT test. It can be heard on my body camera Cpl. Atkinson stating Stop but this was directed towards Dunns mother. Dunn misunderstood and thought she was being addressed.  The Turn: Unsatisfactory. Out of the 4 turns that Dunn performed, Dunn would take an extra step to plant her left foot on the ground, and when turning, she would lift her left foot and turn in an unsatisfactory manner.   Total Clues (6/8)  One Leg Stand (4/4 Clues observed) (Instructed and understood/ Defendants Response Yes) I instructed Dunn to assume the starting position for the One Leg Stand test by placing her feet together and keeping her arms by her side. I also told Dunn to not begin the test or move from the starting position until she was instructed to do so. Dunn stated that he understood the instructions. I demonstrated to Dunn, once instructed to do so, she was to raise one of her feet approximately 6 inches off the ground and to point her toes forward to let the foot be parallel to the ground. I then instructed Dunn to look at her toes the entire time while she counted by thousands aloud. (Thousand one, thousand two) I told Dun to continue to count until told to stop. I asked Dunn if she understood the instructions to which she stated Yes.  Balance and Counting Stage  0-10 Seconds: Put foot down: 2 times Swayed: through out Used Arms for balance: once Hops: n/a  11-20 Seconds: Put foot down: 1 time Swayed: 2 times Used Arms for balance: through out Hops: n/a   21-30 Seconds: Put foot down: 1 times  Swayed: throughout  Used Arms for balance: once Hops: n/a  Total Clues (3/4) Additional Field Sobriety Testing After conducting Standardized Field Sobriety testing I also conducted additional field sobriety testing with Dunn.  Lack of Convergence I then administered the Lack of Convergence exam with Dunn. I instructed Dunn to stand with her feet together and to keep her hands to her side. I instructed Dunn to not move from this position until she was told to do so. I asked Dunn if she understood the instructions which she stated he did. I used the same stimulus pen as used in the HGN test and held the pen approximately 12 to 15 inches away from Dunns nose. I then instructed Dunn to follow the stimulus with her eyes, and her eyes only, while keeping her head still. I informed her that I would be making 2 large circles around her head with the stimulus. After the second circle I would bring the stimulus down approximately two inches towards the bridge of Dunns nose and informed her that she would need to cross her eyes to focus on the stimulus. I also advised Dunn that I would not touch her during the test. I asked Dunn if she understood the instructions which she stated that she did. The following observations were made: LOC: not present   Modified Romberg Balance test I then administered the Modified Romberg Balance test with Dunn. I instructed Dunn to stand with her feet together and keep her hands to her side. I informed her to stay in that position until I was finished giving instructions and to not to start the test until I informed her to do so. I asked if Dunn understood the instruction which Dunn informed she did. I then instructed Dunn that when I informed her to start that she would tilt her head back slightly and close her eyes. Once Dunns eyes were closed, she was to remain in that position until she believed that 30 seconds had passed. I asked Dunn if she understood the instruction which she stated he did. The following observations were made: Estimated amount of time passing: Dunn stated Stop after 32 seconds had passed.  Body sway: present Eye tremors: present   Finger to nose test The next test administered to Dunn was the Finger to Nose test. I instructed Dunn that I would be giving her a series of commands stating left, right etc. to indicate which fingertip to bring up to the tip of her nose. I then instructed Dunn to stand with her feet together and her arms to the side but to turn her palms towards me, curling her fingers into fists and then extend her pointer fingers. Once Dunn was in the proper stance I explained and demonstrated that she would tilt her head back slightly and close her eyes. When I instructed her left or right she was to bring that corresponding hand up and touch the tip of her nose with the tip of that finger and then returning the hand back to the starting position. I asked Dunn if she understood the instructions which she stated he did. The following observations were made: Left: touched the tip of her nose with the tip of her finger Right: touched the tip of her nose with the tip of her finger Left: touched the tip of her nose with the tip of her finger Right: touched the tip of her nose with the tip of her finger Right: touched the tip of her nose with the tip of her finger Left: touched the tip of her nose with the tip of her finger   Preliminary Breath: preliminary breath test was not offered because I did not have one at the time of testing.   Arrest Due to my training of over 40 hours in DUI detection with live donors at the Maryland State Police Academy, being certified to conduct ARIDE testing through Baltimore County, and the observations of impairment made during the Field Sobriety testing; I determined I had probable cause to believe that Dunn was driving under the influence and unable to operate the vehicle safely. Due to the following:   Lethargic  Acting in a dazed manner.  Clues of standardized field sobriety testing   margin-left:8px"&gt;Clues of additional field sobriety testing   I then placed Dunn under arrest fordriving or attempting to drive while under the influence of a controlled dangerous substance at 1019 hours. I then transferred Dunn to the Bel Air state police barrack.  Advice of Rights (DR-15) / Certified Breath Test (Accepted). I presented Dunn with the Advice of Rights form (DR-15) in English audio form while transporting her to the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack and she agreedto submit to an intoximeter test at 1035 hours. I then transferred Dunn to the barrack and Sgt. Sanders #5948 administered a certified breath test. Dunn provided a sample at 1108 hours with a result of .00 BAC.  I then presented Dunn with his Miranda rights, and she chose to retain her rights at 1120 hours.  Dunn was charged with driving under the influence of a controlled dangerous substance and issued all pertinent paperwork.  Dunn was released to a license driver at approximately 1146 hours Case Status- Closed due to arrest. All events occurred in Harford County Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 04:59:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 05:00:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Atkinson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5623</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allen</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7267</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Turner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6761</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allen</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7267</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allen</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7267</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500880</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15558</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/31/2023 10:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15558</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 01:20:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 02:08:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500880</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/31/2023 10:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 01:20:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 02:09:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500880</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/31/2023 10:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 01:20:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 02:10:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500880</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/31/2023 10:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 01:20:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 02:11:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500880</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19745</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/31/2023 10:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19745</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 01:20:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 02:12:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>53</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 01:20:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>341751</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dunn</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tara</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/31/1969 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.1690399E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/26/2022 20:20:27</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>DUNN</LastName>
               <FirstName>TANA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MARIE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/31/1969 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dunn</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tara</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/31/1969 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.1690399E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>D500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/26/2022 20:20:27</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>DUNN</LastName>
               <FirstName>TANA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MARIE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/31/1969 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2710</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Park Heights</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baldwin</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21013</Zip5>
               <Zip4>9112</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.4926583</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.5333731</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>866</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1819</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/26/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 02:14:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 02:14:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 02:14:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 01:20:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 01:20:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151501</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7267</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 01:20:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7267</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 01:20:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1HGCG1650YA046775</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2000</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ACCORD</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4D</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1FB5805</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>