<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-037088</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/22/2023 04:48:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/22/2023 04:48:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/22/2023 04:29:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/22/2023 04:29:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/22/2023 04:48:41</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6056</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/17/2023 06:07:49</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>S 270 TO ROCKLEDGE RAMP / ROCKLEDGE BLVD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>711414</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/22/2023 04:48:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/29/2023 12:17:16</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>711414</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>10904</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Earlsgate</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Rockville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20852</Zip5>
         <Zip4>4552</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.140384</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.032646</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/22/2023 04:48:40</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/22/2023 04:48:40</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/17/2023 06:07:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/22/2023 04:48:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cosgrove</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brooke</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7153</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathanael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7454</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>526550</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/22/2023 04:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 12:20:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7454</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/29/2023 12:20:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 12:49:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7454</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/29/2023 12:49:35</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>391566</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Rivas</LastName>
               <FirstName>Maricela</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/28/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/29/2023 12:30:28</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M624</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Rivas</LastName>
               <FirstName>Maricela</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/28/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M624</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/29/2023 12:30:28</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1703</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mount Pisgah</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>21</SubNumber>
               <City>Silver Spring</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.97609</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.01478</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 12:49:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 12:49:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 12:49:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 12:20:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7454</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/29/2023 12:20:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158489</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 12:55:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7454</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/29/2023 12:55:59</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3MZBN1U74HM101183</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MAZD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MZ3</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5EN7215</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/01/2023 16:37:30</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/01/2023 16:37:30</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/17/2023 06:07:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/01/2023 16:37:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*Repeat Offender*   At the time of this incident, I was on-duty, in full uniform, operating fully marked MSP cruiser N-4. This incident was captured on my issued BWC.   Defendant: Maricela Rivas (MD  R120585009990, DOB 12/28/1991, Hispanic/F)  Date of Arrest: Sunday, October 22, 2023  Time of Arrest: 0502 hours  DUI #: 23-231 (Rockville Barrack)   *CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING:  * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. (2021).   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  *I did not witness the vehicle in motion.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):  On Sunday, October 22, 2023 I Tpr. Norman #7454 of the Maryland State Police Rockville Barrack, was in full uniform, and equipped with a fully operational Axon Body Worn Camera (BWC). At approximately 0430 hours, I responded to southbound I-270 north of Rockledge Drive for a single vehicle accident. Upon my arrival, I observed a blue Mazda 3 bearing Maryland registration 5EN7215 on the right shoulder. I made contact with the driver of the Mazda. The driver was identified by her Maryland drivers license as: Maricela Rivas, H/F, DOB: 12/28/1991. Rivas told me that she took the corner too fast and struck the concrete barrier on the right shoulder. During my contact with Rivas, I observed her displaying signs of alcohol impairment. I observed Rivass mannerisms to be slow and her speech to be slurred. I also noted her eyes to be bloodshot and watery and her pupils to be dilated. I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Rivass person. I asked Rivas if she had any alcohol, and she told me she had three Coronas and a shot of tequila approximately one or two hours ago at a friends house. Rivas was not wearing any shoes and stated she left her friends house without them.  Based upon my interactions with Rivas, I asked her to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):  * The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of the roadway. The scene was protected by two marked Maryland State Police patrol vehicles. The surface was level, with some loose gravel on the right shoulder. The weather was clear. Rivas appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visual injuries.  I asked Rivas the following questions:  Injuries - No Medical Conditions - No. Corrective Lenses - No.   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed):  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from Rivass eyes and slightly above eye level. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Rivass pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I asked Rivas if she understood the instructions, and she stated Yes.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes  2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes  3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes  4.) Vertical Nystagmus - Present in both eyes    WALK AND TURN (5/8 clues observed):   Prior to Rivas performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Rivas was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Rivas was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Rivas was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Rivas was to keep her hands flat at her side, keep her eyes looking at her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Rivas was explained and demonstrated to keep her front foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Rivas was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Rivas was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her side, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Rivas if she understood the test, and she stated, Yes. Rivas was only wearing socks.   Instructional Stage:  1.) Lost balance - Feet broke apart  Walking Stage (1st Nine):  1.) Misses heel to toe  2.) Steps off the line by more than the width of her foot  3.) Improper number of steps: 8  Turn:  Improper   Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  1.) Misses heel to toe  2.) Steps off the line by more than the width of her foot   ONE LEG STAND (4/4 clues observed):  Prior to Rivas performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Rivas was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep both of her legs straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Rivas if she understood the test, and she stated Yes.   *Balanced on her left foot.  Instructional Stage:  * Swaying side to side.   Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10:  1.) Swayed body to the left and right.  2.) Puts foot down.  3.) Raised arms more than 6 inches from his side for balance.  4.) Hops on left foot several times.  *At second 10 Rivas nearly falls over.   Seconds 11-20:  *Rivas spends almost the entire 10 seconds recovering from almost falling over.  Seconds 21-30:  1.) Swayed body to the left and right.  2.) Puts foot down twice.   Based on the following, I had reason to believe Rivas was so far impaired she could not drive a vehicle safely.  *Rivass admission to consuming alcohol that night.  * Causing a Motor Vehicle Accident.  * Mannerisms to be slow and her speech to be slurred.  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle.  * Bloodshot and watery eyes.  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person.  * My observed signs of impairment as she performed field sobriety tests.   ARREST:  Due to the above observations, I arrested Rivas for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0502 hours without incident. Rivas was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Rockville State Police Barrack. I played the DR-15 Advice of Rights form in English from the MVAs official website to Rivas. She was also provided a copy to read along with and review. Rivas refused to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the DR-15 indicating the same at approximately 0534 hours.   * Maricela Rivas was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to a sober adult.   Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/01/2023 16:45:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7454</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/01/2023 16:47:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gaines</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6056</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathanael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7454</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>