<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008978</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/11/2023 13:23:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/11/2023 13:23:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/11/2023 12:55:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/11/2023 12:55:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Handgun Violation</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 13:23:08</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 10:08:42</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>687029</AddressId>
      <City>MDC196</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 13:23:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 09:39:32</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>687029</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>70</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I70 Eb</StreetName>
         <City>Mount Airy</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.13516</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.35476</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/11/2023 13:23:06</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/11/2023 13:23:06</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/28/2023 23:56:30</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 13:23:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:20:55</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23-MSP-008978  Nature of Incident: CR 4-203 Wear, Carry, Transport Handgun on Person  Scene Processing: The traffic stop was recorded. Marked MSP patrol vehicle is equipped with MVR. I am equipped with BWC.  Firearm: Glock 19 Serial# BGYY951 9MM  Location: W/B I-70 near the Howard County Line  Offender: Michael Paul Merlino W/M 04/22/1987  Narrative:    On 3/11/2023 at approximately 1255 hours, I, TFC Nield #6851, was on routine patrol of W/B I-70 in the area of the Howard County line in Mount Airy, Maryland. At this time, I observed a black Honda Odyssey traveling in the westbound travel lanes displaying a handwritten sign on the rear of the vehicle reading Tag Applied For. I positioned my vehicle directly behind the Honda and activated my emergency equipment to conduct a traffic stop on the Honda.    I made contact with the driver at the passenger side window, introduced myself, explained the reason for the traffic stop, and advised the driver that the traffic stop was being audibly and visually recorded. I asked the driver for his drivers license and registration, and I was able to positively identify the driver asMichael Paul Merlino (W/M 04/22/1987) by his Virginia drivers license. Merlino explained that he had just purchased the vehicle and that he literally just signed for it today as he handed me the title for the Honda. I asked Merlino if he had valid insurance on the vehicle, which he was able to provide to me. A routine METERS check of the Hondas VIN (5FNRL5H63DB034719) revealed that it was not registered in any state. This was confirmed by the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack Emergency dispatcher.    During the traffic stop,Merlino voluntarily explained to me that he had his concealed carry on him. I then asked Merlino if he has a Maryland Wear and Carry permit, to which he stated that he did not. Merlino was, however, able to provide me with a Virginia conceal carry permit. During the traffic stop, Merlinos firearm was removed from his right hip and identified as a Glock 19, serial number BGYY951. A routine METERS check of the serial numberBGYY951 did not reveal any stolen or lost flags. Additionally, the firearm is not registered in the State of Maryland.I observed that the Glock contained 14 rounds of 9MM ammunition, but did not have a bullet loaded in the chamber. Due to the State of Maryland not having a reciprocity agreement with Virginia regarding handgun permits, Merlino was placed into custody without incident and transported to the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack for processing. Also within the vehicle was Merlinos adolescent daughter. She was also transported in marked MSP patrol vehicle G-23 to the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack utilizing the appropriate child safety seat.   Once at the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack, I made several investigatory phone calls. The first phone call was to the Virginia State Police, who were able to verify that Merlinos carry permit was in good standing in the State of Virginia. The second phone call was to the Maryland Gun Center, who advised that they have transitioned to an educational phase of enforcement for valid out-of-state conceal carry permits. The Maryland Gun Center stated that they are encouraging Troopers to educate out of state visitors of Marylands laws and to make the firearm legal to transport in Maryland by unloading the ammunition and separating it from the firearm. The Maryland Gun Center also recommended that I contact the Carroll County States Attorneys Office for charging advice before asking for the applicable charges. My third and final phone call was to the on-call States Attorney for Carroll County, Adam Culver. Culver stated that the States Attorneys Office for Carroll County would not be interested in pursuing charges for a valid out-of-state conceal carry permit, and that the appropriate course of action would be to follow the Maryland Gun Centers recommendation and return the firearm safely without charges.  Merlino was then released from the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack without criminal charges. The Glock was unloaded and returned to Merlino, who was instructed on how to travel through Maryland with his firearm in the future. Merlino and his daughter left the Barrack without incident.  All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland.  I request this case be closed on the traffic charges alone.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 11:08:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6851</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 01:27:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nield</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6851</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498377</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>20</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 5212</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 12:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 5212</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:41:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6851</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 11:35:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 11:01:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:44</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371811</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Merlino</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Paul</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/22/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 11:01:25</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M645</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Merlino</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Paul</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/22/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M645</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 11:01:25</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 23:17:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 23:17:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:41:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6851</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 09:41:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 11:07:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6851</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 11:07:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>MSPPI</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <SerialNumber>BGYY951</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>245565</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>GRY</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>GRY</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>Glock</Make>
         <Model>19</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>