<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-038064</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/29/2023 02:30:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/29/2023 02:30:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/29/2023 02:24:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/29/2023 02:24:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>MSP BK G DUI 23-166, TA 21-902A1 (CORY ALEXANDER JONES)</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 02:30:21</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/16/2023 10:43:02</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>2560 BALTIMORE,FINKSBURG</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>711378</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 02:30:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 05:19:35</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>711378</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2560</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Baltimore Finksburg</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.9047348333333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.5090103333333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/29/2023 02:30:19</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/29/2023 02:30:19</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/16/2023 08:33:02</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 02:30:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 20:22:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23-MSP-038064  Incident: MSP Barrack G DUI 23-166 (CORY ALEXANDER JONES)  TA 21-902(A)(1) DUI  Date  Time: 10/29/2023, 0220 hours  Location of Offense: W/B MD 140 at Cedarhurst Rd to, Finksburg, Carroll County, MD.  My investigation was recorded on AXON digital recording system assigned to G-39 and AXON body camera assigned to M/Tpr Fair.  Minors in Vehicle:NO  Prior DUI: YES  PBT: refused at 0252 hours  EVIDENTIARY TEST:refused at 0318 hours  DRE (Drug Recognition Expert): N/A  Weather: clear, approximately 65 degrees Fahrenheit  Qualifications:  -Maryland State Police Academy (June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007)  -I am trained to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through NHTSA and the Maryland State Police (MSP Academy, June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007).  -I have attended and graduated from the University of Maryland University College Advanced DUI College (UMUC January 7-11, 2013).  -I have attended and completed training Enhanced DUI Enforcement: The Complete Arrest (MPCTC, 05/11/2016).  -A.R.I.D.E.: Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (MPCTC, 03/29-03/30/2017)  -Cannabis Impairment Detection Workshop (MPCTC, 09/29/2021)  -Preliminary Breath Test Instructor (MSP CTAU, 09/11-09/12/2023)  Driver:  MD DL MD10273747757 CORY ALEXANDER JONES 949 SOUTH MARLYN AVE ESSEX, MD 21221 1/M, DOB 11/22/1991  Phase I: Reason for Stop  On 10/29/2023 at approximately 0218 hours I was on duty, in uniform, operating a marked Maryland State Police Patrol vehicle, G-39. I observed a vehicle (described as a black 2016 Nissan passenger vehicle, subsequently found to be displaying expired Virginia temporary registration M75338) was traveling W/B MD 140, approaching Cedarhurst Rd, Finksburg, Carroll County, MD with and inoperative headlight. This vehicle was traveling W/B in the left lane of travel with the tag lights inoperative (failing to illuminate the rear registration plate). I also observed this vehicle while traveling W/B MD 140, approaching MD 91, had both driver side tires over the broken white lane divider line between lane 1 and the left turn lane to turn onto S/B MD 91, and was braking unnecessarily as it was approaching a green light of MD 140 at MD 91. The vehicle corrected and continued W/B MD 140 in the left lane (lane 1). The vehicle slowed to 23 mph in the posted 50 mph zone (paced). W/O MD 91 on MD 140, I observed the vehicles driver side tires on the yellow left shoulder line, and the vehicle increased its speed to greater than 50 mph in the 55 mph zone, before slowing again. I moved to the left lane, directly behind the vehicle, and the vehicle then changed lanes to the right lane of travel of W/B MD 140 (lane 2). The vehicles passenger side tires were observed on the right shoulder fog line. Based on these observations, I conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle by activating my overhead red and blue flashing lights. The vehicle continued to swerved/ drift side to side within lane 2, but did not immediately pull over. The vehicle then turned on its flashing hazard lights, but did not pull over to the right or stop immediately (continued for another 15 seconds). I activated the patrol vehicle siren, and the vehicle finally moved to the right shoulder and stopping (total of approximately 37 seconds and low speed). I was able to observe the driver was the sole occupant of the vehicle. The weather was clear and approximately 65 degrees Fahrenheit.  Phase II: Contact  I approached the vehicle on the drivers side. As I was approaching the vehicle, I could see the driver light a cigarette as both driver side windows were down. I made contact with the driver at the drivers window. I identified myself, advised the stop was being recorded, and stated the reasons for the stop. I asked the driver for the vehicles registration card and his drivers license. The driver handed me his Maryland ID card. I asked if there was a reason the card said Identification Card, and not Drivers License. The driver advised it was due to him not having a license. I advised if that is the case, he cannot be driving and would need to call a ride. The MD ID card identified the driver as CORY ALEXANDER JONES. The driver was able to locate the Virginia Temporary License, which did show expired as of 10/10/2023. The driver asked to use my phone to call someone to pick him up. While speaking with the driver, I made the following observations:  -slow speech -strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from the passenger compartment of the vehicle  I returned to my patrol vehicle to enter the drivers information for the business needs of the traffic stop. The vehicles registration status was confirmed as expired by MSP Westminster dispatch. The driver was waiving at me, so I made contact with him again. The driver asked if he could use the bathroom. I advised he could not at this second, and I obtained a phone number to call for a ride. I called the number and left a voicemail, requesting they call him on his cell phone. The driver had a security lockout on his phone for approximately 2 hours. The drivers license was confirmed by MSP Westminster dispatch to be ID only, with a suspended privilege. I advised the driver I left a message and the driver threw out a cigarette butt. I had the driver exit the vehicle to pick it the litter to avoid a littering charge.  While speaking with the driver again, I continuously noted the following:  -strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath and person -slow slurred speech -eyes glassy  The driver was constantly smoking cigarettes and eating pistachios. Based on my observations of the driver and the vehicle in motion, I made the decision to administer the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  Phase III: Pre-Arrest Screening  Outside the vehicle, the driver asked if he could use the restroom. As there were none available in the immediate area, I advised not at this second. The driver reiterated several times that he needed to urinate badly, saying I really gotta piss.  I asked the driver the following questions:  Q. Have you had anything to drink as far as alcohol is concerned? A. No, despite swaying, the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath and person, glassy eyes, and slurred speech.  Q. Are you diabetic? A. No.  Q. Do you wear contacts or glasses? A. No.  Q. Have you consumed anything that would be considered a controlled substance, this would include (but not be limited to) heroin, marijuana, cocaine, methamphetamine, or anything like that? A. No, sir.  Again, the driver stated he had to urinate.  Q. Do you have any physical issues that would prevent you from standing on one leg for approximately 30 seconds or walking a straight line heel touching toe? A. No, sir.  While speaking with the driver, I observed the following:  -strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath and person -glassy eyes -swaying front to back and side to side -slurred speech  SFSTs: All tests were explained and demonstrated prior to asking the driver to attempt them. The tests were conducted in a flat, well-lit area, free of debris. The driver was wearing a black sandals, green pants, and green t-shirt. The area was approximately level and free of defects.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus:  The drivers eyes displayed equal pupil size, tracking, and reaction. I was able to observe 6 clues out of the 6 potential clues:  -both eyes lacked smooth pursuit -distinct nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes -onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degree deviation in both eyes  Additional observations:  -eyes glassy -had to be reminded to keep his head still several times -slight front to back sway -strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on breath and person  The test was interrupted as the driver became more and more agitated about having to urinate. Under the circumstances, I allowed the driver to step off of the roadway into the drainage area and urinate. I made sure the driver did not try to conceal or dispose of anything. The SFSTs were restarted from the beginning, as the driver was no longer distracted by the urge to urinate.  HGN:  The drivers eyes displayed equal pupil size, tracking, and reaction. I was able to observe 6 clues out of the 6 potential clues:  -both eyes lacked smooth pursuit -distinct nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes -onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degree deviation in both eyes  Additional observations:  -eyes glassy -slight front to back sway -strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on breath and person  Vertical Nystagmus was not observed.   Walk  Turn:  The driver conducted this test with his sandals on. I observed 7 clues out of the potential 8 clues:  -stepped out the instructional position four times  I gave the instructions and demonstrated the test a second time.  -stopped walking after 1 step to ask questions -raised arms more than 6 inches away from his body for balance -stepped offline: each step taken with his left foot was to the side and -missed heel to toe with every step of his left foot -took 17 steps for the first set of 9, 2nd set of steps not completed -incorrect turn: turned to the right (not left as instructed and demonstrated), did not leave front foot in contact with the ground during the turn  Additional observations:  -eyes glassy -strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath and person -had to stretch prior to the test  One Leg Stand:  The driver conducted this test with his sandals on. The driver indicated he understood my instructions. The driver stood on his right foot and raised his left. I observed 3 out of the 4 potential clues:  -the driver swayed side to side during the test 2 inches or more -raised arms more than 6 inches away from body for balance -put foot down once  Additional observations:  -strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on breath and person -eyes glassy in appearance -counted 1015, 1015, 1014, 1015 during the test -had to stretch prior to the test  Additional Tests: A.R.I.D.E.  Lack of Convergence:Not completed due to the drivers inability to follow instructions.  Finger To Nose: Not completed due to the drivers inability to follow instructions.  Modified Romberg:Not completed due to the drivers inability to follow instructions.  The driver was offered a Preliminary Breath Test, which he refused. Based on my observations of the driver during contact and the SFSTs, I made the decision to place CORY ALEXANDER JONES under arrest for DUI. This decision was supported by the following observations:  -STRONG odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath and person -glassy eyes -swaying throughout contact -slurred speech -the observations made of the vehicle in motion -the observations of the SFSTs (HGN, WT, and OLS)  The driver was advised he was under arrest for DUI, handcuffed, and placed in my patrol vehicle. The vehicle was secured on the shoulder of the roadway. While in the patrol vehicle, the driver nodded off/ passed out. The driver was transported to the MSP Westminster Barrack, where he was read the DR15 Advice of Rights at 0317 hours on 10/29/2023. The driver signed the DR15 at 0318 hours, refusing the intoximeter. An intoximeter operator was readily available. The driver was issued the D15, DR15A, the Notice to Right of Counsel, the Notice to Appear, and traffic citations MCF0DJH-MCQ0DJH. While in the DUI processing room, the driver nodded off/ passed out. The driver was advised not to drive without a valid license. The driver was released to a sober family member.  All events did occur in Carroll County, MD.  Case closed on arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 11:45:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/16/2023 07:50:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>FAIR</LastName>
            <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5334</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>527526</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/29/2023 02:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 05:20:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 05:20:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 09:01:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 11:49:41</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>324686</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>JONES</LastName>
               <FirstName>CORY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ALEXANDER</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/22/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/27/2021 21:26:20</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>JONES</LastName>
               <FirstName>CORY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ALEXANDER</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/22/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/27/2021 21:26:20</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4515</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Pall Mall</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21215</Zip5>
               <Zip4>6438</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.6643579</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.341873</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>949</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>MARLYN</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>ESSEX</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21221</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.45606</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.295123</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 11:49:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 11:49:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 11:49:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 11:49:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 05:20:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 05:20:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158980</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 11:57:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 11:57:26</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1N4AA6AP7GC392375</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2016</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4H</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>M75338</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>TM</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>