<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012473</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/08/2023 02:39:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/08/2023 02:39:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/08/2023 01:58:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/08/2023 01:58:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Single Vehicle ACRS DUI/PCP Blood Draw</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 02:39:15</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5951</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/22/2024 15:22:38</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I97 / NEW CUT RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>583702</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 02:39:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 07:17:34</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>583702</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I97</StreetName>
         <City>Glen Burnie</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.64122</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.12805</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11901-11906 I97 / 0-0 NEW CUT RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11801-11900 I97 / 0-0 NEW CUT RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/08/2023 02:39:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/08/2023 02:39:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/22/2024 15:22:40</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 02:39:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5951</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/22/2024 15:22:40</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car Camera Operational. Trooper #7362 BWC was functioning and in use during this incident.   DUI # P-23-034   CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING:  - National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) certified to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs)  - Certified Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator  - NHTSA Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) certified  -Northeast Counter-drug Training Center (NCTC) Drug Identification and Recognition: Dissociative Anesthetics  -NCTC Drug Identification and Recognition: Opioids  -NCTC Drug Identification and Recognition: Stimulants  - Multijuristictional Counter-drug Task Force Training (MCTFT) Introduction to Narcotics Trafficking  - MCTFT Introduction to Patrol Drug Investigation    VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)    On April 8, 2023, at approximately 0208 hours, I, Trooper Litz #7362, was traveling Southbound on Interstate 97 in the area of New Cut Road in Anne Arundel County, Maryland. While in my marked patrol vehicle, P-9, myself and Anne Arundel County Emergency Medical Services (EMS) personnel were canvasing the area in an attempt to locate an overturned vehicle being reported by passersby. While traveling Southbound, I was able to observe both the Southbound, and the Northbound traveling lanes of Interstate 97, and did not observe any overturned, parked, or disabled vehicles in the area. Upon turning around and proceeding to travel Northbound on Interstate 97, I observed EMS and Anne Arundel Police Officer Gonzalez #1910 stopped with a vehicle that drove into the guardrail, South of New Cut Road. I stopped with them, and observed a black Audi A6 bearing Maryland temporary registration T1243882, which had collided with the guardrail in the grass median of the roadway. The Audi had damage to the front, drivers side and passengers side and the drivers door was the only door that was opened. Using my training, knowledge and experience from the Maryland State Police and handling 138 reportables vehicle collisions between November 1, 2021, and April 7, 2023, I was able to determine that the tire marks in the grass leading up to the Audi indicated there was a long distance traveled between the Audi leaving the roadway and making contact with the guardrail. The damage to the guardrail, the outside of the vehicle and the lack of airbag deployment inside the Audi indicated the collision did not occur at a high rate of speed. The fact that myself and EMS personnel had been in the area looking for a rollover collision and did not observe the Audi in the median approximately 2 minutes before my arrival on scene indicated the collision occurred within a 2-minute time period prior to my arrival.       PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  Once on scene, I observed a subject walking in the grass median with Officer Gonzalez, and was eventually able to identify him by his MVA records as Nathaniel Alphonso Harrod (B/M DOB: 08/31/1977). Before I said anything to Harrod, Officer Gonzalez informed me that Harrod claimed that he was not driving. At that time, EMS personnel cleared the scene and did not transport anyone. While speaking with Harrod, I observed his pupils to be constricted and not change appropriately with various lighting situations. I asked Harrod what was going on, and he told me to wait while he continued to attempt to unlock his phone. Harrod appeared to be slurring his words and unable to comprehend simple instructions and questions. When I asked Harrod for his identification, he did not look away from his phone screen, and continued to attempt to unlock his cellphone. I then left Harrod with Officer Gonzalez as I attempted to locate Harrods identification within the Audi. I was unable to locate any identification for him, so when I returned to Harrod and Officer Gonzalez, I asked out loud Hey Nathan, what happened man? Harrod immediately looked at me and stated Nothing. I informed Harrod that his vehicle had collided with the guard rail and asked him again what happened. Harrod again stated Nothing. At that time, Harrod informed me he was the registered owner of the Audi. Senior Trooper Matthews #5973 arrived on scene to assist me.      While speaking with myself and Senior Trooper Matthews, Harrod still struggled to unlock his cellphone, was bending over at the hips often, and was unable to focus on the conversation at hand. I asked Harrod where he was coming from, to which he answered with Im coming then took a quick pause before continuing and stating Im not coming from no-where. I asked Harrod again where it was that he was coming from, to which he did not respond and again attempted unsuccessfully to unlock his cellphone. I asked Harrod where he was driving from, to which he stated he was not driving. I asked Harrod who was driving, at which point he looked in multiple different directions and did not answer the question. I asked Harrod again who was driving, this time he responded with Mario. After asking Harrod where Mario was, Harrod pointed in multiple different directions and stated I dont before quickly returning his attention to his phone. I informed my Police Communications Officer (PCO) that there was potentially another person involved in the collision that may have fled the scene on foot in an effort to be aware of any reports of a person walking along Interstate 97.      I asked Harrod if there was any reason he was struggling so much to open his phone, and asked if he was under the influence of anything. Harrod stated he was not. I asked Harrod again what was going on, to which he responded again with Nothing. While continuing to speak with Harrod, his pupils remained constricted, his words were still slurred, and he showed struggles with comprehending simple questions and communication in general. Senior Trooper Matthews approached Harrod and asked about Mario further. Harrod was unable to describe what Mario was wearing and, again, which direction Mario walked in. At one point, when asked where Mario went, Harrod pointed at the Audi. I asked Harrod if there was any reason Mario would leave the scene, to which Harrod responded with Im right here Officer. At that time, no calls had been received about pedestrians walking along Interstate 97. I asked Harrod if he had the keys to the vehicle, to which Harrod did not verbally respond, but reached down his shirt and retrieved the keys to the Audi from his necklace. I asked Harrod again where it was that he was coming from, to which he responded I wasnt. Harrod took a brief pause and pointed Southbound before continuing with Right there. Harrod eventually informed me that he was coming from Annapolis, but could not remember what happened leading up to me interacting with him.      Based on the fact that Harrod was the registered owner of the Audi, the keys to the Audi were on Harrods person, the drivers door being the only door opened on the Audi, Harrod not being able to describe the other person he claimed was driving or which direction the other person fled on foot in, Harrods inability to contact the other person he claimed to be driving, the lack of incoming calls regarding a pedestrian on the roadway, Harrods inability to explain the events leading up to or during the collision and the limited amount of time between myself and EMS personnel canvasing the area to when Harrod and the Audi were found in the grass median, I felt there was enough evidence on scene to place Harrod as the driver. At approximately 0219 hours, I felt it appropriate to offer Harrod the opportunity to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) in an effort to attempt to make sure Harrod was not operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol or any illegal substances. While still attempting to unlock his phone, Harrod agreed to the tests, and I informed him that he can place his phone in his pocket. Harrod then held his hands out and did not move. I had to tell him multiple times that he could put his phone in his pocket before Harrod responded with Ok. and continued not to move. He then asked me where he could put his phone. I informed him again that he could put his phone in his pocket, at which time he moved his phone from his right hand to his left, held the phone out and said Whatever you want me to do. Harrod then struggled to follow my instructions to put his phone in his pocket and, at one point, asked me to do it for him.    PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed in front of my marked patrol vehicle, on the left shoulder of Northbound Interstate 97, South of New Cut Road. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear. Lighting conditions were clear. Harrod appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries.Harrod was asked the following questions:  Glasses or Contacts - None  Medical Conditions - Type II Diabetes -Harrod claimed the medical condition would not hinder him from performing SFSTs  Medications - Metformin - for Type II Diabetes - Harrod claimed no complications or side effects of taking, or not taking, the medication would hinder him from performing SFSTs  Injuries - Right elbow - Harrod claimed the injury would not hinder him from performing SFSTs      HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 Clues Observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Harrods eyes, slightly above his eye level. Harrod was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes, and his eyes only, until told to stop. Before beginning, I asked Harrod if he understood my directions, to which he stated he did. Harrods pupils were constricted, but were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Harrod was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. While administering this test, Harrod did not follow the stimulus when it moved and remained looking straight ahead. Harrod had to be reminded to follow the stimulus with his eyes, both by myself and Senior Trooper Matthews, multiple times. While I attempted to have Harrod perform the test, he continued to slur his words and claimed he was cold. After that, Harrod continued to stay looking straight ahead and not follow the stimulus. Harrod then asked if he could voluntarily Blow to prove he had not been drinking. After it was explained to Harrod that he would have the opportunity to take a breathalyzer once certain tests were completed, we continued with SFSTs. Harrod was eventually able to complete the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test, which led to the results below:    1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes  2. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes  3. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes    Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was also observed.      WALK AND TURN (Could Not Complete)      Prior to Harrod performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. While I explained and demonstrated the test, Harrod was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch them heal-to-toe on an imaginary straight line. Harrod was instructed, and I demonstrated, to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. As I explained the motions of the test, Harrod was unable to hold the designated position. Harrod stated once more that he was cold, so he could not perform that part of the test. I then had Harrods jacket brought to him, and allowed him to continue the tests while wearing it. Once I began explaining the test again from the beginning, Harrod started shaking his head back and forth, audibly groaning Mhmh. I asked if Harrod was unable to make the requested movement, to which he responded with Im just. Yall got me. Im out here. Im fucked up. Im out here. Im not doing. I acknowledged Harrod, and attempted to give him the full opportunity to complete the tests. Eventually, Harrod could not perform any further SFSTs, stating once again Im fucked up.   Harrod then began to say that he was in pain and needed to lay down, at which point Harrod laid face down on the roadway. In an effort to address any medical conditions stemming from Harrods Type II Diabetes and the collision, I asked EMS to return to the scene. At approximately 0245 hours, EMS arrived on scene and re-evaluated Harrod. Harrods sugar levels were in a normalized zone and did not pose any medical concerns. At one point while being re-assessed by EMS personnel, Harrod exclaimed Fuck you. to one of the EMS personnel while they attempted to help him stand up. Harrod requested to be transported to the hospital, was handcuffed and was placed in the ambulance to be transported. While in the ambulance, Harrod began arguing with EMS personnel and decided he did not want to be transported to the hospital anymore. I informed Harrod that I would be charging him with driving under the influence of alcohol or illegal substances and that he could either go to the hospital or come with me back to the Glen Burnie barrack of the Maryland State Police for further processing. Harrod elected to come with me to the barrack.      ONE LEG STAND (Could Not Complete)  Harrod could not complete any further SFSTs.    PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)  Harrod could not complete any further SFSTs.    ARREST:    Based on the following, I had reason to believe Harrod was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol or illegal substances:  * Harrod having constricted pupils  * Harrod having slow and slurred speech  * Harrod not being able to understand simple questions and instructions  * Harrod not being able to explain events leading up to and during the vehicle collision  * Harrods performance while attempting SFSTs  * Harrod stating Yall got me. and Im fucked up.    At approximately 0303 hours, I placed Harrod in the front passenger seat of my marked patrol vehicle, P-9, per agency policy. I then transported Harrod to the Glen Burnie barrack of the Maryland State Police, and arrived to the barrack with Harrod at approximately 0312 hours.  Harrod was read the DR-15 Advice of Rights form in English, as well as given a copy to read along with. Harrod refused to read along. Harrod once again requested EMS for pain from the collision. For the third time, EMS personnel arrived on scene to assess Harrod. Upon the completion of the DR-15 Advice of Rights being read, Harrod stated that he would take the test at approximately 0343 hours. Due to EMS personnel being on scene and ready to transport him to the hospital, it was explained that he could not perform the Intoximeter test, but would be given the option to provide a blood sample for testing when he arrived at the hospital. Harrod agreed to a blood test kit.     INTOXIMETER RESULT:  Harrod accepted to take the Intoximeter test at 0343 hours, but could not do so due to pressing medical issues. Harrod did agree to provide blood samples in place of the Intoximeter test.  At approximately 0356 hours, myself, Harrod and EMS personnel left the Glen Burnie barrack of the Maryland State Police and were en route to Harbor Medical Center. Trooper Garvey #7075 met us all at the medical center at approximately 0429 hours with Blood Test Kit number P377. Harrods blood was drawn on April 8, 2023, at approximately 0500 hours. Upon Harrod letting the medical personnel draw his blood specifically for the Blood Test Kit, Harrod began refusing to sign anything further and stated that he regretted his decision to provide a blood sample. When I asked if there was any particular reason he regretted it, Harrod informed me that there wasPhencyclidine, or PCP, in his system.    Harrod was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to the care of the medical staff at Harbor Medical Center.  All events listed above occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.    Irequest this case remain open pending Blood Test Kit #P377 results.     </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 22:34:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 14:18:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Matthews</LastName>
            <FirstName>Shawn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5973</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Garvey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Killian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7075</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fuller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Swigert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4622</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Litz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Simon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7362</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501876</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19731</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:01:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 15:59:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501876</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:02:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 15:59:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501876</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:03:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 20:49:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501876</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:05:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 20:49:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501876</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:08:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 15:59:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501876</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:09:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 15:59:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501876</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16616</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16616</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:10:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 15:59:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501876</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16823</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16823</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:12:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 15:59:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501876</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:14:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 20:48:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501876</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:15:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 15:59:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501876</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:17:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 15:59:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501876</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>12</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>12</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:18:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 20:50:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 08:00:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:29</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>207105</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Harrod</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nathaniel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alphonso</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/31/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16922389E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>09/25/2018 18:08:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N354</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Harrod</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nathaniel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alphonso</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/31/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16922389E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>H630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N354</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/25/2018 18:08:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7959</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Telegraph</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>LOT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>127</SubNumber>
               <City>Odenton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21113</Zip5>
               <Zip4>0</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.687582</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.126943</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5208</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Saybrook</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21206</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4025</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.5304768</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.3281044</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>454</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7223</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/25/2018 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 16:16:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 16:16:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 16:16:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 16:16:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 16:16:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 15:58:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 15:58:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152248</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 22:33:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 22:33:12</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WAUF8AFC6HN012451</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>AUDI</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>A6</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>T1243882</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/08/2023 06:07:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/08/2023 06:07:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/22/2024 15:22:40</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 06:07:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5951</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/22/2024 15:22:40</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This stop was recorded on my Axon Body Worn Camera, and on the Axon Digital Video Camera System installed in Maryland State Police unit, J15.  LICENSE INFO: MD H-630-609-125-409, ID, NOT LICENSED              Nathaniel Alphonso Harrod B/M 08/31/1977  BLOOD KIT #P-377  OFFICERS TRAINING  EXPERIENCE (See Curriculum Vitae for detailed list):   *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (August 2011).   *Trained in Advanced Collision Investigation by Maryland State Police, CRASH Team (January 2014).   *Trained in Collision Reconstruction Specialist School by Maryland State Police, CRASH Team (March 2014).   *Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) (December 2017).   *Trained and Certified in IACP/NHTSA Drug Evaluation and Classification Training (DRE) (June 2018).  *Trained and Certified in NHTSA Standardized Field Sobriety Testing  Instructor Development Course (December 2018).  *Trained in NHTSA Drug Recognition Expert  Instructor Development Course (March 2021)  SUPPLEMENTAL NARRATIVE:   On 04/08/2023, at approximately 0158 hours, I, S/TPR S. Matthews #5973 responded to the area of northbound Interstate 97, south of New Cut Road, Millersville, Anne Arundel County, Maryland, in unmarked Maryland State Police unit, J15, for a reported overturned singled vehicle collision. I arrived on scene, at approximately 0211 hours. I observed TPR S. Litz #7362, was on scene with an Anne Arundel County Police unit. I observed TPR Litz was walking around a black Audi, next to the guardrail. I walked over the a tall black male, who was wearing blue jeans, and a red shirt. He was later identified as Nathaniel Alphonso Harrod, B/M, DOB: 08/31/1977, by his MVA record and photograph. I observed Harrod was doubled over facing the median, south of his car. He was trying to do something with his cell phone. I observed his blue jeans was halfway down and his butt was exposed. I made contact with Harrod and asked if he was okay. He stood up slowly and stated with thick, slow, slurred speech, Yeah, Im okay. He stood unsteadily on his feet. He was noticeably unsteadily swaying as he stood there and spoke to me. I identified myself and advised Harron he was being recorded. Harrod slowly and unsteadily bent over at the waist again and began lethargically trying to use his cell phone and appeared to have great difficulty. I asked him what happened. He slowly stood up, looked over at his car, and stated, I dont even fuckin know, in thick, slow slurred speech. Harrod bent over again and continued to tap on the screen of a cell phone. He stated with slow, thickly slurred speech, Im trying to open this fuckin phone. He tapped at the screen, appearing to not even know what he was doing. TPR Litz walked over and asked Harrod what happened. Harrod stated and slurred, Nothin. TPR Litz confirmed the car was Harrods and he was the registered owner. He stated he was. He doubled over at the waist again and continued to unsuccessfully tap at the screen of his cell phone. The cell phone did nothing, but was clearly on. Harrod appeared confused about the cell phone. I asked Harrod what his name was. He stated, Nathaniel Harrod. He slurred his last name so much that I had him repeat it because I did not understand him. He slurred his name again when asked. I asked him to spell his last name. Harrod began to spell his first name. I stopped him and told him to spell his last name, which he did. I asked Harrod for his date of birth and he provided it, with slow, thickly slurred speech. Harrod appeared to have difficulty speaking. I observed he had to take great effort to form the words with his mouth, which caused him to thickly slur his speech. Harrod was intensely focused on his cell phone and kept bending over at the waist, trying to work it. His fingers slowly tapped at the screen and he was unable to work his phone. TPR Litz asked Harrod where he was coming from and Harrod did not respond. TPR Litz asked Harrod who was driving. He looked at TPR Litz with a blank stare, moved his left arm up and down slowly and lethargically, and stated with slow slurred speech, Mario,   VEHICLE DAMAGE:   I walked over to the Audi to examine the damage.I observed a black Audi, bearing Maryland Temporary registration, T1243882 in the center median, next to an aluminum guardrail face. The Audi was stuck in the mud and had clearly observable linear scarps down the passengers side and drivers side of the vehicle, consistent with scraping against a guardrail face. The front of the Audi had minor damage to the right front side of the bumper. I observed the passengers side of the Audi had a long horizontal linear scrap down the side from the front quarter panel, to the rear passengers side door. The seam between the front and rear passengers side doors, at the B-pillar had a large chunk of sheet metal ripped open and bent backwards. I observed the right rear quarter panel, above the right rear wheel was dented. The front passengers side door handle was broken off and missing. The drivers seat was almost all the way to the rear for a tall driver. Harrods height was 6 feet 2 inches tall. There was no air bag deployment in the vehicle. The drivers seat belt was not locked out.    I conducted a check through METERS/NCIC and obtained Harrods Maryland Driving Record and photograph and verified his information. I observed Harrod was only issued a Maryland Identification Card and he was not licensed to drive. I conducted a check of the vehicle registration and observed the vehicle was only registered to Harrod.     I walked back over to Harrod and asked verified if the car was his. He again was doubled over, trying to use his cell phone and work it with his hands, which was an unusual behavior. He appeared to be trying to open his cell phone, which was just a regular touch screen cell phone, not a cell phone which could be opened. He stood up and looked at me blankly. I asked him about Mario. I asked Harrod what Mario was wearing. He looked at me with a blank emotionless stare and then looked at TPR Litz. He did not answer the question. I asked Harrod what way Mario ran. He stared at me blankly again. I verified that Mario was driving and ran from the scene. His response was delayed for a few seconds and Harrod stated, Yes. I asked Harrod which way did Mario go. He pointed using his right hand and cell phone, back toward the Audi. TPR Litz advised Harrod that Mario was not in the car and asked Harrod why he would run away. Harrod appeared confused and stated, I dont know where he..... as he trailed off and gave an incomplete verbal response. TPR Litz asked Harrod if he knew why Mario would run away. Harrod slurred and stated, I dont........Im right here officer. Harrod continued to focus on trying to open his cell phone, which was not designed to open, and bend over at the waist as we spoke with him. TPR Litz asked him again why the driver would run away. Harrod stood up slowly and unsteadily and stated, I dont ...... Harrod gave another incomplete verbal response.    I walked back over to the vehicle to see where the key was. I observed the hood was cold. I observed the drivers side door was open. The drivers seat was almost all the way back. I walked back over to Harrod and TPR Litz and asked Harrod if he knew where the key fob was. Harrod stated he gave it to TPR Litz. TPR Litz stated Harrod had the key fob hanging around his neck, supporting that Harrod was the driver of the vehicle.     TPR Litz requested Harrod to submit to a series of Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Harrod slurred and stumbled through a response, ad stated, Its a little cold. TPR Litz asked Harrod to put his phone away and put it in his pocket. Harrod stood up unsteadily and held his hands out to his sides and appeared confused. TPR Litz advised him he could put his phone in his pocket. He stood there and stared at TPR Litz confused and asked him what he wanted him to do. TPR Litz advised him that he could put his phone in his pocket. Harrod asked TPR Litz what he wanted him to do and continued to be confused. He asked TPR Litz to put the phone him his pocket. TPR Litz advised him he could put the phone in his pocket. Harrod finally placed the cell phone in his back left pocket.    TPR Litz asked Harrod if he took any medications. Harrod stated, Metformin, but badly slurred the word that TPR Litz did not understand his response. He repeated it two more times. I clarified it for TPR Litz and explained that it is a drug for diabetics who suffer from Type II Diabetes.    TPR Litz then began to administer the SFSTs to Harrod.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN) TEST:   During the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) Test, TPR Litz explained the instructions to Harrod. Harrod stood in the instructional position stiffly and unsteadily. His hands were raised approximately six inches away from his waist, awkwardly. He instructed Harrod to follow the pen with his eyes only while holding his head straight. Harrod stared blankly straight ahead. TPR Litz began to administer the test to Harrod. I observed Harrod did not follow the pen with his eyes, as instructed. He stared straight ahead blankly. TPR Litz stopped the test numerous times and reminded Harrod of his instructions. Harrod continued to stare ahead blankly and not appeared confused. I stepped in and spoke with Harrod because he appeared to not understand simple instructions and was confused. I instructed Harrod to stand with his feet together and to just relax his hands down at his waist, normally. He slurred incomprehensibly. I explained the instructions slowly to Harrod and told him that his eyes should follow the pen for this test. I explained that these tests help us determine if a driver is okay to drive. Harrod slurred incomprehensibly again, and stated, Okay. I asked him how many alcoholic beverages had he had tonight. He stated, None. I asked him what drugs had he done tonight. He stated, None. I asked him about Marijuana. He stated, None. I asked him if he took other medications. He stated, None. I asked Harrod on a scale of 1 to 10 how impaired was he, with 1 being sober and 10 being impaired. He stated, Im not drunk. I asked him why he was having so much difficulty following simple instructions. Harrod stated because it was cold out side. The temperature was approximately 53 degrees Fahrenheit. I provided the instructions to him for the HGN Test. I asked him if he understood the instructions. He appeared confused and had a delayed response in answering the question. Harrod stated, Im a little chilly. I advised him we all were standing out in the cold. Harrod continued to try to make excuses and stumbled through spurred speech and gave incomplete response, and had great difficulty speaking. He was swaying just standing in front of us. He stated slowly with slurred speech, I understand this. I explained that TPR Litz was attempting to determine if Harrod was okay to drive. Harrod swayed back and forth. He stated with slurred speech, I dont want to say nothing crazy. Can I blow. I advised him he could but TPR Litz needed to administer the SFSTs in a standardized way before he offered a breath test. I explained to Harrod that TPR Litz needed to administer the HGN Test, the Walk and Turn Test, and the One Leg Stand Test. Harrod slurred and stated, Cause I dont know...I dont know that uh....I dont know all that. Harrod stated, Whatever you need me to do, Ill do, with thick slurred speech. I did not detect any odor of an alcoholic beverage on Harrods breath.    TPR Litz again provided the instructions for the HGN Test. He asked Harrod if he understood. Harrod stated, I underst..... He trailed off with slurred speech and did not complete the response. TPR Litz attempted to administer the test to Harrod. He again stared blankly straight ahead and did not follow the pen with his eyes.    WALK AND TURN (WAT) TEST:   TPR Litz instructed Harrod to assume the instructional position, by placing his left foot online, and then to place his right foot in front of his left foot, touching heel-to-toe. Harrod stared straight ahead blankly and continued to be confused. Harrod stated, Do what. He was moving his hands and fingers slowly and lethargically. Harrod stood stiffly and unsteadily. TPR Litz provided the instructions to assume the instructional position again to Harrod. Harrod attempted to assume the position, and felt the ground with the heel of his right foot. He did not properly assume the position and he appeared extremely unsteady. Harrod complained about how cold it was and he was unable to assume the instructional position. TPR Litz offered for Harrod to have his jacket and Harrod agreed. I went to the Audi and I retrieved a black jacket from the back seat. I checked it for any weapons and then brought it over to Harrod. Harrod put his jacket on and TPR Litz began to administer the test again to Harrod and attempted to instruct him to assume the instructional position. Harrod did not assume the position and stated with thickly slurred, slow speech, You all got me, Im out here, Im fucked up. Im not doing.... (Timestamp 23:09; 5973 Body Cam). TPR Litz continued to instruct Harrod to assume the instructional position. He initially assume it, and then immediately lost his balance, and took one large step to his right, with his right foot. (23:29). Harrod again attempted to assume the position, and immediately lost his balance. Harrod stated, Im gonna fail your tests. TPR Litz explained that he wanted to give Harrod the opportunity to go through the tests. Harrod stated, Im gonna tell you, Im gonna fail your tests. Im frai....Im frail, Im fucked up. TPR Litz asked Harrod what he was mess up on. Harrod stated he was just cold. He stated he had not eaten. He stated he was frail. Harrod stated he was fucked up. I asked Harrod when the last time he checked his blood sugar, and if he had a glucose meter. Harrod did not tell the paramedics that were out with him. He stated his blood sugar normally ran high. Harrod stated he just got out of jail. He stumbled through speech. He stated he was on pretrial release. As I was speaking with Harrod, he stood up stiffly and stumbled backward.    TPR Litz requested EMS to come back to the scene so we could have his glucose level checked. Harrod sat down on the grass. He knelt in the grass. He ended up laying down on his stomach. While we waited for EMS, I documented the damage to the vehicle with my Axon Body Worn Camera and I took seven digital photographs of the vehicle. The Audi appeared as if it was derivable if it was not stuck in the mud. There was no airbag deployment in the vehicle. The vehicle was still in drive.    Harrod laid on his stomach while waiting for EMS. EMS responded back to the scene and checked his glucose level.His glucose level was 155 mg/dL (Normal). Harrod was offered to go to the hospital. He was indecisive and would not make a decision. Harrod ultimately refused to go to the hospital. TPR Litz advised Harrod that he suspected that he was under the influence and unable to safely operate a motor vehicle. Harrod stated, Im not fucked up. He became angry and stated, Fuck you, numerous times. Litz searched Harrod. Harrod appeared to be on the nod, and falling asleep on his feet and failed to answer the question asked by EMS personnel. Harrod stated he was thankful for us numerous times.    Harrod was placed under arrest by TPR Litz and transported to the Maryland State Police, Glen Burnie Barrack for processing.     I observed the following psychophysical impairment and indicators of impairment on Harrod: *Blank Stare. *Confused *Cyclic Behavior *Disoriented *Incomplete verbal responses *Difficulty With Speech/ Non-communicative *Slow slurred speech *Slowed responses *Unsteady Walk / Stance    NARCOTIC ANALGESIC: *Depressed reflexes. *Difficulty concentrating *Droopy eyelids *Drowsiness *On the nod *Slow deliberate movements. *Inability To Follow Simple Instructions *Cold *Stiff Gait / Stance *Abnormally constricted pupils.    Harrod was ultimately transported to the hospital at his request. TPR Litz advised him of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and requested Harrod to consent to a blood test for alcohol. Harrod consented to the blood test. TPR Litz used Blood Kit #P-377 for the blood test.    It was my opinion as a trained and certified Drug Recognition Expert (DRE), that Harrod was showing signs of impairment consistent with a Dissociative Anesthetic and Narcotic Analgesic, and was unable to safely operate a motor vehicle.    On 04/10/2023, at 0508 hours, I emailed F/SGT W. Koch and F/SGT J. Choma, Maryland State Police, Chemical Test For Alcohol Unit, and requested Blood Kit #P-377 be tested for drugs and/or controlled dangerous substances after it was tested for alcohol.    This concluded my portion of the investigation.    All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 06:08:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5973</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 08:15:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>O'Connor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4785</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Matthews</LastName>
            <FirstName>Shawn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5973</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/18/2024 17:24:09</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/18/2024 17:24:09</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/22/2024 15:22:40</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE PROCESSED-REPLACE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/18/2024 17:24:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5951</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/22/2024 15:22:40</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>As of the court date on 01/17/2024, the case has been postponed for approximately the 4th time. A key witness on the defense side has been subpoenaed but has not been able to be found for service and has not shown up for court.  I request this case remain open pending court case ruling.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/18/2024 17:25:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 17:28:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derek</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5951</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Litz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Simon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7362</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>