<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-044554</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/17/2023 02:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/17/2023 02:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/17/2023 01:53:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/17/2023 01:53:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI 23-122On Sunday, December 17, 2023 at approximately 0153 hours, I observed a black Honda CR-V operating with it's high beams on upon approach to other vehicles. The same vehicle was also following too closely and then accelerated to a high rate of speed. Upon iniation of a traffic stop, impairment was suspected, SFST's were conducted and the driver was arrested for DUI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 02:56:09</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1086</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 05:15:05</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>42 MM I95 NB, ELKRIDGE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>716267</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 02:56:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 04:34:58</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>716267</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Northbound I-95</StreetName>
         <City>Elkridge</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.776541</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.187376</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/17/2023 02:56:05</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/17/2023 02:56:05</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>50</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 18:40:42</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 02:56:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The below incident was recorded on an in-car camera system, A-10. TFC Mohr is equipped with a body-worn camera (AXON Body 3 No. 00016805)  Scene Processing: Due to the nature of the incident, scene processing was not conducted. Evidence Processing: Due to the nature of the incident, evidence processing was not conducted. Training/Knowledge/Experience for TFC Mohr:    Proficiency in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) per National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) Manual-Gained during Maryland State Police (MSP) Academy (Class 145, 2016)  NHTSA Certified SFST Instructor- Gained through MSP CTAU (June 2021).  Advanced Roadside Impairment Detection and Enforcement (ARIDE) Trained in 2017 through MSP Chemical Test for Alcohol Unit (CTAU).  Attendee of 2019 DUI Conference through Maryland Highway Safety Office.  Over 100 DUI Arrests involving Alcohol impairment, Controlled dangerous substances impairment or both.  Over five years of active law enforcement officer duties including, but not limited to, traffic safety, DUI detection and DUI apprehension  Certified Traffic Safety Specialist- gained in 2018.  Certified Preliminary Breath Test Operator-Through MSP CTAU and the Office of the Chief Medical Examiner (2016).  Defendant: Eden Nehemias Hernandez Mendoza DOB: 03/05/1982 Address: 25 Bright Sky Court Owings Mills, Maryland 21117  Narrative:  FIRST TIME DUI OFFENDER PHASE I, VEHICLE IN MOTION: On Sunday, December 17, 2023, at approximately 0153 hours, I, TFC Mohr #6743, assigned to the Maryland State Police Waterloo Barracks, was on routine patrol in the area of northbound Interstate 95 and Maryland Route 100. I was operating an unmarked police vehicle, A-10. I was dressed in the uniform of the day while on patrol. My attention was drawn to the rear of A-10, when I observed a dark-colored Honda CR-V approaching my location. I observed immediately the high-beams were on as it approached my location. The SUV began following a lighter SUV in lane two of northbound Interstate 95, with the high-beams still activated. The black Honda followed the other vehicle at a distance of approximately one and a half to two car lengths while at highway speeds. I observed the light-colored SUV change into lane three of Interstate 95. Once cleared, the black CR-V immediately began to accelerate ahead of me. In order to close the distance, I began to accelerate to 112 miles per hour in a 65 miles per hour zone with minimal loss or gain on the CR-V. When I finally caught up to the Honda, I was traveling at 122 miles per hour. The Honda was traveling in lane one. I activated my emergency equipment to initiate a traffic stop on the Honda.  PHASE II, PERSONAL CONTACT: Upon approach to the drivers side of the Honda, I made contact with the driver and sole occupant. He stated that he did not speak English, however, I still explained why I pulled him over. I observed the blue High-Beam advisory light on the dashboard. I asked him in broken Spanish to hand me his drivers license. I saw him open his wallet and thumb overtop what appeared to be a Maryland drivers license at least twice. I initially observed the driver to have bloodshot and glossy eyes. He finally handed me the card and I returned to my patrol vehicle. I requested a MILES/METERS/MVA check on the driver, Eder Nehemias Hernandez Mendoza, DOB: 03/05/1962 and the check revealed that Hernandez Mendoza only had a learners permit in Maryland and not a full driving privilege. At 0157 hours, I requested a Spanish-speaking officer to respond to my location to assist. Attempts were made to contact local Spanish-speaking officers with no results, starting with Howard County Police. At approximately 0228 hours, Corporal Campos #2342, with the Anne Arundel County Police Department, arrived on scene. She was also dressed in uniform for her agency and advised her unique incident number was 2023-352885.  After Cpl. Campos arrived on scene, I returned to the Honda to request Hernandez Mendoza to leave the vehicle and step to the front, towards the bumper area. He complied with my request. I relied on Cpl. Campos to relay the reason for the stop to Hernandez Mendoza. He was made aware, and I asked him where he was coming from. During our contact, I could detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person as he spoke. I was able to detect the odor in an ambient environment, with vehicles driving by. I asked him where he was traveling from. He added that he was coming from a Christmas party. I asked him if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages prior to driving and he stated that he had consumed three beers at approximately 1900 hours the previous day. I asked Hernandez Mendoza if he could complete Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) and he advised he would.  PHASE III, PRE-ARREST SCREENING:  The tests were performed in front of Hernandez Mendozas Honda, parallel to the travel portion of I-95, on the left shoulder. The roadway surface was asphalt. The surface was flat and clear of any debris or obstructions that would inhibit satisfactory performance of SFSTs. The weather conditions were clear, with cool ambient temperatures and minimal wind conditions. Ambient light was provided by vehicle headlamps and flashlights. During the tests, Hernandez Mendoza wore a black outer jacket, a white dress shirt, dark blue jeans and brown loafer shoes. Hernandez Mendoza was explained the instructions in English, and Cpl. Campos translated the instructions into Spanish. Prior to starting the tests, He stated that he was not taking any medications or under a doctors care for any recent or chronic conditions. He stated that he was in a motor vehicle collision in March of 2023 and had contact with a doctor for it. No physical ailments were evident.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test (HGN)  During the HGN test, Hernandez Mendoza displayed six out of six possible clues of impairment. Hernandez Mendoza was prompted to look at the pen and keep his head still. Hernandez Mendoza had equal pupil size and both eyes tracked the stimuli equally.    Hernandez Mendoza had lack of smooth pursuit of the stimulus in both eyes.  Hernandez Mendoza had distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  Hernandez Mendoza had onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees, shown in both eyes.  Walk and Turn (WAT)  During the WAT test, Hernandez Mendoza displayed three out of eight possible clues of impairment:    During the instructional phase, Hernandez Mendoza broke the instructional stance twice. He had to be prompted to keep his right foot in front of his left foot, touching heel to toe.  During the test, first series of steps, Hernandez stopped after his ninth step. He failed to continue the test without delay, even after being told multiple times to continue the test as instructed.  After his ninth step, he was asking for clarification of the instructions. He placed his right foot off the line, at approximately one-half of a foot width beside his left foot.   One Leg Stand (OLS)  During the OLS test, zero out of four clues of impairment were detected.    I offered Hernandez Mendoza a preliminary breath test (PBT), which he elected to take. The result was .07 for two attempts. I gave him two opportunities to provide a breath sample because I could audibly hear him sucking on the straw instead of blowing into the instrument.  ARREST:  Based on the above observations to include: poor driving behavior exemplified by the excessive speed, following too closely, operating with his high beams on inappropriately, slow movements observed when reaching for his license, bloodshot and glossy eyes, the admission to consuming alcohol prior to driving, the odor of alcohol emanating from his breath and person and poor SFST performance, I placed Hernandez Mendoza under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at 0254 hours. I searched Hernandez Mendoza prior to seating him inside my patrol vehicle for transport back to the Waterloo Barracks. No contraband was found on his person. Cpl. Campos also responded to the barracks to assist with translation of the rest of the DUI process. After the arrival at the barracks, the DR-15, Advice of Rights form was read to Hernandez Mendoza using the online Spanish recording on the MVAs website. Upon conclusion of the reading, Hernandez Mendoza elected to take an intoximeter examination. Sergeant Gailor #1086 administered the test at 0340 hours. A result of .07 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath was obtained from Hernandez Mendoza.  As I concluded the DUI paperwork, Hernandez Mendoza was afforded the opportunity to call for a family member to drive him to his residence. The DUI processing was completed without incident and Hernandez Mendoza received all pertinent copies of his paperwork. He signed the DR-15, and the MSP Form 33, Breath Results form. He was issued numerous citations for speeding, operating a vehicle with a glaring light within 500 feet of another vehicle, following too closely, holder of a learners permit operating without proper supervision and driving under the influence of alcohol.  Hernandez Mendozas was parked and secured on the left shoulder of the interstate.  Case closed; no criminal charges filed.  All events occurred in Howard County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 04:49:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 04:52:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mohr</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6743</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gailor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zinnah</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1086</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mohr</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6743</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mohr</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6743</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534031</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/17/2023 02:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 04:32:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 04:33:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534031</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/17/2023 02:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 04:32:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 04:33:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>41</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 04:32:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 04:47:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>395489</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hernandez Mendoza</LastName>
               <FirstName>Eder</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nehemias</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/05/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/17/2023 04:19:44</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E360</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hernandez Mendoza</LastName>
               <FirstName>Eder</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nehemias</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/05/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E360</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/17/2023 04:19:44</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>25</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Brightsky</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Owings Mills</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21117</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1781</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.793497</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.431615</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>704</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6209</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 04:47:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 04:47:47</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 04:47:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 04:47:47</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 04:47:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 04:47:47</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 04:47:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 04:47:47</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 04:32:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 04:32:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159919</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 04:48:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 04:48:13</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5J6RM4H77FL004942</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CR-V</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9FG7826</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>