<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-038224</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/30/2023 10:14:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/30/2023 10:14:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/30/2023 09:06:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/30/2023 09:06:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Domestic complaint leading to an Extreme Risk Protective Order.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 10:14:51</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5162</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:32:53</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>EPRO</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>Incident occurred at the complainant's home and was reported at MSP Prince Frederick Barrack</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>711650</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 10:14:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/24/2023 15:57:46</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>711650</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>419</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Rachaels</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Prince Frederick</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20678</Zip5>
         <Zip4>4163</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.573409</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.532622</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/30/2023 10:14:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/30/2023 10:14:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/23/2023 23:59:06</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 10:14:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:15</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was recorded on Body Worn Camera issued to Cpl. Okafor #5357. Scene Processing: An ERPO was obtained in this case. I responded to419 Rachaels Way, Prince Frederick and seized twenty-seven guns of various makes and calibers as well as ammunition.  The following are attached to this report: One copy (two pages) of MSP Form 93 Firearms Receipt One copy (four pages) of MSP Form 67 One copy (three pages) of MSP Form 63Property Record One Copy of Application for Charges One Copy of MGun Inquiry One Copy of ERPO Return of Service One Copy of ERPO One CD Containing two videos The victim in this case spoke to a domestic violence advocate in person prior to, and waiving the completion of MSP Form 246.   Physical Evidence: One copy of witness written statement Two digital videos One CD Containing two videos  Narrative:   On 10/30/2023, at approximately 1014 hours, I responded to MSP Prince Frederick Barrack for a domestic-dispute complaint.    Upon arrival, I made contact with the complainant, Mucciariello, Michelle Penelope, white female, DOB: 05/16/1984. Mucciariello advised that she walked to the MSP Prince Frederick Barrack from her residence at 419 Rachaels Way, Prince Frederick, because her husband, subsequently identified as Mucciariello, Chitranjan Dave DOB: 10/30/1981, deprived her of her vehicle by taking the keys to the vehicle. I provided Michelle with a Victim/Witness/Suspect form, and she submitted a written statement.   Michelle stated that on 10/29/2023, at approximately 2300 hours, while she was in bed in her bedroom, Chitranjan went to her and wanted to hang out with her. Michelle stated she refused, causing Chitranjan to get upset, calling her a bitch and threatening to kill her, her pastor and her children. Michelle stated she had left the bedroom to get away from Chitranjan when she overheard Chitranjan make that threat while he was venting. Michelle stated she later returned to the bedroom and spent the night there without further incidents while Chitranjan spent the night on a couch in the living room as was usual with him. Michelle advised that this incident never got physical.I asked Michelle how her pastor (Pastor Knoll) and the church became part of the dispute. She advised that in a prior dispute with Chtranjan, she had been compelled by the troubles at home to leave her home and move into and live at the church for a period of time to get away from Chitranjan. Michelle advised that Chitranjan was also a member of the church up until the time she went to dwell at the church. Michelle stated that Chitranjan fell out with Pastor Knoll because Chitranjan believed that Pastor Knoll should not have permitted her to live at the church.   Michelle stated she had been involved in similar disputes with Chitranjan in the past, including one incident in which Chitranjan displayed a handgun to her threateningly. I asked Michelle if she reported that incident to the police. She stated No, but that she had reported a different prior domestic incident to CCSO and nothing happened.   I asked Michelle if there were firearms in the house. She stated that Chitranjan possessed multiple firearms and had a valid concealed-firearms carry permit. I promptly contacted the Maryland Gun Center (MGun) and confirmed that Chitranjan possessed twenty-two firearms with a valid permit. MGun further advised that Chitranjan had no active restraining orders.   By my assessment, I firmly believed Michelle was in a potentially lethal situation and would be rated high-danger in lethality assessment. I asked Michelle of the whereabouts of Chitranjan. She advised he was at home. For urgency reasons, I advised her not to go back home, and to promptly respond to the Calvert County Commissioners Office and apply for a protective order. I also advised her to speak to a domestic violence advocate (domestic violence hotline personnel) while there. I provided Michelle with a Maryland Crime Victim/Witness Rights pamphlet and explained to her the proper procedure for obtaining a Protective Order and for obtaining the appropriate domestic violence counseling services. I closely monitored Michelles progress. At approximately 1203 hours, I contacted Michelle by phone, and she advised that she was still at the commissioners Office and had been granted a protective order, which would be forwarding to the CCSO for service. Michelle also advised that she spoke with a domestic violence advocate while at the commissioners office and that she was receiving advice. I advised Michelle again not to return home while this incident was going on. She assured me she would find somewhere to go.   Upon conclusion at the commissioners office, at approximately 1300 hours, Michelle responded back to the barrack accompanied by Deputy Weems #2434, of the CCSO. She provided me a video from her cellphone in which Chitranjan appeared impaired while carrying a handgun recklessly with his right hand. She also provided another video ofChitranjan slapping her cellphone out of her hand to stop her from recording. Given all the above evidence, I applied for, and obtained an Extreme Risk Protective Order against Chitranjan, in favor of Michelle. I also filed an application charging Chitranjan with Second Degree Assault.  At approximately 1840 hours, I, accompanied by TFC Bauer #6719, ST Rucker #6120 and Tpr. Sivic #7673 responded to 419 Rachaels Way, Prince Frederick and made contact with Chitranjan and served the ERPO. A deputy from CCSO also responded to that address to serve the protective order granted to Michelle. Upon our arrival, Chitranjan appeared intoxicated and emitted a strong odor of alcohol from his breath as he spoke. He declined to sign receipts to the ERPO and the protective order. He also initially denied having any guns in the house but later changed his mind and took us upstairs to a locked safe. He unlocked the safe revealing multiple guns and ammunition. In total, twenty-seven guns of various calibers and makes were recovered from Chitranjans residence. Chitranjan was on scene and that information was confirmed with him. Given that Chitranjan was being removed from the residence per the protective order; given the quantity of the seizure, and also the time of day, a receipt (MSP Form 93) could not be provided to him prior to his eviction. I received his temporary address, and he was advised that the receipt would be prepared and provided to him at the address. Subsequently, Chitranjan secured the doors to the residence and handed me the keys, then left the residence in compliance to the protective order.  At approximately 2003 hours, Michelle responded to the residence and took custody of the keys. She requested that I escort her to the Marriott Hotel at 75 Sherry Lane, Prince Frederick to get her children. She advised that her husband had checked into the same hotel. I escorted her to the hotel and witnessed her check out of the hotel with her children at approximately 2024 hours without making contact with Chitranjan and without any incident.  All seized items were subsequently transported to the Prince Frederick Barrack and processed according to MSP Policy. Copies of the MSP Form 67 and PH are attached to this report.  At approximately 2219 hours, Michelle contacted the barrack and stated that Chitranjan made phone calls to her in violation of the protective order served on him earlier that evening. Tpr. Sivic and TFC Bauer responded to the Marriott Hotel at 75 Sherry Lane, Prince Frederick and arrested Chitranjan for violation of protective order. Upon contact with Chitranjan, the troopers observed very pronounced clues of high level of alcohol impairment. Based on that observation, Chitranjan was transported to CHMC for medical evaluation. Upon arrival, CHMC made a determination that Chitranjan would be admitted for extended treatment. Chitranjan was released to the care of the hospital.  On 10/31/2023, at approximately 0025 hours, upon conclusion of medical treatment and release from the hospital, Chitranjan was transported to CCDC. He was provided with all relevant paperwork including the MSP Form 93.  I recommend that this case remain open pending the determination of the temporary ERPO, the Protective Order, and the application of charges.   All events occurred in Calvert County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 14:33:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 06:01:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hunt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kemery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5162</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruth</LastName>
            <FirstName>Casey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6188</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Okafor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Oliver</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5357</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>527687</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>01</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4D</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/30/2023 09:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4d</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 03:44:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 03:49:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>42</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>C</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 09:48:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 04:00:12</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393044</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mucciariello</LastName>
               <FirstName>Chitranjan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dave</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/30/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 09:44:19</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M264</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C365</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mucciariello</LastName>
               <FirstName>Chitranjan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dave</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/30/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M264</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C365</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 09:44:19</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>419</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Rachaels</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Prince Frederick</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20678</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4163</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.573409</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.532622</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>798</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1809</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5357</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 04:00:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5357</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 04:00:12</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5357</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 04:00:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5357</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 04:00:12</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 09:56:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 03:59:07</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393046</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mucciariello</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michelle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Penelope</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/16/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 09:55:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M264</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mucciariello</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michelle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Penelope</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/16/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M264</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 09:55:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>419</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Rachaels</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Prince Frederick</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20678</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4163</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.573409</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.532622</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>379</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3554</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>R</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5357</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 03:59:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5357</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 03:59:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5357</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 03:59:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5357</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 03:59:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 09:59:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/24/2023 16:39:49</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>15</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>605</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256572</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>27</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/09/2023 06:04:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/09/2023 06:04:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/23/2023 23:59:06</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5357</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 06:04:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:15</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 11/02/2023 at approximately 1510 hours, Trooper Miguel-Hernandez #7266 responded to Calvert County Detention Center located at 325 Stafford Rd, Prince Frederick, Maryland, where Chitranjan was already in detention, and served him with an Arrest Warrant. Chitranjan was retained in detention.  I request this case remain open pending the determination of the ERPO.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/09/2023 06:05:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/09/2023 06:05:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hunt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kemery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5162</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Okafor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Oliver</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5357</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/19/2023 10:13:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/19/2023 10:13:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/23/2023 23:59:06</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5357</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/19/2023 10:13:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:15</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>All determinations related to ERPO, Protective Order, and Application for Charges, in this case, have been made by the court and available on the Maryland Case Search.  Case closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/19/2023 10:14:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/19/2023 10:22:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruth</LastName>
            <FirstName>Casey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6188</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Okafor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Oliver</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5357</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>