<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011828</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/03/2023 01:19:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/03/2023 01:19:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/03/2023 00:45:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/03/2023 00:45:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>1st Degree Assault / MDOP</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 01:19:26</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2637</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/04/2023 15:15:49</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>MDOP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>689436</AddressId>
      <City>MDC146</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 01:19:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 02:56:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>689436</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>180</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Delancy</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Elkton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.791782</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.610738</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/03/2023 01:19:24</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/03/2023 01:19:24</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>Y</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/03/2023 05:44:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 01:19:27</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:26</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police North East Barrack. Marked patrol F-26 has an operable mobile recording device. Tpr. Jones #7445 has an operable body worn camera system.  Attachments: Multiple still photographs of damaged vehicle and deck. Still photographs of seized screwdriver and shell casing. Written statement from Dileonardi. Uploaded surveillance videos.  Scene Processing: Took multiple still photographs of the damaged vehicle, wooden stairs to the homeowners deck and the railing of the deck. Packaged and submitted both the screwdriver and shell casing into evidence.  Neighborhood Check: 170 Delancy Rd. Elkton, MD 21921 Has ring cameras. Does not record.  See supplement from TFC. Nagovich documenting the several neighborhood checks he made.  Narrative:  On 04/03/2023 at approximately 0045 hours, I, Trooper Jones #7445 of the Maryland State Police - North East Barrack was on duty and dispatched to 180 Delancy Rd, Elkton, MD 21921 in reference to an attempted robbery involving a gun.  Upon arrival, I made contact with the victim who I was able to identify through his State of Maryland Drivers License as Antonio Vincent Dileonardi (W/M, DOB: 10/14/1988). It is noted at this time, the only involved party on-scene was Dileonardi. Dileonardi advised the multiple suspects had fled prior to my arrival. I then asked Dileonardi what happened. He advised he returned home from being out approximately one hour prior to calling 911 at 0045 hours. Dileonardi stated he was inside his home making food when he noticed there was motion detected at the front of his house through a surveillance camera app on his cellular phone. Dileonardi continued by explaining when he saw the detected motion on his phone, he opened the app and observed 2 male subjects standing at the rear bumper of a parked vehicle in his driveway. Dileonardi then advised he saw an SUV backing down his driveway when he stepped out onto his front porch and yelled to the suspects. At this time, Dileonardi stated he believed he saw 3 suspects at his vehicle which was a green, Jeep Track Hawk bearing Pennsylvania registration KRP1693, but did not know how many were inside the SUV that backed down his driveway. I asked Dileonardi if he was the registered owner of the vehicle, and he stated he was not and that it belonged to a customer of his. I later ran the registration plate through the NCIC database and was able to identify the owner of the vehicle to be a Katelyn Marie Miller. After yelling at the suspects, Dileonardi advised the 3 suspects he saw started to run away when he observed one of the suspects turn and face him while in the driveway and point his arm in his direction. I asked Dileonardi if he saw a weapon in the suspects hand, and he stated he did not, but assumed if he was pointing his arm in his direction there was possibly a gun in his hand. Dileonardi then advised as soon as he saw the one suspect turn and point his arm at him, he heard a loud bang which he claimed to have been the sound of a gunshot. Dileonardi stated the gunshot was very distinct, and he knew without a doubt that was what he heard. I then asked Dileonardi if he saw a muzzle flash, and he advised he did not. I asked if he heard a secondary noise after the gunshot such as the possible bullet striking his house. Dileonardi advised he did not hear anything hit his house nor did he see any bullet holes in the house as well. Dileonardi was then asked what happened after he heard the gunshot, and he stated he took cover behind the siding/wall on his porch. Dileonardi then informed me when he first came outside, due to the number of unknown subjects in his driveway, he grabbed his personal firearm from within his residence. I asked Dileonardi if he fired any rounds back at the suspects once he heard the gunshot, and he stated he did not because they were running away, and he was not sure if he could shoot back. While speaking with Dileonardi, another trooper on scene had located a flat head screwdriver with a red and black grip on the ground a few feet from the vehicle. Dileonardi indicated the suspects were possibly using the tool to steal the Jeep and advised that the vehicle is one of the popular makes and models that have been stolen lately. Dileonardi also indicated that the screwdriver was not his and he had never seen before.  While speaking with Dileonardi, I observed there to be 2 cameras on the outside of his residence. I asked Dileonardi if they recorded the incident, and he replied that he would look on the app to see if he had any video showing what occurred. After a few minutes of searching, Dileonardi was able to find 2 videos. 1 video was from when he stepped out onto his front porch and the second video was on the deck which was directly above the driveway. I asked if I could view the videos and the Dileonardi allowed me to take possession of his phone to view them. The first video I watched was at the front door of the residence when Dileonardi stepped out onto his porch after seeing the unknown suspects. I observed Dileonardi standing at the top of the steps on his porch with an unknown make and model pistol in his right hand. I then heard Dileonardi yell to the suspects fuck yall doing? immediately followed up with the sound of a gunshot going off. In the video I could see the Jeep that the suspects were attempting to steal and what looked to be one of the unknown suspects standing at the rear bumper of the vehicle. Once the gunshot was heard, I observed a suspect exit the drivers seat of the Jeep and run away as well as the SUV that originally backed down the driveway speed off and flee the area. The second video I observed showed the camera over top of the deck on the side of the house where the driveway is. In that video, it started out with two male suspects standing behind the Jeep and what looked to be attempting to push the vehicle up the driveway. After a few seconds of the video playing, I observed a third suspect enter the screen from the right and walk up to the two suspects behind the Jeep. As the third suspect got closer to the camera, I noticed he was armed with what appeared to be an unknown make and model pistol. A few seconds later, the armed suspect left the two suspects trying to push the vehicle and ran back up the driveway in the direction he originally came from.  After viewing the surveillance videos, I then looked at the damage to the vehicle and Dileonardis deck. I observed the right rear bumper of the vehicle had damage from when the vehicle was put in neutral and rolled back into the deck once Dileonardi caught the suspects on his property. I also observed the rear passenger window had been busted which Dileonardi stated he heard as he opened the motion notification on his phone. Along with the damaged vehicle, I observed the railing and steps to Dileonardis deck was damaged as well due to the vehicle drifting back into it. I asked Dileonardi if he knew how much it would cost to repair the damages done to both the vehicle and deck. Dileonardi advised the vehicle in total would cost approximately $4,000 and the deck would cost approximately $500 to repair. Once I documented the damages, I asked Dileonardi if he noticed any damages to the inside of the vehicle since the suspects were able to gain access inside it. Dileonardi stated the suspects did not damage anything, but the one suspect who was in the drivers seat had taken off a glove he was wearing and left it behind as he ran away. I walked over to the drivers side door and instantly observed a black and gray utility glove sitting on the door panel. Dileonardi denied ever owning a glove like that and stated it was not there when he returned home for the evening.  Due to Dileonardi claiming he heard a gunshot go off, myself and several other troopers canvassed the immediate area for any shell casings. While searching, TFC. Nagovich alerted us all that he had located a brass shell casing on the concrete a few feet from the driveway. Once I responded to where he located the shell, I observed the location to be indicative of where the armed suspect ran once they were confronted by Dileonardi. At that point, both the screwdriver and shell casing was packaged and secured inside my patrol car to be transported back to the barrack for processing.  Dileonardi was then provided with a Maryland State Police Informational Brochure. On the brochure, I provided him with my name and case number for this incident and I advised Dileonardi to contact me with any additional information he may come across pertaining to this case.  All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 03:09:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 04:48:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eby</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6656</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rafer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Luke</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6709</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nagovich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Valentine</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6919</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Black</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0343</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jones</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7445</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501231</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1420</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/03/2023 00:45:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1420</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 02:59:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 02:59:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501231</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>CO193</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/03/2023 00:45:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>CO193</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 03:01:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 03:01:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 03:07:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:21</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>138875</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dileonardi</LastName>
               <FirstName>Antonio</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/14/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/11/2017 08:53:41</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D456</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dileonardi</LastName>
               <FirstName>Antonio</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/14/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D456</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/11/2017 08:53:41</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1007</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Foxwood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21221</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.45283</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.297169</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>180</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Delancy</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Elkton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.791782</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.610738</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>925</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7506</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/07/2018 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>798</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0788</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/11/2017 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 03:07:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>R</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 03:07:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 03:07:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 04:56:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373270</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Miller</LastName>
               <FirstName>Katelyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 04:55:53</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K345</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Miller</LastName>
               <FirstName>Katelyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <SLastName>M460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K345</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 04:55:53</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1879</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Arthurs</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Shiloh</City>
               <StateCode>PA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>17408</Zip5>
               <Zip4>6343</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.784708</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.986476</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 04:56:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151584</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>VI</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 04:52:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 04:52:13</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C4RJFN91JC284057</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2018</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRN</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRN</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>PA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>KRP1693</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>4</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehicleValue>4000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 05:05:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 05:05:54</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Wooden steps and railings to victims deck attached to residence.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>835</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>500</PropertyValue>
         <Value>500</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>246561</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 05:07:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 05:07:52</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Right rear bumper and passenger window damaged from suspects.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>821</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>4000</PropertyValue>
         <Value>4000</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>246562</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>GRN</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>Jeep</Make>
         <Model>Track Hawk</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 05:13:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 05:13:03</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One 9mm shell casing from unknown make and model pistol</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>999</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>1</PropertyValue>
         <Value>1</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>246563</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>GLD</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>BRZ</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>Blazer</Make>
         <Model>Brass</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 05:14:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 05:14:01</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Black and red flathead screwdriver</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>800</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>10</PropertyValue>
         <Value>10</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>246564</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>RED</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>unknown</Make>
         <Model>unknown</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 05:14:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 05:14:58</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Black and gray utility glove</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>510</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>10</PropertyValue>
         <Value>10</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>246565</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>GRY</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>unknown</Make>
         <Model>unknown</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/03/2023 04:19:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/03/2023 04:19:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/03/2023 05:44:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6919</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 04:19:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:26</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On Monday 04/03/2023 at approximately 0045 hours, I, TFC Nagovich 6919 of the Maryland State Police North East Barrack, conducted a neighborhood check for residences with external video surveillance systems. I contacted the following residences:   340 East Village Rd, Elkton, Maryland 21921     Resident: Noemi Recio, 443-504-7629   Recio had a surveillance camera facing the area of interest; however, a tree obstructed the cameras line of sight. Recio was advised to contact the Maryland State Police North East Barrack of new findings.   Recio stated she heard one gunshot, a car collision, and a strong engine acceleration approximately an hour before law enforcements arrival.   Recio noted a suspicious encounter with two white adult males walking in the area at approximately 1700 hours. These two unknown adult males were never seen in the neighborhood and seemed to be surveilling the area of interest.      346 East Village Rd, Elkton, Maryland 21921     Resident: Jeanie Baeder, 302-690-8389   Jeanie had an image of poor quality from her video surveillance system. The image displays a dark colored SUV, and five adult males gathered near the SUV before the incident.   Jeanie noted there was also a black Dodge Charger present at the time. Two of the five adult males initially came from the Dodge Charger.      All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6919</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 04:20:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6919</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 04:22:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Black</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0343</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nagovich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Valentine</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6919</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>