<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011113</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/28/2023 16:40:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/28/2023 16:40:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/28/2023 15:28:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/28/2023 15:28:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The complainant advised she received a small business loan in 2020 and in the course of her interactions with the lender and a third party she was the victim of fraud.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 16:40:04</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5974</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 04:14:27</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FRD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>531711</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 16:40:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 03:19:09</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>531711</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>27725</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Three Notch</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Mechanicsville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20659</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-76.720207</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.42952</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>THE USED CAR FACTORY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/28/2023 16:40:02</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/28/2023 16:40:02</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/07/2023 04:14:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 16:40:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5974</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 04:14:27</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>SCENE PROCESSING:  Attached to this report are numerous documents pertaining to the communication, and financial transactions between the complainant, the lender, and the suspect.  OFFICER EXPERIENCE:   I, TFC R. Backus #6648, am a sworn police officer currently assigned to uniformed patrol with the Maryland State Police, Prince Frederick Barrack, located at 210 Main Street, Prince Frederick, Calvert County, Maryland. I have more than 7 years of law enforcement training and experience conducting Criminal and Controlled Dangerous Substance (CDS) investigations, and CDS detection while on uniformed patrol. I received training in the laws pertaining to Constitutional Law, including, but not limited to, the laws pertaining to Search and Seizure. I have arrested and participated in the successful prosecution of several individuals for violating Marylands Criminal laws in both the District and Circuit Courts of Calvert County, Maryland. I have testified in cases before the District and Circuit Courts of Calvert County, Maryland, leading to the conviction of the defendants. Through all of this training and experience, I am familiar with different variations of the use, packaging, and distribution of Controlled Dangerous Substances. I have also conducted countless traffic stop roadside interviews. That accumulative experience, as well as my training, grants me the ability to recognize criminal indicators, nervousness, and signs of deception during brief personal contacts. I know that signs of deception and nervous behavior tends to be present when someone is trying to conceal their involvement in criminal activity. I know that my observations, as a totality of circumstances, can establish a reasonable articulable suspicion that criminal activity is present.  NARRATIVE:   On March 28, 2023 at approximately 1530 hours, I was on uniformed patrol in my unmarked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle, U-25. I responded to the State Police Barrack in Prince Frederick, located at 210 Main Street, Prince Frederick, MD 20678, for a report of fraud.   I made contact with the complainant, Christina Zinn Corson (W/F DOB 4/15/1962). Corson advised in 2020 she contacted the suspect Jeff Sosna (W/M DOB 8/17/1967) to apply for a small business loan. Corson advised Sosna connected her with FMS Advance to facilitate the loan. Corson advised during the height of the Covid-19 Epidemic, she was unable to make payments for a period of time when businesses were shut down. Corson advised after not making payments for a period of time she was contacted by Sosna who advised her she needed to start making the payments directly to him and not to FMS Advance. Corson advised she was contacted by FMS advance and notified that she was in default on her loan and the money she was paying directly to Sosna was not going towards her loan. Corson advised she paid approximately $15,000.00 to Sosna after he instructed her to pay him directly for the loan and not pay FMS Advance. Corson advised after she was notified by FMS Advance that she was in default on her loan she paid the balance of the loan.    I made contact with Sosna via telephone. Sosna advised me that when Corson contacted him for a loan she was originally denied by FMS Advance, and it was only after he vouched for her that they were able to grant her the loan which then made him responsible for the loan. I asked Sosna if that meant he was a co-signer on the loan. Sosna advised he was not a co-signer, he simply vouched.   Sosna advised he had gentlemens agreement with FMS Advance that he would be paid a referral fee out of the interest Corson paid on her loan. Sosna advised when Corson stopped paying on her loan he stopped receiving money from FMS Advance. Sosna advised the money he received from Corson was not repayment of the loan, but the money he was owed for his referral fee. Sosna advised he would contact Corson and workout a way to repay the money he received from her.   I made contact with Corson who advised if Sosna repaid her money she did not want to pursue criminal charges.  Case closed. All events occurred in the United States. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6648</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 04:44:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6648</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 03:23:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Palumbo</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5974</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Backus</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6648</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>55</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6648</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 03:23:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373428</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sosna</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jeff</FirstName>
               <DOB>08/17/1967 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 03:23:07</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J100</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sosna</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jeff</FirstName>
               <DOB>08/17/1967 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J100</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 03:23:07</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>561</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>488</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7477</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6648</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 03:23:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>60</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6648</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 03:33:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:26</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373431</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Corson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christina</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Zinn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/15/1962 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 03:32:53</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Corson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christina</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Zinn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/15/1962 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 03:32:53</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2425</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Garrity</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Saint Leonard</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20685</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.495843</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.417222</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>298</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5665</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6648</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 03:33:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>