<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-035322</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/08/2023 03:43:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/08/2023 03:43:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/07/2023 17:55:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/07/2023 17:55:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Shooting on Bowie State University Campus</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 03:43:24</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/04/2024 12:08:28</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>College Campus</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>110764</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 03:43:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 11:18:07</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>110764</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>14000</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Jericho Park</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Bowie</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20715</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.757842</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.019713</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>BOWIE STATE UNIVERSITY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/08/2023 03:43:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/08/2023 03:43:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 03:43:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>CED Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>INVESTIGATOR: Sergeant B. Whitmore #6094 UNIT: Criminal Enforcement Division - Central South Region DATE ASSIGNED: 10/07/2023 CASE STATUS: Open FOCUS:This report captures the initial response of Troopers on-scene when the incident occurred. It also captures the investigative efforts of CED Investigators and allied agencies.  ATTACHMENTS: -MSP Form 67 (Chain of Custody) -MSP Form 63 (Property Record) -MSP Form 78 (Consent to Search and Seize) -Bowie State Police Report -MSP Form 180 (Advice of Miranda Rights)  Victim #1: Johnel Trayvon Gray DOB 04/10/2004 Victim #2: Terrence Coleman Franklin DOB 12/11/2003  Narrative:  On 10/07/23 Maryland State Police were assigned to assist with crowd control and security at Bowie State University Homecoming Festivities along with Prince Georges County Police and Bowie State University Police. At approximately 2332 hours, Law Enforcement Officers working the detail were notified of a contact shooting on campus involving two victims. Several thousand students and other individuals in attendance began fleeing the event. More attendees than expected were on the campus as the school invited other universities to include Morgan State, Towson and Coppin State. Personnel on site during the event estimated the total attendees were in the range of 5000  7000 people.  Two victims were located in front of the Center for Business along with projectiles and casings scattered on the sidewalk and adjacent roadway. Once the crowd cleared the area, the crime scene was secured by Troopers. Both victims were transported to Captial Regional Medical Center and CED Central South Investigators were contacted and responded to the scene to assist with the investigation. Subsequently, MSP was requested by Bowie State University Police to assume the investigation.  Upon contact with personnel assigned to the event, it was determined that there were two other locations where additional shots were fired. At this time, it is unknown if there are any additional shooting victims. A Prince Georges County K9 responded to the scene and conducted a scan of the area. No firearms or additional shell casings were located.  One witness remained on scene and was interviewed by CED Investigators. This yielded no additional investigative leads. A supplement of the interview was completed by Cpl Null #6149.  Bowie State University Police provided surveillance footage of the incident to investigators. During the video, several groups of people are seen walking in the area of the Center for Business and Graduate Studies. One suspect is seen displaying a firearm on surveillance footage and firing at a group walking in the opposite direction. Two victims were struck by this gunfire. Another individual who fled in the opposite direction was also observed firing several rounds towards the first shooter. Surveillance also showed one victim, later identified as Terrence Franklin removing a firearm from his person and tossing it nearby after he sustained a gunshot wound. The firearm was recovered by Troopers and secured. MSP Crime Scene responded to process the scene and collected the firearm and casings for additional processing.  Investigators responded to the hospital to interview the shooting victims. One victim identified as Terrence Coleman Franklin DOB 12/11/2003 was unable to be interviewed due to being in the middle of a surgery. The other victim identified as Johnel Trayvon Gray DOB 04/10/2004 was interviewed and provided a vague clothing description of the shooter. Gray also stated that he was in no altercations with anyone on the campus prior to the shooting. Further detail is captured in Sergeant Lanes supplement of this report.  On Sunday, 10-8-2023, MSP Forensic Sciences Division-(FSD), Crime Scene Technicians-(CSTs) completed their crime scene processing. Over 20 spent casings of different calibers, 6 projectiles, a semi-automatic handgun and the victims clothing was collected for further processing/analysis. The number of spent casings and their locations corroborate video surveillance footage of the shootings. It should be noted, the semi-automatic handgun recovered from the scene is of a different caliber than the spent casings recovered; therefore, it doesnt appear this weapon was fired during the incident. All evidence was packaged and stored per policy.At approximately 9:30A.M. the crime scene processing concluded, the crime scene tape was lifted and the area was relinquished to public use.    On Sunday, 10-8-2023 at approximately 7:00 P.M., BSU Police contacted MSP after finding a projectile had penetrated a window and embedded in the interior drywall of a hallway located inside BSU Martin Luther King Jr. Communication Arts Center. The location of the projectile corresponds with the known direction of gunfire from one of the Suspects as captured on surveillance footage. MSP FSD CSTs responded to BSU and recovered, packaged and stored the projectile for further examination/testing.  On 10-8-2023 at approximately 0346 hours, Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack units responded to the area of Maryland Route 214 and Campus Way to assist Prince Georges County Police Department with a traffic stop on a black Tesla Model Y. MSP Forestville Barrack units were advised by PGPD the driver and front passenger of the Tesla were both asleep inside the vehicle while in lane 2. PGPD also observed a handgun located in-between the driver seat and the center console. A second handgun was observed on the passengers waist band. After several attempts, the driver and passenger woke up and were ordered out of the Tesla. Both handguns were recovered without incident. Both individuals provided their Firearm Permits which were verified through the Maryland State Police Gun Center. Later it was discovered the driver and passenger, were heading home from Bowie State University. One subject also stated he was in a physical altercation where he was assaulted and led him to leave campus. Both were detained and Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Southern Region investigators were then contacted due to the very recent shooting on campus of BSU.  Their handguns were seized and later test fired after both subjects signed a MSP form 78 (Consent to Search and Seize). The test fire casings were entered into NIBIN on 10-13-2023 and both entries received No NIBIN Lead notifications. The firearms were subsequently returned to their owners on 10-17-2023. For further details see supplement completed by S/Tpr Maldonado in reference to the interviews.  On Sunday, 10-8-2023, investigators requested the status of the BSU BEEs notification asking students to share any information with police via the BSU Tips Line. A BEEs notification is BSUs mechanism for texting/notifying their student body of important information or safety related issues such as shelter in place announcements.   On Monday, 10-9-2023, CED, Central South Region, Investigators completed the final interviews of both victims. The victims were interviewed separately and the interviews were recorded. The victims cannot identify the Suspects and maintain they were in the wrong place at the wrong time. The victims said they had no altercations at any time before the shooting.The victims remained in the hospital but were expected to make full recoveries. Refer to Sgt Lanes supplement for further details on the interviews.  As previously mentioned one of the victims was found in possession of a 9mm, semi-automatic handgun. The Maryland Gun Center queried this handgun and determined it is notreported stolen, and is notregistered. The MD Gun Center determined the victim is age prohibited as he is under 21 years of age. The MD Gun Center determined this victim was charged in April of 2023, for having a loaded handgun in his vehicle  a loaded handgun on his person; however, this case has not yet been resolved and is currently in the Circuit Court of Prince Georges County MD. Since the gun isnt registered and not reported as stolen an ATF Trace investigation has been requested. The results of the ATF Trace investigation could take up to 14 days.  On 10-10-2023 at approximately 12:50 P.M., investigators recovered a spent 9mm casing from the crime scene. At the time, this was the only 9mm casing found in the crime scene. It was not located in the vicinity of where the victim was found injured or, after reviewing the surveillance, not in the area of where the victim was as the incident unfolded. The casing was packaged as evidence and transported to Sgt. Whitmore.  On 10-10-2023 at approximately 1:13 P.M., investigators recovered another spent casing in a caliber consistent with those previously collected by MSP Crime Scene Technicians. The casing was packaged as evidence and transported to Sgt. Whitmore.  On Tuesday, 10-10-2023, Sgt Whitmore met at the MSP Crime Lab and retrieved the recovered spent shell casings, projectiles and the victims firearm for transport to the ATF on Wednesday, 10-11-2023. See NIBIN supplement for further details.  OnTuesday, 10-10-2023, members of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Southern Region (MSP CED) received a tip from Prince Georges County Polices Crime Solvers (TIP Number 266-H-9436). This tip was anonymous and there is no contact information to follow up with the reporting civilian. This tip indicated it was from a Lyft driver; whom on the night of October 8, 2023 received a Lyft ride request from an account with the possible name of Jebbrel-(or some other variation). The Lyft was for pick up in the area of Pomery Road S.E. Washington, DC and drop off at the new apartment orcondo complex, on the right, off Harry S. Truman . The rider was picked up at approximately 7:12P.M. and dropped off at approximately 7:43 P.M. The Lyft driver alleges, in the Tip, during transport the rider was on the cellphone talking about the shooting at Bowie State University which occurred the night prior-(10/7/2023). The Lyft driver advises, in the Tip, while on the phone the rider states numerous times the shooter was Foot, and that he arrived in one of two cars ``full of people. Additionally the Lyft driver believed, based on the conversation that the rider was in one of the two cars mentioned. The Lyftdriver explains, in the Tip, the rider stated Foot saw people he had problems with which led to him producing a firearm and shooting first but the person he had problems returned fire. It was the Lyft drivers belief the accounts of the rider were firsthand knowledge and they were present for the shooting. The Lyft driver advised, in the Tip, that they were unsure if the Jebbrel  subject was the actual passenger or just the account holder who ordered the ride for someone else.  Investigators contacted Zel Windsor-(PGCOPD Crime Solvers) who advised they took the call from the anonymous Lyft driver. Windsor informed investigators, while the tipster was providing the information she physically typed out the details contained within the tip. Windsor further advised the tipster, could not pull up the full details of the Lyft transport, as once the transport is complete they no longer have access to it; however they recalled it was the newer apartment/condominium complex directly off Harry S. Truman Drive possibly near Central Avenue.  Investigators located numerous apartments/condominiums in the general area described. Of these, investigators determined the Everly Complex located at 97 Capital Court, Largo, Maryland 20774 most closely matched the description provided. An additional search revealed the approximate travel time from the pick-up location of Pomery Road S.E. Washington, DC to 97 Capital Court was approximately 22-28 minutes which matches the Lyft pick-up and drop-off times. Investigators conducted a search of possible residents within the Everly complex and located only one name similar to Jebbrel, (Jarelle Lynard Antoine B/M DOB: 10/20/1987). Investigators later contacted the leasing office to determine if this individual is on record for the complex.  On Thursday, 10-12-2023 at approximately 1:30 P.M., investigators, responded to the Everly Apartments located at 97 Capital Court, Largo, Maryland and made contact with Nicole Summers, assistant manager of Everly Apartments. Investigators provided Nicole Summers with the name, Jarelle Lynard Antoine B/M DOB: 10/20/1987, to see if he was a resident of the apartment complex. Nicole advised no one by that name is a resident. Nicole also checked past residents and the prospective residents lists and both were negative for anyone matching that name. Nicole also advised if Antoine was a cohabitant or was co-leasing an apartment his name would show up as well. Investigators showed Nicole an MVA photo of Antoine which she advised Ive never seen that person before. Nicole also spoke with the main leasing agent of the building in our presence and showed her the picture to which she responded Nope, never seen him. Investigators asked Nicole if she had ever heard anyone at the apartment complex go by the moniker foot, to which she replied no. Investigators asked Summers if the apartment complex had cameras and she advised yes however all the cameras are interior cameras and there are no exterior cameras. Nicole showed investigators where the surveillance camera control panel was located and allowed investigators to view the footage. Investigators identified two cameras of interest, Camera 1: main lobby entrance and Camera 16: Rear door apartment entrance. Investigators viewed Camera 1 first, 60 minutes prior to the Lyft drop off time and 60 minutes past the drop off time. Camera 1 showed a partial view of the main entrance to the parking lot of the apartment complex. Investigators did not observe any vehicle identified as a Lyft or a vehicle dropping anyone off. During the time in question two females were seen entering the lobby area one of which was an employee. Investigators then watched Camera 16, 60 minutes prior to the Lyft drop off time and 60 minutes past the drop off time of the Lyft. Camera 16 showed a couple individuals using their key card to gain access to the building during this time, some of which were walking their dog(s). Investigators did not observe anyone matching Antoines description or any visitors let in without an access card. It should be noted investigators came up with Antoines name off of an open search and nothing of substance has been corroborated to identify him to be involved in this incident or the rider of the Lyft that was mentioned in the PG Crime Solvers Tip.  On Friday, 10-13-2023. MSP CED Central South Region Investigators responded to Bowie State University and met with BSU IT personnel to gain access to missing camera footage. The missing cameras are run by a different system and are not cloud based like the ones already being reviewed by investigators. Due to an issue with accessing the VPN, Bowie State University IT allowed Investigators to sign out a BSU computer to conduct detailed reviews of any BSU cameras. Many cameras were not operational on this platform but those that are operational will be reviewed thoroughly.  After learning the Baltimore City Police Department made an arrest in reference to the Morgan State shooting, MSP CED Command provided Central South Investigators with a point of contact in that investigation. Sgt Whitmore contacted Detective Banker (BPD) and learned ATF executed a search and seizure warrant in Washington DC at a residence linked to a suspect from the Morgan State shooting. They recovered three firearms (9mm handguns). Det Banker advised their scene only had 9mm casings as well. Det Banker advised if any of his investigation correlated to this BSU shooting he would contact Sgt Whitmore.  Lt Bell-(BSU) was notified of an additional projectile located on campus near the area of the shooting. Investigators responded to seize the evidence and later transported it to MSP Crime Lab.  LT Bell told investigators she received an email from a citizen in a neighborhood adjacent to the University who wished to provide information. The tip was forwarded to Investigators for review. Sgt Whitmore made contact with the concerned citizen via the phone number provided in the email. The citizen was identified as Manford Patterson and stated he resided at 9203 Filly Court Bowie, MD. He explained he lives close enough to the University that he heard all of the gunshots on the night of the incident and multiple homecoming attendees parked in his court. Patterson said his neighbor had a home surveillance camera which pointed at the street where a suspicious group of three individuals parked the day of the incident. Sgt Whitmore responded to the neighborhood after receiving this information and attempted to make contact with the homeowner with the surveillance camera. The homeowner wasnt at the residence but Patterson provided Sgt Whitmore with his contact information. Patterson advised his wife had a picture and video of the suspicious vehicle and one of the individuals who was an occupant. Upon review of the picture, it did not appear that this individual was a suspect from the shooting. The vehicle observed was a white Honda Civic and had an MD registration of 1FP6149 which investigators conducted an MVA check on. The owner is not a current person of interest.  On 10-16-2023 received the signed Lyft subpoena from Prince Georges County SAO in reference to the Jebrrell subject mentioned in the crime solvers tip. It was promptly submitted to Lyft via their law enforcement portal.  On10-17-2023 Sgt Whitmore conducted an additional neighborhood check and contacted the resident at 9201 Filly Ct. She advised her footage did not save properly and would not be available for further review. She believed she saw individuals on surveillance around 11:32 PM so it would appear these individuals are not persons of interest as it is over a mile from the residence to the shooting location.Sgt Whitmore also contacted a resident at 14802 Arabian Lane since he also had surveillance cameras. The resident advised the camera doesnt save footage. No additional surveillance footage was recovered in the neighborhood. Sgt Whitmore provided clothing descriptions of suspects to the residents. If any other homeowners locate anything noteworthy they were advised to contact MSP.  On 10-19-2023 Lieutenant Bell from Bowie State Police Department forwarded an email in reference to screenshot of a text she received from two students. The text stated niggas talkin about lighing Bowie ip tonight so be safe slim. LT Bell provided contact information for both students and Sgt Whitmore contacted them regarding the text. Sgt Whitmore first contacted Nalani Byrd. She advised she received the screenshot from another student named Chiamaka and had no further details to assist with investigation. She provided Chiamakas number to investigators. Sgt Whitmore then contacted Chiamaka via the phone number provided. Chiamaka also stated this message had been forwarded to numerous individuals all over campus and didnt know who the original send was. The screenshot has a blurred out background and does not show any identifying number or person who sent this message. Sgt Whitmore advised both students to contact MSP if they gain any more information about the shooting.  Lieutenant Bell also forwarded a voicemail to Sgt Whitmore regarding an attendee who witnessed a subject display a firearm at Homecoming festivities. Sgt Whitmore contacted Steven Copeland who advised he witnessed a confrontation between two groups in the main area of the festivities. He described the subject as 1/M who was wearing a white shirt, black pants, short hair and approximately 62 in height. Copeland stated this subject pulled the weapon out of a satchel on 2 occasions and displayed toward the group he was having an altercation with. The time frame it likely occurred was from 1930 hours - 2000 hours. Investigators will review footage in the area but based on the description provided to investigators it is not either of the suspects involved in the contact shooting on campus.  An additional 9mm casing was recovered on campus by Investigators on 10-19-2023. It was subsequently transported to MSP Crime Lab and entered in NIBIN. It produced a NIBIN Lead Notification on 10-20-2023. It matched the casing which was recovered on 10-10-2023 in the same general area which was entered by the ATF on 10-11-2023.  For information and investigative efforts not detailed in this report see the following supplements:  Supplement #1 - Trooper Theinhom - Response to shooting scene Supplement #2 - Trooper Hershberger - Response to shooting scene Supplement #3 - Trooper Moorman - Response to shooting scene Supplement #4 - Trooper Shai - Response to shooting scene Supplement #5 - Trooper Barnhart - Response to shooting scene Supplement #6 - Corporal Null - Interview with witness on-scene Supplement #7 - Sergeant Lane - Interviews with victims at hospital Supplement #8 - Senior Trooper Maldonado - Interviews with subjects from a traffic stop Supplement #9 - Corporal Null - MARC train surveillance review Supplement #10 - Trooper Strong - Response to shooting scene Supplement #11 - Trooper Albaugh - Response to shooting scene Supplement #12 - Detective Sergeant Heath - Response to shooting scene and additional efforts Supplement #13 - Trooper Norman - Response to shooting scene Supplement #14 - Corporal Posey - 911 Call Records Supplement #15 - Corporal Null - Witness Interview  CASE OPEN </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 11:30:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6094</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/24/2023 15:12:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>3</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Surveillance Footage Review</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>INVESTIGATOR: Sergeant B. Whitmore #6094 UNIT: Criminal Enforcement Division - Central South Region DATE ASSIGNED: 10/07/2023 CASE STATUS: Open FOCUS:This supplement documents investigators efforts while reviewing surveillance from the Bowie State University Campus  Investigators have begun reviewing the footage in hopes of tracking the movements of the suspects. Preliminary observations are as follows:      Suspect#: 2-(wearing light colored blue jeans and white hooded sweatshirt) produced a handgun while walking past a group of three individuals in the area of Henry Circle and Henry Way.      As Suspect#: 2passes the three individuals, one of the three individuals identified and referred to as Suspect#: 1-(wearing black/ dark-colored clothing) produces a firearm and fires the handgun in the direction of Suspect#:2.      Suspect#:2flees from the gunshots and fires multiple rounds behind him while running up the hill on Henry Way towards Jericho Park Rd. Camera footage loses sight of Suspect #:2on Henry Way in the area of Jericho Park Rd intersection. Suspect #2then doubles back and is seen on the very bottom left edge of the surveillance footage firing additional rounds towards the direction of suspect #1at 11:33:08 PM. Multiple muzzle flashes were observed next to the tree and the majority of the 10mm casings were located in this area. Investigators believe it is the same suspect after the Crime Gun Intelligence Specialist determined all of the 10mm casings were fired from the same handgun. Camera footage loses sight of Suspect #:2on Henry Way in the area of Jericho Park Rd intersection.      Thefootage from Suspect#: 2was gathered from building #1 which is defined as the Center for Business and Graduate Studies.      Suspect #1:flees the scene from Henry Circle at Henry Way and travels in between buildings # 1-( Center for Business and Graduate Studies) and #2-(Martin Luther King Jr. Communication Arts Center) out of sight of the cameras. It should be noted that building #2 Martin Luther King Jr. Communication Arts Center only has interior cameras and Suspect #:1is not seen on this footage.      Itshould also be noted that building #28-(Entrepreneurship Living Learning Community) only has interior cameras as well, so it does not capture Suspect#:2 after he enters the intersection of Henry Way at Jericho Park Rd.    Additional supplements will document further review.    CASE OPEN    </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 13:34:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6094</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/20/2023 13:36:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>4</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>NIBIN</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>INVESTIGATOR: Sergeant B. Whitmore #6094 UNIT: Criminal Enforcement Division - Central South Region DATE ASSIGNED: 10/07/2023 CASE STATUS: Open FOCUS:This supplement documents the NIBIN results from the casings located on-scene along with the (victims) firearm. Attachments:NIBIN exhibit information  OnWednesday, 10-11-2023, I met ATF TFO Cheuvront at the Howard County Police Northern District at which point the victims handgun was test fired. Upon completion, I transported the casings and projectiles recovered on scene and the test fired casings to the ATF office in Linthicum to expedite the National Integrated Ballistic Information Network (NIBIN) entry. The casings were inspected by a Crime Gun Intelligence Specialist and subsequently entered into NIBIN for comparison. The victims handgun which was test fired earlier in the day subsequently hit on a shots fired investigation in Bladensburg Police Departments Jurisdiction.  Atapproximately 4:14 P.M., I received an email from the Crime Gun Intelligence Specialist who attached three No Leads Notification documents. Each attachment was in reference to the spent casings recovered on scene.  Insummary, the NIBIN entries produced no leads to further the shooting investigation at Bowie State University. Investigators will coordinate with Bladensburg Police Dept in the near future in reference to the NIBIN hit involving the victims handgun. It should be noted the one 9mm casing recovered on scene on Tuesday, 10-10-2023, did not match the casing of the test fire; therefore, was not fired from the victims gun at the time of the shooting.  CASE OPEN </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/11/2023 16:45:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6094</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/24/2023 15:02:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>5</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Instagram</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>INVESTIGATOR: Sergeant B. Whitmore #6094 UNIT: Criminal Enforcement Division - Central South Region DATE ASSIGNED: 10/07/2023 CASE STATUS: Open FOCUS:This report captures the investigative efforts in reference to persons of interest located on Instagram  On October 12, 2023, investigators reached out to numerous contacts at Anne Arundel County Police, Prince Georges County Police, Baltimore City Police, Washington Metropolitan Police Department, Maryland State Police SOG, and the FBI in reference to the subject referred to as Foot in the Crime Stoppers Lyft tip.  While inquiring about the Foot individual, S/A Crout of the FBI advised Washington DC Metropolitan Police Department is familiar with an individual known as Foot and further advised the following: Foot is a shortened nickname of Young Foot Soldier, a Push Dat Shit crew member and rapper. Push Dat Shit is a subset of 10th Place Killas out of South East Washington DC. He is also affiliated with Fox 5. Fox 5 is conglomerate of multiple crews in the Washington DC and Prince Georges County Area. His true name is Steven Metts (B/M DOB: 06/20/2005. He also goes by the nickname Big Steve.  A query of law enforcement and public forums revealed an Instagram account belonging to Metts. The Instagram account was identified aswww.instagram.com/realyoungfootsoldier. Metts posted a picture in his feed (Sunday, October 8, 2023) of himself and two unknown individuals in a black Chevrolet. The caption of this post is  Hop Out Blowing That Sh**Me  Bruh Got Dracs Thats My Spinning Twin  #MostWantedTapeOnTheWay. Dracs is a common slang term that references firearms. Metts is wearing a black hoodie with a design on the front, black pants, and gray tennis shoes. Metts an adult black Male, average height, slim build with similar physical characteristics to the individuals observed in the video surveillance (person of interest #1).  In the same post described above another individual is tagged in the post. This Instagram account was identified aswww.instagram.com/____gen5. Contact was made with Washington DC Metropolitan Police Department who was able to identify @___gen5 as Anthony Monroe (B/M DOB: 09/22/2006) as the account owner. MPD advised that MPD homicide is currently investigating Monroe in reference to an unrelated robbery/homicide. Furthermore, Monroe makes a feed post on October 8, 2023, wearing a black hoodie with white writing on the chest, black pants, and gray shoes. This post is captioned We get cars   Torch da city  Might hit like 2-3 hoods inna row!! Monroe is of the same physical characteristic as those observed in the video surveillance (suspect #1). Additionally, in the aforementioned @___gen5 post, a bulge appears on Monroes waist band consistent with concealing a firearm. Additionally, in the same post collection Monroe is posing inside an unidentified residence with a black firearm on the counter.  A query of Metts revealed the following criminal history: Kidnapping, threats of bodily injury, firearm offenses, and family disturbance.  A query of Monroe revealed the following criminal history: Assault on police, unlawful entry of a motor vehicle, destruction of property, firearms possession, motor vehicle theft, robbery, and theft.  A Maryland Gun Center Check was conducted on both Metts and Monroe and revealed the following: -Metts is prohibited from possessing a firearm as he is under the age of 21, a respondent of a protection order and a fugitive from justice. -Monroe is prohibited from possessing a firearm as he is under the age of 21 and a fugitive from justice.  On 10-19-2023 investigators obtained a potential phone number for Metts via law enforcement resources (202) 321-2879. It was subsequently subpoenaed for subscriber records for further investigation.  Further investigation will be conducted on these individuals until they can be identified as suspects or ruled out of the investigation.  Case Open</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/24/2023 15:02:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6094</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/24/2023 15:11:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ortiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Angel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5858</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6931</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fleming</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sierra</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7439</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shai</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7463</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweckard</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7221</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>70</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>De Santis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sabatino</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thienhom</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bryce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7518</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barnhart</LastName>
            <FirstName>Clay</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7328</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>NIKODEMSKI</LastName>
            <FirstName>JONATHAN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7510</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Estrin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6052</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Houck</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mitchell</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7577</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reyes</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nichalas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7369</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Heath</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4437</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Albaugh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Josiah</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7339</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ngoushema</LastName>
            <FirstName>Penyinema</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7453</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CVED</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Moorman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6980</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathanael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7454</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hershberger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gavin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7444</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Richards</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jerrell</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7514</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lane</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5164</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Whitmore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6094</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524782</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1420</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>52</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/07/2023 23:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1420</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 11:27:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6094</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 11:27:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 11:29:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6094</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 10:51:33</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389944</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/09/2023 11:29:25</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <DateOfInfo>10/09/2023 11:29:25</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 11:29:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 11:29:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6094</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 10:51:24</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389945</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/09/2023 11:29:25</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <DateOfInfo>10/09/2023 11:29:25</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 11:29:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>19</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/17/2023 13:03:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/17/2023 13:03:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390031</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Gray</LastName>
               <FirstName>Johnel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Trayvon</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/10/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 13:48:03</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Gray</LastName>
               <FirstName>Johnel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Trayvon</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/10/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 13:48:03</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1389</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Congress</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>SE</StreetSuffixCode>
               <SubNumber>3</SubNumber>
               <City>Washington</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20032</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5074</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.984782</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.844665</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>669</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2017</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/17/2023 13:03:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>19</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/17/2023 13:05:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/17/2023 13:05:13</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390032</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Franklin</LastName>
               <FirstName>Terrence</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Coleman</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/11/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 13:50:03</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T652</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Franklin</LastName>
               <FirstName>Terrence</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Coleman</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/11/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T652</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 13:50:03</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9703</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Summit</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>4B</SubNumber>
               <City>Upper Marlboro</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20774</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.838536</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.901978</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>467</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7040</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/17/2023 13:05:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/08/2023 04:01:08</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/08/2023 04:01:08</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 04:01:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 10/07/2023, I, Trooper Thienhom#7518, was assigned to Bowie State University Homecoming event in Bowie, Prince Georges County, Maryland.  At approximately 2332 hours, Troopers Shai#7463, Barnhart#7328, Hershberger#7444, and I were driving to Bowie State University Police Department, which was located in the area of parking lot H. As we were waiting for the gate to open, I heard multiple gunshots and observed people running away from where the gunshots were heard. I immediately activated my emergency vehicle equipment and kept driving towards where the gunshots were heard. I then observed a black male subject who suffered from gunshot wounds lying on the ground and a tan handgun next to him in the area of Henry Way and Henry Circle. The subject was later identified as Franklin, Terrence Coleman, JR (B/M, DOB:12/11/2003). Troopers Barnhart and Shai secured the handgun that was next to Franklin. We then started rendering aid to Franklin. Franklin suffered from two gunshot wounds on the back of his hip, with one visible exit wound through the front. We kept rendering aid to Franklin until the EMS personnel were able to transport him to the hospital.  This concludes my assistance in this investigation.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 04:02:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 13:58:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bowling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0392</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thienhom</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bryce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7518</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/08/2023 04:03:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/08/2023 04:03:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7444</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 04:03:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>       **** Incident captured on N-14 in car camera and MSP Issued BWC****    ATTACHMENTS: N/A  VICTIMS:  Johnel Trayvon Gray, DOB 04/10/2004 Terrence Coleman Franklin Jr, DOB 12/11/2003 EMS: Prince Georges Fire Department Ambulance 818 Run # 23100700000487  SCENE PROCESSING: CED Southern Region, as well as Crime Scene Technicians responded to the scene for processing.  NARRATIVE: On Saturday, October 7, 2023, I Trooper Hershberger of the Maryland State Rockville Barrack, was assigned to a special assignment at Bowie State University. I was in full MSP uniform operating fully marked MSP cruiser N-14 for the purpose of providing traffic control and security.The troopers on the detail were advised to report to parking lot H to shut the event down early, due to an overcrowded atmosphere. While en route to parking lot H, at approximately 2332 hours, I heard possible gunshots, which was confirmed over the radio by a CVED unit. I immediately activated my emergency equipment, and started to the sound of gun fire. While en route, I was flagged down by campus security at the intersection of Jericho Park Rd  Henry Way,Campus Security advised they had located a gunshot victim that displayed an injury to the chest. I immediately notified the officer in command, D/Sgt. Heath #4437 via radio. At that time, three Prince Georges county units had arrived, as well as Trooper Richards # 7514, of the Maryland State College Park Barrack. I then grabbed my Maryland State Police issued medical bag, and went to assess the victim. It was discovered that the victim, identified as Johnel Trayvon Gray DOB 04/10/2004, has suffered a gunshot wound to the lower right part of his abdomen/chest area. Gray also had an exit wound on his lower right area of his back/side area. Once the victim was assessed, myself, Trooper Richards and Prince Georges County Police Officers Sgt. Maxwell #3241, Cpl. Gavin #3226, and Cpl. Carvalto #4035, all assigned to Division II, applied two separate chest seals, one to the entry wound, and one to the exit wound. Once the wound was sealed, it was wrapped with an ace bandage by a PGPD officer. We then checked for additional wounds, and stayed with Gray until EMS arrived. Gray was transported by Prince Georges County Fire Department Ambulance 818 to Capital Regional Medical Center, run number 23100700000487. I then remained on scene for traffic control. The second victim, Terrence Coleman Franklin Jr, DOB 12/11/2003, received medical treatment from other responding officers until EMS arrived.     CASE STATUS: This case is being handled by CED Southern Region.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7444</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 04:04:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7444</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 08:44:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zimmerman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6514</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hershberger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gavin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7444</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/08/2023 05:07:06</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/08/2023 05:07:06</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>CVED</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6980</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 05:07:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Narrative:  On October 7, 2023, at approximately 2335 hours, I, TFC Moorman #6980, was on uniformed patrol, assisting with traffic control entering and leaving Bowie State University, located at 14000 Jericho Park Rd, Bowie, Maryland 20715. At approximately 2335 hours, I heard multiple gunshots, and car alarms going off near my location. TFC Strong #6786 and I, began running towards the area where the gunshots were heard. I noted people were screaming, and some people were running away from the area the gunshots were heard. At that time, it was transmitted on the radio that shots had been fired, and multiple victims were injured. I responded to the area of Henry Way and Henry Circle and observed one male victim lying on the ground with an apparent gunshot wound to his buttocks in front of the Center for Business and Graduate Studies. The male victim was later identified as, Terrence Coleman Franklin Jr (B/M, DOB: 12/11/2003), by his Maryland drivers license. Multiple officers were already rendering medical aid to Franklin Jr when I arrived. I assisted in establishing a perimeter around the area of the shooting for evidentiary purposes.  This concludes my assistance in this investigation.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6980</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 05:08:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6980</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 05:08:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Heath</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4437</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CVED</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Moorman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6980</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/09/2023 01:45:43</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/09/2023 01:45:43</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7463</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 01:45:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #4 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> Narrative: *Bodyworn Camera was operational and activated* On 10/07/2023, I, Trooper Shai #7463, was assigned to the Bowie State University Homecoming event in Bowie, Prince Georges County, Maryland.  At approximately 2332 hours, Troopers Thienhom #7518, Barnhart #7328, Hershberger #7444, and I were driving to Bowie State University Police Department, which was located in the area of parking lot H. While enroute to the meeting point I heard multiple gunshots and observed a large crowd of people running away from where the gunshots were heard. I immediately activated my emergency vehicle equipment and followed Troopers Thienhom and Barnhart towards where the gunshots were heard. I then observed a black male subject who suffered from gunshot wounds lying on the ground and exited my vehicle with my department issued handgun drawn at a low ready and scanned the area for a shooter with negative results. Trooper Barnhart removed a tan handgun from reach of the injured subject, and I secured the weapon and locked it in my vehicle before returning to help Troopers Thienhom and Barnhart render aid to the subject. The subject was later identified as Franklin, Terrence Coleman, JR (B/M, DOB:12/11/2003). Franklin suffered from two gunshot wounds on the rear of his hip, with one visible exit wound through the front. We kept rendering aid to Franklin until the EMS personnel were able to transport him to the hospital.  This concludes my assistance in this investigation.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7463</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 02:07:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7463</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 02:08:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bowling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0392</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shai</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7463</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>5</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/09/2023 09:59:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/09/2023 09:59:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7328</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 09:59:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #5 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*Bodyworn Camera was operational and activated* Narrative: On 10/07/2023, I, Trooper Barnhart #7328, was assigned to the Bowie State University Homecoming event in Bowie, Prince Georges County, Maryland.  At approximately 2332 hours, Troopers Thienhom #7518, Shai #7463, Hershberger #7444, and I were driving to Bowie State University Police Department, which was located in the area of parking lot H. While en-route to the meeting point, I heard multiple gunshots and observed a large crowd of people running away from where the gunshots were heard. I immediately activated my emergency vehicle equipment and drove towards where the gunshots were heard. I then observed a black male subject who suffered from gunshot wounds lying on the ground. I exited my vehicle with my department issued handgun drawn at a low ready and scanned the area for a shooter with negative results. I removed a tan Glock 19X from reach of the injured subject, ejected the thirty (30) round magazine along with removing the chambered bullet. Trooper Shai secured the weapon and locked it in his vehicle before returning to help Troopers Thienhom and I render aid to the subject. The subject was later identified as Franklin, Terrence Coleman, JR (B/M, DOB:12/11/2003). Franklin suffered from two gunshot wounds on the rear of his hip, with one visible exit wound through the front. We continued rendering aid to Franklin until the EMS personnel were able to transport him to the hospital.  After the event was shut down, Sergeant Estrin #6052, Senior TrooperOrtiz #5858, Trooper Richards #7514, and I conducted patrol checks of Jericho Park Rd, Loop Rd, and MD 197 to ensure there were no other injuries. Once the campus was secure, I set perimeter security at the crime scene for the crime scene technicians.  This concludes my assistance in this investigation.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7328</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 10:05:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7328</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 10:44:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kemp</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5753</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barnhart</LastName>
            <FirstName>Clay</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7328</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>6</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/09/2023 12:55:46</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/09/2023 12:55:46</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 12:55:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Lee'bey Interview</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*BWC was activated for this interaction*  Focus: The focus of this supplement is to document a recorded interview with Lee-Bey  Witness:   Lee-bey, Mecca Jamal     B/M DOB: 07/17/2003      Additional Information:    Greenwood, Hasimah     B/F DOB: 03/11/1984   Leebeys Mother      Narrative:  On October 8, 2023, I, Corporal Z. Null 6149 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division, was requested to respond to Bowie State University located at 14000 Jericho Park Rd, Bowie, Prince Georges County, MD, 20715 in reference to a shooting investigation.    Upon my arrival, I was requested by Sgt Whitmore, the lead investigator, to conduct an interview with a witness identified as Lee-bey, Mecca Jamal (B/M DOB: 07/17/2003). Lee-bey was seated in the front seat of a marked Maryland State Police Vehicle wrapped in an emergency blanket.    I approached Lee-bey and introduced myself. I advised him my body worn camera was activated, and he was being audibly and visually recorded. I asked him to explain to me the series of events leading to the shooting. Lee-bey advised he was picked up by a friend TJ who was later identified as Franklin, Terrence Coleman (B/M DOB: 12/11/2003) by Troopers at the Hospital. Lee-bey advised he met Franklin today; Lee-bey further advised that their relationship is through associates and living near the same area but today was the first time they met in person. Lee-bey further advised that Franklin is from Southeast Washington DC. Lee-bey described he was walking along Henry Cir near the Center for Business and Graduate Sciences Building when he heard shots. Lee-bey further advised after the shots he was either pushed or fell and began to play dead. Lee-bey advised heard multiple shots and was laying on the ground with Franklin. Lee-bey advised the area was being traveled by pedestrians and vehicles. He stated he heard a vehicle after the shots while he was lying on the ground. When asked, Lee-bey approximated 20 shots were heard in rapid succession and that the shots were close to him.    I asked Lee-bey about the firearm located at the scene. Lee-bey seemed genuinely surprised that Franklin was in possession of a firearm. Lee-bey stated he never saw a firearm on Franklin, and he would be surprised if Franklin carried a firearm. Lee-bey advised that he was never in possession of a firearm. Lee-bey provided no information of any suspects and stated he blacked out during the incident in fear of his life.    I advised Lee-bey how to contact the Maryland State Police in he had any additional information in regard to the event.    I then made contact with Greenwood, Hasimah (B/F DOB: 03/11/1984) who was identified as Lee-beys mother. I explained to her the situation and that her son was ok and did not report any injuries. I asked if she knew Franklin which she stated she did not. She further advised that to her knowledge she was not aware of fights or problems that Lee-bey was involved in. I encouraged Greenwood to speak to her son about the incident and if any information came to light that made aid investigators to contact the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack.    During my interaction with Lee-bey and Greenwood, both appeared to be honest and truthful with me.    I was able to review a short video from the schools surveillance which seemed to corroborate Lee-beys series of events. After the shots were fired, Lee-bey laid on the ground with Franklin. While on the ground, it appeared Franklin discarded a firearm which was concealed on his person. There was a black sedan that traveled passed the scene after the shooting, but it appeared to come from a different direction that the suspect ran to after the shots were fired. No other vehicles were observed during the incident.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 12:57:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 13:36:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lane</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5164</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Null</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zakery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6149</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>20</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 13:42:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 13:42:52</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389969</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lee-bey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Mecca</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jamall</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/17/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/09/2023 13:42:43</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lee-bey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Mecca</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jamall</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/17/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/09/2023 13:42:43</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1233</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Valley</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>SE</StreetSuffixCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>304</SubNumber>
               <City>Washington</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20032</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.98908</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.837415</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>427</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4865</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 13:42:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 13:47:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 13:47:46</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389970</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Greenwood</LastName>
               <FirstName>Hasinah</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>L</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/11/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.77178253E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>10/09/2023 13:47:37</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G653</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Greenwood</LastName>
               <FirstName>Hasinah</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>L</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/11/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.77178253E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>G653</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/09/2023 13:47:37</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1233</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Valley</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>SE</StreetSuffixCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>304</SubNumber>
               <City>Washington</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20032</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.98908</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.837415</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>541</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6216</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/09/2023 13:47:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>7</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/10/2023 08:52:15</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/10/2023 08:52:15</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5164</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 08:52:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle> Victim Interviews </NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Date / Time of Incident: October 7, 2023, at 2332 hours  Type of Incident: 1st Degree Assault  Follow-Up Action: Victim / Witness interviews at Capital Regional Medical Center  Interviews: 1) Johnel Trayvon Gray (Victim #1) DOB: 04/10/2004 (19 years old) 1389 Congress St Apt 3 SE, Washington DC 202-669-2017  2) Tanika A. Gray (Johnel Grays mother) 1389 Congress St, APT 3 SE, Washington DC 240-795-2584  3) Terrence Coleman Franklin MD-10273536572 DOB: 12/11/2003 (19 years old) 9703 Summit Cir Apt 4B, Largo MD. 20774 240-467-7040  4)Monique Shante Bell (Terrence Franklins mother) 9703 Summit Cir, Apt 4B, Largo MD 20774 301-605-0045  5)Trayona Buchanan 3407 13th Place SE, Washington DC 202-743-9229  Attachments: 1) BWC recordings on October 8 and October 9  Narrative: On October 8, 2023, shortly after midnight I was notified of an active 1st degree assault investigation ongoing at Bowie State University and responded to assist. I was subsequently requested to respond to Capital Regional Medical Center located at 901 Harry S. Truman Dr, Largo MD 20774 to make contact with victims of this incident.  Upon arrival at approximately 0120 hours, I made contact with EMS units and identified the units who transported the victims.  1) Terrence Franklin - PG County Fire / EMS Unit 819, run number 231007000000487 2) Johnel Gray - PG County Fire / EMS Unit 818, run number 23100700000487 and 23100700000482  I was notified that there were two victims of this shooting, one party who had an injury to their torso / chest area and one who was injured in their lower back or legs. One victim was receiving ongoing treatment and taken to surgery before I was able to make contact with him, although he was later identified as Terrence Coleman Franklin Jr, DOB: 12/11/2003. MD Soundex: MD-10273536572  I made contact with Johnel Trayvon Gray, DOB: 04/10/2004 who had suffered a gunshot wound to his torso. When I made contact with Gray he was not undergoing any direct medical interventions and agreed to speak with me for a few minutes. I also made contact with his mother, Tanikia A Gray who provided me he full name and date of birth.  I made contact with Johnel Gray who advised he is not a Bowie State University student, and he was invited to go to the homecoming events by friends of his. Gray advised he was walking back to his car with a group of people, some of whom he did not know. Gray advised he was not in any confrontations with anyone during the evening and did not have any other sort of altercation with anyone that would have caused this kind of incident.  Gray advised he heard approximately 10 shots, started running and eventually stopped due to his injuries and after being contacted by police officers.  Gray advised he did not see anyone with guns, fire a gun, or see flashes of gun fire.  It was later determined that Victim #2, Terrence Coleman Franklin is one of the people Johnel Gray was walking with and had traveled to the event with him. Gray knows Franklin as TJ.  I found a bag of personal property that had been set aside by hospital staff containing Grays clothing, much of which had been damaged by the efforts of EMS and hospital staff. Myself and S/T Maldonado also asked Gray about what he was wearing at the time of the incident. In his property were some gray jeans and a white shirt. Gray further described that he was wearing a black Hollister jacket. Gray described Franklin as wearing black pants and a blue coat. We located items of personal property at the hospital for Franklin including black pants and a black shirt. No jacket or coat was present, based on BWC footage I reviewed of the initial medical treatment provided to Franklin, it appears this blue coat was left behind on scene.  I believe, based on some BWC footage I reviewed that Grays black jacket was left on scene when initial medical attention was being provided to Gray and was subsequently recovered by Southern Region investigators.  Gray also advised he was walking with someone he identified as Key. He did not have additional identifiers for Key and we were unable to locate a telephone number for him. It was later determined during a subsequent interview that Key is a male aged 15-16 years old, that Gray was not traveling with him, he saw him at the homecoming event and Key may have been walking a significant distance ahead of him during the shooting.  Tanikia Gray advised she did not know Johnel Gray was going to the homecoming. She advised, and subsequently clarified during later interviews, that she left their residence to retrieve other children from Six Flags and went to Wendys on Central Ave. T. Gray advised when she left, Gray was still there and believes she left around 2100 hours, and estimates Gray would not have been able to get to the area of Bowie State University until 2200 hours, approximately.  While conducting these interviews, I was advised by a member of the investigation team reviewing surveillance footage that Terrence Franklin was observed with a gun and a gun was subsequently recovered near his position while he was receiving initial medical attention.  I asked Johnel Gray if he has any information about TJ having a firearm, which he said no. Gray again described hearing shots, running and making contact with an officer who provided medical attention. Gray stated he did not know that TJ had been injured until a few minutes before when speaking with us.  Also located in Johnel Grays property were two cell phones, one of which I allowed him and T. Gray to use while they attempted to find contact information for Key. One of these cell phones, a black iPhone, was misplaced by T. Gray before eventually being located again. T. Gray advised me on October 9, 2023 that she took it home.  T. Gray also advised me there was someone at the hospital she identified as Trayona (I believe this is Trayona Buchanan of 3407 13th Place SE, Washington DC 202-743-9229) that was on the phone with Franklin when the shooting occurred. I made contact with Trayona who advised she was on the phone with TJ (Terrence Franklin), heard shots and people screaming and then the call dropped.  Neither Trayona nor any additional family / friends that were with Gray were able to say who Key is or provide a phone number for him.  At approximately 0405 hours I made contact with Monique Shante Bell who identified herself as Terrence Franklins mother. Bell advised that Franklin is not a Bowie State Student and advised she was concerned about where the house keys are that Franklin had with him. It appeared to me that Bell was concerned someone with negative intentions may have shot Franklin and stolen property with the further intention of going to the house and harming more people. I advised her based on the investigation so far, Franklin had not been targeted and was caught in a crossfire and that none of his items had been stolen from him and that some keys may be in his property that we took from the hospital.  Bell was unable to provide further information about who else may have been with either Franklin or Gray.  Prior to leaving the hospital, I was informed Franklin was out of surgery and in recovery. I was contacted by Sgt. Brian Whitmore and asked to respond to Campus Way and 214 to interview two subjects that had been identified as being at Bowie State University during the shooting and may have additional information.  For further information regarding these interviews, refer to supplement written by S/T Maldonado.  October 9, 2023 Follow-Up Interviews On October 9, 2023 after meeting with Sgt. Whitmore and discussing the investigation, I identified several items of interest for follow-up interviews with Gray and Franklin. I spoke to M. Bell in the morning who advised me that Franklin had another surgery during the morning of October 9, 2023 and was currently in recovery. I responded back to Capital Regional Medical Center with Sgt. Newcomer and located Franklin in the recovery area. Franklin provided a similar statement to Gray, that they were walking back to their car, heard shots and were injured. Franklin denied being involved in any altercations or fights earlier in the evening that would have led to this type of incident.  I reviewed surveillance footage from the campus and the area of the shooting and observed Gray and Franklin walking. There faces were not clearly visible, but based on primarily Grays description of the clothing they were wearing, I was able to determine their general movements on the footage. Franklin can be seen getting injured and laying down on a sidewalk area next to another party wearing an Under Armour sweatshirt. This person was also visible on BWC footage from the responding officers. I showed Franklin (and later Gray) a picture of this subject Franklin denied knowing who they are. I later learned that Cpl. Null made contact with this subject and there is a separate supplement about it. In reference to who Key is, Franklin mentioned a young woman named Kally phone number 240-492-8184, which was similar to information I was provided on Saturday morning. Franklin is also seen on campus surveillance footage with a firearm and was asked by Sgt. Newcomer and I about this.  Franklin denied having a firearm and M. Bell indicated she did not want anymore questions being asked and she had contacted a lawyer earlier because she was initially told at the hospital that Franklin was under arrest. I told her he was never under arrest and still isnt, which she acknowledged she understood that now, but during the early morning hours of October 8, 2023, she was under a different impression. This follow-up interview with Franklin was concluded and I responded to Floor 5 S Room 104 to make contact with Gray.  Johnel Gray was also shown an image of the person wearing an Under Armour sweatshirt and advised he doesnt know who that is (this party was interviewed by Cpl. Null). Johnel Gray reiterated his explanation of the events again; that he and TJ were walking to their car, had not been involved in any altercations, didnt see any; heard shots and ran. Gray did not recall seeing anyone holding a gun or shooting, just hearing the sounds and being injured.  I also talked to T. Gray about a black cell phone that was originally in J. Grays possession and he was using it to attempt to locate contact information for the people that he was with, so they could potentially be interviewed as witnesses. T. Gray advised she accidentally took it outside the hospital and left it there until a security guard returned it to her and it was currently located at home.     </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5164</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 08:53:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5164</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 08:07:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Null</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zakery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6149</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lane</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5164</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5164</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 13:52:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 13:52:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390033</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Gray</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tanikia</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 13:51:35</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Gray</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tanikia</FirstName>
               <SLastName>G600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 13:51:35</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1389</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Congress</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>SE</StreetSuffixCode>
               <SubNumber>3</SubNumber>
               <City>Washington</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20032</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5074</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.984782</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.844665</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>795</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2584</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5164</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 13:52:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5164</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 13:53:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 13:53:16</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366049</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Monique</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shante</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/07/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/13/2023 18:11:47</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Monique</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shante</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/07/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/13/2023 18:11:47</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9703</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Summit</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>4B</SubNumber>
               <City>Upper Marlboro</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20774</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.838536</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.901978</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5164</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 13:53:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5164</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 14:02:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 14:02:12</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390034</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Vassell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kahul</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Mohan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/17/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 14:01:49</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>V240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Vassell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kahul</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Mohan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/17/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>V240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 14:01:49</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>10916</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Kencrest</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Bowie</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20721</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.814843</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.944868</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>312</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7016</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5164</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 14:02:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5164</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 14:03:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 14:03:45</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390035</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Vassell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Norris</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alexander</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/02/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 14:03:28</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>V240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Vassell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Norris</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alexander</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/02/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>V240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 14:03:28</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>742</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4193</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5164</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 14:03:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>8</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/10/2023 13:30:55</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/10/2023 13:30:55</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6171</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 13:30:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #8 Narrative-Traffic Stop</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments: -MSP 67 Handguns -MSP 180  Victim:  -State of Maryland  Witness: - Kahlil Mahan Vassell DOB 3/17/1994 10916 Kencrest Dr Bowie, Maryland 20721 -Norris Alexander Vassell DOB 3/17/1992 10916 Kencrest Dr Bowie, Maryland 20721 -Trooper First Class Strawser #7677 MSP Forestville Barrack -Trooper First Class White #6931 MSP Forestville Barrack  Suspect: -Unknown  Scene Processing: -On scene interviews  Narrative: BWC activated and fully operational.  -On 10/8/2023 at approximately 0346 hours, Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack units responded to the area of Maryland Route 214 and Campus Way to assist Prince Georges County Police Department who were on a traffic stop with a black Tesla Model Y bearing Maryland registration 3FM3640. MSP Forestville Barrack units were advised by PGPD the driver and front passenger of the Tela were both asleep inside the vehicle while in lane 2. PGPD also observed a handgun located in-between the driver seat and the center console. A second handgun was observed on the passengers waist band. After several attempts, the driver and passenger woke up and were ordered out of the Tesla. Both handguns, Glock 19 #BZNC573 and Glock 19 #BWRU314, were recovered without incident. Both Kahlil and Norris provided their Firearm Permits which was verified through the Maryland State Police Gun Center. It was then discovered the driver, identified as Kahlil Mahan Vassell (MD V-240-461-609-202), and passenger, identified as Norris Alexander Vassell (MD V-240-636-044-088) were heading home from Bowie State University. Kahlil also stated he was in a physical altercation where he was assaulted and which led him to leave campus. Both Kahlil and Norris were detained and Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Southern Region investigators were then contacted due to the very recent shooting on campus of BSU.  Upon arrival, investigators along with MSP Forestville Barrack units, moved the vehicles to the nearby BP gas station. Kahlil and Norris were both mirandized and elected to speak to investigators.  Kahlil stated he was a BSU Alumni and was attending BSUs homecoming with his brother, Norris, and friends. Towards the end of the night, Kahlil approached a female who he met during the night to say goodbye. Kahlil was then approached by an unknown male who advised the female was his girlfriend and requested Kahlil not to speak with her. The unknown male became aggressive, and his friends began surrounding Kahlil. Kahlil believes this unknown male to have punched him in the face. At this point, Kahlil did not engage and began running away. A few minutes later, Kahlil observed several of the students and guests running. Kahlil could hear others saying they heard the sounds of gun shots. Kahlil stated he personally did not hear the gun shots and notified his brother, Norris, to meet at the vehicle via telephone. Kahlil advised he did not carry his handgun and left it in the vehicle.  Norris stated he was attending the BSU homecoming as a guest and was never a student of the University. Norris also stated he was in the same area on campus as Kahlil. Norris did not observe or had knowledge of the assault involving Kahlil. Norris also observed several students and guests running. Norris received Kahlils message and met at vehicle. Norris did not hear any gun shots. Norris also advised he left his firearm in the vehicle during the event.  After viewing footage of the incident, investigators did not believe both Kahlil and Norris were involved in the on-campus shooting. Kahlil and Norris were released on scene and the handguns were seized for future examination. The handguns were transported to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack for storage.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6171</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 13:33:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6171</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 13:34:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lane</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5164</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Maldonado</LastName>
            <FirstName>Steve</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6171</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>9</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/11/2023 13:29:29</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/11/2023 13:29:29</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/11/2023 13:29:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>MARC Train Surveillance</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Narrative: On October 11, 2023, I, Corporal Null 6149 of the Maryland State Police Crimina Enforcement Division, responded to the Maryland Mass Transit Administration Police to review video surveillance of the MARC Station at Bowie University. I met with Sergeant J. Scheidt supervisor for the Criminal Intelligence Unit who showed me the video surveillance.  The video surveillance captures primarily the train platform, tunnels connecting the platforms, and a small portion of the parking lot near the station. I reviewed the footage and noted one individual of interest. The individual was seen for a short period of time running towards the Campus at approximately 2345 hours. The individual meets the physical description of an individual with one of the shooters of this investigation. Additionally, while the person of interest is running he appears to be grasping an object concealed in his waistband which based on my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, believe to be a firearm.  Still photographs were obtained of the individual and were forwarded to MCAC for additional assistance in identifying this person.    Icompleted an official request for the video surveillance which will be available at a later date.    On October 12, 2023, I responded to the Maryland Mass Transit Administration Police Department and retrieved official copies of the video surveillance. The surveillance provided was in reference to camera numbers 102, 103, 106, 112, 129, 232, 233, 234,236,and 237 between October 7, 2023, at 2320 hours and October 8, 2023, at 0030 hours. The video was submitted as evidence per MSP policy.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/11/2023 13:30:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 12:11:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lane</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5164</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Null</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zakery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6149</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>10</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/11/2023 14:40:14</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/11/2023 14:40:14</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>CVED</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6786</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/11/2023 14:40:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #10 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On October 7th, 2023, I, TFC B. Strong #6786, was working at the Bowie State University Homecoming Event located at 14000 Jericho Park Rd, Bowie, MD, 20715. I was assisting with traffic control at the entrance of Loop Road at Jericho Park Road while working alongside TFC Moorman #6980.  At approximately 2330 hours, I heard what sounded like multiple gunshots to the northeast of my location. D/Sgt Heath then advised over the radio that there were shots fired on the Bowie State University Campus. I returned to my patrol vehicle and activated my emergency equipment and drove North on Jericho Park Road. I located the first gunshot victim at Jericho Park Road at Henry Way. This victim was later identified as Johnel Trayvon Gray, B/M, DOB: 04/10/2004. I observed that there were several officers on scene already treating Gray for his wounds. I was made aware of a second gunshot victim inside the campus. I located the second gunshot victim on Henry Circle at Henry Way. The victim was lying on his stomach on the sidewalk directly in front of the Center for Business  Graduate Studies building. This victim was later identified as Terrence Coleman Franklin Jr, B/M, DOB: 12/11/2003. Franklin was being treated by multiple officers on scene. I radioed to the College Park Barrack the location of both shooting victims. There was also a bystander nearby who claimed to be friends with Franklin. Both Franklin and his friend, Mecca Leebey, were not able to provide suspect description or even a direction of travel.  Due to medical care already being provided to both victims, I began to secure to the scene. I began placing caution/crime scene tape around a large area of where the shooting occurred near Franklin Jr. Multiple casings and projectiles were located at the scene. Trooper Barnhart #7328 and Trooper Shai #7463 were two troopers rendering aid to Franklin Jr. They observed a firearm next to Franklin and secured it. I later took custody of the firearm and secured it. The firearm was identified as a Tan Glock 19 with a black extended magazine. The magazine had a capacity of 31 rounds. The Glock was loaded with 18 9mm rounds of ammunition total. The Glock also had what appeared to be blood on it, which was most likely Franklins blood. The firearm was given to MSP Crime Scene Technicians when they arrived on scene.  This concludes my assistance in this investigation.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6786</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/11/2023 14:41:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6786</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/11/2023 15:03:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Heath</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4437</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CVED</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Strong</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6786</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>11</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/13/2023 08:58:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/13/2023 08:58:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7339</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 08:58:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #11 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On October 7, 2023 I, Trooper Albaugh of the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack was assigned to work the Bowie State Homecoming Event. Our initial assignment was to remain visible and take a couple of walks through the campus every so often. At 2048 hours Trooper Norman and I were assigned to go stop foot traffic from coming into the camps on MD 197 at Racetrack Road. At around 2230 hours Trooper Norman and I started to make our way back, due to heavy traffic congestion, to Lot H to meet up with Detecive Sergeant Heath by 2345 hour as we were going to come up with a plan to get ready to shut everything down. Trooper Norman and I, were sitting in our vehicles in Lot H when we heard loud popping sounds which we thought were fireworks. About a minute later, there were more loud popping noises and people started running out of the quad. We immediately got out of our vehicles and met up with Detective Sergeant Heath in front of the Bowie State University Police building. We made a scan of the area and made contact with the command staff of the University Police inside the quad. While we were standing with the University Police we heard a third round of gunfire coming from the back right corner of the quad. We ran towards that section of the quad trying to identify any threats or suspects. We asked numerous students if they saw anything to which everyone was not able to give us any information. We made our way back to Lot H to wait for additional units to show up. While we were waiting a call came out for possible shooting on the train tracks at the MARC station. Trooper Norman, Trooper Houck, Trooper Flemming, and myself all drove over to the MARC station to canvas the area in which we did not see anything. We were told to wait there as they were attempting to set up a command center in the parking lot at the MARC station. Once a Trooper from the Special Operations Division showed up we were tasked with heading back down to the main command center in Lot H. Once back at the main command post Trooper Norman and I were tasked with securing a witness at Henry Circle at Henry Way. We waited at that location with witness until Troopers from the Criminal Enforcement Division arrived on scene to speak with the witness. Once CED was finished we released the witness and returned back to the command post in Lot H. We were then tasked with securing a third crime scene area while we waited for the Crime Scene Unit to get to the scene. I cleared the scene at 0600 hours on October 8, 2023. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7339</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 08:59:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7339</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 09:00:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Heath</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4437</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Albaugh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Josiah</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7339</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>12</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/13/2023 14:25:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/13/2023 14:25:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP4437</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 14:25:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #12 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Case Number:  23-MSP-035322   Date: Saturday, 10/07/2023  Sunday, 10/08/2023   Location: Bowie State University  14000 Jericho Park Road Bowie, MD 20715 Prince Georges County   font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Crime(s): Shooting investigation (non-fatal) -Attempted murder -Assault 1st degree -Reckless endangerment  -Related criminal violations   font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Suspect(s): Unknown / unidentified at this time   Victim(s): -Johnel T. Gray, DOB: 04/10/2004  -Terrence C. Franklin, DOB: 12/11/2003   font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Primary Investigator(s): Sergeant B. Whitmore #6094, MSP  Criminal Enforcement Division   font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Assisting Investigator(s): MSP  Criminal Enforcement Division (lead investigative unit) -MSP  Field Operations Bureau (initial / supplemental investigative unit) -MSP  Commercial Vehicle Enforcement Division (initial / supplemental investigative unit) -MSP  Forensic Sciences Division (supplemental investigative unit) -Bowie State University Police (initial / supplemental investigative unit) (Refer to individual supplemental reports of each involved Trooper / Officer / Technician for information regarding their respective role in this investigation)   font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-color:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-thickness:initial"&gt;Summary of initial incident and investigation: On Saturday, 10/07/2023 Bowie State University (BSU) continued a week-long series of celebrations and events as part of their annual homecoming. Specifically, on 10/07/2023 and into 10/08/2023 BSU held their homecoming football game with additionally scheduled post-game events and celebration.    At the request of BSU, the Maryland State Police (MSP) assigned a contingent of uniformed Troopers as supplemental security to BSU Officers during post-game events and celebrations. The MSP detail was to begin at 1900 hours on 10/07/2023 and conclude at 0300 hours on 10/08/2023. The primary focus of MSP during this detail was to provide and increased law enforcement presence and added security through motorized and foot patrols. I (Detective Sergeant W. Heath, assigned to the MSP - College Park Barrack) was assigned as the MSP Officer-In-Charge of the MSP detail. In addition to myself, the following Troopers were also assigned to this detail: Tpr. C. Barnhart  College Park Barrack Tpr. J. Albaugh - College Park Barrack Tpr. N. Norman  Rockville Barrack Tpr. G. Hershberger  Rockville Barrack Tpr. Z. Shai  Forestville Barrack Tpr. B. Thienhom  Forestville Barrack TFC. B. Strong  Commercial Vehicle Enforcement Division TFC M. Moorman - Commercial Vehicle Enforcement Division   In addition to MSP, BSU Police detailed 8-10 BSU police officers (to include the BSU Chief of Police who was on-location), 6 BSU security guards, and 25 private security guards to the events on 10/07/2023  10/08/2023. In total, 17-19 law enforcement officers and 31 security guards were assigned to the campus.   Upon arrival to the aforementioned detail I learned, in addition to BSU students, alumni, and outside guests, students from Morgan State University in Baltimore, MD had also been invited to the homecoming events held on 10/07/2023  10/08/2023. This was done in response to the cancellation of Morgan State University homecoming events as result of an (unrelated) on-campus shooting incident on 10/03/2023 in Baltimore. Due, in-part, to the additional attendees it was apparent the number of on-campus guests and students far exceeded the number anticipated by BSU during initial planning. Upon the arrival of myself and other Troopers, on-campus events and celebrations were already underway with additional planned throughout the evening / night. A large crowd was already present on-campus which continued to grow in size throughout the evening.   As additional people continued to enter the campus, it was requested by BSU Police that a portion of the MSP contingent respond to two locations in effort to prevent further vehicular and foot traffic from entering. Two Troopers were directed to the main campus entry at Jericho Park Road (north of Rt. 197) and Henry Way, while an additional two Troopers were directed to an additional entry point at Jericho Park Road and Loop Road. Remaining Troopers provided both motorized and foot patrols of the campus.   At approximately 2235 hours I was contacted by BSU Police who advised, at the direction of the Chief, they would be terminating all events and activities at midnight. As result, they would be requesting all guests (non-students) and unauthorized people to exit the campus. This was in response to the large number of campus attendees. I notified all MSP personnel of the decision and requested that each respond to the staging location, in Lot H, at 2345 hours so a coordinated effort could be made by MSP and BSU Police. Additionally, I requested additional assistance of College Park Troopers not assigned to the BSU detail.    At approximately 2330 hours I was contacted via MSP radio that Troopers in the area of the BSU main entrance at Jericho Park Road and Henry Way heard several gunshots and observed several people fleeing from the area on foot. I was stationed in the Lot H staging location at that time. Moments later I was advised Troopers encountered two subjects suffering obvious gunshot wounds. One gunshot victim (later identified as Johnel Gray) was located along Henry Way south of Henry Circle in the area of the Entrepreneurship Living and Learning Center. Gray had suffered a gunshot wound to his chest/shoulder area. An additional gunshot victim (later identified as Terrence Franklin) was located in along Henry Circle, in the area of the Center for Business and Graduate Studies, and had suffered a gunshot to his hip / thigh area. Troopers immediately requested the assistance of medics and provided medical care until the arrival of EMS. Prince Georges County Fire / EMS later transported each victim to the Capital Regional Medical Center for emergency medical treatment. Gray was transported via ambulance #818 (run number 23100700000487) and Franklin was transported via ambulance #819 (run number 23100700000482).   While responding to and treating Franklin, Troopers located a Glock handgun lying on the ground in close proximity to his location. The firearm was recovered and made safe by Tpr. Barnhart. It was held as evidence pending follow-up investigation. Shortly thereafter a preliminary crime scene was located by Troopers along Henry Circle spanning through Henry Way north of Jericho Park Road. The crime scene consisted of various clothing items, blood evidence, and a number of spent shell casings all consistent with a shooting scene. Troopers secured the crime scene location and preserved physical evidence in its original location for follow-up investigation and processing.   Upon first being notified of the shooting I immediately made contact with BSU Police and advised them of the two confirmed gunshot victims and updated them of the preliminary location of the shooting incident. At that time Tpr. Albaugh and Tpr. Norman had arrived at the staging location and were present with me. Several people, who had heard the gunshots, had begun to flee the Holmes Plaza area on foot. This was the primary location for the evenings events and was the most populated area at the time. Although several people had begun to flee on foot, several hundred people were still present in the Holmes Plaza. At that time Tpr. Albaugh, Tpr. Norman, and I entered the Holmes Plaza to begin clearing people from the area. While making our way through the Holmes Plaza we began walking toward a large crowd of people still congregating in the area of the Holmes Hall and Kennard Hall. While approaching the area, Tpr. Albaugh, Tpr. Norman, and I heard an additional 2-3 gunshots which sounded to be in relative close proximity to us. The gunshots sounded to originate in the area in which we were traveling on foot. The area could best be identified as an area between the Henry Wise Wellness Center and Center for Sciences, Mathematics, and Nursing (south of Holmes and Kennard Halls). Immediately upon hearing the gunshots several people who were congregated in the crowd began fleeing the area on foot. Tpr. Albaugh, Tpr. Norman, and I raced to the area in effort to locate a shooter and canvas the area for potential victims. There were no apparent suspects or victims in the area.    It should be noted that later during follow-up investigation, I was provided surveillance video of two shooting suspects at the original shooting location. During a review of the video I observed two suspects firing handguns. One suspect appeared to be a black male, appearing to be early-mid 20s, thin to medium build, with shorter-style hair. He was wearing black pants, white sneakers, a white shirt, and black jacket. He was last observed fleeing on foot in the direction of Loop Road after firing from a handgun on Henry Circle. An additional suspect appeared to be a black male, believed to be early-mid 20s, thin to medium build, with medium-length dreadlock or braided style hair. He was wearing light colored pants, white shoes, and a white hooded sweatshirt. This suspect was observed fleeing on foot in the direction of Henry Way after firing from a handgun in the area of Henry Circle and Henry Way. Later in the video this same suspect (dressed in the white hooded sweatshirt) is observed returning to the area and firing additional rounds from a handgun, after some time had passed following the initial shooting report. It is possible, after having reviewed the video footage, the second set of gunshots Tpr. Albaough, Tpr. Norman, and I heard may have likely come from this same suspect when he returned to fire additional rounds.    Several minutes following the second set of gunshots, I was advised by BSU Police that additional gunshots were reportedly heard in the area of the on-campus MARC Penn Line parking lot. I immediately directed Troopers to respond to the area in effort to locate shooting suspects, victims, or evidence of a shooting scene. Responding Troopers were unable to locate suspects, victims, or evidence supporting an additional shooting had taken place.   Following the aforementioned events I requested additional MSP resources to include an additional patrol response from neighboring Barracks, activation of the Mobile Field Force, and response from Special Operations Division personnel. Prince Georges County Police Department aviation was requested and responded to provide aerial support. Each of those resources later responded in support of the detail.   Additionally I made contact with the BSU Chief of Police and Prince Georges County Police and established a unified command post in Lot H. BSU Police, Prince Georges County Police, MSP, and Prince Georges County Fire / EMS Officers-In-Charge maintained the unified command post until the arrival of additional resources. Upon the arrival of MSP Special Operations Division they also joined the unified command post. On-scene follow-up operational (non-investigative) assignments were distributed to supporting personnel through the command post. Throughout I provided command notifications to MSP commissioned ranks to ensure updated information was available for their use as necessary.   I made contact with the MSP  Criminal Enforcement Division and advised them of the incident. I requested investigators respond to the location to assume primary investigation. Several members of the Criminal Enforcement Division responded to the scene while additional investigators were directed to the Capital Regional Medical Center to make contact with victims Gray and Franklin. I remained on-scene to assist investigators and coordinate additional patrol functions as needed.    While still on-scene I was contacted by the Forestville Barrack who advised they had stopped to assist a vehicle in the area of Central Avenue following the shooting. During contact with the occupants of that vehicle, the Trooper identified the occupants as Khalil Vassell and Norris Vassell. During contact with them the Trooper located two Glock 19 handguns, one upon the person of Khalil and a second in the common area of the vehicle. The Vassells indicated they had been at BSU earlier in the evening. As result, a Criminal Enforcement Division investigators responded to the scene and took custody of the two Glock handguns for further investigation. They were transported to and stored at the College Park Barrack.   On 10/12/2023 I successfully completed a test fire of each Glock handgun which confirmed both to be operational and capable of being fired. I am certified through the Maryland State Police to operate and test fire with the Operation Test Shot system stored within the College Park Barrack property room. Two projectiles and two shell casings from each firearm were collected from the Operation Test Shot system and were turned over to Sgt. Whitmore, who witnessed the successful test fires. On 10/13/2023 Sgt. Whitmore transported the projectiles and shell casings to the MSP  Forensic Sciences Division for analysis and entry into NIBIN. The firearms remain stored in the College Park Property room, along with the handgun recovered from BSU which was turned over from Sgt. Whitmore.   I am currently working to obtain radios transmissions from the College Park Barrack related to the BSU detail and shooting incident which, once available, will be provided to Sgt. Whitmore.   I will remain available to assist the Criminal Enforcement Division as necessary and additional supplemental reports will be completed as necessary.   This case remains open pending further investigation.       </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4437</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 14:26:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4437</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 15:41:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Whitmore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6094</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Heath</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4437</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>14</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/16/2023 13:49:24</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/16/2023 13:49:24</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5239</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/16/2023 13:49:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #14 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On Tuesday, 10-10-2023, investigators requested copies of any/all 9-1-1 calls related to the incident. Investigators await the Prince Georges County 9-1-1 Centers response. Investigators will contact them again on Wednesday, 10-11-2023 in hopes of reviewing any/all 9-1-1 calls in hopes it generates some investigative leads.   On Tuesday, 10-10-2023, investigators contacted the Bowie City Police Department regarding 9-1-1 calls and learned that all calls are routed through the PG County 9-1-1 center. On Wednesday, 10-11-2023, Cpl. Posey of MSP CED Central South Region will contact Bowie City Police Department to obtain any/all calls for service on the roadways/neighborhoods that border BSU in hopes it generates some investigative leads.   On Wednesday, 10-11-2023, Cpl. Posey-(MSP Central South Region) contacted Prince Georges Countys 911 call center to get a timeframe on compliance with the audio request. Cpl. Posey spoke with Ulrica Lee at 301-352-1401 who stated the request was received, but she could not advise on a timeline. She stated it takes about thirty days. Cpl. Posey asked if there was a way to expedite the process? Cpl. Posey was put on hold for her to consult her supervisor. Cpl. Posey was told the department was short staffed and it would more than likely take thirty days. It was then stated, once the audio is copied it has to go through the Office Of Law before being released to the Maryland State Police and they do not control how long the Office Of Law takes. Cpl. Posey requested to come down and listen to whatever calls they may have in person. Cpl. Posey was put on hold and transferred to an audio technician who provided most of the same information but also suggested he get a copy of the Prince Georges County Police Departments CAD card in the meantime.Cpl. Posey was able to obtain information for two different Prince Georges County officers, one of which was Deputy Chief Oleary. Deputy Chief Oleary was given the information requested and is attempting to help expedite the process and obtain the information needed to assist this investigation.Cpl. Posey contacted the Bowie City Police via email. Sgt. Howard of Bowie Citys investigative unit was sent an email requesting any and all emergency or non-emergency calls for service close to Bowie State University or surrounding areas.   On October 20, 2023 at approximately 1300 hours, Cpl. Posey and Sgt. Newcomer responded to17321 Melford Blvd., Bowie Maryland to Prince Georges County 911 call center to listen to all emergency call. Numerous calls were heard from Bowie State University to the 911 center and additional 911 calls from the surrounding areas. Various phone numbers and names were obtained to follow-up on the information provided to the 911 center.   Cpl Posey contacted one of the 911 callers at347-399-8272Cpl. Posey contacted the number listed and got an answer. Cpl. Posey stated who he was and why he was calling. Without any questions asked, the call taker (unnamed at this point) stated she arrived in the area of Bowie State University after the shooting to meet up with friends. She stated she took a wrong turn and her vehicle ended up stuck on a rail trail. She stated she called the police an nobody helped her. Cpl. Posey asked her name and she stated Shayne Stevens. Cpl. Posey asked Ms. Stevens to meet to record her statement to potentially get more details and further the investigation? Stevens adamantly refused stating she wasnt involved in the shooting, she showed up after, and the police did not help her so shell probably never call the police again. Cpl. Posey reassured her that we are not the department she called and would love to sit and speak to her about her incident in detail. Stevens stated she did not have time shes a college student and would not get involved. Cpl. Posey asked her to please reach out if she hears anything regarding the shooting from other students.   Cpl. Posey made several attempts to contactHarley Holmes 301-892-1734. Ms. Holmes has not responded to any of Cpl. Poseys calls, voicemails, or text. Cpl. Posey responded to the 7 Eleven on7404 Laurel - Bowie Rd, Bowie, MD 20715. Cpl. Posey made contact with the manager and was able to obtain video from the 7 Eleven displaying the accident that Holmes reported. Cpl. Posey reached out to Prince Georges County Det. Denise Shapiro in an attempt to get further information for Holmes. Cpl. Posey has not heard anything back as of yet.   On 11/16/2023 at approximately 1033 hours, Harley Holmes contacted Cpl. Posey by phone. Cpl. Posey discussed the reason for the call to Holmes and Holmes agreed to meet Cpl. Posey for a recorded interview in the future. Due to Holmes class schedule and the Holiday no interview has been conducted.         </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5239</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/16/2023 14:05:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5239</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 14:24:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Null</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zakery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6149</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Posey</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5239</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>15</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/20/2023 12:49:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/20/2023 12:49:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 12:49:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Jones-Peoples Interview</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*BWC was NOT activated for this interaction*  Focus: The focus of this supplement is to document an interview with Jones-Peoples  Witness:   Jones-Peoples, Kyle Anthony     B/M DOB: 04/12/1995      Narrative: On October 19, 2023, I, Cpl Z. Null 6149 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division, was reviewing open forum social media posts in an attempt to identify possible leads and/or witnesses. While doing so, I noted a Twitter post by username Thatmanpeanut that was suitable for follow up.  On October 8, 2023, Thatmanpeanut retweeted a news post about the shooting on October 7, 2023, at Bowie State University with the caption SMH. On October 8, 2023, Thatmanpeanut subsequently made a post stating, That shooting happened in front of me smh glad I made it home safe. Dude emptied the clip. Through investigative efforts utilizing Law Enforcement and Public Databases, I was able to identify the account owner as Jones-Peoples, Kyle Anthony (B/M DOB: 04/12/1995).    On October 19, 2023, Iwas able to make contact with Jones-Peoples via telephone and conducted an interview. Jones-Peoples advised he was walking south on Henry Cir when he heard the shots. He described numerous shots being fired. Jones-Peoples advised he fled between buildings in the general direction of the train station. When asked, Jones-Peoples stated he did not hear any confrontation or fighting before the fight, therefore, he was not able to get a description of any suspects or persons of interest. Jones-Peoples did not have much information to pass along because he stated he was in fear for his life so he just ran away. Jones-People was very cooperative, he just did not seem to have information that could aide the investigation.    Jones-Peoples advised he was in a black crew neck long sleeved shirt, black pants, and possible vans when the shooting occurred.  Contact information was provided to Jones-Peoples, and he advised he would be available for additional interviews should the need arise.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 12:57:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/20/2023 13:07:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lane</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5164</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Null</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zakery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6149</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>28</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 12:57:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/20/2023 12:57:12</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390834</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Jones-Peoples</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anthony</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/12/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>4.37919231E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>10/20/2023 12:56:53</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J521</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Jones-Peoples</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anthony</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/12/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>4.37919231E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>J521</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/20/2023 12:56:53</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>612</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Harry S Truman</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Upper Marlboro</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20774</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2062</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.829877</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.882522</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>925</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1609</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 12:57:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>16</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/25/2023 12:26:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/25/2023 12:26:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:10:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/25/2023 12:26:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>911 Caller Interviews</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>INVESTIGATOR: Sergeant B. Whitmore #6094 UNIT: Criminal Enforcement Division - Central South Region DATE ASSIGNED: 10/07/2023 CASE STATUS: Open FOCUS:This report captures 9-1-1 caller interviews for individuals who made calls in reference to the shooting investigation.  BWC activated  Chassidy Hernandez DOB 11/22/2001 Phone # 240-602-9385  On 10-24-2023 at approximately 1525 hours I made contact with 9-1-1 caller, Chassidy Hernandez, at the Bowie State University Campus. Hernandez advised she was on campus during the homecoming event in proximity to Lot H on the campus. She advised she heard the sounds of gunshots and fled the area. She stated she attempted to enter a building but was denied entry by campus staff / security personnel. Hernandez then called 911 and reported this to the emergency communication dispatcher. Hernandez advised she wasnt anywhere near the contact shooting location and would not be able to provide details on possible suspects. She was advised to contact investigators if she learned of anything to assist the investigation. --------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Interview recorded audibly  Chaedon Rosemond Phone # 860-814-2567  On 10-25-2023 at approximately 1518 hours I made contact with 9-1-1 Chadeon Rosemond in Towson, MD. Rosemond advised he is a student at Morgan State University, and he was on campus during the homecoming event on Henry Circle when he heard multiple sets of gunshots. He believed there were multiple shooters and heard the sounds of projectiles hitting trees in the area. I showed Rosemond a map of Henry Circle and asked him to explain where he was in relation to the shooting. He explained he was on the opposite side and ran in the opposite direction towards the computer science building. He was unable to provide any suspect descriptions. Rosemondwas advised to contact investigators if he learned of anything to assist the investigation. ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- BWC activated  Jeffrey Wright DOB 07/15/1965 Phone# 443-953-9159  On 10-26-2023 at approximately 1405 hours I made contact with Jeffrey Wright at the Community College of Baltimore County - Catonsville. Wright is a Bowie State University Alumni and was attending the event with friends and former fraternity brothers. Wright showed me his location on a map and it was in the area of Holmes Plaza. He was not in proximity to the shooting and was unable to provide any suspect descriptions. Wright was advised to contact investigators if he learned of anything to assist the investigation.  Case open  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/25/2023 12:27:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6094</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/19/2023 14:34:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>3</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Crime Scene Report, Crime Lab</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>INVESTIGATOR: Sergeant B. Whitmore #6094 UNIT: Criminal Enforcement Division - Central South Region DATE ASSIGNED: 10/07/2023 CASE STATUS: Open FOCUS:This report captures investigative efforts in reference to DNA testing and latent fingerprint processing. The report also contains the crime scene report completed by the Crime Scene Technician and the Latent Print Report.  ATTACHMENTS: -Crime Scene Report -Crime Scene Notes and Sketches -360 Photographs of Scene (stored on disc separate from report) -Latent Print Report  MSP  Forensic Sciences Division was contacted on Thursday, 10-26-2023 regarding the possibility of testing the spent shell casings for touch DNA and for latent prints. Following a request to the Director, Biology advised they would conduct the DNA tests but also advised the success rates of these tests are very minimal. Biology also advised this type of testing is outsourced to BODE labs and latent lift attempts will need to be processed first. Latent Print advised the process could be completed by Friday 11-3-2023; However, if they recovered prints from the casings the process could be extended due to the prints needing to be analyzed and compared.  On 12-11-2023 Sgt Whitmore received the Latent Print report in reference to the shell casings recovered. The analysis revealed there are no latent print impressions suitable for identification purposes.  On 12-13-2023, Sgt Whitmore responded to MSP Crime Lab to retrieve the casings and sent them via Fedex to BODE Lab for subsequent DNA testing. Testing should be completed in approximately 60 days.  CASE OPEN </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 14:05:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6094</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 13:37:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>4</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Search Warrants - Tower Dump, Instagram, T-Mobile</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>INVESTIGATOR: Sergeant B. Whitmore #6094 UNIT: Criminal Enforcement Division - Central South Region DATE ASSIGNED: 10/07/2023 CASE STATUS: Open FOCUS:This report captures investigative efforts involving the suspects social media and cell carrier information.  ATTACHMENTS: -Tower Dump Data(large file - retained externally) -Lyft subpoena return -Instagram Warrant -T-Mobile Warrant -Tower Dump Warrant -T-Mobile Data (202) 321-2879(large file - retained externally) -Instagram return (large file - retained externally)   Lyft subpoena results were returned on Tuesday, 10-24-2023. No actionable leads were generated from these results. Only one user made a ride request in the area described in the crime solvers tip. The customer was dropped off in Northwest DC and not in Prince Georges County. Three other accounts with the name Jebbrel were located by Lyft in the region but none of the users received a ride during the time frame in question.  On Tuesday, 10-31-2023, after Prince Georges County States Attorneys Office approval was received, Sgt Whitmore submitted a search warrant for tower records to Prince Georges County Circuit Court Judge Stenise Rolle. The warrant was later signed and authorized during the evening hours of 10-31. Sgt Whitmore served the warrant to Verizon, T-Mobile and ATT on 11-1-2023.  T-Mobile provided tower records to Sergeant Whitmore on November 9, 2023. Sgt Whitmore conducted a search of the records and located Mettss known phone number (202) 321-287944instances from 2322 hours to 2338 hours. It should be noted again that the shooting occurred on surveillance footage at 2332 hours. This phone was active on tower data consistently up until 2338 hours. It was also active at 2331 hours with the next activation at 2333 hours, approximately one minute after the shooting. The phone was not active during the shooting.  ATT provided their tower records on 11-15-2023 and Verizon provided theirs on 11-28-2023.  The phone number(202) 321-2879was obtained by allied law enforcement agencies who are also investigating Metts for separate crimes and he is known by multiple agencies to utilize this number. A subpoena was previously sent to T-Mobile for subscriber information and revealed the subscriber was listed as Jake Baker with an address of 3335 7thStreet SE Washington DC 20032. The last known address for Metts is also 3335 7thStreet SE Washington DC 20032. It is an active number with an activation date of 03/08/2020.  The following phone numbers were in contact with Mettss known number during times of 2322 hours - 2342 hours  301-367-1859 202-704-1242 240-940-7199 202-302-6930 202-903-7551 301-836-8208  Each number was subpoenaed for subscriber information and call detail records (CDRs). They were sent to their respective carriers on 11-20-2023.  Sgt Whitmore completed a search and seizure warrant for Metts known Instagram again after learning his phone was present in the area during the shooting and an additional warrant was authored for his known T-Mobile phone number. These warrants were sent for review to a Prince Georges County Circuit Court Judge on 11-21-2023 and were subsequently signed. Each warrant was sent to their respective company on the afternoon of 11-21-2023. On 11-30-2023 Sgt Whitmore received the returns from both Meta and T-Mobile. Both accounts were thoroughly reviewed but revealed no admission of Foot being involved in the shooting on the campus.Upon review of data received from Mettss Instagram, several direct messages to Metts were located which other individuals addressed him as Foot. Another user messaged Metts and asked You fumbled ur stick moe?. This message was sent approximately two hours after the shooting occurred and investigators know from previous investigations that stick is often a slang term for a firearm.   Investigators also submitted a request to Apple to determine if Mettss phone number has an iCloud account associated with it. Apple replied that the number corresponded to an iPhone, so investigators authored a warrant for his iCloud account.  On 12-15-2023 Sgt Whitmore submitted the warrant to Prince Georges County Circuit Judge Coderre for review, following approval from the States Attorneys Office. The warrant was signed and submitted to Apple.  Investigators are in the process of reviewing T-Mobile data; however, at this time it appears no SMS messages were retained or provided by the carrier.  CASE OPEN  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6094</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 22:06:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6094</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/19/2023 14:37:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Null</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zakery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6149</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Whitmore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6094</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>