<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000444</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/04/2023 15:57:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/04/2023 15:57:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/04/2023 12:11:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/04/2023 12:11:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>RECOVERY OF STOLEN VEHICLE FOR ARLINGTON POLICE DEPARTMENT (VA) STOLEN VEHICLE TASK-FORCE</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 15:57:21</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4199</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/08/2023 20:35:23</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>EVD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SVR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>29157</AddressId>
      <City>MDC135</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 15:57:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/05/2023 07:36:07</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>29157</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>242</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Somers</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>CV</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Crisfield</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21817</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.861726</Longitude>
         <Latitude>37.975245</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/04/2023 15:57:15</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/04/2023 15:57:15</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>Y</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/07/2023 11:20:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 15:57:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4199</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/08/2023 20:35:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack X Tpr. B. Salgueiro, IBM 7370 Field Operation Bureau January 4th, 2023   Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle:X-4is an unmarked 2021 Ford Explorer equipped with an MVR system and body-worn camera. Type of Report: Assist Arlington Police (VA) stolen vehicle task force with locating and recovering of reported stolen vehicle. Suspect:Suspects unknown at the time of this report. Victim: Dejana Krstic DOB: 04/22/1996 /// VA Soundex: C60044298 /// Contact Information: (703)343-3658 Stolen vehicle Information: Make/Mazda Model/Mazda 3 style/Four-door sedan Color/Dark Grey Plate/MD Temp T1138861 Vin/3MZBPABL5NM315170Value/$26000.00   Troopers Training/Experience:  * Trained in Human Trafficking through the Federal Bureau Of Investigations (FBI) and Maryland State Police (MSP)  * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).  * Trained and certified to operate Radar and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  * NHTSA certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E).  * Attended multiple NHTSA-certified cannabis impairment detection workshops.  This report has been prepared based upon the observations of this trooper and/or those of other troopers relative to the offense(s). The facts contained herein are intended solely to give the prosecuting authority a basic understanding of the facts pertaining to this case. The facts contained herein are not intended to be an exhaustive recitation of the facts pertaining to pretrial or trial issues. Instead, this trooper anticipates that during the pretrial proceedings, in this case, the prosecutor will take the opportunity to interview this trooper in order to ascertain any and all relevant facts which might be the subject of this troopers testimony during court proceedings.  Narrative:     On 01/04/2023 at 1211 hours, the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack was contacted by Arlington Police Department (VA) Detective Master Police Officer Scott Whalin #1160, in reference to a stolen motor vehicle. Detective Whalin advised the vehicle was stolen from the parking lot of Caliber Collision, located at 4072 S Four Mile Dr, Arlington, Virginia 22206 at approximately 0435 hours on the morning of Saturday, December 31, 2022. Detective Whalin advised they had an active ping on the vehicle showing a location of 242 Somers Cove, Crisfield, Maryland 21817. Detective Whalin later advised the suspect(s) had entered eleven other vehicles on the date of the vehicle theft in the Caliber Collison parking lot. Detective Whalin advised one of the suspect(s) description was a black or African American, male, with a thin body frame, wearing a black hoodie with the hood up concealing the face and jeans. This initial description matched with the suspects I observed exit the vehicle which will be detailed later in this report.  I, Trooper Salgueiro #7370, was on duty wearing my class b uniform displaying my badge of authority and was dispatched by the Maryland State Police Princess Anne X Barrack to 242 Somers Cove, Crisfield, Maryland 21817 to attempt to locate the vehicle and/or suspect(s) involved with the vehicle theft. The vehicle was described as a four-door, dark gray 2022 Mazda 3, at the time of theft bearing Maryland temporary registration T1138861 and VIN 3MZBPABL5NM315170. Myself and my shift partner Trooper First Class J.Barfield #7185, conducted a search of the area at approximately 1242 hours and were unable to locate the vehicle. I was able to receive further information from Detective Whalin that the stolen vehicle was now pinging in the area of the Fruitland Walmart located at 409 N Fruitland Blvd, Fruitland, Maryland 21801. All early shift Maryland State Police and Somerset County Sheriffs Office deputies stayed in the area of Princess Anne in an attempt to locate the stolen vehicle. At approximately 1500 hours while stationary on Brittingham Ln, parallel to U.S. HWY 13, I observed a grey Mazda matching the description of the stolen vehicle approaching the traffic signal of southbound U.S. HWY 13 and MT Vernon Rd. I observed the front seat passenger of the vehicle maintain eye contact with my vehicle as the driver made an evasive left turn from southbound U.S. HWY 13 onto eastbound MT Vernon Rd. The vehicle then accelerated hard enough for me to see the rear bumper of the Mazda lower. The Mazda proceeded to make a right turn from eastbound MT Vernon Rd onto southbound Somerset Ave. I then lost sight of the vehicle and attempted to search the area to locate it and was unsuccessful.  At 1518 hours, Trooper First Class J. Barfield was able to locate the vehicle in the area of Route 413 (Crisfield Highway) and Kingston Lane. TFC Barfield was able to follow behind the vehicle undetected while more units attempted to reach his location. At approximately 1525 hours, I was able to reach TFC Barfield and also observed the vehicle. TFC Barfield, observed multiple traffic law violations while following the vehicle that now was bearing Virginia registration TVH7932 and had probable cause for a traffic stop. At 1526 hours, TFC Barfield and I activated our emergency equipment and attempted to conduct a traffic stop on the Mazda at southbound Route 413 and Cullen Park Way. The vehicle then started to decrease speed onto the right-hand shoulder of 413, but quickly reentered the travel lane southbound and continued to drive at a constant speed. The barrack was notified of the events actively occurring, and the duty officer advised we were not authorized to pursue the Mazda. TFC Barfield and I both deactivated our emergency lights and sirens and decreased our speed. We did not attempt to pursue the Mazda and parked at southbound HWY 413 and N Somerset Ave. TFC Barfield advised the barrack we would be conducting a patrol check of Crisfield to attempt to locate the vehicle while more resources from local law enforcement agencies entered the area. At 1531 hours, I returned to the original address at 242 Somer Cove and observed the Mazda parked directly in front of 242 Somers Cove with headlights activated. I then observed two light build, black or African American males exit the front driver and passenger doors of the vehicle wearing black hoodies with both hoods up concealing their faces, and slowly walking behind the residence of 241 Somers Cove. I lost sight of both suspects at this time. I then waited for more units to arrive before approaching the vehicle.  At 1534 hours, TFC Barfield arrived on the scene, and we moved in and secured the Mazda. A Crisfield Police Department K9 unit was requested to the scene in an attempt to locate the suspects. At 1546 hours, I began a K9 track with Crisfield Police Department. The K9 was able to get odor off the Mazda and tracked the odor to the rear door of 242 Somers Cove and the K9 track ended without incident. At 1552 hours, it was confirmed both the Virginia tags on the vehicle and the VIN confirmed by me on the scene were returning stolen through NCIC. Ronnies Garage was then contacted to respond to the scene and collect the vehicle for state storage (MVI 23-004). On scene, the only damage visible was the right front bumper being slightly popped off. The vehicle was followed by a trooper to the Maryland State Police Barrack and was stored in the barracks vehicle storage garage. Maryland State Police Crime Scene was notified, and responded to the barrack on 01/05/2022 at 0852 hours to process the vehicle for latent prints or any obtainable evidence for collection.  Contact for Arlington Police Criminal Enforcement Division: Detective Scott Whalin #1160 /// swhalin@arlingtonva.us /// Phone: 703-228-4159  The investigation iscontinuing.  All events detailed in this incident did occur in Somerset County, Maryland, and Arlington, Virginia.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 07:49:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7370</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/05/2023 11:45:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barfield</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jacob</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7185</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Salgueiro</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7370</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barkley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ivan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4199</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Chatham</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5149</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Salgueiro</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7370</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 10:55:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:38</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365275</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>U</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dejana</LastName>
               <FirstName>Krstic</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/22/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 10:55:06</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dejana</LastName>
               <FirstName>Krstic</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/22/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 10:55:06</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetName>2028 S Shirlington Rd</StreetName>
               <City>Arlington</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>22204</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 10:55:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:39</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148247</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>ST</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 11:01:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7370</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/05/2023 11:01:29</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/04/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <DateOfInfo>01/04/2023 18:53:33</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3MZBPABL5NM315170</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MAZD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MZ3</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>T1138861</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicNumber>T1138861</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>TM</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>TM</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehConditionCode>F</VehConditionCode>
         <VehDamageCode>12</VehDamageCode>
         <VehDamageDesc>Front bumper damaged unknown if damage was already there.</VehDamageDesc>
         <VehicleValue>25000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/07/2023 09:55:26</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/07/2023 09:55:26</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/29/2023 13:29:10</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 09:55:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4199</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/08/2023 20:35:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack X Tpr. B. Salgueiro, IBM 7370 Field Operation Bureau January 4th, 2023    Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle:X-4is an unmarked 2021 Ford Explorer equipped with an MVR system and body-worn camera. Type of Report:Assist Arlington Police (VA) stolen vehicle task force with locating and recovering of reported stolen vehicle. Suspect:Suspects unknown at the time of this report. Victim:Dejana Krstic DOB: 04/22/1996 /// VA Soundex: C60044298 /// Contact Information: (703)343-3658 Stolen vehicle Information:Make/Mazda Model/Mazda 3 style/Four-door sedan Color/Dark Grey Plate/MD Temp T1138861 Vin/3MZBPABL5NM315170Value/$26000.00    This report has been prepared based upon the observations of this trooper and/or those of other troopers relative to the offense(s). The facts contained herein are intended solely to give the prosecuting authority a basic understanding of the facts pertaining to this case. The facts contained herein are not intended to be an exhaustive recitation of the facts pertaining to pretrial or trial issues. Instead, this trooper anticipates that during the pretrial proceedings, in this case, the prosecutor will take the opportunity to interview this trooper in order to ascertain any and all relevant facts which might be the subject of this troopers testimony during court proceedings.  Narrative:   On 01/05/2023 at approximately 0850 hours, Maryland State Police Crime Scene Technicians arrived at the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack to conduct a DNA, fingerprint, and evidence inventory of the recovered stolen Mazda. Crime Scene technicians examined the vehicle and were able to locate multiple items inside the vehicle. I contacted the victim and determined that the only personal items she possessed in the vehicle were one (1) set of Apple Air Pod earbuds. With this information I suspect all other items in the vehicle to be directly connected to the perpetrator of the vehicle theft and all subsequent crimes. A Maryland learners permit and PNC bank debit card were also located in the vehicle. Both the license and bank card were registered to Amir Phillip Wilson (DOB:05/28/2002 B/M). The vehicle also contained multiple articles of clothing that were photographed and seized as evidence (photos will be attached to this supplement)  On 01/06/2023 at approximately 0717 hours, I was conducting a patrol check of Somers Cove in Crisfield, Maryland. I then observed a silver Honda 4-door sedan traveling westbound on Charlotte Ave approaching Cove St. I observed the entire front bumper of the Honda to be missing and no front registration plate being displayed on the vehicle which is required under Maryland traffic article TA-13-411(a). I conducted a lawful traffic stop on the Honda at Cove St and S 3rd St. The vehicle yielded and stopped for my emergency equipment and I made a drivers side approach to the vehicle. I made contact with the driver and owner of the vehicle, Lashae Caprice Smith (DOB: 06/16/1993 B/F), and advised the reason for the traffic stop and gathered her valid Maryland drivers license and registration card. I confirmed through her license that her current address was 242 Somers Cove, After the business needs of the traffic stop were completed, I advised Smith that she was free to go and the traffic stop was over. I asked Smith if she was able to answer a few questions regarding who was residing at the 242 Somers Cove address. She advised me of her own free will that she and her two children and her boyfriend Amir Wilson lived at the address.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 09:57:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7370</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/29/2023 12:24:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barkley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ivan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4199</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Salgueiro</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7370</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/08/2023 20:17:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/08/2023 20:17:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/08/2023 20:35:23</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 20:17:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4199</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/08/2023 20:35:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The suspect(s), in this case, are being investigated by Arlington Police Department for the vehicle thefts, and all further actions related to this case will be completed byArlington Police Department.  Due to this, I request this case be Closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 20:18:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7370</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/08/2023 20:21:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barkley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ivan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4199</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Salgueiro</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7370</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>