<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-007947</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/03/2023 11:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/03/2023 11:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/03/2023 11:07:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/03/2023 11:07:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>PWID</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 11:08:08</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 12:48:14</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>21196</AddressId>
      <City>MDC166</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 11:08:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 10:03:52</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>21196</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>18345</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Col Henry K Douglas</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Hagerstown</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21740</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.732708</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.604221</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MSP O</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>HAGERSTOWN/WASHINGTON COUNTY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>COUNTY WIDE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MSP HAGERSTOWN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/03/2023 11:08:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/03/2023 11:08:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>04/18/2023 12:47:33</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/03/2023 11:08:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 12:47:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>  On 3-3-2023, Master Trooper Hood and Sgt Roberts were notified of a possible supplier of Fentanyl to the Washington County area. M/T Hood coordinated with TFO Jesson from Brunswick Police Department in regard to an incoming parcel possibly containing CDS. A K-9 scan of the parcel was completed by Master Trooper Thompson from the Hagerstown Barrack and a search warrant was written for the parcel. On 3/3/2023, Detective Jesson, M/T Hood and Sgt Roberts executed the search warrant on the parcel. The parcel contained three bags of M-30 Counterfeit Fentanyl pills. Throughout the weekend surveillance and planning for a delivery took place. One Monday 3/6/2023 Members of Western Investigators along with MSP State Team, Brunswick Police Detective Jesson, members of the Frederick County Sheriffs Office (Frederick HIDTA), and Hagerstown City Police Department attempted a controlled delivery by a US Postal Inspector. The original parcel was repackaged with 40g of fentanyl. A delivery was attempted but no one answered at the addressed apartment. Due to the location and visibility issues the parcel was not left on scene. A door tag was left at the apartment and contact was later made with an individual who inquired about the parcel earlier in the case. An arrangement for the parcel to be delivered was coordinated by phone by the US Postal Inspector for 3/7/2023.  On 3/7/2023, Members of the above team including MSP drone pilots, First Sergeant Shaffer and Master Trooper Hite attempted the parcel delivery again at the apartment. Due to the possibilities of this parcel being picked up outside the apartment by an unknown individual, drone pilots were utilized and observed the delivery attempt. The parcel contained a GPS tracking device however in a large urban area the drones were used to provide outstanding oversight if the parcel would go mobile. MSP State Team, Team Leader Hartsock was also assisted by the MDTA team. As team members were in place a delivery was attempted and there was no answer at the apartment. The parcel was then taken back to the Hagerstown Post Office. One final attempt to contact the individual who inquired about the parcel was made, and the individual asked if someone could pick it up. On 3/8/2023, M/T Hood, Sergeant Roberts, Officer Jesson, and Detective Schlosser conducted surveillance at the Hagerstown Post office in regard to an individual attempting to pick up the parcel. Surveillance was conducted until 1200 hours and was concluded. The Fentanyl was taken to the Hagerstown Barrack where it was stored with the remaining Fentanyl. The total weight of the Fentanyl stored at the Hagerstown Barrack is 334.9g. At this time this case is closed. Additional investigation will continue into the source and possible location in Hagerstown. Any further information will be captured under a new case number.  All the above events occurred in Washington County Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 09:40:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 09:40:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>64</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thompson</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3053</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hood</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daryl</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5345</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>