<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011018</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/27/2023 21:19:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/27/2023 21:19:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/27/2023 21:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/27/2023 21:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Accident</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 21:19:53</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3321</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 14:06:40</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MOUNTAIN RD/ OLD MOUNTAIN RD CENTRAL RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>607743</AddressId>
      <City>MDC446</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 21:19:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 23:34:15</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>607743</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Mountain</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Joppa</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.35996</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.4573</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>- MOUNTAIN RD / - OLD MOUNTAIN RD CENTRAL RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2016-2120 MOUNTAIN RD / 2201-2220 OLD MOUNTAIN RD CENTRAL RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2200-2220 MOUNTAIN RD / 2201-2220 OLD MOUNTAIN RD CENTRAL RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/27/2023 21:19:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/27/2023 21:19:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/31/2023 01:54:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 21:19:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3321</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 14:06:31</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This accident report was completed in Delta Plus.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 23:34:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 23:34:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Urbano</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6588</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Turner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6761</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kumador</LastName>
            <FirstName>Linford</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7052</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/29/2023 16:44:31</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/29/2023 16:44:31</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/26/2023 11:14:53</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 16:44:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3321</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 14:06:31</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Detailed Crash Investigation Report (For review by the MSPCrash Team)    Section I. - Introduction:  On Monday March 27, 2023 at approximately 2100 hours, Troopers from the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack responded to a two vehicle collision in the area of northbound Maryland Route 152 (Mountain Road) in the 2500 block in Harford County, Maryland.  During the course of the investigation it was revealed that a orange 2021 Chevrolet Spark bearing Maryland registration 6ES4800 was traveling southbound on Mountain Road traveling north of the residence of 2511 Mountain Road. The driver of the Chevrolet was identified as Anna Maire Deaver (W/F, DOB 10/24/2004). At that time, a black Ford Edge bearing Maryland registration 8EH0321 was traveling northbound on Mountain Road approaching 2511 Mountain Road. The operator of the Ford was identified as Jordon Michael Eckman Junior (W/M, DOB 09/06/2004). The Chevrolet failed to yield the right of way while conducting a left turn into 2511 Mountain Road, traveled directly in the traveling path of the Ford. The Chevrolet was struck on the right side by the Ford. The Chevrolet left the roadway to the right side, coming to final rest on the right shoulder area just north of 2511 Mountain Road. The Ford spun clockwise approximately 45 degrees leaving the roadway to the right side coming to a position of final rest in the concrete drainage ditch.      Section II. - Scene Description: (The following descriptions are based on the area where the collision occurred.)  Primary Roadway:  Mountain Road (Maryland Route 152) was a State of Maryland State Highway Administration maintained roadway and was constructed of asphalt. Mountain Road was a paint line divided roadway, with north and south travel lanes. Mountain Road was posted at 50 miles per hour in the area of the collision. The section of Mountain Road was not under construction and there was no road debris. The roadway was dry. At the time of the collision, traffic was light.  The travel lanes of Mountain Road in the area of the collision consisted of one northbound and one southbound lane with a shoulder area on each side of the roadway. Thecenter of the roadway was identified by a solid yellow line and intermittent yellow lines painted on the roadway surface. The solid line was for northbound traffic and the intermittent lines that were about 10 feet in length and separated by about 30 feet in length were for southbound traffic. Within those lines, Sonic Nap Alert System (SNAP) devices had been engraved into the roadway surface. SNAP devices are commonly known as rumble strips. The shoulders were divided by a white solid painted line.The edge of the roadway was an eased asphalt edge terminating into soil.   I measured the northbound lane, southbound lane and each shoulder. I measured the northbound shoulder from the edge of the asphalt to the middle of the solid white painted fog line which measured approximately 10. I measured the northbound lane from the middle of the solid white painted fog line to the middle of the solid double yellow painted lane divider which measured approximately 11 and 4. I measured the southbound lane from the middle of the solid double yellow painted lane divider to the middle of the solid white painted fog line which measured approximately 10 and 11. I measured the southbound shoulder from the middle of the solid white painted fog line to the edge of the asphalt which measured approximately 11 and 6.   Environmental Conditions:  The weather was clear. The temperature was approximately 47 degrees Fahrenheit.    Section III. - Scene Evidence:  I began walking the scene on Mountain Road going from south to north. I observed three (3) skid marks that went from Mountain Road extending to the shoulder area and then off road. An area of impact (AOI) was determined by the placement of the un-tampered post impact debris trails, pre and post impact skid marks and the position of both vehicles uncontrolled final rest. The position of final rest for the Chevrolet was marked and measured. The Chevrolets front left tire measured approximately 136 and 10 from the AOI. The Chevrolets front right tire measured approximately 134 and 6 from the AOI. The Chevrolets rear left tire measured approximately 144 and 2 from the AOI. The Chevrolets rear right tire measured approximately 142 and 2 from the AOI. The Chevrolet traveled approximately 40 from the area that it left the roadway before coming to the position of uncontrolled final rest.  The position of final rest for the Ford was marked and measured. The Fords front left tire measured approximately 112 and 5 from the AOI. The Fords front right tire measured approximately 105 and 10 from the AOI. The Fords rear left tire measured approximately 114 and 6 from the AOI. The Fords rear right tire measured approximately 108 and 10 from the AOI. I observed one (1) gouge in the dirt from the Ford. The gouges were both extended from Mountain Road towards the front for the Ford. The gouge was measured and was found to be approximately 17 and 8 in its entirety.  The scene was measured in its entirety from the beginning of pre-impact evidence to the Chevrolets position of final rest which measured approximately 153. In the area that the collision occurred, there are no businesses that are immediately surrounding the area of the collision.  The scene was documented with digital photographs taken by myself. The scene was marked utilizing orange colored florescent paint and measurements of the evidence was captured.    Section IV. - Vehicle(s) Involved:  Vehicle #1: Registration: 6ES4800  Maryland Vehicle Identification Number: KL8CB6SA6MC220756 Make: Chevrolet Model: Spark Year: 2021 Insurance Provider: Nationwide Owner: Christopher John Deaver Owners Phone Number: (470) 707-0140  Examination: The Chevrolet sustained significant structural and body damage to the front passenger side door, right fender, windshield, hood, front bumper, apron, engine compartment, wheel and suspension, roof and the A pillar areas. The Chevrolet had damage to the front left fender, left front door, rear right door and the front left tire. The interior of the Chevrolet had property throughout. While examining the interior, I observed the steering wheel, shin, curtain and seat airbags were deployed and the front left seat belt was extended in a locked position. I observed a large amount of intrusion to the right front seat position with blood pooled on the front right seat.  Vehicle #2: Registration: 8EH321  Maryland Vehicle Identification Number: 2FMDK4AK6DBA62974 Make: Ford Model: Edge Year: 2013 Insurance Provider: State Farm Owner: Melissa Eckman   Examination: The Ford sustained damage to the front of the vehicle. The vehicles front fenders, hood, front bumper, and grille were damaged from the impact. The interior of the Ford was examined. The vehicles steering wheels airbag was deployed from the impact and the front left seat belt wasextended in a locked position. The vehicle was in Park gear and was not running/idling. The headlight switch as activated.  Section V. - Person(s) Involved:  Operator Vehicle #1: Name: Anna Marie Deaver Date of Birth: 10/24/2004 Operator License Number: MD-10272602071 Address: 2511 Mountain Road, Joppa, Harford County, Maryland Injury Severity: Life Threatening Injuries Impairment: None Statement: Due to injuries sustained, Deaver was not able to provide a statement.   Operator Vehicle #2: Name: Jordon Michael Eckman Junior Date of Birth: 09/06/2004 Operator License Number: E-255-439-603-694 Address: 2398 Reckord Road, Fallston, Harford County, Maryland Injury Severity: Minor Injuries,transported by ground to Bayview Medical Center. Impairment: None  Statement: Eckman was injured during the collision and no written statement was obtained.    Witnesses: No third party witnesses were identified during the course of this investigation.    Section VI. - Follow-up Investigation:  Date: 03/28/2023 I contacted Bayview Medical Center via telephone attempting to receive an update on Deavers condition. I was told no patient was at their facility with that name. I then contacted all regional trauma centers with no success. I contacted Harford County Emergency Operations Center and was advised that Deaver was transported to Bayview Medical Center. I contacted Melissa Eckman via telephone to obtain consent to download the crash data from the Ford. She gave verbal consent. I advised her that a Trooper would be at her residence to complete the paperwork and she declined that action.   Date: 03/30/2023 Sergeant Rumaker #5661 authored a search warrant for the Chevrolet and Fords collision data. The warrant was granted by the Honorable Judge Clara Campbell and the warrants were executed on March 30, 2023.   Date: 04/10/2023 I responded to the site of the collision and obtained the sight distance for northbound and southbound Maryland Route 152 utilizing a Pro 4 Laser #552. Northbound was found to be 1246 feet from the AOI. Southbound was found to be 713.8 feet from the AOI. The measurements were sent to Sergeant Rumaker.  Date: 04/26/2023 After many unsuccessful attempts to obtain a condition of Deaver, I responded to the residence and there was no answer. I left a note with a request to be contacted.   Date: 04/28/2023  I was contacted by Christopher Deaver, the father of Anna Deaver. I was advised that if she survives, the injuries that Anna sustained would cause life altering conditions for her.    Section VII. - Analysis of Electronic Control Modules: Sergeant Rumaker conducted a vehicle download from the Chevrolet and Fords EDR modules. Refer to Sergeant Rumakers supplemental report for data.    Section VIII. - Speed Analysis: Sergeant Rumaker determined that the Chevrolet was traveling approximately 15 MPH and the Ford was traveling 71 MPH, in a posted 50 MPH zone at the time of impact. Sergeant Rumaker completed the time distance formulas and found that if the Ford was traveling at the posted speed limit that the Chevrolet would have cleared the travel lane and the Ford would not have had to complete any evasive maneuvers to avoid the collision. Refer to Sergeant Rumakers report for further information.    Section IX. - Crash Dynamics:  Vehicle 1 (Chevrolet) was traveling southbound on Maryland Route 152 (Mountain Road) north of 2511 Mountain Road, Joppa, Harford County, Maryland. Vehicle 2 (Ford) was traveling northbound on Maryland Route 152 south of 2511 Mountain Road, Joppa, Harford County, Maryland. Vehicle 1 failed to yield the right of way while conducting a left turn into 2511 Mountain Road, bearing into the direct traveling path of Vehicle 2. Vehicle 2 collided with Vehicle 1 on its right side. From the impact Vehicle 1 left the roadway to the right side, coming to a position of uncontrolled final rest in the grass/brush facing in a southbound position. From the impact with Vehicle 1, Vehicle 2 spun clockwise approximately 45 degrees, leaving the roadway to the right and coming to a position of uncontrolled final rest in the concrete drainage ditch.    Section X. - Attachments that were included in for this report:  The following items were attached to this report: 1) Automated Crash Report (ACRS MSP705200CM) 2) MSP Form 062  75 photos 3) Vehicle Storage Reports 4) Diagram prepared by TFC. Dill #6465      Conclusion:  The following conclusions are based upon the totality of this investigation, to include, the review of the documents provided to date from assisting investigators and the physical evidence accumulated. These conclusions are based upon my training, knowledge and experience as an advanced collision investigator.  During the course of the investigation, it was determained that Anna Marie Deaver was traveling southbound Mountain Road (Maryland Route 152) north of her residence at 2511 Mountain Road, Joppa, Maryland in an orange 2021 Chevrolet Spark. Jordon Michael Eckman Junior was traveling northbound on Mountain Road (Maryland Route 152) south of 2511 Mountain Road, Joppa, Maryland in a black 2013 Ford Edge. Deaver did fail to yield the right of way while conducting a left turn into the driveway of 2511 Mountain Road. Due to this, Deavers vehicle entered the direct traveling path of Eckman. Eckman subsequently struck the Chevrolet on its right side causing the Chevrolet to leave the roadway to the right, coming to a position of uncontrolled final rest in the grass/brush shoulder area. The Ford spun clockwise approximately 45 degrees and the Ford leaving the roadway, coming to a position of uncontrolled final rest in a concrete drainage ditch.  Through my investigation I found that Anna Marie Deaver is responsible for the motor vehicle collision by failure to yield right of way on left turn (TA 21-402 a) with Jordon Michael Eckman Juniors action of driving vehicle on highway at speed exceeding the limit (TA 21 801.1) as a contributing factor in this collision occurring.  Uponapproval of this case, it will be presented to the Office of the States Attorney for Harford County. A supplement will be completed for any additional investigation or charges.  All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.   Authored by: Trooper First Class Matthew Dill #6465 Bel Air Barrack 1401 Belair Road Bel Air, Maryland 21014 410-838-4101 </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/29/2023 09:42:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6465</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 11:23:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CT</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Menchey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3321</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6465</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500421</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>MSP1004</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 21:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 17:01:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6465</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/29/2023 17:01:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500421</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15910</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 21:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15910</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 17:01:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6465</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 11:15:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500421</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 21:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 11:15:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6465</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 11:15:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 17:06:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372931</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Eckman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jordon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/06/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>03/29/2023 17:06:28</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E255</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J635</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Eckman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jordon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/06/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>E255</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J635</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/29/2023 17:06:28</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2398</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Reckord</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Fallston</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21047</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2939</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.388575</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.483349</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>617</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0572</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 17:06:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 17:09:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:01</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372932</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Deaver</LastName>
               <FirstName>Anna</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/24/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/29/2023 17:09:09</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D160</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Deaver</LastName>
               <FirstName>Anna</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/24/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D160</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/29/2023 17:09:09</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2511</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mountain</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Joppatowne</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21085</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2321</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.358963</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.456405</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 17:09:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151356</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AC</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 16:59:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6465</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/29/2023 16:59:26</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 23:23:36</DateOfInfo>
         <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2FMDK4AK6DBA62974</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>EDG</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8EH0321</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8EH0321</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehConditionCode>TOTALED</VehConditionCode>
         <VehDamageCode>12</VehDamageCode>
         <VehDamageDesc>INVOLVED IN HEAD-ON COLLISION</VehDamageDesc>
         <VehicleMiscID>MVI-23-022</VehicleMiscID>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151354</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AC</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 16:59:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6465</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/29/2023 16:59:48</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 22:15:05</DateOfInfo>
         <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>KL8CB6SA6MC220756</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2021</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SPA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4D</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>ONG</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>ONG</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>ONG</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>ONG</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6ES4800</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6ES4800</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehDamageCode>11</VehDamageCode>
         <VehDamageDesc>Main impact on front passenger side.   </VehDamageDesc>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/10/2023 08:22:15</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/10/2023 08:22:15</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>CT</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/06/2023 17:35:09</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5661</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 08:22:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3321</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 14:06:31</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Detailed Crash Investigation Supplement   (For review by the MSPCrash Team)  Synopsis of Investigation:  On March 27th, 2023 at approximately 2100 hours,Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack Troopers were dispatched toa motor vehicle collision that occurred on Maryland Route 152 south of Old Mountain Road Central, Joppa, Harford County, Maryland. The collision involved two vehicles and one life-threatening injury. I, Sgt. Daniel Rumaker (ID5661) was tasked to assist Advanced Collision Investigator TFC. Matthew Dill (ID6465) with completing the imaging and analysis of event data recorders. Attached is a report documenting my assistance.  Case Status: Upon approval, this supplement will be provided to TFC. Dill for his investigation.    Author:  Sergeant Daniel R. Rumaker #5661 MSP Crash Team  North East Office 2433 Pulaski Highway North East, Maryland 21901 410-996-7838 Daniel.Rumaker@Maryland.Gov </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5661</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 08:23:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5661</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 08:27:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CT</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5555</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CT</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rumaker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5661</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/09/2023 11:01:02</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/09/2023 11:01:02</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/10/2023 08:06:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/09/2023 11:01:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3321</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 14:06:31</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Supplement Narrative:  On Wednesday, July 26, 2023, I sent this report in its entirety to State Attorney Alison Healey via departmental email.  Case remains open pending States Attorney review.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/09/2023 11:02:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6465</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/09/2023 11:04:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CT</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5555</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6465</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/15/2023 08:15:02</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/15/2023 08:15:02</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/15/2023 14:06:30</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/15/2023 08:15:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3321</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 14:06:31</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #4 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Supplement Narrative:  On Tuesday, October 31, 2023, I received notification from the Harford County States Attorneys Office in regard to their decision for charges. The Office has declined to charge any person with traffic or criminal charges in relation to this event. Attached is Harford County States Attorney Office letter head with the outlined decision.  All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.  Case closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/15/2023 08:17:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6465</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 08:21:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CT</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Menchey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3321</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6465</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500421</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15910</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>4</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/15/2023 08:15:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15910</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/15/2023 08:15:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6465</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 08:15:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500421</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>4</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/15/2023 08:15:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6465</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/15/2023 08:15:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6465</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 08:16:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>