<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002657</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/22/2023 01:31:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/22/2023 01:31:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/22/2023 01:16:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/22/2023 01:16:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI - Delgadillo</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 01:32:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5932</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/20/2023 01:36:30</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>681364</AddressId>
      <City>MDC210</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 01:32:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 03:24:13</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>681364</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Perrylawn</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Perryville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21903</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.063189</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.588739</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/22/2023 01:31:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/22/2023 01:31:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/03/2023 09:35:37</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 01:32:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:38</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23-019 MSP Unmarked Patrol Vehicle F-32 is equipped with a Mobile Recording Device. I am equipped with an Axon 3 body-worn camera. The incident was captured on both devices. Defendant: Joseluis Delgadillo (Hispanic/Male; DOB 08/31/1995) Date of Arrest: January 22, 2023 Time of Arrest: 0131 hours  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: I am trained by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration to administer standardized field sobriety tests. I am certified as a RADAR/LIDAR operator through the Maryland State Police. I am a certified Preliminary Breath Test operator through the Maryland State Police. I am certified by the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE).  VEHICLE IN MOTION (Phase 1) On Sunday, January 22, 2023, at approximately 0115 hours, I, TFC Bachu #7184, was traveling northbound on Perrylawn Drive in the area of Turnpike Drive when I observed a silver Chevrolet Camaro traveling southbound on Perrylawn Drive. The Camaro was following a white pickup truck directly in front of it too closely. I was able to observe less than one car lengths distance between the two vehicles. I made a U-turn and followed the vehicles to the intersection of Perrylawn Drive at Reservoir Road. While stopped at the light, I was able to observe the Camaro to be bearing California registration 8LDA773. The Camaro failed to use a turn signal when turning left onto Reservoir Road. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle.  PERSONAL CONTACT (Phase 2) After the vehicle came to a complete stop, I observed the driver open his door and then shut it very quickly. When I walked up and made contact with the driver, I introduced myself, gave my name and rank, and advised the driver that he was being audibly and visually recorded. Before I could advise the reason for the stop, the driver stated, I have herpes. I have herpes. My dad died yesterday. He then increased the volume on his radio and began to sing along with the song.  The driver provided his license, and I asked him to step out of the vehicle. While he was doing so, I requested that the North East Barrack start me an additional unit. The driver was the sole occupant in the vehicle and was identified by his California drivers license as Joseluis Delgadillo (Hispanic/Male; DOB 08/31/1995).  I observed Delgadillo to have slurred speech, speaking extremely fast, and continually sniffling his nose.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (Phase 3) Once additional units had arrived on scene, I asked Delgadillo if he would voluntarily submit to a Standardized Field Sobriety Test (SFST) to which he agreed.  The evaluation was performed in a parking lot on Reservoir Road at Perrylawn Drive. The surface was level, dry, and free from any obvious debris.  Delgadillo advised that he had just gotten off of work, but did not recall what time he had gotten off. He also advised that he was not under the care of a doctor for any ailment, nor did he wear glasses or contacts.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my right pointer finger was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Delgadillos eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping hishead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Delgadillos pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I asked Delgadillo if he understood the instructions, and he indicated that he did.   Lack of smooth pursuit: Present in both eyes.  Distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation: Present in both eyes.  Onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees: Present in both eyes.   Observation: Vertical gaze nystagmus: Present. Observation: Resting nystagmus: Present.  WALK AND TURN (4/8) Prior to Delgadillo performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Delgadillo was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel-to-toe. Delgadillo was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Delgadillo was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel-to-toe on every step. Delgadillo was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, Delgadillo was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Delgadillo was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Delgadillo was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Delgadillo if he understood the test, and he indicated that he did.  Instructional Stage:Cannot keep balance. Starts too soon. Walking Stage(First Nine Steps):    Actual number of steps (10 steps)  Walking Stage(Second Nine Steps): No observations. Turn: Did not complete a turn to turn himself around. Stopped after his tenth step, and then causally turned around, and began his second set of steps.  ONE LEG STAND(3/4) Prior to Delgadillo performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Delgadillo was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, one thousand-three, etc.), and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Delgadillo if he understood the test, and he indicated that he did.  Instructional Stage:No observations. Balance and Count Stage:    Raise Arms  Swaying   Hopping   PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT) Not offered.  ARREST Due to the number of clues observed, my training, knowledge, and experience, I placed Delgadillo under arrest for driving under the influence of a controlled dangerous substance (CDS) at approximately 0131 hours. Subsequently, Delgadillo was placed in my patrol vehicle and an audio version of the DR-15 Advice of Rights was played for him in English. A check of Delgadillos oral cavity was conducted at approximately 0150 hours.   Delgadillo was the transported to the North East Barrack for processing. He listened to an audio version of the DR 15 while en route to the barrack. He signed a copy of the DR 15 at approximately 0155 hours and agreed to submit to an evidentiary breath test.  Delgadillo provided a breath specimen containing an alcohol concentration of 0.00 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 0219 hours.  Due to the elimation of alcohol impairment, I concluded that the impairment displayed by Delgadillo was a result of an unknown controlled dangerous substance (CDS) that he consumed prior to operating a motor vehicle.  Before a Drug Recognition Expert (DRE) could be requested, I requested that EMS be called to check Delgadillo, as he was complaining of pain in his throat.  North East Medic 491 responded to the barrack to perform an evaluation on Delgadillo. He was subsequently transported to Union Hospital in Elkton, Maryland, at approximately 0250 hours.  Prior to leaving for the hospital, Delgadillo was provided with copies of all relevant paperwork.  I request that this case be closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7184</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 05:18:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7184</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 01:23:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Scott</LastName>
            <FirstName>Conor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7217</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kim</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6166</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bachu</LastName>
            <FirstName>Farhan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7184</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Spayd</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5369</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bachu</LastName>
            <FirstName>Farhan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7184</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bachu</LastName>
            <FirstName>Farhan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7184</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492040</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/22/2023 01:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7184</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 03:22:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7184</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 03:24:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7184</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 03:22:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:11</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366852</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Delgadillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joseluis</FirstName>
               <DOB>08/31/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 03:14:46</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D423</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J242</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Delgadillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joseluis</FirstName>
               <DOB>08/31/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D423</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J242</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 03:14:46</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1580</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Solista</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Colton</City>
               <StateCode>CA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>92324</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1977</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-117.351954</Longitude>
               <Latitude>34.083448</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>909</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>965</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8393</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7184</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 03:25:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:43</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7184</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 03:25:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:43</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7184</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 03:25:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:43</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7184</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 03:24:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7184</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 03:24:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148922</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7184</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 03:26:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7184</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 03:26:22</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1G1FA1RX5K0127299</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CAM</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>CA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8LDA773 </VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>6</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>