<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013429</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/15/2023 20:02:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/15/2023 20:02:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/15/2023 16:12:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/15/2023 16:12:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Shooting investigation that occurred at Bowie State University.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 20:02:52</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6094</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 12:12:01</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>110764</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 20:02:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 15:29:59</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>110764</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>14000</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Jericho Park</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Bowie</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20715</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.757842</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.019713</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>BOWIE STATE UNIVERSITY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/15/2023 20:02:45</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/15/2023 20:02:45</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>Y</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/29/2023 12:12:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 20:02:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 12:12:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Suspect:    Unknown   Victim:    Unknown   Evidence:    One swab suspected blood from curb at bottom of lot G  One swab suspected blood from weed pulled by Sgt Adkins  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: S+B 45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: RP45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: S+B 45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: RP45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: RP45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: RP45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: S+B 45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: RP45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: S+B 45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: Blazer45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: *--*45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: S+B 45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: RP45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: WIN 9mmauto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: 9mm Luger CBC  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: 9mm Luger CBC  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: GFL 9mm Luger  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: Sig 9mm Luger  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: TRN 22 9x19mm  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: TRN 22 9x19mm  One black Glock 21 Gen 4 with light with one live cartridge in chamber SN: BKFU439  One swab possible DNA from Black Glock 21 GEN4 SN: BKFU439  One swab possible DNA from Black Magazine and extended Magazine  6600zaywiild Instagram Result  6600zaywild Instagram Result  6600zaywild_ Instagram Result  Photo array conducted with McNeil  Stolen Property:    Due to the nature of this incident, no stolen property was captured.  Scene Processing:    Maryland State Police Crime Scene Technician N. Palmer responded to the scene and processed it for evidence. Multiple subpoenas were submitted to different entities. Interviews were conducted.   Neighborhood check:     Due to the nature of the incident no neighborhood check was conducted.   Witness information:    Jones, Izayah Jakori     B/M DOB: 12/01/2000      McNeil, Kevin     B/M DOB: 06/11/2002       Additional Information:  Training and Experience: I am a certified Police Officer in the State of Maryland With over 40 hours of training in DUI detection at the Maryland State Police Academy. The training included classroom instruction, practical application, alcohol workshops, written testing and practical application examination. During my time as a Maryland State Trooper I have arrested over 50 impaired drivers and have been trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE). Additionally, I have been recognized by the Maryland State Highway Safety Office for my Impaired Driving Enforcement. I have attended Street Narcotic Investigation Training as well as Gang Identification and awarenessprovided by the Maryland State Police. I have also attended 40 hours of Basic Criminal Investigator School provided by the Maryland State Police. I have attended an8 hours of 4th Amendment Search and Seizure Training presented by the Honorable Judge Wahlen. Furthermore, I have completed Total Traffic Stops, a drug interdiction course presented by the Northeast Counter Drug Training Center. I also completed the Heroin Interdiction Initiative hostedby Washington-Baltimore High Intensity Drug Trafficking Area and Anne Arundel County Police Department, presented by Maryland State Police Proactive Criminal Enforcement Team. During my time as a Maryland State Trooper I have arrested over 60 drug related offenses and assisted on many more. Additionally, I am a certified RADAR/LIDAR Operator in the State of Maryland. Furthermore, I have completed a 24 hour, Interview and Interrogation with Forensic Analysis. Additionally, I am certified in CastViz;CastViz is a analytical tool produced by the Federal Bureau of Investigations to map and analyze cellular data. During my time as a Maryland State Trooper I have investigated crimes such as Burglaries, Robberies, Assaults, Computer Crimes, Fraud, Theft, Drugs, Traffic offense, Threats of Violence, Weapon Offenses, Rapes, and other crimes which required traditional investigative efforts to include surveillance, interviews, evidence collection, title 3 wire taps; as well as non-conventional investigative methods such as social media use, electronic surveillance and analysis, and computer investigations.  Narrative:  On April 15, 2023, I, Corporal Z. Null 6149 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division - Central South Region, was contacted in reference to assisting with an ongoing shooting investigation that occurred at Bowie State University. Bowie State University Police (BSU) requested the assistance of Maryland State Police Crime Scene to process the scene. BSU conducted an initial investigation and CST Palmer responded to process the scene. I was informed that a firearm, further identified as a Glock G21 .45 caliber (S/NL BKU439), was recovered and was requested to conduct queries into the firearms status. The firearm was not reported stolen, nor was it registered.    On April 16, 2023, TFC Hussey, D/SGT Collier, and I met with LT Bell (BSU) to discuss the investigation and further identify investigative leads. LT Bell advised that on April 14 into April 15, 2023, a Greek Letter Organization was hosting a school sanctioned party in the G Parking lot of the campus. LT Bell advised there were approximately 500 attendees. At approximately 0130 hours as the party was coming to a close, shots were fired, and several people were fleeing the area. BSU Officers arrived at the scene and were unable to locate a victim or suspect. During the exodus, information was relayed to Officer Adkins (BSU) that a black sedan with a New York Registration was involved with the shooting. Furthermore, Officer Adkins observed shell casings and a blood trail at the scene. Due to the nature of the incident, BSU contacted Maryland State Police College Park Barrack and requested the assistance of the Maryland State Police Crime Lab. Crime Scene Technician N. Palmer responded to the scene and processed the evidence per MSP policy.    CST Palmer, photographed the scene and collected evidence. CST Palmer also advised that Sgt Rumaker of the Maryland State Police, CRASH Team, conducted a Total Station mapping of the scene (23-MSP-013350 a copy of this report and attachments are attached this report for reference). CST Palmer collected the following evidence:    One swab suspected blood from curb at bottom of lot G  One swab suspected blood from weed pulled by Sgt Adkins  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: S+B 45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: RP45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: S+B 45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: RP45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: RP45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: RP45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: S+B 45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: RP45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: S+B 45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: Blazer45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: *--*45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: S+B 45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: RP45 auto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: WIN 9mmauto  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: 9mm Luger CBC  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: 9mm Luger CBC  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: GFL 9mm Luger  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: Sig 9mm Luger  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: TRN 22 9x19mm  One live cartridge from bottom of lot G headstamp: TRN 22 9x19mm  One black Glock 21 Gen 4 with light with one live cartridge in chamber SN: BKFU439    CST Palmer also, at a later time, took two swabs from the recovered firearm. Investigators attempted to contact the Maryland State Police Forensic Sciences Division in an attempt to submit the swabs collected from the scene and the firearm. I learned that the FSD is unable to submit the swabs (believed to be that of a victim) for testing due to Federal Regulations.    Additionally, LT Bell advised that there were reports taken on the night of the incident or the following day that may aide in the investigation. The reports are summarized below:   2304-0022 (Assault) 4/15/2023 at 0216 hours     After the shooting, McNeil Jr, Kevin Scott (B/M DOB: 06/11/2003), Mack, Shaniyah (B/F NFI), and Johnson, Tanaja Monay (B/F DOB: 01/23/2001) were walking towards Henry Circle when they were approached by 3 unknown suspects (2 B/F and 1 U/M). The unknown suspect shouted derogatoryslurs towards McNeil and a fight ensued. During the altercation, Johnson advised her Michael Kors Purse which contained her wallet, keys, and school identification were taken. The suspects fled the area and no description was provided. McNeil requested Emergency Medical Services but ultimately refused being transported to the hospital.      2304-0023 (Assault) 4/15/2023 at 0200 hours     On Loop Rd near Lot G a minor collision occurred involving Steele, Sierra Monae (B/F DOB: 05/22/1998). Steele exited her vehicle in an attempt to exchange information with the other vehicle. When Steele approached the vehicle, the suspect sprayed mace in Steeles face and fled the scene. No vehicle or suspect information was provided in the report.      2304-0025 (Assault) 04/15/2023 at 1125 hours     Brown, Rajanea Chamaria (B/F DOB: 04/09/1999) contacted BSU to report lost property. Officer James - BSU responded and learned that Brown was assaulted, and her belongings were stolen. Brown reported to Officer Hames that shortly after the shooting and in the area of the shooting, she was involved in an altercation with 2 unknown B/F and 1 unknown B/M. Brown advised during the altercation her cousin Watkins, Taron DaShaun (B/F DOB: 12/15/1997) attempted to intervene and became involved in the altercation. Brown advised after the altercation she noted her Louis Votton Purse; containing her wallet, keys, and school identification; and shoes were missing. Furthermore, Brown advised Watkins purse was also missing.Brown advised in Watkins purse was a firearm further described as a 9mm firearm. Brown advised Watkins reported the stolen firearm to another agency.        Based on the information learned thus far numerous investigative tasks were identified.    Lt Bell and TFC Hussey contacted hospitals and trauma centers in Maryland and Washington D.C. in an attempt to identify any walk-in shooting victims. No victims were identified through these efforts.    I conducted an investigative inquiry into the firearm seized on-scene and into Watkins. It was learned the firearm seized on-scene, the Glock 21, is not registered and has not been reported stolen. TheBureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives (ATF) was contacted to conduct a historical investigation in an attempt to identify the owner or last person in possession of the firearm. Additionally, it was learned that Watkins has a Glock 43x 9mm (S/N: BMGW391) registered to her in Washington D.C. This firearm has not been reported stolen to date nor could I locate a police report involving Watkins and her firearm.    After the shooting, BSU sent out an alert to the Campus and Students using a mass communication platform requesting information pertaining to the shooting. Lt Bell was put in contact with an individual who wished to remain anonymous, but wanted to help investigators with the shooting investigation. TFC Hussey, D/SGT Collier, LT Bell and I spoke to the anonymous witness via phone who provided information pertaining to the shooting. The witness advised they were present at the party and witnessed the shooting. The source advised they were in the area of the DJ Booth (this is in close proximity to the shooting) when they observed two females get into an altercation with 2 other females and a male. Furthermore, the source stated they received information about the identity of the suspect but would not advise where this information came from. The sourcedid not provide a name for the shooter, but provided a description and the Instagram account of the suspect. The source provided an Instagram username of 6600zaywild and images of the suspect.    I began an inquiry into the user of this account. In an image dated April 6, 2023, an apparent self-portrait was taken and posted to the account showing a male similar in description to what the source described at the party. A slender, 1/M, approximately 20 years old with long hair. Thesource described the suspect as wearing dark clothes and a facial covering (ski mask) during the party. Iknow through my training, knowledge, and experience, that users of Instagram post images and videos that appear in a timeline, but also post images and videos to a feature that Instagram refers to as a Story. On May 4, 2023, while reviewing images posted to the accounts Story, I noted a picture of an individual wearing black clothes, and a black ski style facial covering that covers his face and head except the area around his eyes, similar to what the anonymous source described as the attire during the party. Inoted through review of the identified Instagram account, the user appears to have several distinct tattoos on his hands, arms and neck. Further investigation led investigators to identify this party as Izayah Jakori Jones (B/M DOB: 12/01/2000). I also identified two additional Instagram accounts with similar usernames that appear to also be used by Jones, 6600zaywild_ and 6600zaywiild.  Further review of the account revealed a video posted in approximately February 2022; with the video showing many bottles of Promethazine, a popular prescription medication that is often used by drug users, added to various types of soda or other flavorful drinks, to obtain a state of being high. The numerous bottles of Promethazine visible in the video indicate, based on my training, knowledge, and experience that they are intended for distribution. An additional Story post shows a video of Jones standing in front of the camera holding a bottle of soda and mixing it with Promethazine, this video indicates it was taken in March 2023.  Based on the information learned thus far, 1 subpoena was submitted to Meta Platforms Inc in reference to the identified Instagram Accounts. The following information was learned from the subpoenas.   6600zaywiild     Name: No response   Email: ajokeade@gmail10p.com   Registration Date: 01/14/2023 @ 1809:34 UTC   Registration IP: 102.89.47.120      6600zaywild     Name:*Emoji* Of The Hills   zaywildtv@gmail.com   Registration Date: 06/24/2019 @ 0223:13 UTC   Registration IP: 2601:14C:280:2E20:50E8:51A4:A9F7:3009      6600zaywild_     Name: Wild Willd Hills *Emjoi*   Email: rkalu7557@gmail.com   Registration Date: 05/07/2021 @ 1637:15 UTC   Registration IP: 103.216.184.38      Based on this information, a subpoena was submitted to Google for the Gmail accounts: ajokeade@gmail10p.com, rkalu7557@gmail.com, and zaywildtv@gmail.com. Google essentially, stated that a search warrant would be required for the account contents; based on the investigation thus far, probable cause linking the aforementioned Gmail accounts and the crime have not been established.    Based on the information learned thus far, Ibegan a further investigation into the background and possible residences of Jones. Through my investigation, I became aware of a Bureau of Alcohol Tobacco Firearms and Explosives (ATF) and Prince Georges County Police investigation that occurred in May 2022. On May 13, 2022, an ATF task force conducted an investigative refuse removal from 4903 Wickham Drive, Temple Hills Prince Georges County MD 20748. During this incident, several items of interest were located including:   Empty bottle of promethazine  5 plastic bags with trace amounts of marijuana  28 clear used plastic bags that appeared to have been used for storage of CDS based on their training and experience  1 heat sealed bag  An at home marijuana testing kit  Based on the above details and other items from their investigation, the ATF task force obtained a search and seizure warrant for the residence which was executed on June 16, 2022. During the search warrant, officers located Jones and other co-defendants. Officers identified that Jones is prohibited from possessing firearms or ammunition in Maryland due to being convicted of possessing a stolen vehicle in South Carolina in October 2020. In a bedroom they identified as being Jones, officers located 3 rounds of live handgun ammunition. Elsewhere in the residence, officers located amounts of cocaine, a Glock 22 handgun, a SIG Sauer P250 handgun, a device intended to turn a semi-automatic handgun into a full auto handgun (commonly called an auto switch) and a 7.62mm rifle, a Glock 23 handgun, a Glock 43X handgun, 20 grams of cocaine, and 382 grams of marijuana. Several parties were arrested due to this event, including Jones. Jones was indicted as a result of the evidence located on July 21, 2022, in Prince Georges County Circuit Court and charged with ten crimes, including Conspiracy to Distribute and Handgun on Person. Hearings conducted in mid-March 2023 show that Jones pled guilty to Handgun on person and Manufacturing/Distributing/PWID. A sentencing hearing is scheduled for May 24, 2023, and it appears from court records that Jones is currently not incarcerated. Several other parties arrested during this search warrant at 4903 Wickham Dr, Temple Hills MD were also indicted in Prince Georges County Circuit Court in July 2022, and are awaiting sentencing.  In addition to this, Jones was charged with several handgun related offenses on January 5, 2022, in Prince Georges County including Illegal Possession of a Regulated Firearm and Handgun on Person. Jones was scheduled to appear for a motions hearing on April 21, 2023, and failed to appear. A bench warrant was issued for his arrest on April 25, 2023, and Jones is currently wanted.    Furthermore, an investigative work-up into the Glock recovered from BSU on the night of the incident revealed the Glock 21 (SN: BKFU439) was purchased by Blue, Kyle Hunter (U/M DOB: 04/15/1994) from an FLL at Camp Lejeune, NC on November 29, 2018. On May 22, 2023, I attempted to contact Blue via phone without answer and left a message to further investigate this lead. I was later able to speak with Blue who advised he sold the aforementioned to Crawford, Casey Clarence (W/M DOB: 12/22/1998) while in North Carolina. I subsequently contact North Carolina Law Enforcement to determine the process of transferring firearms. I was advised that there is no formal process to sell firearms, and that one individual may conduct a hand to hand in person sale of a firearm.    Based on the information learned thus far, a subpoena was authored for the email addresses associated with the Instagram Subpoena response and the IP Address2601:14C:280:2E20:50E8:51A4:A9F7:3009. To date no response has been obtained from these subpoenas.    Continuing the investigation, into Jones revealed multiple CashApp accounts associated with Jones. A subpoena was submitted to CashApp in reference to accounts $6600ZayWild, $joelulsista, and $ZayWild. The response yielded no investigative leads to pursue.    On May 6, 2023, Jones was arrested by Prince Georges County Police Department in reference to an outstanding warrant. During the arrest Jones was in possession of a Glock firearm and a cellular telephone. Based on the totality of their investigation they authored a search and seizure warrant for Jones seized cellular telephone identified as a blue iPhone 13 cell phone with no case. The warrant included call logs, contact information, SMS and MMS messages, digital media, application and usage data, cell site and GPS Data, contacts, notes, internet activity, device and user identifying information and other related information between March 13, 2023, and May 6, 2023. I reviewed the information in the cellular telephone analysis and noted a picture taken by Jones at Bowie State University on April 15, 2023. The picture depicts the area of the party held at Bowie State University. Additionally, I reviewed location data for the night of the shooting. I noted Jones location data showed the following points of interest:   April 14, 2023, at 2126:38 hours - Bowie State University  April 14, 2023, at 2126:41 hours - Bowie State University  April 14, 2023, at 2342:47hours - 2434 Elvans RD SE  April 14, 2023, at 2342:54hours - 2441 Elvans Rd SE  April 15, 2023, at 0126:41hours - Bowie State University  April 15, 2023, at 0126:45hours - Bowie State University  April 15, 2023, at 0126:56hours - Bowie State University  April 15, 2023, at 1106:03hours - 1201 Ashleigh Station Ct  April 15, 2023, at 1108:34hours - 1201 Ashleigh Station Ct  April 15, 2023, at 1108:38hours - 1201 Ashleigh Station Ct  April 15, 2023, at 1109:48hours - 1201 Ashleigh Station Ct  April 15, 2023, at 1112:23hours - 1201 Ashleigh Station Ct  April 15, 2023, at 1119:05hours - 1201 Ashleigh Station Ct  April 15, 2023, at 1119:47hours - 1201 Ashleigh Station Ct  April 15, 2023, at 1124:45hours - 1201 Ashleigh Station Ct  April 15, 2023, at 1125:06hours - 1201 Ashleigh Station Ct  April 15, 2023, at 1125:22hours - 1201 Ashleigh Station Ct    It should be noted the call for the shooting occurred at 0130 hours on April 15, 2023. There was no location data for Jones between 0126 hours and 1106 hours.    On Friday, June 2, 2023, myself and other investigators attempted numerous interviews in reference to the night of the shooting.    Sgt Newcomer and I attempted to interview Watkins, Taron Dashaun (B/F DOB: 12/15/1997). We responded to 7235 Hylston St, Captiol Heights, MD, 20743 and 2300 Good Hope RD SE, Apt 822, Wahington DC, 20020 and were unable to make contact with her at either residence. I later made contact with Watkins via telephone and scheduled an interview on June 12, 2023, at the MSP Forestville Barrack.    TFC Hussey and Senior Trooper Maldonado responded to 6957 Blanche Rd, Baltimore MD, 21215 and made contact with McNeil Jr, Kevin Scott (B/M DOB: 06/11/2003) and conducted an interview. During the interview, three photo arrays were presented to McNeil. McNeil did not identify either Watkins or Brown as the individuals involved in the altercation with him. McNeil was also presented a photo array containing Jones. McNeil identified Jones and advised he was present at the party but could not identify him as the shooter due to his proximity of the shooting. McNeil advised that he was at the party with Mack and Johnson. During the party he observed Jones present at the party. When the shooting occurred he was in the parking lot of the party and on the opposite side of the DJ booth. Once the shooting occurred McNeil advised he fled the area towards the courtyard of the campus. In the area of the courtyard he was approached by an unknown male and two unknown females who began a physical altercation with Mack, Johnson, and himself. McNeil advised he heard through school gossip the shooter was identified and an unidentified friend of a friend showed him a picture of the suspected shooter but did not have any additional information related to the shooter. McNeil further advised that the victim of the shooting was an older unidentified male who was possibly grazed in the leg. McNeil was unable to provide specific details related to any part of the events that occurred at the party.  TFC Hussey and Senior Trooper Maldonado responded to 4403 Moravia Rd, Apt 8, Baltimore MD, 21206 to attempt to interview Mack, Shaniyah (B/F DOB: 10/06/2002). They were not able to make contact with anyone at the residence and left contact information. Senior Trooper Maldonado was later contacted by an individual who identified themselves as Macks mother who stated she would have Mack reach out. On June 12, 2023, I was able to make contact with Mack via phone at 240-313-6276 and an interview will be conducted at a later time.    Corporal DiToto and TFC Ruggles responded to 6674 Ducketts Ln, Elkridge MD, 21075 in an attempt to interview, Johnson, Tanaja Monay (B/F DOB: 01/23/2001).They were not able to make contact with anyone at the residence and left contact information. To date I have not been able to make contact with Johnson.    Corporal DiToto and TFC Ruggles responded to 2513 Lewis Ave, Suitland MD, 20746 in an attempt to interview, Brown, Rajanea Chamana (B/F DOB: 04/09/1999).They were not able to make contact with anyone at the residence and left contact information. To date I have not been able to make contact with Brown.    On June 12, 2023, I was able to make contact with Crawford and questioned him in reference to the recovered firearm. I confirmed Blue sold Crawford the aforementioned firearm. Crawford advised he separated from the Military in November 2021 and moved in with his mother who resides in Montgomery Village. In April 2022, Crawford moved from his mothers residence to Greenbelt Maryland. Crawford further advised his property was in storage until approximately May 2022. In May 2022, Crawford advised his firearm was missing, and he failed to report it to a police jurisdiction. In November 2022, Crawford moved from Greenbelt to 20418 Apple Harvest Cir, Germantown MD. I asked Crawford if he has been to Bowie State University, and he advised he was there one time to pick up a friend of his wife during daytime hours but does not remember the date of that of his trip. Furthermore, Crawford advised he had timesheets from work that showed he worked in Chantilly, VA until 1800 hours on April 14, 2023, and checked in at Planet Fitness at 1925 hours. Furthermore, Crawford advised he, his wife, and child departed for New York at approximately 0300 hours on April 15, 2023. On June 12, 2023, I spoke to ASA Caldwell of the Prince Georges County States Attorneys Office who declined prosecution of Crawford for failing to report his firearm lost or stolen within 72 hours.    On June 12, 2023, I waited for Watkins at the Forestville Barrack. Watkins never showed for the scheduled interview. I attempted to contact Watkins via phone on numerous occasions without any response.    Investigators have not been able to locate any of the aforementioned persons identified from the BSU reports.    On July 18, 2023, I responded to the Upper Marlboro Detention to conduct a recorded interview with Jones. The interview was recorded and a copy of the interview was later submitted as evidence at the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack. Jones was read a Maryland State Police Advice of Miranda Rights (MSP 180) verbatim. Jones waived his rights and agreed to speak to me about my investigation. During the interview Jones confirmed he was present at the time of the shooting but denied any involvement with the shooting. Jones did not provide any additional information which would aid in the investigation. I later reviewed Jones recorded jail calls. During multiple calls Jones spoke of the interview but continued to deny any involvement.    No additional investigative leads have been identified as a result of this investigation.    This case remains open pending results from the casings collected by CST Palmer.    All events occurred in Prince Georges County, MD.  Case: Open Corporal Z. Null 6149</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 13:22:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 11:06:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ortiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Angel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5858</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CVED</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0568</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Morrison</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6069</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CVED</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Waner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Rodney</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4852</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Strine</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6972</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6931</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CVED</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ramirez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gabriel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6307</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Madera</LastName>
            <FirstName>Janidy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7449</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ware</LastName>
            <FirstName>Traevon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7467</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Reily</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7338</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CVED</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Walther</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7066</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Speak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7219</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Webb</LastName>
            <FirstName>Noah</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7303</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>NIKODEMSKI</LastName>
            <FirstName>JONATHAN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7510</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathanael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7454</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oleyar</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6495</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Heath</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4437</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Houck</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mitchell</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7577</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bowling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Caleb</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7419</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stacey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7390</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Skutovas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robertas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7332</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Murray</LastName>
            <FirstName>Niall</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7580</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Olds</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7581</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Whitmore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6094</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Null</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zakery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6149</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502836</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1425</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>52</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 16:12:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1425</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 11:49:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 11:49:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 11:51:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377919</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Jones</LastName>
               <FirstName>Izayah</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jakori</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/01/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16595788E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 11:48:46</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Jones</LastName>
               <FirstName>Izayah</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jakori</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/01/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16595788E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 11:48:46</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4903</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Wickham</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Temple Hills</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.924343</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.797276</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>416</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5444</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 11:51:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/26/2023 08:32:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/26/2023 08:32:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/29/2023 12:12:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/26/2023 08:32:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 12:12:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Narrative:   To date, the last investigative lead to follow up on is the firearm analysis by the Maryland State Police Forensic Sciences Division. On September 6, 2023, I contacted MSP FSD and learned that this evidence has still not been assigned for analysis.    This case remains open pending FSD follow up.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/26/2023 08:34:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/26/2023 08:35:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Whitmore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6094</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Null</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zakery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6149</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/22/2023 13:57:33</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/22/2023 13:57:33</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/29/2023 12:12:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/22/2023 13:57:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 12:12:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Narrative:   On November 22, 2023, I received a National Integrated Ballistics Information Network (NIBIN) lead related to the 9mm casings that were recovered from this investigation. The NIBIN lead reference a shooting which occurred June 2, 2023, at approximately 2200 hours, at the Temple Hills Neighborhood Park (5200 Hagan Rd, Temple Hills); case number 23-001062.    In short, the report states that a shooting occurred during a large unsanctioned party at the park. On June 3, 2023, the victim walked into an area Hospital for treatment to a gun shot wound to the leg. The victim advised they were involved in an altercation with unknown individuals and as he was running away was shot in the leg. The Maryland National Capital Park Police handled the investigation but had not developed any suspects in their investigation. A copy of the report is attached to this investigation.    Based on the totality of the circumstances, this case is considered suspended. If additional leads are developed, follow up will be conducted in the future.  Case: Suspended Corporal Z. Null 6149</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/22/2023 13:59:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/22/2023 14:14:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Whitmore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6094</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Null</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zakery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6149</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502836</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>04</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1425</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>52</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>2</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/22/2023 13:57:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1425</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/22/2023 13:57:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/22/2023 13:58:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>