<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-005329</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/11/2023 02:11:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/11/2023 02:11:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/11/2023 01:51:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/11/2023 01:51:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI / DWI 23-96-031 / Poss of Handgun</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 02:11:44</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1773</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/23/2023 08:24:32</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>BALTIMORE AVE/ 7TH ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>683861</AddressId>
      <City>MDC208</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 02:11:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 16:42:33</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>683861</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Baltimore</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.08269</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.3381</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>600-699 BALTIMORE AVE / 100-104 7TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/11/2023 02:11:41</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/11/2023 02:11:41</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/20/2023 09:33:59</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 02:11:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI AND POSSESSION OF HANDGUN DUI CASE # 23-96-031 SUSPECT: CHERRON BOOKER 2/12/1979 LICENSE # A65463128 VA DUI CITATION #4570URD SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER: UNKNOWN ACCIDENT INVOLVED: NO VIDEO: MARYLAND STATE POLICE UNIT V-5 EQUIPPED WITH VIDEO RECORDING EQUIPMENT ITEMS SIEZED: SCCV MODEL CPX-1 (S/N: 681280) WITH AMMUNITION NARRATIVE  Phase #1 - Vehicle In Motion: On 2/11/2023 2023 at 0151 hours, I, TFC Brader was operating unmarked police vehicle in the downtown area of Ocean City, Worcester County, MD. Ocean City Dispatch broadcasted a vehicle lookout for a white Ford SUV bearing Virginia tags driving the wrong way on the posted one-way Baltimore Ave at Wicomico Street.  I, TFC Brader located a white Ford Escape (SUV) bearing Virginia Reg TXN6485 traveling northbound on Baltimore Ave prior to North Division Street.  I observed the vehicle in lane 1. I observed the vehicle to drift to the right, crossing into lane 2. The vehicle jerked back to the left into lane 1.  In the area of North Division Street, I observed the vehicle to drift to the left, nearly striking the curb before drifting to the right in lane 1.  In the area of 1st street, I observed the vehicle drift to the left, coming very close to a telephone pole on the street corner.  I continued to observe the vehicle drift left and right in lane 1.  In the area of 3rd street, I observed the vehicle drift to the right, crossing into lane 2 by approximately two feet before drifting to the left back into lane 1.  I observed the vehicle to accelerate, appearing to travel above the posted speed limit of 30 MPH. I activated my in car Kustom Golden Eagle Radar unit in the front antenna same direction moving mode and recorded a speed of 43 MPH in the posted 30 MPH zone. My radar unit was tested and found to be operating properly. I am a certified radar operator through the Maryland State Police.  I continued to observe the vehicle fail to maintain its lane as it was swerving back and forth.  In the area of 6th street, I observed the vehicle drift to the right, crossing into lane 2 by approximately two feet.  I activated my emergency lights and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle came tp a stop in lane 1.  Phase #2 - Personal Contact I approached drivers side window and explained to the driver for the reason of the traffic stop. While speaking with the driver, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person as she spoke. I observed the drivers eyes to be bloodshot and glassy with her slow speech. The driver was the sole occupant of the vehicle. The driver stated she thought the speed limit was 40. I asked why she was not maintaining her lane and she stated because the speed limit has been changing. I advised the driver the speed limit has not changed.  I requested the drivers license and registration. The driver, held her hands in the air and stated Im reaching for it. I asked the driver how many alcoholic beverages she consumed and she stated she had a martini. I asked the driver 1 martini? And she stated yes sir. The driver retrieved her wallet from her coat pocket. I asked the driver where she was coming from, and she stated the Cork Bar. I asked the driver where she was going and she stated her hotel.  I observed the driver to retrieve her VA drivers license out of wallet and hand it to me. The drivers license fell between the inside of the door and the drivers seat. The driver opened the door. As the driver located the license on the floor, I observed a handgun placed in the drivers side door pocket of the vehicle.  The driver provided her VA License and I identified her as Cherron Booker (DOB:2/12/1979).  I requested Booker to exit the vehicle and she stated you asked me for the registration. I again asked Booker to exit the vehicle because I located a handgun within her reach. I positioned my body near the door pocket between myself and the handgun. Booker removed her seat belt. Booker continued to occupy herself with her wallet. I told Booker to stop and to exit the vehicle and she stated she is.  I again asked Booker to exit the vehicle and she stated GEEZ. I stated to Booker that I needed her to exit the vehicle. Booker continued to mess with her wallet so I grabbed onto Bookers sleeves because she was not following my commands. I told Booker I needed to see her hands. Booker stated sir Im just putting my stuff back in. Booker stated Please stop as myself and TFC Kreiling continued to ask her to exit the vehicle. Booker grabbed her cell phone. I stated that there was a gun and Booker stated yes sir its registered. I placed the gun on the windshield of the vehicle to remove it within the immediate reach of Booker since she was uncooperative. Booker refused to exit the vehicle and stated dont touch me. Booker stated Im not doing anything sir. Booker began to cry and shout stating shes just trying to get to her hotel. Booker stated the gun is registered.  Eventually, Booker exited the vehicle. I asked Booker to walk to the front of my vehicle and she did.  The handgun was secured in my patrol vehicle. The handgun was a SCCV Model CPX-1 (S/N: 681280). The gun did not come back registered or stolen. Phase #3 - Pre Arrest Screening Booker continued to cry stating she did not know what was going on. Booker mentioned she was coming from the cork bar and going to the Aloft Hotel. I asked Booker if she was on any medications and she stated no. I asked Booker if she is wearing contacts and she stated no. I asked Booker if she has any balance issues and she stated no. I asked Booker if she is in overall good health and she stated yes.  While speaking with Booker, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. I continued to observe Bookers eyes to be bloodshot and glassy with slow speech.   I observed Booker to be wearing dress and shoes with a jacket.  Booker agreed to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. I began with the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Resting Nystagmus: NO Equal Tracking: YES Equal Pupil Size: YES  Lack of smooth pursuit: Present in both eyes Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation: Present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees: Present in both eyes   Total Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Clues6 of 6  Walk and Turn I next explained and demonstrated the Walk and Turn Test to Booker. Booker removed her shoes. Weather: Clear Surface: Flat blacktop surface free of any debris Instruction Stage Broke the Instructional Stage Position, contrary to my instructions. Began walking down the line, contrary to my instructions. I asked Booker to stop because I was not completed with my explanation and demonstration. Booker began to cry stating she felt like she was being targeted and that she has no criminal record. I reexplained this test and Booker stated she understood. Walking Stage 1st 9 Missed heel to toe Stepped off line on step 8 Took 8 steps, contrary to my instruction Raised hands greater than 6 inches Turn Completed Walking Stage 2nd 9 Stops walking after turn and had to be instructed what to do next.  Missed heel to toe on step 1 Steps off line on step 4 Takes a total number of 4 steps, contrary to my instructions. Total Walk and Turn Clues7 of 8  One Leg Stand I next explained and demonstrated the One Leg Stand Test. Booker began the test my raising her right foot. Weather: Same as Above Surface: Same as Above Seconds 0-10 Booker immediately swayed to her left and out her foot down. Hopped Raised arms -Booker stated I cant do this.   Total One Leg Stand Clues 4 of 4  Preliminary Breath Test Booker was offered a preliminary breath test. She refused and began to question me as to the traffic stop. Arrest and Transport At 0210 hours, I placed Booker under arrest. Bookers mouth was checked. Booker began to beg me to not arrest her. Booker then became uncooperative and would not walk to my police vehicle. Booker began to yell telling me to taker her handcuffs off. I requested an OCPD caged vehicle to transport Booker due to her actions. Bookers vehicle was towed from the scene.      I did not locate any addional contraband inside of the vehicle. I did locate a clear cup containing an alcoholic beverage placed in the center console of the vehicle. It appeared the cup was recently placed inside the center console because it still contained ice, and it did not spill. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the liquid.  OCPD Caged vehicle arrived. Booker was placed into the vehicle and transported to the Barrack.  Upon arrival at the barrack, Booker was placed into the cell.  I provided Booker with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. I played the MVA Audio Version of the DR-15 Advice of Rights to Booker, while she was in the cell and after the recording was completed, Booker advised she agrees to submit to the breath test. Breath Test: Booker was removed from the cell and completed her 20 minute observation period in front of me after her mouth was checked. I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Bookers breath and person as she spoke to me. I continued to observe Bookers eyes to be bloodshot and glassy with slow speech.  Cpl. Shockley, a certified Intoximeter Operator contacted Booker. At 0338 hours, Cpl. Shockley administered the Intoximeter Breath test with the result of .17 grams of alcohol per 210L of breath.  Booker stated the gun was hers and legal. Booker did not possess a Maryland Carry Permit. I asked Booker if she had a Virginia Carry Permit and she stated no.  Processing: The handgun, magazine and ammunition were submitted to Temp. Storage. MSP 67 and MSP 63 were completed per policy.  While back in the cell, Booker continued to be uncooperative, hitting the cell door and yelling.  Initial Appearance: Booker had her initial appearance with the Commissioner and was held on a bond. Booker was transported to the Worcester County Jail.  Booker was charged with the following: 1) Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol 21-902(a1) 2) Driving While Impaired by Alcohol 21-902(b1) 3) Driving under the influence per se 21-902 4) Transport a handgun under the influence 5) Did transport a loaded handgun in a vehicle 6) Did transport a handgun in a vehicle upon the roads used by public.  All events did occur in Worcester County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 10:12:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6714</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 12:48:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kreiling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Chad</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7113</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brader</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6714</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shockley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4814</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brader</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6714</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brader</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6714</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494715</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0175</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0175</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:03:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6714</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 17:11:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494715</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>6 5210</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>6 5210</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:03:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6714</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 17:09:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494715</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:03:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6714</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 17:10:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494715</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:03:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6714</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 17:11:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494715</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:03:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6714</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 17:11:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>43</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:03:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:40</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368808</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Booker</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cherron</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Fayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/12/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 16:47:34</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Booker</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cherron</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Fayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/12/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 16:47:34</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>15007</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Creekpointe</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>L</SubNumber>
               <City>Midlothian</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>23114</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.675209</Longitude>
               <Latitude>37.466945</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>804</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>519</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8320</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:12:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:12:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:12:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:12:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:03:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6714</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 17:03:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149728</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:03:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6714</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 17:03:15</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ECP</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>TXN6485</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:14:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6714</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 17:14:06</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>MSPPI</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <SerialNumber>681280</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243427</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLU</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>SCCY </Make>
         <Model>CPX-1</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:14:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6714</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 17:14:50</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>ACC</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243428</Property_ID>
         <Make>SCCY</Make>
         <Model>Magazine</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6714</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 17:15:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6714</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 17:15:14</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>424</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243429</Property_ID>
         <Make>9mm Luger</Make>
         <Model>Ammunition</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>