<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012756</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/10/2023 17:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/10/2023 17:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/10/2023 16:31:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/10/2023 16:31:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI CHRISTIAN DAILEY</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 17:54:06</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1773</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/28/2023 12:44:37</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY/ OLD OCEAN CITY BLVD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>587183</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 17:54:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 19:10:10</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>587183</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>BLVD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.195509</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.341599</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 / 346</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50 / 346</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 / 346 CENTER MEDIAN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50 /346</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>50 / 346</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10325-10489 OCEAN GTWY / 10551-10554 OLD OCEAN CITY BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>8900-9248 OCEAN GTWY / 9380-9430 OLD OCEAN CITY BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>9250-9498 OCEAN GTWY / 9380-9430 OLD OCEAN CITY BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10324-10488 OCEAN GTWY / 10453-10549 OLD OCEAN CITY BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10490-10522 OCEAN GTWY / 10454-10550 OLD OCEAN CITY BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10491-10621 OCEAN GTWY / 10551-10554 OLD OCEAN CITY BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10324-10488 OCEAN GTWY / 10551-10554 OLD OCEAN CITY BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10524-10698 OCEAN GTWY / 10454-10550 OLD OCEAN CITY BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10490-10522 OCEAN GTWY / 10453-10549 OLD OCEAN CITY BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/10/2023 17:54:01</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/10/2023 17:54:01</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/23/2023 13:32:51</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 17:54:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:47</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Driver: Christian Karla Dailey MD License: MD10273434805 DUI #: 23-96-081 Video: Yes, Cpl Lenz and WCSO also on scene.  This report is a summary and is notpurported to havecaptured every detail that was recorded on video.  Narrative: On 4/10/2023 at approximately 1633 hours, I, TFC Zaykoski along with other Troopers were dispatched to the area of eastbound US Route 50 and the Worcester County Line to attempt to locate a black GMC Acadia with MD Registration 6FG2016. This vehicle was the subject of 911 calls reporting it to be driving erratically and all over the roadway, possibly intoxicated. One caller indicated that the vehicle almost struck a marked Ocean City Police vehicle in the area of US Route 50 and Forrest Grove Road.  Troopers attempted to locate the vehicle but were unable to find it. A short time later, at approximately 1709 hours, multiple additional 911 calls were received about this same exact vehicle, again driving all over the roadway in a dangerous manner. Callers reported the vehicle was now traveling eastbound on US Route 50 in the area of MD Route 90 (Second caller: 301-325-2085, third caller: 443-223-4267, fourth caller: 443-953-0091).  Callers reported the vehicle was varying speeds, running on and off the roadway, drifting between lanes, and it appeared that the female driver was passed out at the wheel.  Vehicle in Motion: Cpl. E. Lenz located the vehicle, a black GMC Acadia MD 6FG2016 in the area of eastbound US Route 50 and MD Route 346. Cpl. E. Lenz conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle in the area of eastbound US Route 50 and Caleb Road. See his supplement for his observations.  Personal Contact: I arrived to assist. I spoke with the driver, who Cpl E. Lenz identified by her drivers license as Christian Dailey. She had initially told Cpl. Lenz that the vehicle had mechanical issues. She then told me she was very tired. She appeared to be in a daze or confused state and was having trouble forming sentences. He speech was slurred and sometimes in-coherent. She was unable to sit still and constantly fidgeting and contorting her body. She told me she was leaving from the Salisbury area after getting food with her boyfriend and heading back home to Poplar Road, Berlin.  Pre-Arrest Screening: I felt the need to investigate further whether or not she was impaired and otherwise safe to operate a motor vehicle based on the multiple 911 calls and her unusual state that I observed. Her behavior and mannerisms seemed to be consistent with someone under the influence of a stimulant drug. I had her exit the vehicle to continue my investigation.  She constantly was moving and shaking her head, biting her lips, fidgeting, twisting, moving her hands and arms, bending over, and pacing around. She said she ran off the road because she was tired. She denied taking any alcohol, medicine, or drugs. She said she was sick. She was leaning and touching the vehicle many times.  She said she has a metal plate in her leg but denied any issues with her eyes or vision. She said she takes Aleve liquid gels for being sick.   She denied the need for EMS after I asked and offered to call an ambulance multiple times.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test (HGN): 0 HGN I explained the instructions. I told her to stand with her hands at her side and to follow my pen with her eyes. I held my pen twelve (12) to fifteen (15) inches from her eyes, slightly above eye level. She did not display any resting nystagmus. Her pupils were equal in size and tracked equally. Bell displayed:  -Zero of the standardized clues of HGN, however, her eyes were not moving in a smooth or normal fashion. They would dart side to side as if he had no control over her eye movement. -She could not stand still and was swaying side to side, forwards and backwards. -She raised her arms for balance. -Fell backwards and caught her balance on the vehicle hood.  Walk and Turn (WAT): 7/8 clues I explained the test and directed her to the starting position. I told her she will be taking nine steps in a line in a heel-toe fashion. I demonstrated the procedure. On her last step, to keep her front foot planted and she is to take short choppy steps and turn around to take nine steps back. I told her to keep her hands at her sides and to count out loud what step she is on. She said she did not have any questions.  Clue 1: Cant maintain balance in starting position. Stumbled, used arms for balance, could not stand still. Clue 2: Started too soon. Clue 3: Arms for balance. Clue 4: Missed heel-to-toe. Clue 5: Stepped off the line. Clue 6: Improper Turn. Clue 7: Stopped walking.  -She gave up after the first series of 9 steps. -Nearly fell down.  One Leg Stand (OLS): 3/ 4 Clues I explained and demonstrated the test. I told her she will be lifting any foot of her choosing and hold it six inches off the ground, the height of a soda can or dollar bill. She is to keep her leg straight and hands at her side. She is to count upward in the fashion of one thousand one, one thousand two upwards until about thirty seconds. She did not have any questions.  Clue 1: Put foot down. Clue 2: Sway. Clue 3: Arms for balance.  She stopped after a few moments and gave up.  Alphabet: C to M. She took a few moments and then sang the alphabet from C to Z.  PBT: 0.00  Arrest Based on the above facts she was placed under arrest for DUI/CDS Drugs at 1736 hours. The DR-15A Advice of Rights audio was played while she followed along with printed copy on the screen.  Intoximeter: REFUSED  She was released from the barrack on citations.   All events occurred in Worcester County, MD (initial calls started in Wicomico County). Case closed      </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7068</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 02:30:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7068</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 03:03:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lenz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4839</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zaykoski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7068</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zaykoski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7068</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zaykoski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7068</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502160</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/10/2023 17:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7068</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 19:10:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7068</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 19:11:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7068</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 19:10:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:26</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>9285</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dailey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Karla</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/07/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/16/2014 20:53:52</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dailey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Karla</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/07/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/16/2014 20:53:52</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9049</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>POPLAR</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>BERLIN</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.21696797785455</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.31114927927183</Latitude>
               <SubBeat>966</SubBeat>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>359</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2146</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/16/2014 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>600</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5467</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/07/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7068</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 19:11:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7068</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 19:11:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7068</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 19:10:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7068</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 19:10:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/23/2023 10:41:05</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/23/2023 10:41:05</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/23/2023 13:32:51</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 10:41:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:47</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This traffic stop was captured in my Axon Body Cam and the MVC in V-21.    On 4/10/2023 at approximately 1633 hours, I was on routine patrol in marked MSP cruiser V-21 when I was dispatched to the area of eastbound US Route 50 and the Worcester County Line to attempt to locate a black GMC Acadia with MD Registration 6FG2016. This vehicle was the subject of 911 calls reporting it to be driving erratically and all over the roadway, possibly intoxicated. TFC Zaykoski and I attempted to locate the vehicle for several minutes.    By now, the Berlin Barrack hadreceived numerous calls, in which the drivers and passengers consistently reported that they observed what appeared to be an intoxicated operator driving the above described GMC Acadia, swerving across lane markings, erratic traveling speeds, from 10 mph travel speeds to highway speed, 55-60 mph. The GMC also nearly struck other motor vehicles, including a marked OCPD police vehicle.    I was stationary in the crossover US Rt 50/ Ocean Gateway, observing eastbound traffic whenI observed the GMC, E/B US Rt 50 at MD Rt 346/ Old Ocean City Road, in lane #2. As the GMC SUV passed my position, I observed as the female operator who was later identified as Christian Dailey striking the steering wheel simultaneously with both hands. I positioned my vehicle behind the black GMC, and observed as it traveled approximately 10 mph in a 55 mph zone, drifted to the right onto the shoulder line marking. I continued to observe, as the GMC then drifted left then the vehicle very rapidly jerked left and right, because the driver jerked the steering wheel left and right. I activated my vehicles emergency equipment, and observed as the GMC then drifted onto the right shoulder, but straddled the white shoulder line marking for 100-150 feet, finally coming to a stop on the right shoulder, E/B US Rt 50 at Caleb Road.    Upon contact with the driver, I identified her as Christian Dailey by her Maryland drivers license photograph. I explained to Dailey why I stopped her and I observed that she was unable to sit still. Dailey repeatedly touched her face and mouth and as I spoke to her, she moved her head rapidly as she looked up, down and past me.    TFC Zaykoski #7068 responded to assume the traffic stop investigation. See his report for further information.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 10:42:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4839</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 13:20:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lenz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4839</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>