<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002015</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/17/2023 15:09:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/17/2023 15:09:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/17/2023 15:08:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/17/2023 15:08:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Distribution</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 15:09:15</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5464</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/16/2023 11:27:49</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DSM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>10702</AddressId>
      <City>MDC119</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 15:09:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/26/2023 16:11:22</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>10702</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>829</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Fieldcrest</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Cambridge</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21613</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.05871</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.547519</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>DORCHESTER DETENTION CENTER</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>Dorchester County EMS-Emergency Management</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>DORCHESTER COUNTY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MSP CAMBRIDGE DETACHMENT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>DORCHESTER SHERIFFS DEPARTMENT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/17/2023 15:09:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/17/2023 15:09:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>Y</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40F</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/06/2023 21:55:53</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 15:09:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5464</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/16/2023 11:27:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>During the week of January 15, 2023, I S/Tpr. Morton of the Dorchester County Narcotics Task Force (DCNTF) initiated a distribution of controlled dangerous substance investigation, regarding Brian Jermaine Wongus of 639 Robbins Street Alex Way, Cambridge, Dorchester County, Maryland. I request this case remain open pending further investigation.  All the above events occurred in Dorchester County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/26/2023 16:12:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/26/2023 16:15:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tyler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Carl</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Morton </LastName>
            <FirstName>Tony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5478</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/18/2023 12:05:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/18/2023 12:05:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>Y</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40F</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/06/2023 21:55:53</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 12:05:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5464</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/16/2023 11:27:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>TARGET: Brian Jermaine WONGUS B/M DOB: 7/9/88  NARRATIVE:   During the month of December 2022, your Affiant of the Dorchester County Narcotics Task Force hereinafter referred to as DCNTF initiated an investigation of Brian Jermaine WONGUS (Date of Birth-7/9/88).  During the month of December 2022, I, Your Affiant of the Maryland State Police (MSP) currently assigned to the Dorchester County Narcotics Task Force (DCNTF), received information about an African-American male distributing crack-cocaine, cocaine throughout Dorchester County, Maryland. Through the investigation, this male was identified as Brian Jermaine WONGUS hereinafter referred to as WONGUS, date of birth: 7/9/86. As a result of investigative techniques, Your Affiant was able to develop probable cause for a search and seizure warrant of 639 Robbins Street Cambridge, Dorchester County, Maryland which included curtilage and all outbuildings. Your Affiant was also able to obtain a search and seizure warrant for WONGUS person. Your Affiant presented electronically the Application for Search and Seizure Warrants to the Honorable Judge William Jones of the Circuit Court for Dorchester County. Judge Jones reviewed and signed the aforementioned Search and Seizure Warrants on July 31, 2023.   On August 3, 2023, before the execution of the aforementioned search and seizure warrant, WONGUS was observed operating a white 2017 Dodge Charger displaying Maryland registration 3FG7603 at approximately 0908 hours. Your Affiant identified WONGUS through previous surveillance and noted that WONGUS was wearing at the time a white tank top and red shorts. Your Affiant observed WONGUS exit the drivers seat of the aforementioned vehicle after parking at his residence at 639 Robbins Street, Cambridge, Dorchester County, Maryland. It should be noted that WONGUS has been seen operating this vehicle previously by your Affiant on several occasions and that its known by a Motor Vehicle Administration check to be registered to John Henry Dawson and Anna Cephas Dawson of Cordova, Maryland.  On August 3, 2023, at approximately 0912 hours, your Affiant observed an unknown black male wearing a blue t-shirt and white pants, and a black backpack riding a bicycle to 639 Robbins Street, Cambridge, Dorchester County, Maryland. At approximately 0912 hours, your Affiant observed the unknown black male hand WONGUS something from his hand. WONGUS was observed going inside the white Dodge Charger displaying Maryland registration 3FG7603 and grabbing what appeared to be a black plastic bag. WONGUS was then observed to sit in a chair located on the porch of the aforementioned residence at which point he began to manipulate the item located in the black plastic bag. WONGUS was then observed handing the unknown black male with the blue t-shirt an item that came from the black bag. A short time later the unknown black male terminated his contact with WONGUS. It is your Affiants belief that the transaction between WONGUS and the unknown male was a hand-to-hand with controlled dangerous substance. Your Affiant knows a hand-to-hand can be further described as a transaction involving the illegal sale of an amount of controlled dangerous substance for an amount of U.S. currency. This transaction usually occurs in a discreet manner away from the public eye to hinder and elude the detection of law enforcement. It is your Affiants belief that WONGUS was selling an amount of CDS to the individual for U.S. currency and that inside the black bag that was in the possession of WONGUS was an amount of CDS.  On August 3, 2023, at approximately 1040 hours, your Affiant observed WONGUS operating the same white Dodge Charger displaying Maryland registration 3FG7603. WONGUS was observed exiting the vehicle and at that time WONGUS had a white T-shirt with red shorts. WONGUS was observed making contact with an unknown white male operating a grey truck at which time WONGUS then reached inside the drivers seat of the white Dodge Charger which he was operating. As WONGUS was still inside the vehicle members of DCNTF, members of Dorchester County Sheriffs Office CID, and members of the Maryland State Police executed the search and seizure of WONGUS at approximately 1042 hours.  Members of the Maryland State Police S.T.A.T.E. Team were sent to execute the search and seizure warrant for 639 Robbins Street, Cambridge, Dorchester County, Maryland at 1053 hours.   The items listed below were located on WONGUS person and were seized by Your Affiant and submitted as evidence:     text-align:justify"&gt;One black wallet (Returned) with Misc. denominations of U.S. Currency located in the front left pocket of WONGUS red shorts. (Approximately $245.00)    The items listed below were located at 639 Robbins Street, Cambridge, Dorchester County, Maryland by Your Affiant and seized and submitted as evidence:     text-align:justify"&gt;One clear plastic baggie containing one rock of crack cocaine.        text-align:justify"&gt;One clear empty baggie containing trace amounts of CDS residue, located in Bedroom #1.      text-align:justify"&gt;One clear plastic baggie containing a white rock-like substance, suspected crack cocaine.       text-align:justify"&gt;One black iPhone located in bedroom #2    I located several clothes and shoes that would fit the description and build of WONGUS inside Bedroom #1. WONGUS later advised that Bedroom #1 was his room and that Bedroom #2 was his sons room. Your Affiant also located WONGUS Maryland Drivers license amongst credit cards that displayed his name within a wallet located in his pocket. It should be noted that at no point during the search did your Affiant or members of DCNTF locate any pill bottles or prescriptions for Oxycodone. The above-located suspected CDS were all identified through my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper. In addition to the located CDS, several empty plastic baggies were observed in the kitchen of the residence.   Throughout this investigation, WONGUS was known to operate several vehicles, one being a white Dodge Charger displaying Maryland registration 3FG7603 which was located in front of 639 Robbins St., Cambridge, Dorchester County, Maryland. Cpl. Orndorff of the Maryland State Police and his K-9 Ruthie conducted a K-9 scan of the aforementioned Dodge Charger which displayed Maryland registration 3FG7603. K-9 Ruthie was positively alerted to the odor of narcotics within the vehicle. After the alert, the vehicle was then searched.  The items listed below were located inside a white 2017 Dodge Charger displaying Maryland registration 3FG7603, by Your Affiant and seized and submitted as evidence:     text-align:justify"&gt;One black plastic bag   1A) One clear plastic baggie containing a white rock-like substance suspected crack cocaine. (41.6 grams)  1B) One clear plastic baggie containing 15 clear plastic baggies of white rock-like substance suspected crack cocaine. (10.8 grams)  1C) One clear plastic baggie containing 19 oxycodone pills. (2.6 grams)     text-align:justify"&gt;One rose gold iPhone with a black phone case    Based upon the items seized and the totality of the evidence regarding the search seizure warrants it is my belief that items seized are indicative of possession with intent to distribute CDS more specifically crack cocaine. Your Affiant knows through my training, knowledge, and experience as a narcotics investigator that the located CDS was cocaine and oxycodone. No smoking devices were located or items that could be utilized to introduce the aforementioned CDS into an individuals body which your Affiant would consider to be an indicator of possession with intent to distribute CDS. The money located was in small denominations which your Affiant would consider indicative of possession with intent to distribute CDS.  All above occurred in Dorchester County, MD.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 15:56:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 12:33:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tyler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Carl</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Morton </LastName>
            <FirstName>Tony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5478</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491398</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0233</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/03/2023 10:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0233</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 14:05:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:11:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491398</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/17/2023 15:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 14:10:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:10:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>C</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 16:01:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:06:43</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>306695</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Wongus</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jermaine</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/09/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13212475E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>05/11/2021 11:17:02</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W522</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Wongus</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jermaine</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/09/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13212475E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>W522</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/11/2021 11:17:02</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>639</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Robbins</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Cambridge</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21613</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2740</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.0841735</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.5632216</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>477</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4525</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/11/2021 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 14:06:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 14:06:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 14:05:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:05:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 13:36:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:13:26</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One clear plastic baggie containing a rock-like substance suspected Crack-Cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255912</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1.5</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 13:36:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:13:46</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One clear plastic baggie containing a rock-like substance suspected Crack-Cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255913</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1.7</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 13:36:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:14:03</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One plastic baggie containing trace amounts of Crack-Cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255914</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 13:36:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:14:17</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One plastic baggie containing a white rock-like substance suspected Crack-Cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255915</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>41.6</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 13:36:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:14:28</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One clear plastic baggie containing 15 clear plastic baggies containing a white rock-like substance suspected Crack-Cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255916</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>10.8</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 13:36:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:14:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One clear plastic baggie containing 19 green rounded suspected oxycodone pills.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255917</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>H</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>19</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 13:40:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 13:40:47</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>C</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>CSH</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>10</PropertyValue>
         <Value>10</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255918</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>10</Quantity>
         <Amount>10</Amount>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 13:40:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 13:40:47</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>C</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>CSH</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>135</PropertyValue>
         <Value>135</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255919</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>27</Quantity>
         <Amount>135</Amount>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 13:40:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 13:40:47</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>C</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>CSH</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>100</PropertyValue>
         <Value>100</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255920</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>5</Quantity>
         <Amount>100</Amount>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 13:44:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 13:47:30</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One black iPhone located in bedroom #2</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>489</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255921</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>iPhone</Make>
         <Model>Unknown</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 13:47:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 13:47:01</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One rose gold iPhone with a black phone case</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>489</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255922</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>GLD</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>iPhone</Make>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 14:13:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:13:26</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One clear plastic baggie containing a rock-like substance suspected Crack-Cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255912</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1.5</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 14:13:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:13:46</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One clear plastic baggie containing a rock-like substance suspected Crack-Cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255913</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1.7</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 14:14:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:14:03</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One plastic baggie containing trace amounts of Crack-Cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255914</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 14:14:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:14:17</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One plastic baggie containing a white rock-like substance suspected Crack-Cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255915</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>41.6</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 14:14:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:14:29</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One clear plastic baggie containing 15 clear plastic baggies containing a white rock-like substance suspected Crack-Cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255916</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>10.8</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5478</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/30/2023 14:14:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5478</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 14:14:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One clear plastic baggie containing 19 green rounded suspected oxycodone pills.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>255917</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>H</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>19</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/20/2023 10:46:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/20/2023 10:46:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>Y</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40F</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/16/2023 11:27:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5496</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 10:46:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/16/2023 11:27:49</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Date and Time:  October 6, 2023 at 1015 hours  Location:  829 Fieldcrest Drive, Cambridge, Dorchester County, Maryland.  Suspect:  Brian Jermaine Wongus, A/A/M, DOB: 7/9/19889)  Scene Processing:  This incident was not captured on a body worn camera.  Evidence:  DNA swabs from Brian Jermaine Wongus, A/A/M, DOB: 7/9/1988  Narrative:  On October 6, 2023, I, Cpl Cummings of the Maryland State Police, currently assigned to the Dorchester County Narcotics Task Force received information that Det. Mcdaniel of the Dorchester County Sheriff Office had conducted a traffic stop on Brian Jermaine Wongus, A/A/M, DOB: 7/9/1988. Brian Wongus had an active arrest warrant and an indictment.  On October 6, 2023 at approximately 1015 hours, I, Cpl. Cummings authored a search and seizure warrant for the DNA of Brian Wongus. At approximately 1033 hours, the warrant was signed by the Honorable Judge Jones of the Dorchester County Circuit Court.  On October 6, 2023 at approximately 1142 hours, Sgt Tyler of the Maryland State Police, currently assigned to the Dorchester County Narcotics Task Force served the search warrant on Brian Wongus by obtaining his DNA, at the Dorchester County Sheriffs Office. The DNA swabs were held on a MSP form 67 Chain of Custody and will be sent to the MSP Crime Lab for analysis.  Case Closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5496</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 10:47:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5496</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/20/2023 11:03:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tyler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Carl</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cummings III</LastName>
            <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5496</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>