<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008260</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/06/2023 02:55:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/06/2023 02:55:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/06/2023 01:49:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/06/2023 01:49:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI, Traffic Stop</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 02:56:00</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/04/2023 21:51:25</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>25 MM CAPITAL BELTWAY NB, COLLEGE PARK</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>686418</AddressId>
      <City>MDC132</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 02:56:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 09:09:11</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>686418</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>25</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm Capital Beltway Nb College</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PARK</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.917948</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0186954166667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/06/2023 02:55:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/06/2023 02:55:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/16/2023 07:47:27</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 02:56:00</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Q-25 IS EQUIPPED WITH AN IN CAR CAMERA THE EVENT WAS AUDIBLY AND VISUALLY RECORDED Defendant: Matute Carrillo, Obed Date of Birth: 09/19/1987 Time of Arrest: 0252 hours DUI#: 23-053 TRAINING/CERTIFICATES Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On March 6th, 2023, at approximately 0255 hours, I, Trooper Fleming #7439 and Trooper Stallings #7589 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, were on routine uniform patrol in the area of the outer loop of 495 south of Baltimore Avenue, College Park, Prince Georges County, Maryland. I was in full uniform operating a marked patrol vehicle Q-25. The incident was audibly and visually recorded on my body worn camera and Q-25s in-car camera. I observed a brown Ford F150 bearing the Maryland temporary registration 8EL9069 swerving and jerking within lane two in the distance. I moved to lane two approximately two car lengths behind the vehicle to better observe the drivers actions. The vehicle was weaving within the lane and the left side wheels of the vehicle fully weaved over the white dotted line into lane one. The vehicle then increased his speed from approximately 60 MPH to 75 MPH. Once again, the left side wheels of the vehicle fully weaved over the white dotted line into lane one. The vehicle then slowly changed lanes from lane two to lane three without the use of its right turn signal. I moved to lane three approximately two car lengths behind the vehicle to better observe the drivers actions. The vehicle then activated its left turn signal for approximately three seconds for no apparent reason. The vehicle then drifted towards the left side of lane three. The left side wheels of the vehicle touched the white dotted line separating lanes two and three for approximately five seconds. I then activated my emergency lights to signal the vehicle to the shoulder. The barrack was notified of my location and the vehicles information. The left side wheels of the vehicle fully weaved over the white dotted line into lane two. The vehicle weaved fully back into lane three and then slowly changed lanes from lane three to lane two. The left side wheels of the vehicle fully weaved over the white dotted line into lane one on two separate occasions. I attempted to signal the vehicle to the left shoulder; the vehicle instead pulled to the right shoulder. The vehicle took approximately 1 minute 20 seconds to pull over from the time I activated my emergency lights. The vehicle came to a stop on the right shoulder of the outer loop of 495 at the Triple Bridges, College Park, Prince Georges County, Maryland. I exited my patrol vehicle to make contact with the driver. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) The driver was identified as Matute Carrillo, Obed (5/M, DOB: 09/19/1987) via his Maryland Drivers License. I approached the passengers side of the vehicle in order to make contact with the driver. Upon making contact with the driver, I observed that his eyes were bloodshot and glassy. There was a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from within the vehicle. Matute Carrillos speech and movements were slow and lethargic. I asked the driver and passengers where they were driving from and where they were driving to; they stated that they were driving from a passengers brothers residence in Lanham to a passengers residences in Hyattsville. I requested Spanish speaking officer in order to perform field sobriety. Corporal Cervantes #3891 of Prince Georges County Police arrived on scene. Matute Carrillo was asked to exit the vehicle. When Matute Carrillo opened the drivers side door, I observed an empty glass Heineken bottle located in the drivers side door panel. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) Corporal Cervantes #3891 assisted in translating the Standard Field Sobriety Tests. I asked Matute Carrillo to perform field sobriety in order to rule out alcohol as a contributing factor to his swerving. I asked Matute Carrillo where he was coming from, Matute Carrillo stated that he was coming from dropping some friends off after playing soccer. I asked Matute Carrillo if he had anything to drink, Matute Carrillo stated that he hadnt had alcohol in a while. I asked when was the last time Matute Carillo had something to drink. Matute Carrillo stated that had something to drink at 1700 hours on March 5th, 2023. The evaluation was performed on right shoulder of the outer loop of 495 at the Triple Bridges, College Park, Prince Georges County, Maryland. The shoulder area was level and dry. Matute Carrillo did not display any visible injuries. Matute Carrillo limped with his left leg. Medication  Matute Carrillo informed me that he does not take any kind of medication. Physical Injuries  Matute Carrillo informed me that he had an injury to his left knee. Glasses or Contacts  Matute Carrillo stated he did not wear glasses or contacts. HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 Clues Observed) The test was explained. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus. The stimulus was held approximately 12-15 inches from Matute Carrillos eye, slightly above eye level. Matute Carrillo was instructed to look straight ahead, keep his head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. Matute Carrillos pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Before beginning the test, I asked Matute Carrillo if he understood my instructions, to which he confirmed. Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Additional Observations  Resting gaze nystagmus was not present. Vertical gaze nystagmus was present. I had to remind Matute Carrillo to continue to follow the stimulus with eyes on four separate occasions. I had to remind Bunch to follow the stimulus with only his eyes and to not move his head on one occasions. WALK AND TURN TEST (4/8 Clues Observed) The test was explained and demonstrated. Matute Carrillo was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Matute Carrillo was then instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and remain in that position until told to begin. Matute Carrillo was advised to take nine steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line, and take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Matute Carrillo was instructed to complete the second series of nine steps in the same heel to toe fashion. Matute Carrillo was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, to count every step out loud, and once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Matute Carrillo if he understood, and he confirmed that he did. Instructional Phase  Walking Stage (First Nine Steps)  Misses Heel-Toe  On steps eight through ten of his first nine steps, Matute Carrillo missed his heel to toe by more than one half inch. Steps Off Line  On steps eight through ten of his first nine steps, Matute Carrillo stepped off line by more than one half inch. Actual Number of Steps  Matute Carrillo stepped ten times and counted the first nine steps out loud. Improper Turn  Matute Carrillo turned counter clockwise when his left foot was behind his right foot which resulted in an unnatural turn. Matute Carrillo pivoted with both feet instead of stepping around with his rear foot. Walking Stage (Second Nine Steps) Misses Heel-Toe  On steps three through nine of his second nine steps, Matute Carrillo missed his heel to toe by more than one half inch. ONE-LEG STAND TEST (3/4 Clues Observed) The test was explained and demonstrated. Matute Carrillo was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch the raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two, etc.), and not put his foot down until the end of the test. I asked Matute Carrillo if he understood the test, and he confirmed. Seconds 1-10 Raises Arms  Matute Carrillo would keep his right arm raised greater than six inches from his body throughout the first ten seconds. Seconds 11-20 Puts foot down  Matute Carrillo lowered his foot to the ground, touching the ground with his entire foot once during this period. Raises Arms  Matute Carrillo would raise his arms greater than six inches from his body on one occasion during the second ten seconds. Hopping  Matute Carrillo would hop on his right foot in attempt to maintain his balance during the second ten seconds. Seconds 21-30 Additional Observations  Matute Carrillo did not start counting until the third ten seconds. ARREST Based on the totality of circumstances, I concluded Matute Carrillo was driving a motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol. Matute Carrillos failure to maintain designated lane directions. Matute Carrillo took approximately 1 minute 20 seconds to pull over from the time I activated my emergency lights The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Matute Carrillos breath and person. Matute Carrillos eyes were bloodshot and glassy. Matute Carrillos slow movement and speech. An open alcoholic beverage was inside the vehicle and within arms reach of the drivers seat. Matute Carrillo was dropping friends off after playing soccer at approximately 0200 hours. Clues during Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (6/6), WAT (4/8), OLS (3/4) On March 6th, 2023 at approximately 0252 hours, I placed Matute Carrillo under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack. A search incident to arrest of Matute Carrillos person was conducted. The search of Matute Carrillos person was negative. I transported Matute Carrillo to the College Park Barrack. Matute Carrillo was played the DR-15 Advice of Rights Spanish recording provided by MVA. Matute Carrillo was provided with a copy of the DR-15 to read along as well. At approximately 0318 hours, Matute Carrillo agreed to take an alcohol concentration test. 20 MINUTE OBSERVATION I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Matute Carrillo beginning with his arrest. A preliminary search of Matute Carrillo was conducted on scene and it was revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. I observed Matute Carrillo from the time of arrest until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by Tpr. Peris #7511 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Matute Carrillo had a result of .16 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 0404 hours. Intoximeter Result: .16 BrAC Matute Carrillos vehicle was left on the right shoulder of the outer loop of 495 at the Triple Bridges, College Park, Prince Georges County. Matute Carrillos vehicle was entered in CADs unattended/disabled vehicle log and an MSP Form 23A was attached to the vehicle. I processed Matute Carrillo and released him to Hernandez Nicolas, Marvin N (5/M, DOB: 07/18/1985). Matute Carrillo was issued the following citations. TA - 21-902(a1i) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL TA - 21-902(a1ii) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL PER SE TA - 21-902(b1i) DRIVING VEH. WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL TA - 21-901.1(a) RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OF PERSONS AND PROPERTY TA - 21-901.1(b) NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON TA - 21-201(a1) DRIVER FAILURE TO OBEY PROPERLY PLACED TRAFFIC CONTROL DEVICE INSTRUCTIONS The defendant was issued copies of the following documents: -Citations (listed above) -DR-15 Advice of Rights -DR-15a Order of Suspension -MSP 33 Notification to Defendant of Result of Test for Alcohol Concentration All documents were forwarded to the Prince Georges County, State Attorney Office. All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 09:47:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 09:47:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stallings</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7589</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Aaron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fleming</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sierra</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7439</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497659</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/06/2023 01:49:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:10:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 09:10:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:12:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:34</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370848</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Matute Carrillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Obed</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/19/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/06/2023 04:57:22</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M332</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>O130</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Matute Carrillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Obed</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/19/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M332</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>O130</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/06/2023 04:57:22</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11439</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Cherry Hill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>304</SubNumber>
               <City>Beltsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20705</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.949769</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.044639</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>481</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4056</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:13:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:13:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:13:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:13:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:10:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 09:10:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150569</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:14:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 09:14:38</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FTFW1ET8BFB30173</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2011</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>F15</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BRO</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8EL9068</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>12</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>