<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-005350</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/11/2023 06:48:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/11/2023 06:48:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/11/2023 06:28:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/11/2023 06:28:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>2 vehicle collision that resulted in a DUI arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:48:18</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 00:56:05</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>330267</AddressId>
      <City>MDC253</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 12:35:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/12/2023 12:38:55</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>330267</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I-95 S/B at MD Rt 212</StreetName>
         <City>Beltsville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.9281</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0566</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/11/2023 06:48:14</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/11/2023 06:48:14</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/20/2023 22:49:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:48:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The following incident was captured on a body-worn camera. Q-17 is not equipped with an MVR. Title: DUI 23-032 ID: 23-MSP-005350   DEFENDANT: Kayla Ann Mineo Date of Birth: 03/31/2005 Date of Arrest: 02/11/2023 Time of Arrest: 0713 hours (7:13 AM) VA DL#: B65921904 DUI#: 23-032 (College Park Barrack)  TRAINING / CERTIFICATES: *I am trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Safety Administration (NHTSA)  PERSONAL CONTACT: On February 11th, 2023 at approximately 0628 hours (6:28 AM), I, Trooper Harris #7179, was responding to a two vehicle collision that occurred on southbound I-95 at Maryland Route 212. Upon my arrival at 0633 hours (6:33 AM), I observed a black Chevrolet Impala displaying Virginia registration VVF1573 parked on the right shoulder with heavy right side and front side damage. I also observed a dark-colored bag that was placed behind the Impala. I made contact with the occupants of the vehicle. The person seated in the driver seat of the vehicle was identified as Laura Michelle Beatley (DOB: 03/31/2005) and the person seated directly behind the driver seat was identified as Kayla Ann Mineo (DOB: 03/31/2005). I asked Beatley who was driving the Impala. Beatley pointed to her rear towards Mineo. At that point, Mineo advised me that she was driving the Impala. I attempted to retrieve both of the occupants drivers license information. Beatley advised me that they left their information in the bag that was located at the rear of the Impala. I asked both of the occupants to retrieve their information. While both of them exited the vehicle, I observed a Twisted Tea Can located on the driver side floorboard of the vehicle.  Both Beatley and Mineo walked to the rear of the Impala to retrieve their information. While Beatley and Mineo reached into the bag, I observed 3 cans of closed Twisted Tea located in the bag. After I retrieved their information, I asked Mineo what happened. Mineo said she was driving from Baltimore after visiting friends at LongWood University. While driving, Mineo stated she fell asleep which caused her to strike the other vehicle in the rear. After, the Impala traveled off of the roadway to the right and struck the guardrail. During the conversation, I observed Mineo had bloodshot and glassy eyes.  After Mineo provided her statement, I then asked her why she was driving the vehicle. Mineo stated that Beatley was tired and could not drive. While speaking with Mineo, I observed a faint odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath. I asked Mineo how many alcoholic beverages she consumed and she stated Maybe 4 like beers, like White Claws. I then asked how long ago she consumed the alcohol. Mineo took a long pause and said Like 4 hours.  After initial questioning, I returned to my patrol car to conduct routine checks. Afterwards,I conducted a secondary approach to Mineo and asked for her to walk in front of my vehicle to which she complied. I questioned Mineo further to verify how much alcoholic beverages she consumed as well as to verify that she was driving the Impala. While doing so, I began to observe a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath. Based on my observations of Mineo, I asked her to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests and she agreed.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING: The evaluation was conducted on the right shoulder. The asphalt was solid, dry, flat and free from any debris. The weather conditions at the time were clear and approximately 40 degrees. Sunlight and the headlamps from my patrol vehicle lit the area. Mineo appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any injuries. I asked Mineo the following questions:  Medical Conditions: No. Injuries: Mineo stated she had a knee injury but also advised me that it would not affect her mobility. Corrective Lenses: No.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN): 6/6 CLUES OBSERVED. Mineo was given the instructions for the test and was asked if she understood to which she said yes in response. Her pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus.  Lack of smooth pursuit - Present in both eyes. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes.  WALK AND TURN (WAT): 1/8 CLUES OBSERVED. I instructed Mineo to stand in the instructional position, with her right foot in front of her left foot, with her hands flat down at his sides. I instructed Mineo to remain in that position until I told her to begin the test and she stated she understood. I then demonstrated and instructed how the test should be conducted.  Instructional Stage: Mineo failed to maintain the instructional position.  Walking Stage (1st Nine Steps): Nothing Observed.  Turn: Nothing Observed.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine Steps): Nothing Observed.   ONE LEG STAND (OLS) - 1/4 CLUES OBSERVED.  Prior to Mineo performing the test, I demonstrated and instructed her to stand with her feet together and arms down by her sides while the instructions were given. I then instructed how the test should be conducted. Mineo was asked if she understood to which she said yes in response. Mineo raised her left foot for the test.  Instructional Stage: Nothing observed.  Balancing and Counting Stage: Mineo put her foot down twice.  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT): I offered Mineo a Preliminary Breath Test to which he declined to submit to.  ARREST: Based on the following, I had reason to believe that Mineo was driving under the influence of alcohol. Responded to a vehicle collision where Mineo was the at-fault driver. Mineo stated she fell asleep while driving. Bloodshot and glassy eyes. Mineo admitted to drinking 4 white claws 4 hours prior to the collision. Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Mineos breath. One Twisted Tea Can that was located on the driver side floorboard of the Impala. Three Twisted Tea Cans that were located in the bag located at the rear of the Impala.  Due to the number of observations, I concluded that Mineo was driving under the influence and was unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0713 hours (7:13 AM), I placed Mineo under arrest for Driving While Under the Influence of Alcohol. A preliminary search of Mineo was conducted on the scene. A tow truck responded to the scene to tow the Impala. While doing so, the tow truck driver alerted Gonzales on red cups that were located underneath of the passenger side airbag and Gonzales took pictures of the cups.  Mineo was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle per department policy and was transported to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack for processing.  While at the College Park Barrack, I provided Mineo a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. I then played the DR-15 Advice of Rights audio aloud and instructed Mineoto to follow along. After Mineo was advised of her rights, she requested to consult with her mother prior to making a decision on taking an alcohol concentration test. Mineos mother, Stephanie Ann Sandoval (DOB: 04/23/1981), arrived at the College Park Barrack. At approximately 0810 hours (8:10 AM), Mineo refused to submit to an alcohol concentration test after speaking with her mother.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: REFUSAL  Mineo was provided copies of all pertinent paperwork and was released to her mother and was advised not to drive a motor vehicle for 12 hours.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland. Case closed by arrest.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 22:11:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7179</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/20/2023 22:45:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gonzales</LastName>
            <FirstName>Javier</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7442</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stewart</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7590</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Long</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5477</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harris</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bruce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7179</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494736</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 06:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 13:14:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7179</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/12/2023 13:14:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>17</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/14/2023 14:47:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:59</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368782</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>A</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mineo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kayla</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/31/2005 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 09:36:09</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mineo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kayla</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/31/2005 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 09:36:09</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5106</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Woodmere</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>202</SubNumber>
               <City>Centreville</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20120</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.442632</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.866255</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>571</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>263</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7298</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/14/2023 14:47:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/14/2023 14:47:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/14/2023 14:47:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/14/2023 14:47:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 13:14:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7179</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/12/2023 13:14:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149718</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/14/2023 14:48:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7179</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/14/2023 14:48:20</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2G1155S32E9183949</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>IMP</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLU</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>VVF1573</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>