<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011057</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/28/2023 08:22:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/28/2023 08:22:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/28/2023 08:22:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/28/2023 08:22:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Distribution of Child pornography multiple cybertips</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 08:22:10</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6049</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/15/2023 11:48:20</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>CAC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>691920</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 08:22:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 13:54:43</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>691920</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>12982</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Augustine Herman</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Kennedyville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21645</Zip5>
         <Zip4>3506</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.930696</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.333959</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/28/2023 08:22:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/28/2023 08:22:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40O</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/15/2023 11:48:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 08:22:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:43</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Narrative:  On March 28, 2023 I received fifteen (15) cybertips from the National Center for Missing and Exploited Children (NCMEC). The cybertips were submitted by Discord, Inc., for images and videos of child pornography that were distributed using their messaging application.  Cybertip 128186283: Nine images included with the cybertip  Image 1: File name: good961.jpg MD5: 195ddc259e2dead8a8136d34ef299cc9 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of two prepubescent boys engaging in sexual conduct. One of the boys is laying on his back, he is naked. His genitals are exposed and the other prepubescent boy is performing fellatio on him.  Image 2:  File name: gooda891853dbc2fd556.jpg MD5: 1c39759f3846756d14fe6310b3945a9c Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent boy. He is laying on a bed with no pants on. His legs are lifted into the air so that his genitals and anus are exposed.  Image 3:  File name: good2ea178b0ab6f0a09.jpg.thumb.jpg MD5: 679a89b7a1c29cfef6edf26194ea04b4 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent boy. The child is on a bed on his knees with his chest and head on the bed. His anus and genitals are exposed.  Image 4:  File name: good959466.JPG MD5: 6f658bba51e9e0ce88a630590b0cc9e6 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of two prepubescent boys. On of the boys is sitting on a couch and has his pants pulled down so his genitals are exposed. The other boy is performing fellatio on him.  Image 5: File name: good344fd.jpg MD5: 8899dbc0cb6384ddf361877da4b8d44e Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of two prepubescent boys. One of the boys is laying on his back on the floor. He is naked and the other boy is performing fellatio on him.  Image 6:  File name: good-5f66-474c-bd9f-148426242ff1.jpg MD5: 8c847991101132b26bfc1b822306a224 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is a close up of a prepubescent boys penis. It appears there is an adults hand touching the penis.  Image 7:  File name: good9685821200.jpg MD5: b3ea544f47981695af709742f96d3d82 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent boy laying on a bed. His underwear is pulled down so that his genitals are exposed.  Image 8:  File name: good00634.jpg MD5: c127a92aab454324dcbbc26eb194c56b Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of two prepubescent boys. The boys are on a bed and are both naked. They are performing fellatio on each other.  Image 9: File name: good14068110871.jpg MD5: d0a425d44c8cb461f52cf1e5615b66c4 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of two prepubescent boys. Both are naked. One of the boys is laying on his back on a bed, the other boy is performing fellatio on him.  Images 9, 8, 5, 4, and 1 appear to be from the same image series.   IP Address: 172.243.134.108 Date: 05-19-2022 17:38:54 UTC Screen/User Name: Boys R Better#6021 ESP User ID: 976771528999968808  Subpoena sent by Cumberland County Prosecutors Office to ViaSat for IP address subscriber information.  Subscriber Information: Account Holder: Cluade Westcott Service Address: 44 Town Point Road, Chesapeake City MD, 21915 Account No: 400608166 Phone Number: 410-347-0642 Email: N/A Modem Mac Address: 00:a0:bc:30:cf:10 Activation Date: 6/7/2012 Type of Service: Fixed Satellite Internet Service Payment Method: Billing Handled by DISH Network Customer Host Name: WNR1000v2  Uses DHCP but probable the same IP address will be reissued every 12 hours.  Cybertip 128223150  Two images included with cybertip  Image 1: File name: goodpic89495.jpg MD5: 250fffa4dc000b03e552bfc36b3e4d59 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent boy. The boy is laying on his back on a bed and is naked. There is an adults hand touching the boys penis.  Image 2:  File name: goodDscf0016jp_8882049_31192767.jpg MD5: 250fffa4dc000b03e552bfc36b3e4d59 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent boy. The boy is laying on his back. His pants and underwear are pulled down so that his genitals are exposed. An adult males hand is touching the boys penis and chest.  IP Address: 172.243.134.108 Date: 05-19-2022 17:45:02 UTC Screen/User Name: Boys R Better#6021 ESP User ID: 976771528999968808  Cybertip 128441923  Two files included with cybertip  Image 1:  File name: Screen_Shot_2022-04-18_at_8.46.54_PM.png MD5: 9a3fbf964366cc8790f75f22b7a717c9 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of two prepubescent boys. On of the boys is sitting on a couch and has his pants pulled down so his genitals are exposed. The other boy is performing fellatio on him. This is the same image as Cybertip 128186283 Image 4.  Image 2: File name: 4EGweQPFF1EvOP4O4xopnIJM8-421gl-xcKZSVi4Kds1.jpg MD5: f8f33abe55bde69ca3d6f24f801528d8 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of two prepubescent boys. Both boys are naked. They are on a Twister mat. One of the boys is performing fellatio on the other boy.  IP address: 172.243.134.108 Date: 05-28-2022 06:10:38 UTC Screen/User Name: Deleted User 7892b657#7565 ESP User ID: 979240796630962177  A subpoena was sent by Cumberland County Prosecutors Office to ViaSat for IP address subscriber information.  Subscriber Information: Account Holder Name: Claude Westcott Service Address: 44 Town Point Road, Chesapeake City, MD, 21915 Account No: 400608166|300556974 Phone Number: 410-347-0642 Email: N/A Modem Mac Address: 00:a0:bc:30:cf:10 Activation Date: 6/7/2012 Type of Service: Fixed Satellite Internet Service Payment Method: Billing handled by DISH Network Customer Host Name: WNR1000v2  Cybertip 128714546  Four files included with cybertip  Image 1: File name: 2018-11-08_06.01.14.jpg MD5: 55304808eada21b86f86e8a2755c4401 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent girl. She is bent over facing away from the camera with her pants pulled down to expose her buttock and vagina.  Image 2: File name: 367_1000.jpg MD5: 798e42496da3ff35562b871afa504544 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent girl. She is on her knees on a bed with her chest and face on the bed. She has no pants on and her anus and vagina are exposed.  Image 3:  File name: 263.jpg MD5: aaae430fa8a813a0d858da90ee9e5ff6 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of two prepubescent boys. The two boys are on a couch and are both naked. They are kissing and one of the boys is touching the other boys erect penis with his hand.  Image 4:  File name: 018.jpg MD5: afcd9cf850c81467461b31048c23175d Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent boy sitting on a couch. The boy has no pants on so his penis is exposed. His penis is erect.  IP address: 172.243.134.108 Date: 5-31-2022 22:02:07 UTC Screen/User name: Deleted User 7892b657#7565 ESP User ID: 979240796630962177  Cybertip 133931982  One file included with cybertip  Image 1: File name: 640480a_147.jpg MD5: 7e8dd9cf60d6a14fd33d962dcd2dd04a Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent boy. The boy is laying on his back on a bed and is naked. There is an adults hand touching the boys penis.  IP address: 172.243.178.146 Date: 9-05-2022 06:49:46 UTC Phone: 5511982581986 (Verified) Email Address: newsteveydiscord@mail.com (verified) Screen/User Name: Boys R Better#4357 ESP User ID: 1016224070750191686  I searched the IP address in MaxMind and the ISP is ViaSat.  Cybertip 133932062  One file included with cybertip  Image 1: File name: robbie.jpg MD5: 1a48d10452157069b349f3ccffa9faf3 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a naked prepubescent boy. His genitals are visible.  IP address: 172.243.178.146 Date: 09-05-2022 07:03:28 UTC Phone: 5511982581986 (Verified) Email: newsteveydiscord@mail.com (Verified) Screen/User Name: Boys R Better#4357 ESP User ID: 1016224070750191686  Cybertip 133945459  One file included with cybertip  Image 1:  File name: 6yggthvgtf6h_16.jpg MD5: a95881412eac2614ec2b7d0c9b813606 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of what appears to be two prepubescent boys. In the image one of the boys is licking the anus of the other boy.  IP address: 172.243.178.146 Date: 09-08-2022 08:22:52 UTC Phone: 5511982581986 (Verified) Email: newsteveydiscord@mail.com (Verified) Screen/ User Name: Boys R Better#4357 ESP User ID: 1016224070750191686  Cybertip 133945479  One file included with cybertip  Image 1: File name: Boy_pics_01-preteen_young_cute_nude_pjk_boys_hard_sex_full_boylove_582.jpg MD5: 5dace2bb984f386861234df61105b7a2 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of two prepubescent boys. Both of the boys are naked. Boy 1 is laying on his stomach on the ground with his buttock visible. Boy 2 is sitting on Boy 1 with his genitals touching Boy 1s buttocks.  IP Address: 172.243.178.146 Date: 09-08-2022 07:53:17 UTC Phone: 5511982581986 (Verified) Email: newsteveydiscord@mail.com (Verified) Screen/ User Name: Boys R Better#4357 ESP User ID: 1016224070750191686  Cybertip 133945505  One file included with cybertip  Image 1:  File name: 101_Dalmatians_Series_-_Mikael__William_Martin_53.jpg MD5: 719cd13a82ad0b7ba258b752eafb6b74 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent boy and another person of unknown age/gender. The prepubescent boy is naked and his penis is visible. It appears he is about to have anal or vaginal sex with the other person in the image.  IP Address: 172.243.178.146 Date: 09-08-2022 08:24:44 UTC Phone: 5511982581986 (Verified) Email: newsteveydiscord@mail.com (Verified) Screen/ User Name: Boys R Better#4357 ESP User ID: 1016224070750191686  Cybertip 133945513  One file included with cybertip  Image 1: File name: 101_Dalmatians_Series_-_Mikael__William_Martin_51.jpg MD5: 0a3673292da2dc03a9777971302262ee Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image of two prepubescent boys. Both of the boys are naked. One of the boys is having anal sex with the other boy.  IP Address: 172.243.178.146 Date: 09-08-2022 08:24:31 UTC Phone: 5511982581986 (Verified) Email: newsteveydiscord@mail.com (Verified) Screen/ User Name: Boys R Better#4357 ESP User ID: 1016224070750191686  Cybertip 135221234  One file included with cybertip  Image 1:  File name: download_10.jpg MD5: 8bc8a7ec8e92580896be9a4ea0da14e1 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent girl. She is naked. She is on her hands and knees on a bed. Her buttock is visible.  IP Address: 172.243.178.146 Date: 09-19-2022 23:58:54 UTC Email: boysrbetter6@mail.com (Verified) Screen/ User Name: Boys R Better#6600 ESP User ID: 1017366499792519188  Cybertip 135224626  One image included with cybertip  Image 1: File name: Screen_Shot_2022-07-19_at_6.45.47_PM.png MD5: 6a3853487c9161d6b59c3733c6bd8a15 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent boy. The boy is naked. His genitals are exposed. He is digitally penetrating his anus.  IP Address: 172.243.178.146 Date: 09-20-2022 04:00:34 UTC Screen/ User ID: Boys R Better#858 ESP User ID: 1021629280515538955  Cybertip 135287897  One video included with cybertip  Video 1:   File name: GOODa247f6564d.720.mp4 MD5: f13dc2a031db1178617dfca0a2d6c00a Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: This is a 28 second video. The video is of a prepubescent girl. She is filming herself. The girl is naked. In the video the girl uses her hands to expose her vagina and her anus.  IP Address: 172.243.178.146 Date: 09-21-2022 03:01:56 UTC Phone: 5511961488584 (Verified) Email: boysrbetter7@mail.com (Verified) Screen/ User Name: Boys R Better#3409 ESP User ID: 1021642521757093918  Cybertip 135287899  One video included with cybertip  Video 1: File name: good99384.mp4 MD5: b1897fd9bc4d8c86089bc2a312a0197d Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The video is of a prepubescent girl. She is filming herself and is naked. She is using various objects to penetrate her vagina.  IP Address: 172.243.178.146 Date: 09-21-2022 03:39:57 UTC Phone: 5511961488584 (Verified) Email: boysrbetter7@mail.com (Verified) Screen/ User Name: Boys R Better#3409 ESP User ID: 1021642521757093918  Cybertip 136185904  One image included with cybertip  Image 1: File name: gooda891853dbc2fd556.jpg MD5: 1c39759f3846756d14fe6310b3945a9c Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent boy. He is laying on a bed with no pants on. His legs are lifted into the air so that his genitals and anus are exposed.   IP Address: 172.243.178.146 (Login) Date: 10-08-2022 08:00:05 UTC Phone: 5515938379286 (Verified) Email Address: boysrbetter9@mail.com (Verified) Screen/ Use Name: Boys R Better#2007 ESP User ID: 1025540608170938448  Cybertip 137713768  One image included with cybertip  Image 1: File name: goodoiggdkswlejezogju.jpg MD5: 865bcab3b403a81caf62c9a2349b2252 Did Reporting ESP view entire contents of uploaded file? Yes Were entire contents of uploaded file publicly available? Yes Description: The image is of a prepubescent boy. The boy is sitting down and is naked. The image is a close view of the boys genitals.  IP Address: 172.243.178.146 (Login) Date: 10-26-2022 17:16:25 UTC Email: boysrbetter12@email.com (Verified) Screen/ User Name: 3 Boys#5551 ESP User ID: 1033613608032149564  A subpoena was sent to ViaSat for subscriber information by Northumberland County.  Subscriber Information: Account Holder Name: Claude Westcott Service Address: 44 Town Point Rd, Chesapeake City, MD Account No: 300556974 Phone No: 410-347-0642 Email: NA Modem MAC Address: 00:A0:BC:30:CF:10 Activation Date: 2012/06/07 Type of Service: Fixed Satellite Internet Service Payment Method: Billing handled by DISH Network   Case remains open. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6080</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 14:00:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6080</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 14:01:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Donald</LastName>
            <FirstName>Frank</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6049</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sarver</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6080</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500460</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0300</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/28/2023 08:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6080</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 13:56:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6080</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 13:56:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP6080</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 13:59:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:14</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375268</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Westcott</LastName>
               <FirstName>STEPHEN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicholas</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/02/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/25/2023 13:58:36</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W232</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Westcott</LastName>
               <FirstName>STEPHEN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicholas</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/02/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W232</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/25/2023 13:58:36</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12982</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Augustine Herman</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Kennedyville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21645</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3506</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.930696</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.333959</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6080</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 13:59:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6080</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 13:56:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6080</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 13:56:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>