<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-010904</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/26/2023 21:05:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/26/2023 21:05:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/26/2023 20:49:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/26/2023 20:49:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect was arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/26/2023 21:05:15</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0392</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 12:23:54</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>581524</AddressId>
      <City>MDC557</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:53:35</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 09:57:02</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>581524</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>495</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Capitol Beltway</StreetName>
         <City>Suitland-Silver Hill</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20746</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.887065</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.822371</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/26/2023 21:05:13</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/26/2023 21:05:13</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/07/2023 04:58:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/26/2023 21:05:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:01</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car (L-42) and Body Worn Camera Operational.   Defendant: Christopher Michael Tolson  Date of Birth: 07/17/1989  Date of Arrest: 03/26/2023  Time of Arrest: 2104 Hours    DUI:  23-104  Certificate and Training:  Trained in Administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) through the Maryland State Police (MSP) and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA)  Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.)  Soundex:  T-425-115-603-564/Maryland  Narrative: VEHICLE IN MOTION (Phase 1):  On March 26, 2023, at approximately 2035 hours, I, Trooper J. Barlow #7186, of the Maryland State Police, currently assigned to the Forestville Barrack, was on duty in my marked patrol vehicle, traveling southbound Capitol Beltway at Allentown Road (Exit 9,) Suitland, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20746, in lane 1. I observed a black Hyundai Genesis (G80) bearing Virginia registration UHJ5516 traveling in the same direction in lane 2, following too closely to a white SUV and crossing over the right lane divider lines into lane 3 by more than half a car width, also braking excessively. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. After activating my emergency equipment, the vehicle took approximately 50 seconds to move over to the right shoulder where the flow of traffic was light.   PERSONAL CONTACT (Phase 2):  Upon stopping the vehicle, I made a passenger side approach where I requested the drivers license and vehicle registration. The driver provided me his registration card and advised he did not have his license in his possession. I identified the driver as the registered owner of the vehicle as Christopher Michael Tolson (B/M DOB: 07/17/1989.) While talking to Tolson, it was hard to hear him because he was speaking really low with the vehicles passing by. I requested Tolson to raise the volume of his voice to which he barely did so. With Tolson volume being so low, his speech was also slow and lethargic at this time. I detected the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I observed his eyes to be glossy. I asked Tolson where was he coming from to which he stated, Football practice. I asked Tolson if he came straight from football practice or did he go somewhere else right after, to which Tolson advised he stopped somewhere else first. I asked Tolson if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages to which he stated, Yes. Tolson did not advise what he had consumed when I asked. I asked Tolson would he perform the voluntary Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) to which he agreed to perform.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (Phase 3):  Before performing SFSTs, I requested Tolson to exit and walk to the front of his vehicle. Tolson opened his door and stated, You want me to get out in traffic? I advised Tolson to exit and walk to the front of his vehicle. Tolson complied and safely walked into the front of his vehicle. While in the front of his vehicle, I asked Tolson if he wore glasses/contact lenses to which he advised he did not. I asked Tolson if he took any medication or had any injuries which would hinder him from walking in a straight line or standing on one leg for any duration of time to which he advised he did not.   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) 6 out of 6 clues observed:  Before performing HGN, I instructed Tolson to stand with his legs and feet together, with his arms down by his sides and not to move from this position until I instructed him to do so. I asked Tolson if he could see the silver tip of my stimulus to which he advised he could. I instructed Tolson to follow the silver tip of my stimulus with his eyes only without moving his head, neck, or shoulders. I asked Tolson if he understood the instructions I gave him to which he advised he understood. Tolson exhibited equal pupil size and Resting Nystagmus was not present. Tolson did not display equal tracking as he would stop following the stimulus in motion. It should be noted Tolson stopped looking at the silver tip of my stimulus multiple times and was instructed to continue to look at it.   Lack of Smooth Pursuit:  Tolson showed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.   Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation:  Tolson showed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.   Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees:  Tolson showed onset of nystagmux prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.  Vertical Gaze Nystagmus:  Tolson did not show vertical gaze nystagmus in either eye.  Walk and Turn (WAT) 4 out of 8 clues observed:  Before performing WAT, I advised Tolson to imagine the solid white boundary line was in front of him. I instructed Tolson to place his right foot in front of his left foot touching heel to toe with his arms down by his sides and not to move from this position until I instructed him to do so. I instructed Tolson to take nine (9) heel to toe steps down the imaginary line, looking down at his feet, and counting each step out loud. I instructed Tolson once he got to his 9th step, to leave his lead foot planted and take a series of small steps turning around to the left and take 9 more heel to toe steps back down the imaginary line. I instructed Tolson once he starts the tests, do not stop until he has completed the test. I demonstrated how the test should be performed by taking three (3) steps simulating 9. After demonstrating the test, I asked Tolson if he understood the instructions and demonstration to which he advised no. I gave the instructions and demonstration again to which he advised he understood. I instructed Tolson to begin the test.   Instructional Phase:  Tolson was unable to maintain balance during the instructional phase.   Walking Stage (1st Series):  Tolson missed heel to toe on step 4 by more than one half inch.  Tolson took the improper number of steps totaling 10.  Turn:  Tolson did not turn as instructed, as he lifted both feet when he turned around.  Walking Stage (2nd Series):  Tolson missed heel to toe on step 3 by more than one half inch.  One Leg Stand (OLS) 3 out of 4 clues observed:  Before performing OLS, I instructed Tolson to stand with his legs and feet together with his arms down by his sides. I instructed Tolson not move from this position until I instructed him to do so. I instructed Tolson to lift either leg of his choosing approximately six inches off the ground. I instructed Tolson whichever leg he chooses to lift, look down at the toes of the raised leg and count out loud in the manner of one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-three, and so on until I instructed him to stop. I asked Tolson if he understood the instructions I gave him to which he advised he understood. I asked Tolson which leg will he lift off the ground to which he advised and pointed to his right leg. I instructed Tolson to begin the test. Tolson was advised to look down at his feet after the test began.   Puts Foot Down:  Tolson put his foot down during seconds 3-5 and 27-30.  Uses Arms for Balance:  Tolson used his arms for balance, raising them approximately six inches from his sides during seconds 1-3.  Sways:  Tolson swayed side to side during seconds 7-30.  Hops:  No clues observed.   Arrest:    Following too closely  Failure to drive right of center  Glossy eyes  The odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person  The admission of consuming alcoholic beverages   margin-left:8px"&gt;The observations during SFSTs    Preliminary Breath Test:  Refused  At approximately 2103 hours, Tolson was advised of his Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) rights and offered a PBT. Tolson refused to take the PBT. At 2104 hours, Tolson was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. Tolson was searched prior to being placed into my marked patrol vehicle to be transported to the Forestville Barrack. Tolsons vehicle was locked and secured on the right shoulder of the roadway. While enroute to the Barrack, Tolson was provided a digital copy of the Advice of Rights (DR-015) form from the mva.maryland.gov website to follow along while I played the audio version of the form downloaded from the website in its entirety.   Intoximeter Test:  Refused  After having been read the DR-015, at approximately 2119 hours, Tolson refused to take the Intoximeter Test.   Tolson was charged with DUI/DWI and other traffic related incidents. It should be noted this is Tolsons second time being charged with DUI/DWI within two years. Tolsons license was suspended for not having an interlock system installed in his vehicle after the first incident.   Tolson was released from the Forestville Barrack to a sober driver at 2210 hours.  Case closed by arrest.   All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 13:22:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 22:59:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6931</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>York</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6327</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>12</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 21:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:00:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17578</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 21:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17578</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:02:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3096</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 21:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3096</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:03:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3101</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 21:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3101</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:04:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 21:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:08:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 21:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:09:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 21:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:10:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15566</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 21:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15566</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:11:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>46</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 21:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:16:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 21:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:17:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 21:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:18:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>12</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>12</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 21:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:19:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>13</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>45</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>13</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 21:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17272</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:20:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:19</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372790</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Tolson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/17/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 09:12:28</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Tolson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/17/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/28/2023 09:12:28</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>10845</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Smugglers Notch</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>White Plains</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20695</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.948799</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.599695</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>8230</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Harvest Bend</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>21</SubNumber>
               <City>Laurel</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20707</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.8638387</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.0895849</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 10:27:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 10:27:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 10:27:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 09:59:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>120776</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 10:28:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 10:28:55</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/29/2021 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>KMHGN4JE4HU175711</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HYUN</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>GENESIS</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>UHJ5516</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2022</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>