<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-005851</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/15/2023 07:29:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/15/2023 07:29:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/15/2023 07:20:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/15/2023 07:20:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Arrest Warrant Service - Handgun Recovered - Regulated Firearm Illegal Possession</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 07:29:32</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3355</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 16:57:53</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>684379</AddressId>
      <City>MDC103</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 07:29:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/15/2023 17:04:56</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>684379</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1114</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Kevin</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Baltimore</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21229</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.69048</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.298427</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/15/2023 07:29:30</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/15/2023 07:29:30</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40N</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/14/2023 14:00:08</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 07:29:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3355</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 16:43:38</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Scene Processing: Digital photographs were obtained and attached. The recovered firearm was packaged and processed in accordance with MSP policy and procedures. The firearm was placed on a property held (P-339327) and form 67 - chain of custody. Search and seizure warrant was authored and obtained for Elbournes DNA. DNA was obtained and submitted into property. Search warrant return was completed and attached.  Narrative: In February of 2023, I, Cpl. Tittle #6005, of the Maryland State Police  Maryland State Apprehension Team / U.S. Marshals  Capital Area Regional Fugitive Task Force, was assigned an investigation for a fugitive, identified as Crystal Anetra Rhodes, B/F, DOB: 9/17/1988. Rhodes is wanted through the Baltimore County Police Department for Assault 1st Degree and related offenses (D-08-CR-22-004055), which was issued on 5/4/2022. In addition, Rhodes is wanted through the Howard County Police Department and the Maryland Transportation Authority Police for a must appear traffic offense.  Upon being assigned the fugitive investigation, Task Force members conducted an in-depth background investigation into Rhodes family, friends, associates, and pattern of life. During the course of the investigation, Task Force members identified a current address of 1114 Kevin RD Baltimore City, MD 21229 for Rhodes.  On 2/15/2023, at approximately 0650 hours, Task Force members responded to 1114 Kevin RD in an attempt to locate and apprehend Rhodes. Upon arriving, Task Force members established a perimeter around the residence. Task Force members began knocking and announcing their presence at the front entry door. While knocking, Task Force members observed a male, later identified as Tyjaye Tyjuan-Syvonn Elbourne, B/M, DOB: 5/18/2004, in the front living room and immediately run upstairs.  Task Force members continued to knock and announce their presence while an additional Task Force member made contact with a neighbor who was looking outside. The neighbor confirmed that Rhodes resides at 1114 Kevin RD.  While continuing to knock and announce their presence, a male, later identified as Kevin Brown B/M DOB: 10/3/2007, opened the door. Brown stated that Rhodes was his mother. When questioned, Brown stated he didnt believe his mother was home, however he was unsure because he was asleep in the basement. When questioned as to the other occupants in the residence, Brown stated his uncle, and two younger sisters were inside (ages 13 and 1). It was confirmed that Elbourne was Browns uncle. The children were later identified as Doloriy Loneon, B/F, DOB: 11/5/2020 and Pion Cherry, B/F, DOB: 11/5/2009.  Task Force members entered the residence to search for Rhodes. Task Force members called out for the remaining occupants to exit onto the first floor. Elbourne exited the second floor holding the one-year-old child. Task Force members conducted a protective sweep of the couch in the living room prior to Elbourne sitting down. On the couch, Task Force members observed a black handbag / satchel lying on the couch. Task Force members picked up the handbag / satchel to move it so Elbourne could be seated. As soon as Task Force members picked up the handbag /satchel, they immediately, based on their training, knowledge, and experience, detected, what they believed, was a handgun inside the bag.  The thirteen-year-old child then exited the second floor and was seated on the same couch. Task Force members conducted a detailed search of the residence and were unable to locate Rhodes. Information obtained revealed Rhodes resides at the residence, however was not there at this time.  Task Force members opened the handbag / satchel and observed one (1) silver Jennings Company model 48 (serial# 094244) .380 caliber handgun inside. The handgun was loaded with six (6) rounds of ammunition, including one (1) in the chamber.  Based on where Elbourne was observed coming from, Task Force members believe he was sleeping on the couch in the living room where the firearm was recovered.  A NCIC/METERS inquiry revealed Elbourne was currently wanted through the Prince Georges County Sheriffs Office for Violating a Protective Order (D-05-CR-22-005269), which was issued on 12/6/2022.  The Maryland State Police Gun Center was contacted regarding the firearm and Elbourne. The Gun Center conducted a work-up and advised Elbourne was prohibited from possessing firearms / ammunition for the following reasons:   Under 30 years of age with a juvenile adjudication of a disqualifying crime   margin-left:8px"&gt;Fugitive from justice   Elbourne was convicted for the following:     margin-left:8px"&gt;6/21/2018  Maryland Transit Authority  18MTA00002185  petition ID 618176014   Elbourne is also the respondent of a final protective order, valid until 1/5/2024, which prohibits Elbourne from possessing firearms.  The firearm was seized and later transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack for packaging and processing in accordance with MSP policy and procedures.  Elbourne was transported to the Central Booking Intake Facility for processing. At CBIF, Elbourne indicated to Task Force members that he was asleep on the couch in the living room when Task Force members began knocking on the front door. Elbourne stated he ran upstairs because its the ghetto, and he wasnt sure who was at the door. Elbourne stated if he knew it was the police he wouldve opened the door.  On 2/15/2023, Cpl. Tittle authored a search and seizure warrant for Elbournes DNA to compare against DNA recovered from the firearm. The search warrant was reviewed and authorized by Judge Hammond of the Anne Arundel County District Court.  Cpl. Tittle responded to the Central Booking Intake Facility and served Elbourne with the DNA warrant at approximately 1208 hours. Cpl. Tittle obtained one (1) buccal swab of saliva from Elbourne. The DNA specimen was packaged and processed in accordance with MSP policy and procedures. The DNA specimen was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack and submitted into evidence pending analysis.  The MSP 234 - Forensic Biology Casework Submittal Form, was sent and approved by the Maryland State Police - Forensic Science Division.  All events occurred in Baltimore City, MD.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 09:40:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6005</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/15/2023 17:52:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Vanhoy</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3355</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tittle</LastName>
            <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6005</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495246</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1106</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/15/2023 07:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1106</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 17:06:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6005</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/15/2023 17:06:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495246</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 5285</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/15/2023 07:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 17:07:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6005</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/15/2023 17:07:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495246</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1285</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/15/2023 07:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 17:08:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6005</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/15/2023 17:08:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 17:11:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369176</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Elbourne</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyjaye</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Tyjuan-Syvonn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/18/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/15/2023 17:10:32</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Elbourne</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyjaye</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Tyjuan-Syvonn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/18/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>E416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/15/2023 17:10:32</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1114</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Kevin</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21229</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.69048</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.298427</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 17:11:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 17:11:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 17:06:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6005</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/15/2023 17:06:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 17:13:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6005</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/15/2023 17:13:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Loaded with six (6) rounds of ammunition </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>MSPPI</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <SerialNumber>094244</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243701</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>SIL</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>Jennings Firearms Co</Make>
         <Model>48</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/16/2023 11:37:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/16/2023 11:37:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40N</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/14/2023 14:00:08</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 11:37:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3355</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 16:43:38</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 2/16/2023, I, Cpl. Tittle #6005, reviewed jail calls from the Central Booking Intake Facility for Elbourne in reference to this investigation. The following information was obtained from the recorded jail calls.  On 2/16/2023, at 0145 hours, Elbourne (inmate ID 22010345) calls phone number 443-374-8320. This phone number is associated with Elbournes mother, Kim Artee Harris-Elbourne, B/F, DOB: 3/19/1973. Cpl. Tittle spoke with Ms. Harris-Elbourne on 2/15/2023 on this phone number regarding her daughter, Crystal Rhodes, turning herself into law enforcement for the open arrest warrant. The following is a summarization from the jail call:  -Ms. Harris-Elbourne asks Elbourne if he has seen the commissioner yet  - Elbourne tells Ms Harris-Elbourne that they added a gun charge and that they are going to keep him (referring to being held without bond) and that he has court in the morning  -Ms. Harris-Elbourne tells Elbourne that when he saw the police at the door, why wouldnt he hide the gun  - Elbourne tellsMs. Harris-Elbourne that he ran upstairs because the baby was crying  -Ms. Harris-Elbourne tells Elbourne that she thought he was smarter than that  - Elbourne tellsMs. Harris-Elbourne he doesnt know why they (referring to police) checked his stuff and that they werent there for him  -Ms. Harris-Elbourne tells Elbourne that she knew Crystal had a warrant and that she told him to stay out of her house  -Ms. Harris-Elbourne tells Elbourne to tell them it wasnt your gun because they didnt find it on you  -Ms. Harris-Elbourne tells Elbourne that if he is released on the box (referring to GPS monitoring device) that he cant stay at her house due to her job  Case remains closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 11:38:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6005</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/20/2023 18:39:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Vanhoy</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3355</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tittle</LastName>
            <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6005</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/20/2023 10:17:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/20/2023 10:17:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40N</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/14/2023 14:00:08</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 10:17:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3355</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 16:43:38</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 2/17/2023, at 1751 hours, Elbourne (inmate ID 4144968) calls phone number 443-374-8320. This phone number is associated with Elbournes mother, Kim Artee Harris-Elbourne, B/F, DOB: 3/19/1973. Cpl. Tittle spoke with Ms. Harris-Elbourne on this phone number regarding her daughter, Crystal Rhodes, turning herself into law enforcement for the open arrest warrant. The following is a summarization of the jail call:  Elourne tells Ms. Harris-Elbourne that he has court in a month and that he is going to take a plea  Elbourne tells Ms. Harris-Elbourne the gun was not on him  Elbourne tells Ms. Harris-Elbourne that Kevin opened the door because he went upstairs because the baby was crying. He tells Ms. Harris-Elbourne that he wasnt thinking about no gun. He says that his niece was crying so was going to choose his niece over a gun  Ms. Harris-Elbourne asks Elbourne if the gun was inside a bag or a box. Elbourne tells Ms. Harris-Elbourne that the gun was inside a bag next to him  Ms. Harris-Elbourne tells Elbourne that he needs to watch what he says on these calls  Ms. Harris-Elbourne asks Elbourne if there was anything else in the bag, any information about someone. Elbourne tells Ms. Harris-Elbourne that there was nothing else in the bag   On 2/18/2023, at 1056 hours, Elbourne (inmate ID 4144968) calls phone number 443-374-8320. This phone number is associated with Elbournes mother, Kim Artee Harris-Elbourne, B/F, DOB: 3/19/1973. Cpl. Tittle spoke with Ms. Harris-Elbourne on this phone number regarding her daughter, Crystal Rhodes, turning herself into law enforcement for the open arrest warrant. Ms. Harris-Elbourne three-ways her daughter, Crystal Rhodes. The following is a summarization of the jail call:  During the conversation, Ms. Rhodes says to Elbourne that she has to ask him a question. Ms Rhodes asks Elbourne where the wallet was, yes or no. Ms. Rhodes reiterates you know what Im saying. Ms. Rhodes asks Elbourne if the wallet was on him. Elbourne states on the chair. Ms. Rhodes asks was it inside there. Cpl. Tittle has reason to believe that Ms. Rhodes is asking Elbourne if the handgun was located on his person or on the chair. Elbourne indicates that the handgun was located on the chair. Ms. Rhodes asks if it was inside there, indicating if the firearm was inside the handbag that the handgun was located in.  Ms. Rhodes makes comments about the police being cruddy  Elbourne states again that he ran up the stairs to grab the baby, reiterating that Elbourne was in the living room, where then handgun was located, when police knocked on the front door   Case remains closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 10:18:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6005</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/20/2023 10:57:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Vanhoy</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3355</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tittle</LastName>
            <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6005</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/12/2023 19:52:29</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/12/2023 19:52:29</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40N</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/14/2023 14:00:08</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 19:52:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3355</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 16:43:38</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 3/10/2023, I, Cpl. Tittle #6005, received the Maryland State Police Forensic Science Division Report regarding latent prints obtained from the recovered firearm. The report indicates that no latent prints were obtained.  DNA swabs were recovered from the firearm and DNA analysis is still pending.  The MSP FSD report has been attached.  Case remains closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6005</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 19:54:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6005</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 19:56:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Vanhoy</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3355</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tittle</LastName>
            <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6005</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/21/2023 19:08:49</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/21/2023 19:08:49</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/17/2023 16:43:38</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP1174</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 19:08:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 16:43:38</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #4 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On March 21, 2023, I, D/Sgt. Douglas Forrester # 1174 transported the following firearm to the Maryland State Police Forensic Science Division in Pikesville, Maryland. I could not test fire the firearm at the barrack due to the caliber not being suitable for the MSP Forensic Buddy. (The Forensic Buddy is a portable, compact bullet trap used to capture intact bullets.   Make: Jennings Firearms  Model: 48  Caliber: .380 auto  Serial Number: 094244   I met with Whitley Adrams of the Firearm  Toolmarks Unit. Abrams and I inspected the firearm, magazine, and ammunition evidence. We determined it was safe to be test fired. We also compared it to the related paperwork for the evidence and found that it matched the evidence.   Abrams utilized ammunition from the MSP FSD to test-fire the firearm. The firearm was discharged into a large water tank specifically made for test-firing firearms and collecting shell casings and projectiles from the test fires. Abrams testified the firearm by firing two test shots into the water tank, I observed. We determined that the firearm was operable. Abrams collected and packaged the two test shots for NIBIN database entry and storage. See attached Maryland State Police Witness Test Fire Certificate 21-71.   I am certified to test fire firearms by the Maryland State Police.  I attended the MSP Forensic Buddy training and successfully completed a competency test. I successfully completed recertification on December 14, 2022. I am also a certified handgun instructor by the Maryland State Police; see attached certificate # QHIC-2022-0756.   I am assigned to the Golden Ring Barrack Barrack located at 8908 Kelso Drive, Essex, MD 21221. I can be reached at 410-780-2706 Office or by email at douglas.forrester@maryland.gov.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP1174</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 19:09:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/21/2023 19:10:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Vanhoy</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3355</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Forrester</LastName>
            <FirstName>Douglas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1174</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>