<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-003797</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/30/2023 13:40:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/30/2023 13:40:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/30/2023 13:32:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/30/2023 13:32:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Harassment of State Officials.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 13:40:47</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/08/2023 13:09:56</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>HMP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>625854</AddressId>
      <City>MDC249</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 13:40:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/08/2023 12:35:12</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>625854</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>322</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Main</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westminster</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21158</Zip5>
         <Zip4>4349</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.0152915</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.5863989</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/30/2023 13:40:45</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/30/2023 13:40:45</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/08/2023 13:09:34</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 13:40:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:21:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>ATTACHMENTS:   Email Printouts   Cease and Desist Letter  NARRATIVE:    On January 30, 2023 I was contacted by Corporal Mills requesting I follow up with an investigation pertaining to threats being made to a government official. Corporal Mills provided multiple email attachments with rude and harassing content from suspect, Brittany Sears, emailed to multiple employees of the Maryland Commission of Civil Rights.    The following isa brief synopsis of the complaint provided via email by Deputy Director Cleveland Horton: The emails are coming from Brittany Sears who had a complaint with our agency. Upon completion of our investigation, our Investigator Tarik Donaldson, contacted her to conduct an exit interview. Ms. Sears became very combative during that interview and has been sending threateningemails directlyto our general mailbox, Tarik Donaldson, Gary Monroe and myself.  The address that we have on file for Ms. Sears is 322 West Main Street, Unit 202, Westminster, MD 21158. Her contact number is 410-844-2892 and the email address that she uses isbas020@mcdaniel.edu.     I reviewed the emails from Sears which have been attached to the case file. The overall tone of the emails is of a generally rude and ranting nature. The suspect using foul language and references her dissatisfaction with the Commission failing to find probable cause with a complaint she had previously filed over two years ago. When reviewing the emails, I noted the following statements to be particularly heinous:   You deserve to die for dicking me around for 2 years just to be ignored. Youre dead. This is not over. You all need to suffer and die.I hope your kids get fucked up the ass by a bloody Jesus cock and they suffer immeasurably. Id love to see a mass murder. Fake fucking dirty stinky government. This is why were out here fucking shit up.   I know what you all look like and its sloppy, dusty, ugly trash. I fucking cant wait to give you what youre ugly asses have coming. You would be pissed if the government dicked you around for almost 2 years for some bullshit. I wish and all your families death. Im keeping close tabs on everyone someone, if not all, needs to get their skull bashed in for what youve done to me and my daughter. Im not afraid to go back to Springfield at all. Die bitches.  Youre going to get everything you deserve. You old, ugly, sloppy disgusting worthless piece of shit. Id love to see you stretched out and caught on fire while getting sliced. Die bitch.   At approximately 1345 hours, TFC Poff of the MSP Westminster Barrack and I made contact with Sears at her residence as provided by Deputy Director Horton. The encounter was captured by TFC. Poffs MSP Issued Body Worn Camera. Sears was identified by her previously obtained MVA photograph. I introduced myself to Sears and identified us as law enforcement following up on a complaint she had previously filed with the Commission of Civil Rights.    Sears initially seemed confused that law enforcement had arrived at her residence, but stated she had filed a complaint a few years ago and was not happy with the outcome. When asked she further explained that she had been sending multiple emails to the Commission over the last few days expressing her concerns and voicing her complaints. When asked who handled her case and who these messages were sent to, she identified Horton, Monroe, and Donaldson. I asked if the messages were polite and professional and Sears acknowledged that some were not. When I began to ask about the content of the messages and what was said, Sears requested TFC Poff and I enter her home to avoid having the conversation in public in her hallway.  Once inside, I continued the interview regarding the content of the messages. Sears was asked if any threats were made, and she acknowledged that she may have made threats in the messages, but stated she was hoping for a response. However, Sears stated TFC Poff and I responding to her house was not the response that she meant. When asked about having contact information regarding the recipients of the emails, Sears only seemed to know their professional email addresses and did not seem aware of any personal contact information or addresses.    I asked Sears if she intended to hurt or harm any of the recipients, and she stated she couldnt because she had a child. I asked Sears if she didnt have a child would she harm them, and she stated no. Additionally, Sears denied any threats of harm to herself or any others. Sears advised she would stop sending additional emails when she was told that this was inappropriate and harassing behavior, and the interview ended.    Following the interview with Sears, the Carroll County States Attorneys Office was consulted in reference to this case. They provided advisement that the victims in this case should have an official letter drafted notifying Sears to cease further contact directly to the victims emails. They also requested attempt to determine the victims desired action in this case.    At approximately 1500 hours, I contacted Deputy Director Horton. I explained that I had spoken with the suspect in this case, as well as consulted with the States Attorneys Office and provided the information received. In reference to Sears, Horton stated his office was concerned because information obtained from their investigation led them to believe that Sears had a mental health disorder, as well as a prior violent history. They further believed she was a prior patient of Springfield Hospital which was also mentioned in her emails above. I asked Horton how he wished to proceed with this case. I advised I had spoken with the suspect and she stated she would cease further contact. I further explained that written notification should be made to cease further contact. I also asked Horton if he wished to proceed with any criminal charges that may apply in consultation with the States Attorneys Office. Horton stated he had a meeting later in the afternoon with other members of the Department where this matter would be discussed. Horton advised he would call me back later in the afternoon after it was discussed further.    On February 2, 2023 I received an email from Mr. Cleveland Horton. The letter contained an attachment of a cease and desist letter addressed to Brittany Sears. The letter was labeled as being sent via Certified/Return Receipt and Regular Mail. A copy of the letter has been attached to this report for documentation purposes.  CASE CLOSED - VICTIM REFUSAL </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6265</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 23:47:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6265</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/08/2023 12:57:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Poff</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mitchell</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6889</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barry</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6265</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493180</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>13</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0477</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>11</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/30/2023 13:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6265</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 12:36:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6265</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/08/2023 12:36:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6265</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 12:47:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:44</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368514</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>SEARS</LastName>
               <FirstName>BRITTANY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ANN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/25/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/08/2023 12:45:04</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B635</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>SEARS</LastName>
               <FirstName>BRITTANY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ANN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/25/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B635</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/08/2023 12:45:04</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>322</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Main</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>202</SubNumber>
               <City>Westminster</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21158</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.015291</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.586398</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>191</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>VIRGINIA</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>A</SubNumber>
               <City>GLEN BURNIE</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21061</Zip5>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>365</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1178</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6265</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 12:47:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:48</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6265</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 12:49:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:02</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368515</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>U</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Horton</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cleveland</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/08/2023 12:48:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H635</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C414</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Horton</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cleveland</FirstName>
               <SLastName>H635</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C414</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/08/2023 12:48:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6265</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 12:49:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>