<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-005337</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/11/2023 03:18:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/11/2023 03:18:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/11/2023 02:49:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/11/2023 02:49:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI: 23-086 "R" Trujillo Romero</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 03:18:08</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 09:22:15</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>560582</AddressId>
      <City>MDC564</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 08:59:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 09:00:28</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>560582</AddressId>
         <StreetName>IL I-695 @ I-83 North</StreetName>
         <City>Towson</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21204</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/11/2023 03:18:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/11/2023 03:18:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/08/2023 09:22:16</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 03:18:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E.) TEAM* The following incident was captured on in-car camera Title: DUI 23-086 R TRUJILLO ROMERO ID: 23-MSP-005337 Defendant: Nery Evelina Trujillo Romero TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:    I am trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).  I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor as of July 2021.  I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of September 2020.  I am a distinguished graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute as of August 2021.  I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of 2020.   margin-left:8px"&gt;I have apprehended more than 300 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On February 11, 2023 at approximately 0250 hours, I (TFC. Speak #7219) was on patrol in marked Maryland State Police vehicle DUI-7 on the Inner Loop of I-695 in the area of Maryland 83, Baltimore County, Maryland. I observed a grey Honda Pilot traveling below the posted speed limit and failing to drive within a single lane. The Honda was bearing Maryland registration 1DY3261.    Right over dotted white lane line with passenger side tires.  Drove on dotted white lane line with driver side tires.  Drove on solid white fog line with passenger side tires.  Drove on dotted white lane line with driver side tires.  Drove on dotted white lane line with passenger side tires.  Drove on dotted white lane line with passenger side tires.  Fluctuating speed.  Drove on dotted white lane line with passenger side tires.  Driving below speed limit of 55 MPH.  Drove on dotted white lane line with driver side tires.  49 MPH in a 55 MPH speed zone, with traffic approaching from the rear.  Swerving side to side within lane three.  Right over dotted white lane line with passenger side tires.  Right over solid white fog line with passenger side tires.  Drove on dotted white lane line with passenger side tires.  Left over dotted white lane line with driver side tires. Swerved right, drove on dotted white lane line with passenger side tires.  Drove on dotted white lane line with driver side tires.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Drove on dotted white lane line with passenger side tires.  The Honda fluctuated speed throughout the duration of observation. The posted speed limit is 55 MPH. I paced the Honda by keeping an equal distance between the Hondas rear bumper and marked patrol vehicle DUI-7s front bumper. During the pace, I did not increase distance between the Hondas rear bumper and marked patrol vehicle DUI-7s front bumper. The Hondas speed was observed at 49 MPH in a 55 MPH speed limit. Upon witnessing these traffic violations, I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the Honda on I/L I-695 at Perring Parkway.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Honda on the driver side and made contact with the female operator of the vehicle, who was the sole occupant. I explained the reason for the stop and requested her drivers license and vehicle registration. The driver attempted to locate her drivers license for several minutes. While looking for the license, the driver was unable to turn the flashlight on her cellphone on and checked the same jacket several times for the license. The driver looked for her drivers license for approximately five (5) minutes and was unable to locate it. While speaking with the driver, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. I observed her eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. When asked about her consumption of alcoholic beverages, the driver stated she had one beer. The driver then identified herself as the registered owner as Nery Romero. I then returned to my patrol vehicle to notify the barrack who I was out with. Upon a METERS/NCIC/MVA browse of the registration, I confirmed the drivers identity as Nery Evelina Trujillo Romero. The search also revealed that her Maryland drivers license is expired as of 2022.  I returned to the Honda and requested Trujillo Romero to exit her vehicle. She complied and exited her vehicle. While speaking to Trujillo Romero outside of her vehicle, in an ambient environment, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. When asked about her consumption of alcohol prior to driving again, Trujillo Romero stated she had two beers (Heineken). Additionally, Trujillo Romero stated her last Heineken was approximately one hour prior to driving. I informed Trujillo Romero that I wanted her to perform standardized field sobriety tests, to which she agreed to the tests. I informed Trujillo Romero she was able to grab her jacket from the backseat and she did.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed in front of the Honda on the right shoulder of I-695. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of patrol vehicle headlights, streetlights, and flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. She appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. She was a jacket, pants, and heels.  I asked Trujillo Romero the following questions:  Glasses or contacts  None Physical Injuries  None Medication  None Medical Conditions  None  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual.    Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus.     Lack of Smooth Pursuit: Present in both eyes.  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes.  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes.      margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Vertical Gaze Nystagmus  Present in both eyes.  WALK AND TURN (5/8 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Trujillo Romero stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. I asked Trujillo Romero if she had a change of shoes and she stated, No. I then asked if she was able to walk in the heels and she stated, Yeah, I think so.  Instructional Stage:     margin-left:8px"&gt;Lost her balance, stepped completely offline to the right once.  Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Missed touching heel to toe by more than  inch on steps 1-9.  Used arms to maintain balance on steps 1, 2, 7, 8, and 9.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Completed 10 steps instead of the instructed nine steps.  Turn: Did not complete turn as instructed.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine):    Missed touching heel to toe by more than  inch on steps 1-9.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Used arms to maintain balance on steps 1-9.  ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Trujillo Romero stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed.   -Right foot raised.  Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10:    Used arms to maintain balance.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Placed raised right foot on the ground.  Seconds 11-20:    Used arms to maintain balance.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Placed raised right foot on the ground.  Seconds 21-30:     margin-left:8px"&gt;Used arms to maintain balance.  PBT #70005012 with a result of .18 BrAC.  ARREST: Due to the number of observations, I concluded Trujillo Romero was driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0315 hours, I placed Trujillo Romero under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. She was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and was transported to the Baltimore County Police Department  Towson Precinct for processing.  Upon arrival at the Towson Precinct, I provided Trujillo Romero with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Trujillo Romero was advised of her DR-15 Advice of Rights in English from the MVA website. She stated that she understood the form. At 0350 hours, Trujillo Romero refused to take a breath test.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: *****REFUSAL*****  Trujillo Romero was polite and cooperative during the encounter. Trujillo Romero was given all copies of the pertinent paperwork and released.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 09:02:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7219</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/01/2023 14:27:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Speak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7219</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Speak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7219</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Speak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7219</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494723</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 03:15:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 08:59:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7219</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 09:00:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 08:59:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:44</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369236</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Trujillo Romero</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nery</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Evelina</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/02/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/16/2023 08:55:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T624</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Trujillo Romero</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nery</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Evelina</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/02/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T624</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/16/2023 08:55:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6706</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>German Hill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21222</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 09:02:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 09:02:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 09:02:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 08:59:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7219</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 08:59:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149874</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 08:59:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7219</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 08:59:53</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2011</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>PLT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1DY3261</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>