<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-006563</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/20/2023 10:36:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/20/2023 10:36:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/20/2023 10:14:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/20/2023 10:14:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Unwanted contact/attempted sexual harassment</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 10:36:12</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4927</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 07:35:51</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SAS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>226624</AddressId>
      <City>MDC217</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 10:36:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/28/2023 20:56:38</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>226624</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>30317</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Deal Island</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Princess Anne</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.701195715012</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.20335432488867</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/20/2023 10:36:06</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/20/2023 10:36:06</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/13/2023 07:35:53</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 10:36:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On Monday, February 20, 2023 at approximately 1014 hours, I, Trooper First Class Hunt 6939, responded to the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack and made contact with a female subject and her daughter in the front lobby, who wanted to file a report of an adult male sending inappropriate messages to the daughter via Snapchat. The mother was identified by her Maryland Drivers License as, Laura Nicole Williams (DOB: 04/11/1985, 5/F), and the juvenile was identified as, Jadyn Alise Williams (DOB:12/13/2008, 1/F). I asked Laura what had happened and she stated, A grown man was sending her inappropriate messages and sent a picture of his gentiles. Laura then pointed to her daughter and Jayden proceeded to read the messages (messages via Instagram and Snapchat attached to the report for reference). I asked Jadyn who the man was and she stated, His name is Khai he used to work at my school, Somerset Intermediate. I then asked Jadyn how this all started and she stated, He followed me on Instagram and asked me to add him on Snapchat and I did. Laura then stated, I told her when he started sending some of the questionable messages to keep talking to him and we will see if he does anything he should.  While messaging with Khai on Snapchat, Khai sent a photo and deleted it prior to Jadyn being able to view the photo. Jadyn asked Khai what the message was that he had deleted to which he stated, O my fat dick. Jadyn stated, u sent me it? Khai then stated, Yea my fault. I asked Jadyn if she was ever able to see the photo that Khai had sent and she stated, No he deleted it. I asked Jadyn when the last time that she had contacted Khai to which she stated, January 26 but then he deleted me. I asked if she knew Khais last name and she stated, No but he lives down in Marion. I asked Jadyn if she had Khais phone number to which she stated, No, but he has been messaging my friend too. I then asked Jadyn if she knew how many people he was messaging like this and she stated, No but its a few.  Khai was later identified as, Khai Nathaniel Sterling (DOB:10/10/2002, H/M). Contact was not made with Khai in regards to this incident.  Laura and Jadyn both completed written statements in regards to this incident and both have been attached to the report for reference.  I request that this case be forwarded to CED for further investigation. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/02/2023 21:48:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6939</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/02/2023 21:49:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Marshall</LastName>
            <FirstName>Randolph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5794</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hunt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colbey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6939</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>20</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 21:00:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6692</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 14:02:59</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>246865</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sterling</LastName>
               <FirstName>Khai</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nathaniel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/10/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.15653927E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>09/26/2019 18:05:37</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S364</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K000</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sterling</LastName>
               <FirstName>Khai</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nathaniel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/10/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.15653927E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S364</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K000</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/26/2019 18:05:37</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>28464</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hudson Corner</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Marion Station</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21838</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.768151</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.040408</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>365</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8196</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/26/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6692</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/12/2023 14:02:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 21:00:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>14</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 21:06:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 14:03:24</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370402</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Williams</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jadyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alise</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/13/2008 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/28/2023 21:06:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J350</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Williams</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jadyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alise</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/13/2008 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J350</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/28/2023 21:06:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 21:06:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 21:11:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:20</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>1830</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Williams</LastName>
               <FirstName>Laura</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/11/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2013 08:27:11</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Williams</LastName>
               <FirstName>Laura</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/11/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2013 08:27:11</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>30317</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Deal Island</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Princess Anne</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21853</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.700928</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.203058</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>119</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Moonglow</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Fruitland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21826</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.608927</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.307845</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>540</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>313</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0783</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2013 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>540</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>313</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0783</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2013 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>BUS</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>651</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2539</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2013 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 21:11:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 21:11:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/12/2023 13:59:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/12/2023 13:59:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/13/2023 07:35:53</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6692</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/12/2023 13:59:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>CED Initial </NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Reason for Submission:  CED Initial Interview of Khai Sterling Arrest of Khai Sterling  Narrative:   Based on the nature of the incident, Investigators from the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division were requested to assist with the investigation.   Based on a separate active investigation (23-MSP-020379), I was familiar with the subject identified as Khai Nathaniel Sterling [hereinafter referred to as Khai]. A subpoena was previously submitted to Snapchat on August 3, 2023, in reference to Snap chat Username: draco_boygang.  I reviewed the report and messages sent between Jadyn and Sterling and below is a synopsis of the messages.  Instagram:   On January 25, 2023, Instagram user Kxnkoux became friends with Jadyn on Instagram. Below is a synopsis of the conversation and not a direct transcript. During the conversation, Instagram user Kxnkoux identifies himself as Khai and asks to become friends.  Khai says: 18 Jadyn says ur kinda to old for me Khai: We can be friends right Jadyn: uhmm idk Khai: You got snap fr Jadyn: whatchu want my snap for? January 26, 2023 Khai: You know me Jadyn: its frjadyn Khai: Added mine draco_boygang Jadyn: added u back  Snapchat:    During a review of the Snapchat messages between Draco_boygang and Jadyn on January 25 and January 26, below is a depiction of the messages:  Draco: Damn I remember when we was talking at the middle school Jadyn: when? Draco: You remember practice Jadyn: yea we only had like one conversation thp Draco: Fr tho we should talk more you down fr Jadyn: talk more like what? Draco: So we can be friends finally now Jadyn: wdym finally Draco: Nothing but any way between only question Draco: Wait are you thick or skinny no crazy shit Jadyn: Im skinny Draco: Damn skinny fr, Proof me wrong then Jadyn: wdym? Im skinny Draco: Your ass skinny fr Jadyn: is that a bad thing? Draco: Nah cause I dont know show some pics fr Jadyn: pics of what, ur like 18 Draco: Damn be quiet tho Jadyn: abt what Draco: About your skinny ass body Jadyn: down for what ur not telling me Draco: Ok wait if I ask can I get it tho Jadyn: get what Draco: I was going to smack it fr but I didnt want to Draco: ik that ass not fr Jadyn: u wanted to smack my butt Draco: you let me Jadyn: did u want to? Ur 18 Draco: Ok so nobody got to know shit Jadyn: okay Draco: Yea fs I did I was curious be honest Im ugly Draco: Damn take some then shawty Jadyn: okay, what did you delet? Jadyn: hold on Draco O my fault, srry mamas, Damn shawty you scared Jadyn: wdym am I scared? Draco: Why you never send them fr Jadyn: its weird bc ur 19, 18** Draco: Yea fs I did I was curious be honest Im ugly or nah friend Jadyn: umm ur okay Draco: So you down fr you let me smack it so hard my hand print on your cheeks fr Jadyn: Ill think about it Draco: A picture of Khai saying Yo Friend Draco; Deleted message Jadyn: What did u delete? I didnt get to read it Draco: O my fat dick Jadyn: u sent it me it? Draco: Yeah my fault Jadyn: okay Draco: How fat that ass is fr Jadyn: not fat Draco: Cap show me then, that ass fat Jadyn: no its not Draco: Cap send some with shorts damn Jadyn: I dont have one Draco: Damn take some then shawty Draco: Damn who you with fr Jadyn: no one Im sitting on the bleachers in gym class Draco: Damn what grade you in Jadyn: 8th Draco: An emoji picture of a male and female laying together Jadyn: whats that mean?  Based on a separate investigation (23-MSP-020379), a subpoena was served on Snap chat for subscriber information of Draco_boygang. Upon return the following information was provided ( A copy of the Snap chat response is attached to the case file):   Email address khaisterling10@gmail.com    margin-left:8px"&gt;Backup phone number (443) 953-1187.    A search of Khai Sterling revealed a date of birth as 10/10/2002 with an address of 28464 Hudson Corner Road, Marion Station, Maryland.  On October 10, 2023, Detective Schultz from the Wicomico County Child Advocacy Center and I responded to 28464 Hudson Corner Road, Marion Station, Maryland and made contact with Khai Sterling [hereinafter referred to as Sterling] Sterling was advised that our encounter was being audibly and visually recorded on body camera and that he was free to go and did not have to speak with investigators. Sterling agreed to speak with investigators, below is a synopsis of the interview and not a direct transcript therefore paraphrasing may be utilized:    Sterling acknowledged that today was his birthday   He agreed his Snap chat name was previously draco_boygang  He agreed he previously worked at Somerset Intermediate School  He denied sending pictures to students   He denied any knowledge of the picture or comment my big fat dick  He again confirmed the Draco_boygang was his snap chat   margin-left:8px"&gt;Interview concluded     Based on the age parameters of Sterling being more than 4 years older than Jadyn and the continuing course of conduct, investigators contacted the Somerset County Deputy States Attorney Hayward and decided charges would be filed.   On October 11, 2023, I applied for and obtained an arrest warrant for Khai Sterling.   At approximately 1645hrs, TFC Wilson and I responded to 28464 Hudson Corner Road and made contact with Sterling. Upon contact with Sterling, he was initially confrontational but with the assistance of Sterlings mother and de-escalation techniques Sterling was placed under arrest without incident.   Sterling was transported to the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack for processing. Upon arrival at the barrack Sterling was seated in the processing room. As I was filling out the warrant information, Sterling asked me to explain to him what was going on, prior to going over the warrant. I explained to Sterling that I wanted to make sure he understood his rights prior to me asking any questions, I read Sterling his Miranda Rights from an MSP 180 and Sterling agreed and signed the form. Below is a synopsis of the interview and not a direct transcript therefore paraphrasing may be utilized:    Sterling signed an MSP 180  He identified Draco_boygang as a previous snap-chat username he used  I began explaining the case regarding Jadyn  He explained these girls just want his money  I have hos I dont need her  He identified his Instagram username saying thats me   He agreed he added Jadyn on Snap chat and asked her to add back  He identified his previous phone number   He identified the email address Snap chat provided was his  He agreed the Instagram username was his   He explained Jadyn sent him a picture of her ass and asked him to rate it   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;He agreed by saying facts that it is inappropriate to request explicit photos from underage girls   A virtual hearing was conducted with the Somerset County District Court Commissioners Office via phone. Sterling was held without bond and transported to the Somerset County Detention Center without incident.  Case Closed. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6692</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/12/2023 14:04:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6692</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 14:21:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Towsend</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6692</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pruitt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jonathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4927</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Towsend</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6692</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Towsend</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6692</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495959</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 3799</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/11/2023 14:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 3799</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6692</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/12/2023 14:00:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6692</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 14:01:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>