<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009636</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/17/2023 08:52:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/17/2023 08:52:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/17/2023 08:51:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/17/2023 08:51:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Allegation of inappropriate conduct by school employee</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 08:52:54</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6049</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/14/2023 08:49:08</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>358809</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 08:52:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/30/2023 07:43:38</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>358809</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>110</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>James</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Elkton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.83339784296581</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.62138311688125</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/17/2023 08:52:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/17/2023 08:52:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>05/30/2023 10:54:37</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 08:52:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6049</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/14/2023 08:49:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> Narrative: On March 17, 2023 I was assigned this investigation. The investigation was originally begun by the Elkton Police Department, but the Maryland State Police were asked to assume the investigation due to a conflict of interest.  Case Summary On February 22, 2023, a student at Elkton High School, Ojahnae Boyd (hereafter referred to as Ojahnae) spoke with the Elkton High School resource officer, Officer Roland, about a Cecil County Public School employee, Charles Henry Givens Jr. (B/M, 08/29/1979). Officer Roland wrote a summary of what was discussed. That summary is attached to this report. Ojahnae told Officer Roland that Givens was making her feel uncomfortable. She said he was messaging her via text message as well as over Instagram and that Givens was commenting on her Instagram posts with a clap and fire emojis. Ojahnae told Officer Roland that Givens had approached her and said he wanted to take her out to dinner for her work as the team manager for the boys basketball team. She initially told him she didnt like Mexican food and then left. She said he later messaged her about dinner and this time included his daughter, who is a senior at Elkton High School. Officer Roland informed Ojahnaes father, Jeffery Boyd of what was going on and Jeffery Boyd filed for a peace order on behalf of Ojahnae. Officer Roland noted several other incidents in the past several years that caused concern.  2019-2020 School Year    margin-left:8px"&gt;A parent of a student from Elkton High School contacted the school about a guidance counselor named Mr. Miller bringing a student home. A video of the event was viewed by Officer Roland and Mr. Miller was actually identified as Charles Givens. This incident may have been submitted to the Central Office.   2021-2022 School year    A student, Jada Hopkins, had to be taken home because she did not have a ride. Charles Givens was called to give her a ride. Jada refused to get in a car with him and stated her mother told her never to get in a car with Givens. Jada was transported home by Officer Roland who asked Jada why she wouldnt get in a car with Givens. Jada told Officer Roland that Givens had not done anything inappropriate to her but to her friend. She would not say who her friend was.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Givens kept appearing in Elkton High School Cafeteria. Given does not work at the High School except as an assistant coach to the basketball team. Givens was using a master key to the building to get into the building from the side entrance. He would sit at lunch with his daughter and her friends. Givens was confronted by Mr. Leitgeb about the key and was told he had to sign in to the main office when visiting the building.   2022-2023 School year     margin-left:8px"&gt;Beginning January 24th, Givens began signing in a student to school by the name of Ella Alexander. He signed her in eight (8) times in the Main Office. The summary written by Officer Roland states the school never communicated with Ella Alexander to have Givens pick her up.   On March 21, 2023 Ojahnae was interviewed at the Cecil County Child Advocacy Center. Ojahnae stated she is a freshman at Elkton High School. She said in December Givens would slide up on her Instagram posts. She said he wouldnt message her but would respond to her stories with a clapping hand emoji or a fire emoji. She said she didnt take it as anything at the time. She said he would do it with like every picture. She said it started getting weird then, that she was best friends with his kids. She said he would text her late at night and that he would reply to her stories. She said one time at 9 pm he texted her what she was doing and she said she was going to bed. She said he asked why so early. She said that was the last straw, so she reported it. She said she felt a grown man shouldnt be texted a 15-year-old at 9 pm and that the text wasnt sports related. She said she was the basketball manager with Givens son and daughter. She said she was fine with Givens having her number and Instagram because he was the assistant coach of the basketball team, but that it got weird when he was texting her late at night and that it was making her uncomfortable. Ojahnae gave several examples. She said one time she posted something on Instagram that said something along the lines of when in silence and he messaged her saying kill them in silence. She said she didnt respond because she was confused about what he was talking about. She said another time he sent her a post via Instagram about a dog late at night. She said she didnt respond because she was again confused about why he was sending it. Ojahnae was asked if she talked to anyone about being confused. Ojahnae said she told her ex-boyfriends mother and her ex-boyfriends mother told her that made her uncomfortable. Ojahnae said she kept her ex-boyfriends mother updated on the situation and was told to report it. Ojahnae said she reported it to Officer Roland. She said they talked about it, and Officer Roland told her dad, Jeffrey Boyd, who took it from there. Ojahnae was asked about her relationship with Givens kids. She said his daughter, Shadai is a senior and they know each other from playing soccer together. She said she knew Givens from before and had talked to him a few times. She said he left her backpack in Shadais car. She said he texted her asking if he could drop it off. She said he dropped it off at her house. She said she hadnt given him her address, but she wasnt worried about it, because he was a teacher and could look it up. She said he didnt text her after that. She went on to say she was with Givens children almost every day. Ojahnae said she doesnt talk to Shadai anymore, but still talks to Givens son. She said she told Givens son what happened and he thanked her for telling him. She said she and Shadai never really had a texting relationship. Ojahnae said she is currently doing school online because of the current situation. She said people started asking questions about it and someone in Havre de Grace went to her moms and told her mom they heard Ojahnae was sleeping with Givens. Ojahnae said that wasnt true and that they only texted. She said she never got in a car with him.  Ojahnae was asked if Givens had asked her to do something that made her uncomfortable. Ojahnae said he asked her to go to dinner with him. She said he texted her to go out to dinner, him and Shadai, for being a good manager. She said at the Falston game he asked to take her out to dinner but didnt mention his kids name. She said then the practice before the first playoff game he asked her about dinner again. She said she wish she still had the text messages, but they got deleted. Ojahnae was asked what about Givens makes her uncomfortable. She said he is just a weird guy. She said he makes jokes that arent funny and stands too close to people when he talks to them. She said there were more girls that he makes feel uncomfortable, but she doesnt know who they are. She was asked how she knows there were other girls, and she said Officer Roland told her.  No further pertinent information was obtained from the interview.  I reviewed the screenshots of the Instagram conversations. I noticed the exchanges are all reactions to Instagram stories. Instagram stories are short clips posted to Instagram that self-delete after twenty-four hours. The stories appear at the top of the users application screen. They appear from left to right from newest to oldest. Once one story is clicked, the user can scroll to additional stories from the same users and other users without returning to the home screen. Without looking through all of Givens Instagram account, it would be impossible to determine if he singled out Ojahnae, or if he was just scrolling through stories and reacting to them.  Search of Work phone  Givens was provided a phone by the Cecil County Public School. When the allegation against him was made he was required to turn in his cellphone. When he received the cellphone he signed a policy that the phone was subject to search. A copy of the policy and a form acknowledging the policy is attached.  Cecil County Public Schools signed a consent to search the phone. I reviewed the phone and did not find anything criminal on the phone. I did locate text messages between Givens and Ella Alexander/ her guardian requesting Givens give her a ride to school.  Case remains open pending review from the Cecil County States Attorney. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6080</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/30/2023 07:44:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6080</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/30/2023 07:47:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hall</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bradley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5585</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sarver</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6080</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/13/2023 14:02:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/13/2023 14:02:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40O</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/14/2023 08:49:08</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6080</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 14:02:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6049</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/14/2023 08:49:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On June 13, 2023, I received a declination letter from the Cecil County States Attorneys Office.  Case Closed: Lack of Prosecutorial Merit</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6080</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 14:03:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6080</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 14:04:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Donald</LastName>
            <FirstName>Frank</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6049</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sarver</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6080</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>