<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-021057</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/12/2023 14:02:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/12/2023 14:02:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/12/2023 13:37:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/12/2023 13:37:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Suspect entered the store and caused a disturbance and then departed the store.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/12/2023 14:02:41</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5980</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:14:44</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>148108</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>581</SubBeat>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/12/2023 14:02:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/15/2023 16:32:45</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>148108</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>9543</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Easton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.059461</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.811092</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FAST STOP</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/12/2023 14:02:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/12/2023 14:02:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 09:14:44</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/12/2023 14:02:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5980</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:14:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>TYPE OF REPORT: Disorderly Conduct CASE #: 23-MSP-021057  DATE: Monday, June 12th, 2023 TIME: 1337 hrs. WEATHER: Sunny/Clear  NEIGHBORHOOD CHECKS: Due to the location and type of incident, No neighborhood checks were conducted.  SCENE PROCESSING: I gathered and viewed business camera footage of the incident. The suspect in this case used a credit card to make purchases from the store which connected the timing of the event, along with confirming his visit to the store. The proper identify of the suspect in this case was photo matched with the registration to the owner of the vehicle and the MVA drivers license of the driver.  DISPOSITION: After determining there was no physical or mechanical damage to the glass entrance door to the business, no charges were issued in this case.  PHOTOs: Photos were taken of the front glass entrance doors to the business and were uploaded to the report  file.  VIDEO: Body camera footage was activated upon interviewing the complainant in this incident.  SUSPECT:    Mr. Stewart John Godlewski Jr.   MD-10272830846 (Maryland Lic.)   DOB: 03/06/1986 W/M   61 ht. 215 lbs.   4836 Bethlehem Rd.   Preston, MD 21655  NARRATIVE:    On Monday, June 12th, 2023 at approximately 1:37 PM, I (M/Tpr. Ian C. Rola #2705) was dispatched to respond to the Shell Convenient Store, located at 9543 Ocean Gateway, Easton, Maryland, for a report of disorderly conduct while the night shift crew was working. Upon arrival, I met up with the complainant, Mrs. Dinesha Panduwawala (store owner) who advised that a subject entered the store early that morning around 12:30 AM and demanded that alcohol be sold to him. When the suspect was denied by the counter clerk the subject became upset, made some statements and exited the store. I requested Panduwawala pull the store convenient security cameras so that I may view the incident.    Upon viewing the incident, I observed a middle-aged white male subject with blue jeans, gray T-shirt with a blue baseball cap approach the counter around 12:30 AM and requested the counter clerk to sell him a Redbull, the counter clerk replied that he cannot sell alcohol items from the hours of 12:00 AM to 6:00 AM. The suspect then stated, listen, my dad just died at Easton Hospital, and I want to purchase Fireball and a pack of Newports. The clerk replied that I can sell you Newports, but I cannot sell you alcohol. There was some small conversation and then the suspect stated you know what, then just give me the fucken Newports then. The clerk retrieved a pack of Newports and placed them on the counter and proceeded to conduct the sale. As the clerk was at the register the suspect walked up to the counter across from the register and physically motioned and drew back his right arm making a fist with his right hand and stated, I will reach over this fucken counter and get you! The suspect did not physically assault the clerk, but stated afterwards, I am glad what we did in Pakistan to, I hope we killed some of your family members. The suspect then walked towards the exit and kicked the bottom of the interior glass entrance door, causing the door to dislodge from the frame rails, and exited the store.    After reviewing the different camera angles, it was noted that the suspect drove a white Dodge pick-up truck with Maryland vehicle registration 8BG5707, parked in front of the store. An MVA check was conducted on the vehicle registration, coming back to a Mr. Stewart J. Godlewski Jr. (DOB: 03/06/1986 W/M) of 4836 Bethlehem Rd., Preston, Maryland. Godlewski used a credit card for the purchase of the Newports. The credit card that was used in the store belonged to Godlewski. An MVA drivers license photo match was also conducted to properly identify Godlewski in the convenient store videos to positively identify Godlewski as the suspect in this case.    Upon looking at the entrance door it was noted that there were no signs of physical damaged and the doors operation appeared to be normal. Although Godlewskis statements were alarming, he did not physically assault the clerk. I have attempted to make contact with Godlewski at his residence in Bethlehem regarding this incident with no luck. At this time I request this case SUSPENDED due to no assault occurred in this case. All events occurred in Talbot County, Maryland.  M/Tpr. Ian C. Rola #2705</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP2705</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 11:51:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP2705</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/15/2023 16:29:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tassone</LastName>
            <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5980</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rola</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2705</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP2705</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 16:31:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:02</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>66314</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Godlewski</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stewart</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>John</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/06/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>07/13/2015 14:23:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G342</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S363</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Godlewski</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stewart</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>John</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/06/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>G342</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S363</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/13/2015 14:23:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5004</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>River</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hurlock</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21643</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.825304</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.660127</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4980</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Bethlehem</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Preston</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.94531843438166</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.74507006681757</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>496</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5697</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/04/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>786</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4714</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/13/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP2705</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 16:31:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>