<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-020916</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/11/2023 06:43:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/11/2023 06:43:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/11/2023 05:52:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/11/2023 05:52:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>-Single vehicle accident. -DUI/DWI 23-151.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 06:43:18</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5948</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/28/2023 02:33:10</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>377997</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 06:43:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 14:00:43</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>377997</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>3316</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Churchville</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Aberdeen</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.23098338524802</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.541687296698754</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/11/2023 06:43:14</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/11/2023 06:43:14</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/05/2023 11:56:27</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 06:43:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MARYLAND STATE POLICE BEL AIR BARRACK D HARFORD COUNTY, MARYLAND This incident was recorded. Marked Unit D-10s in-car camera and Tpr. Rowes body worn camera were working properly.  OFFENDER Case #: 23-MSP-020916 Defendant: Michael Shawn Bowers Jr Date of Birth: 6/17/1993 Date of Arrest: 6/11/2023 Time of Arrest: 0633 hours DUI #: 23-151 DUI Citation #: 19M0XD3  FIRST DUI OFFENSE  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING:  *I am trained to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  *I am trained and certified to conduct preliminary breathalyzer tests by the Maryland State Police.  *I received Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement(ARIDE) training through the Maryland State Police in April 2022.  Phase #1 - Vehicle in Motion    On June 11, 2023, at approximately 0557 hours, I, Trooper Rowe (#7015), currently assigned to the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack, responded to a single vehicle accident off the roadway. Investigation revealed that the vehicle was traveling eastbound on MD 22 in the area of Snake Lane when the vehicle crossed the center line, ran off road left, struck a ditch, struck a fence, and destroyed approximately 40 trees belonging to Krohs Nursery located at 3308 Churchville Road, Aberdeen, MD. The vehicle was identified as a silver Chevy Malibu displaying Delaware registration 156034.  Phase #2 - Personal Contact    When I arrived on scene, the Chevy Malibu was backing up in the tree garden as if it was attempting to flee the scene. I order both occupants to exit the vehicle. I asked if they were ok and if they needed medical attention. Both occupants advised they did not need medical attention. Upon making contact with the driver of the vehicle, I asked him how the accident happened. The driver advised that the brakes went out on the car. I asked both occupants to move to the shoulder area of MD 22, so we were not staying on Krohs Nurserys property more than we needed to be. While exiting the garden, the driver and passenger had to lean on each other to keep their balance. As they walked they were swaying side to side. When the driver stepped over the broken fence, his shoe got stuck in the muddy ditch, and he continued walking a few feet with one shoe until he realized his shoe was missing and went back to retrieve it. I asked both occupants if they had their IDs on them. Both advised that they did not have it with them. I had them provide me with their names and date of births. The driver advised his name was Michael Shawn Bowers Jr, DOB 6/17/1993. The passenger attempted to provide her name but could not provide her name clearly and eventually took my note pad and wrote down her name. She provided that her first name was Gabriella and wrote her middle name was Christin and her last name was Ella. I asked her what her date of birth was, and she provided 10/27/2000. This information was incorrect but was later identified as Gabriella Christine Sylvester, DOB 10/27/2000. I asked if their IDs were Maryland licenses, Sylvester advised she does and just did not have it on her and Bowers advised that he does not have his license but is in the process of getting his. While Sylvester and Bowers spoke, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from their breath and person. I asked where they were coming from, and Bowers advised he was dropping off his brother in Glen Burnie and was headed home. Bowers advised he tried to pull over, so he could pee in a bottle, and then he brakes would not work. Bowers then stated a racoon ran out in front of him, and he had to swerve to avoid hitting it, but the brakes gave out. Bowers advised that he attempted to move his vehicle, but he got stuck backing it up over more trees, which is what the caller was referring to him attempting to flee the scene.   I asked Bowers why he was driving when he did not have his drivers license yet. He advised he needed to get home and get his brother home. I asked Bowers if he was out drinking that night. Bowers advised they were, but he stopped drinking at around 2100 hours. He stated they left the bar at around 2300 hours. Bowers then went to his car to attempt to retrieve the registration for the car. Bowers was unable to find the registration or the insurance information. I asked Bowers what kind of drinks he was having the night prior, and he advised some Henney. I then requested Bowers to conduct Standardized Field of Sobriety Tests, to which he complied.  Phase #3 - Pre-Arrest Screening  The tests were conducted on the right shoulder of MD 22, Aberdeen, Maryland. The surface was dry, level, and free from obvious debris. Bowers displayed no visible injuries. The front facing emergency lights of all patrol vehicles were deactivated during all phases of testing.  I asked Bowers the following questions:  Daily/Regular Medications - NONE. Glasses - NONE. Contacts - NONE. Injuries - NONE.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS TEST (6/6 clues displayed)  I used my pen as a stimulus and held it approximately 12 to 15 inches from Bowers eyes. His eyes displayed no resting nystagmus and his pupils were equal in size. His eyes also showed equal tracking. He was advised to stand with his feet together and his hands down at his sides during the instruction, demonstration, and throughout the test. I asked Bowers if he could see the tip of my stimulus, and he stated that he could. I observed his eyes to be bloodshot. Bowers was instructed to follow the stimulus with his eyes only, keeping his head still. After stating that he understood the instructions, Bowers attempted the test with the following results:  1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes. 2. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes. 3. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 degrees - Present in both eyes. 4. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus - Not present.  WALK AND TURN (8/8 clues displayed)  Bowers was placed on an imaginary straight line of the right shoulder of the road way. Bowers was asked if he was comfortable to walk and balance in his shoes. He stated he was. Bowers was instructed to stand on that straight line with his left foot and then place his right foot in front of his left foot with the right heel touching the toe of his left foot. Bowers was instructed to stand in this manner while standing straight with his hands to his sides. Bowers was then further instructed to remain in that position while the test instructions were given, the test was demonstrated, and throughout the test, which Bowers stated he understood. Bowers was instructed to take nine heel-to-toe steps along the straight line in front of him. Bowers was told after the ninth step, he was to turn around by keeping his front foot planted on the ground, and he would take a small series of steps with his other foot to turn around. After turning around, he was to take an additional nine heel-to-toe steps back along the same straight line he had come from. I then demonstrated the test for Bowers, taking only three steps instead of taking nine on each pass, reminding him that he will be taking nine steps. Bowers was then instructed to watch his feet at all times while walking, to count out his steps out loud, to keep his arms down at his sides during the test, and to not stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Bowers if he understood the instructions, and he stated that he did. I then asked Bowers to begin the test with the following results:  Instructional Stage  -Starts too soon 1 time. -Cannot keep balance 6 times.  Walking Stage (1st Nine Steps)  -Stepped off the line by more than 1/2 inch on steps 3, 5, 6, and 7. -Stops walking on step 6. -Completed 10 steps when instructed to complete 9 steps.  The Turn  -Completed improperly, picked up both feet.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine Steps)  -Stepped off the line by more than 1/2 inch on steps 2 and 9. -Missed heel to toe by more than 1/2 inch on steps 2, 8, and 9. -Raised arms on step 2. -Stops walking on steps 1 and 2.  ONE LEG STAND (1/4 clues displayed)  Bowers was instructed to stand with his feet together and his hands flat to his sides while the test instructions and demonstration were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground in front of him approximately 6 inches, keeping his legs straight and his toes pointed out in front of him, parallel to the ground. While his leg was raised, he was to count out loud by starting at one thousand (one thousand one, one thousand two, one thousand three...) and to continue counting until told to stop. After demonstrating the test, Bowers advised he understood, stating that he would be raising his left foot off the ground.  Instructional Stage:  -Bowers would not keep his hands to his side.  Balancing and Counting Stage:  -Swayed left to right throughout the test.   I requested Bowers to complete a Preliminary Breath Test, to which he consented to take. Bowers PBT test results were .11. Bowers was placed under arrest for DUI/DWI at approximately 0633 hours. A search incident to arrest was conducted on Bowers person, no contraband found. I had Bowers open his mouth to check for any foreign material that would interfere in taking a breath test, nothing was observed. I then placed him in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. I attempted to locate the registration and insurance card in the vehicle. While looking for them, I located an opened Hennessy bottle underneath the front passenger seat.  OBSERVATIONS:  -Caused a single vehicle accident. -Could not keep balance throughout the incident. -Admitted to drinking the night prior. -Opened container of Hennessy in the passenger area of the vehicle. -HGN: 6/6 clues displayed. -Walk and Turn: 8/8 clues. -One Leg Stand: 1/4 clues. -PBT: .11  Post Arrest:  While at the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack D, Bowers was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, so he could follow along as the DR-15 Advice of Rights was read out loud. Bowers signed the DR-15 at approximately 0715 hours, acknowledging his consent to take the test. Sergeant Dudek(#5037), a certified Intoximeter Technician of the Maryland State Police, conducted the test for Bowers. Bowers breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of 0.06 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. Bowers was issued all pertinent documentations regarding the incident. Bowers was then released to a sober ride, at approximately 0802 hours. Bowers was polite and cooperative throughout the entire incident. All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.  I request this case to be closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 14:20:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 16:11:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rogers</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6377</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7015</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dudek</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5037</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7015</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7015</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510351</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16616</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/11/2023 06:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 13:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 14:13:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510351</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15408</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/11/2023 06:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 13:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 14:08:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510351</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16833</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/11/2023 06:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 13:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 14:12:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510351</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/11/2023 06:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 13:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 14:12:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510351</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/11/2023 06:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 13:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 14:11:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510351</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/11/2023 06:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 13:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 14:11:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510351</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/11/2023 06:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 13:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 14:09:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510351</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/11/2023 06:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 13:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 14:09:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510351</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/11/2023 06:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 13:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 14:07:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510351</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/11/2023 06:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 13:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 14:08:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510351</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>18602</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/11/2023 06:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 13:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 14:10:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 13:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>209640</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bowers</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shawn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/17/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>10/18/2018 22:14:35</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bowers</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shawn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/17/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>B620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/18/2018 22:14:35</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>201</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Bluegrass</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Elkton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21921</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5253</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.8027029</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.632768</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>201</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Bluegrass</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Elkton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21921</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5253</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.8027029</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.632768</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1969</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Old Philadelphia</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>apt A</SubNumber>
               <City>Elkton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21921</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.867513</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.60579</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>302</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>858</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9250</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/29/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>267</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>401</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6966</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>358</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7323</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/18/2018 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 14:15:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 14:15:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 14:15:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/17/2023 14:00:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 14:00:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>