<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-006870</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/22/2023 19:01:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/22/2023 19:01:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/22/2023 18:24:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/22/2023 18:24:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Possession of CDS</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/22/2023 19:01:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 08:27:15</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DSM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>SALEM AVE/ N BURHANS BLVD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>685172</AddressId>
      <City>MDC166</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/22/2023 19:01:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 12:25:04</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>685172</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Salem</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Hagerstown</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>N</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>BLVD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-77.72493</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.64776</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>400-419 SALEM AVE / 200-299 N BURHANS BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/22/2023 19:01:41</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/22/2023 19:01:41</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/27/2023 09:13:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/22/2023 19:01:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 08:27:15</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 2-22-2023, I Sgt Roberts was on patrol in the area of North Burhans Boulevard near Salem Ave in Hagerstown Maryland. At that time I observed a Black Ford Explorer bearing Maryland registration 784 6Z1 in front of my vehicle. I could clearly see inside the vehicle and observed the front drivers side and passengers side seat belt area of the vehicle. I could clearly see that the seat belt buckles were hanging from the seatbelts on the B pilar of the vehicle. In seeing this, I could determine that both the driver and the front seat passenger were not wearing their seatbelt. As I observed this the vehicle turned onto Salem Ave where I initiated a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle came to a stop on the right shoulder of Salem Ave past North Burhans Boulevard near High Street. As the vehicle came to a stop I conducted a passenger side approach to the vehicle. As I made contact with the driver the passenger had put his seatbelt on, but the driver stated that he could not wear his seatbelt as he had a colostomy bag. In speaking to the driver he was nervous. I asked them where they were going, and I did not get a direct answer from them. As I was on the passenger side of the vehicle the passenger would not make eye contact with me as I spoke to both him and the driver. Once the driver provided me with his information Master Trooper Hood arrived on scene and was at the passenger side of the vehicle. I returned to my vehicle in order to continue working on the traffic stop.     As I continued the traffic stop I contacted the Hagerstown State Police barrack and requested a K-9. In the course of the traffic stop Deputy Atwell from the Washington County Sheriffs Department arrived on scene at the traffic stop. As I continued the traffic Deputy Atwell and his K-9 conducted a K-9 Scan of the vehicle. A positive alert was given on the vehicle from Deputy Atwells K-9 and a probable cause search was conducted. In removing the occupants of the vehicle the Passenger was asked to Step out of the vehicle first. The Passenger was identified as Mr. Thomas James Custer DOB 4-15-1981. Mr. Custer was given instructions on how to exit the vehicle by Master Trooper Hood. Mr Custer exited the vehicle and was pat down for weapons with the passenger side door open. Mr. Custer stated that he had a pill holder on him.    A complete search of the vehicle was conducted, and no contraband was located inside the vehicle. The driver of the vehicle Mr. Gary Wayne Fitzwater DOB 4/9/1960 was in possession of a prescription bottle of Oxycodone. The pills inside the bottle matched what Pill Identifier had listed as the pills. Mr. Custer was searched on scene as he stated that he had a pill holder on him and in the left front pocket of his jeans a white plastic straw used to ingest crushed pills was located. When this straw was pulled out of his pocket with the metal pill holder he stated that it was from his house. He stated that he crushes his pills and snorts them. Mr. Custer was advised that the drug paraphernalia contained residue and that he would be charged on a criminal citation for possession of CDS not Marijuana.    Mr. Custer was issued criminal citation 202001935074 and released. Mr. Custer asked if he could get a warning and I explained to him that he could not have this item and the CDS on him. Mr. Custer was disappointed and stated that he picked that straw up off of the ground. I explained to him that he already told me the straw came from his house and he stated that he used to snort pills, and he stated well my jeans came from the house. I provided him with a copy of his criminal citation, and he was advised he was free to leave. I provided Mr. Fitzwater with his information along with a MSP pamphlet and a written warning for not wearing his seatbelt.    All of the above events occurred in Washington County Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5457</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 21:54:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5457</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 13:50:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Roberts</LastName>
            <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5457</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>41</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5457</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 13:19:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:30</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370019</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Custer</LastName>
               <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>James</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/15/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 13:13:58</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C236</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Custer</LastName>
               <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>James</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/15/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C236</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 13:13:58</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5457</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 13:19:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/16/2023 12:17:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/16/2023 12:17:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/17/2023 08:27:13</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5457</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 12:17:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 08:27:15</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 3-15-2023 at 0931 hours I received an email with the crime lab analysis results. The analysis tested the CDS in this case which tested positive for Oxycodone. The lab results will be attached to this report. At this time this case remains closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5457</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 12:18:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5457</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/16/2023 12:19:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Roberts</LastName>
            <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5457</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>