<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-014464</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/23/2023 23:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/23/2023 23:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/23/2023 23:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/23/2023 23:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Disorderly between family members who do not reside together.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 23:54:47</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1652</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 10:48:46</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>529364</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 23:54:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 01:30:52</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>529364</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>15102</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>New Windsor</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>New Windsor</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.14124</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.5054</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/23/2023 23:54:45</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/23/2023 23:54:45</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/01/2023 10:23:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 23:54:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP1652</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 10:48:46</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Cpl. Sean Slattery // Body worn camera available // Dash Camera not available Trooper Justin Marlatt // Body worn camera available // Dash Camera not available  Attachments: Written Statements  Suspect / Complainant: Tyler Grant Steele DOB: 01/13/2003 15102 New Windsor Rd New Windsor, MD 21776 240-397-0303  Statement: Steele advised that he has lived at 15102 New Windsor Rd for over 15 years. He stated that his Aunt, Melissa Damon, showed up today and, for reasons unknown to him, was planning to stay for an unknown amount of time. He also advised that 15102 New Windsor Rd is owned by his grandparents who have raised him. Steele advised he returned to his house around 2200 hours after visiting with a friend earlier that day. When he arrived home, he noticed that his bed was flipped over, and it appeared as if someone went through his room. He confronted Damon about it and she confessed. Steele advised that Damon was angry with him for some unknown reason and began threatening him. Steele stated she threatened to stab him multiple times even saying she would stab him in his sleep. While walking past Damon on the steps, Steele advised Damon aggressively swung her hand towards him, and he swatted it away to defend himself. Steele later believed that Damon had a pair of scissors when she swung at him. Steele then decided to call the police.  Victim: Melissa Brooke Damon DOB: 08/10/1978 134 Clay St. Boliver, WV 25425 301-606-1257  Statement: Damon advised that she lives with her husband in West Virginia. She stated she was staying overnight at her parents house (15102 New Windsor Rd) due to an altercation earlier that day with her husband in West Virginia. After hearing about how Steele treats his grandparents, Damon took it upon herself to flip over his bed while he was not home. When Steele arrived home, Damon overheard him yelling profanities while everyone was trying to sleep, and she decided to confront him. Damon advised that Steele got upset with her and began to list off any potential weapons he had. Damon stated that Steele did not threaten her at this time, but seemingly wanted her to know the amount of weapons he owns. Damon advised the altercation continued for several minutes and at one point, Damon observed Steele sitting at the top of the stairs pointing a rifle at her. Damon then moved to the kitchen and grabbed a pair of scissors to defend herself. Eventually, Steele put the rifle away and Damon was advised that it was only a BB gun. Damon advised that when Steele pointed the BB gun at her, she believed it was real because it looked real and because Steele said he had a rifle when he was listing the weapons he owned. Damon stated that when Steele was listing his weapons, he did not mention the rifle was a BB gun; just advised that he had a rifle. Damon decided to leave the residence but remained on scene when she heard that Steele was calling the police.  Narrative:   On April 23, 2023, at approximately 2300 hours, I was dispatched to 15102 New Windsor road for reports of disorderly conduct. I arrived on scene and made contact with the complainant, Tyler Grant Steele, who was waiting for me outside. Steele provided the above statement and advised that he had a friend coming to pick him up for the night. Steele requested to go inside and gather some of his belongings. I advised that before he left I would ensure that he had his property.   I went inside the residence and made contact with the other party involved, Melissa Brooke Damon. Damon provided the above statement as to what occurred that evening. Damon was very emotional and would occasionally break down crying. She had a tough time maintaining a chronological order of the events which made it difficult to understand what had happened. It should be noted that I did not believe Damon to be deceitful, as she appeared to tell the entire story, but her delivery of the information was tough to follow. Given the fact that Steele did not make any mention a BB gun when I initially spoke with him, I went outside to conduct a second interview with him.  I asked Steele if he left anything out from what he originally told me. Steele advised that when he learned Damon was walking around with scissors, he grabbed a large knife from his room and kept it in his pocket. Steele made it clear that he had no intention to use the knife and it never left his pocket. However, he retrieved it because he was concerned for his safety. I asked Steele if there was anything else he left out to which he assured me that was the entire story. I asked Steele why he failed to mention anything about a gun. Steele became slightly defensive saying it is not a real gun, only a BB gun. I asked him to continue and he stated that he retrieved his rifle BB gun after the entire altercation was over and moved it to the basement. He stated that he was concerned that Damon would find it and potentially use it against him. Steele confirmed that Damon did see him with the BB gun, but he was holding it with the barrel pointed toward the ceiling and that he never pointed it at her. Steele stated there was nothing else about the incident that he left out. Steele advised that he might wish to pursue criminal charges for Damons attempted assault. He was advised about how to obtain a Peace Order and he responded by saying he would prefer that over criminal charges.   I returned to speak with Damon who advised she never attempted to stab Steele. Damon was unsure if she wanted to pursue criminal charges. She was advised about how to obtain a Peace Order. Damon eluded several times to the incident with her husband from earlier that day in West Virginia. Damon was reluctant to speak about it but made it clear that it was domestic violent related. I further advised Damon about a protection order against her husband if she believed it was necessary. I also supplied Damon with information to the Heartly House in Frederick County, MD. Both Damon and Steele were given victim/witness pamphlets. I advised them both I would be in contact later this week about their decision on criminal charges.  All events occurred in Frederick County, MD  I request this case remain open pending victim decision on criminal charges.        </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:39:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 03:37:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Marlatt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7579</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1652</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Slattery</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6111</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>20</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:31:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:59</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>271047</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Steele</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Grant</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/13/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/29/2020 02:11:49</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S340</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T460</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Steele</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Grant</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/13/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S340</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T460</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/29/2020 02:11:49</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>15102</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>New Windsor</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>New Windsor</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.14124</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.5054</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>821</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6209</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/29/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:31:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>44</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:38:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375125</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Damon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Melissa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Brooke</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/10/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/24/2023 01:38:15</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D550</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M420</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Damon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Melissa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Brooke</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/10/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D550</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M420</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/24/2023 01:38:15</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>134</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Clay</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Bolivar</City>
               <StateCode>WV</StateCode>
               <Zip5>25425</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.751746</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.321884</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>606</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1257</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:38:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/02/2023 07:37:31</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/02/2023 07:37:31</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/03/2023 10:48:46</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/02/2023 07:37:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP1652</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 10:48:46</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Narrative:   On April 28, 2023 at approximately 1145 hours, I made contact with Melissa Damon in reference to this case. She advised that Steele had moved out and has not been a problem since this incident. She stated that she is not interested in having criminal charges filed at this time. I then made contact with Steele who stated that he is very happy since he moved out and does not want criminal charges filed at this time.  All events occurred in Frederick County, MD  I request this case be closed lack of victim cooperation</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/02/2023 07:39:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/02/2023 07:41:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1652</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Slattery</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6111</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>