<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-034782</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/04/2023 00:50:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/04/2023 00:50:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/04/2023 00:31:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/04/2023 00:31:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop DUI, DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 00:50:58</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/24/2023 11:59:36</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MD-100 WB TO TELEGRAPH SB / TELEGRAPH RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>649901</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 00:50:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 00:50:59</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>649901</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Md-100 Wb To Telegraph Sb</StreetName>
         <City>Glen Burnie</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>331-400 MD-100 WB TO TELEGRAPH SB / 7647-7649 TELEGRAPH RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/04/2023 00:50:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/04/2023 00:50:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/18/2023 15:49:23</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 00:50:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Case # 23-MSP-034782 This incident was recorded. Body warn camera operational. In-car camera not equipped. SCENE PROCESSING:  - A visual inspection of the scene was conducted. No evidence additional evidence was located. NEIGHBORHOOD CHECK:  - Due to the location of the crime, a neighborhood check was not conducted. NARRATIVE: DUI#: P-23-135 (Glen Burnie Barrack) Eric Andrew Valdez (08/29/1990) Date/time of arrest: 10/04/2023 @ 0049 hours  CERTIFICATION AND TRAINING *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Test through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * National Highway Traffic Safety Administration in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.)  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On October 4, 2023, at approximately 0031 hours, I, Tpr. Tenney (#7378) of the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack, was on route patrol on I-97 in the area of MD-100. At that time I observed a black GMC Serria traveling northbound on I-97 in lane one displaying Texas Registration plate RBR8798. The GMC was observed taking an immediate right turn cutting across all lanes of traveling to take the exit ramp on to westbound MD-100. I then positioned my marked patrol vehicle P-15 behind the GMC for further observation. Once on westbound MD-100 the GMC was observed crossing the solid white line to its left by approximately two tire widths. I continued to observe the GMC for approximately 1.5 miles. During that time, I observed the GMC cross over the white dotted line to its left on four separate occasions. The GMC was observed veering into lane 2 spitting the vehicle between lanes one and two. I then activated my emergency equipment. The GMC came to a stop on the right shoulder of westbound MD-100 at MD-170.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I exited my vehicle wearing my full Maryland State Police-issued Class-C uniform, complete with a brass breast badge. I approached the GMC on the drivers window and I announced myself, stating my name, rank, and badge number, and informed him that he was being audibly and visually recorded. He acknowledged my presence. I stated the reason for the traffic stop. While speaking with the driver of the GMC, I observed his eyes to be glassy. I then asked the driver if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages prior to driving. The driver provided none verbal response and shock his head indicating he did not consume any alcohol prior to driving. I asked the driver why he was all over the road way? He stated Im sorry, I was trying to put the address in the GPS. I then asked the driver for his drivers license and registration card. At that time, I observed the driver struggling with his fine motor skills and he reached for his drivers license in his wallet, dropping his wallet on the floorboard. After retrieving his wallet from the floorboard, the driver provided me with his Texas drivers license, which I identified him as Eric Andrew Valdez (08/29/1990). The photo on the license matched the drivers appearance. I then asked the driver if he was willing to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Testing. Valdez stated yes, if youre making me, but I dont believe thats necessary. At that time, I observed Valdezs response to be slow and lethargic. I then contacted Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack and requested an additional unit for field sobriety and notified the barrack that I would have the driver out on Field Sobriety momentarily. I then asked Valdez to step out of the vehicle and asked him to proceed to the front of his vehicle for further investigation Once at the front of his vehicle, I detected a moderate odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I informed Valdez of the observations I made of his driving behavior. Valdez stated I have not been here long, I am sorry. I then asked Valdez if he was willing to conduct field sobriety. Valdez stated alright. As I began to ask Valdez the pre-screening question and position Valdez to begin observing his eyes for Horizontal gaze nystagmus Valdez stated can I ask if this is necessary, I am so sorry I didnt mean to serve over all those lanes. I informed Valdez that his driving behavior indicated signs of impairment. Valdez stated I know how that is, I have done that out on the water. I then informed Valdez that I believe that it is necessary to preform field sobriety, however he does have the right to refuse to complete the testing. After conversation with Valdez, repeated the same statement multiple times I can call my wife if you. I am just trying to get home.  Over a period of approximately 10 minutes, I asked Valdez numerous times if he was willing to preform field sobriety testing. Valdez refused to provide a yes or no answer and continued to repeat the same statement. I then instructed Valdez to turn around and place his hands behind his back as a response as an affirmative response was not provided. I then instructed Valdez to spit out the gum in his mouth.    ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe that Valdez was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:   * Observations while the driver was operating the vehicle  * Observation during personal contact while speaking with the driver  I advised Valdez that he was under arrest for driving under the influence of Alcohol. A search incident to arrest was conducted and revealed no contraband was on his person. Valdez was read the DR-15 at 0115 hours on October 4, 2023. Valdez asked for additional time to review the paperwork. Valdez was provided an additional 45 minutes review and ask any question. At 0200 hours, Valdez agreed to take the test. After Valdez agree to take the test, Valdez stated that he took the hand sanitizer that was placed on his hands after using the restroom and stuck his fingers in his mouth. An addition 20-minute observation period was conducted prior to testing. Sgt. Natale (#5455) explained how the test operates and instructed Valdez how to complete the test. Valdez refused to follow instruction providing insufficient samples. After reexplaining the instructions and necessary steps to provide a valid sample, Valdez was never able to provide a sufficient sample. The test timed out and was marked down as a refusal.   Valdez was issued all necessary paperwork before being released into the custody of his wife. All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland. Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 02:19:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7378</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/18/2023 14:58:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ricker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5861</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Natale</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5455</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tenney</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7378</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524240</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/04/2023 00:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 00:44:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7378</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 00:44:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 02:09:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7378</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 02:09:35</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389517</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Valdez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Andrew</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/29/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/04/2023 04:15:19</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>V432</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Valdez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Andrew</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/29/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>V432</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/04/2023 04:15:19</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3205</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Wheaton</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Ellicott City</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21043</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.802037</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.283928</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 02:09:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 02:09:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 02:09:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 00:44:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7378</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 00:44:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>