<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-017337</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/15/2023 18:34:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/15/2023 18:34:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/15/2023 15:36:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/15/2023 15:36:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Intoxicated Pedestrian</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/15/2023 18:34:54</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 00:44:10</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DIS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ESC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>MDOP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OBT</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PIX</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I83 SB TO MT ROYAL AVE/ E MOUNT ROYAL AVE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>694839</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/15/2023 18:34:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 22:44:24</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>694839</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>I83</StreetName>
         <City>21201</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21201</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>AVE</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.615582</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.30672</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/15/2023 18:34:49</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/15/2023 18:34:49</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/15/2023 13:02:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/15/2023 18:34:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:54</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Axon Body 3: Operational Axon In-Car Camera Operational MSP Unmarked Vehicle R-39  All video requests can be emailed to Sgt. Twardowski at joseph.twardowski@maryland.gov.  Physical Evidence The suspected marijuana was recovered and seized from the suspects person after arrest. The total weight of 4.6 grams was verified by Sgt. Fike #5926. The CDS was recognized as marijuana by my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper. The suspected marijuana was seized and processed and stored according to MSP policy and regulations. The marijuana referenced above is listed on the MSP Form 67 chain of custody under the Property Held P-339374. Lastly, Two (2) blue round pills and one (1) white rectangular pill were also listed on the previously referenced property held form.  Narrative   On Monday, May 15, 2023, at about 1549 hours, I, TFC. Lora #7207 responded to I-83 southbound, in the area of W. North Ave, Baltimore City, Maryland on reports of a subject walking on I-83 S (Controlled Access Highway). Prior to my involvement, the Golden Ring Barrack received nine (9) phone calls about this individual walking along a controlled access highway. Secondly, one call on a report of a three (3) car crash that occurred as a result of the individual walking on a controlled access highway.    At that time, I observed a white male, with purple hair in a bowl-cut style, wearing a sleeveless graphic t-shirt, gray graphic shorts, black Nike slides, and carrying a light blue unicycle. I located the individual illegally walking in the middle of lane 1 of S/B I-83 a controlled access highway. He was creating a major traffic incident with vehicles swerving to avoid him causing a disruption of the flow of traffic. When I contacted him I identified myself and advised him he was being audio and visually recorded. I told him he couldnt be walking on a highway and he stated he didnt know he couldnt walk on the road. This led me to believe that he was possibly having a mental episode stating he didnt know he couldnt walk on the roadway intended for vehicle use only. I offered to give him a ride off the highway and requested that he produce identification. The male subject informed me that he did not have any identification on his person and walked away from me. At that time, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath. He appeared to be disheveled, dirty face, dirty face, appeared to be homeless, and carrying a black backpack. I approached the male subject and informed him to sit in my patrol vehicle on the front-right passenger seat. The male subject complied and freely walked to my patrol vehicle and sat in the front seat. Soon after, I informed the male subject to refrain from walking on the Jones Falls Expressway (controlled access highway). I dropped the male subject off at the corner of the 700 block of E. Baltimore Street, Baltimore, MD 21202.    Later, the Golden Ring Barrack received two (2) additional calls about the male subject walking on the northbound side of I-83. At approximately 1832 hours, I was dispatched again in regard to the same male subject, with purple hair, and wearing the same clothes as prior, as well as still carrying a unicycle, while illegally walking on I-83 northbound. I responded and contacted the individual. This time, in the area just south of Falls Road, Baltimore City, Maryland. I placed the male subject under arrest. Once again, the male subject did not identify himself. During a search incident to arrest of the white males person, I located a balled aluminum foil containing a chicken bone, three (3) clear plastic baggies, one (1) yellow Ziploc bag containing a greenish plant like matter (suspected marijuana), and one (1) clear Ziploc bag containing two (2) blue round pills and one (1) white pill, one (1) empty 99 proof alcohol bottle, one (1) silver box containing numerous pieces of paper, and loose change. Based on my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, I identified the green plant like matter to be suspected marijuana. As a result of the investigation, my training, knowledge, and experience, I recognized the blue round pills as Diazepam. Diazepam is classified as a Schedule 4 controlled substance under the Controlled Substance Act (CSA). I recognized the white pill as Alprazolam. Alprazolam is classified as a Schedule 4 controlled substance under the Controlled Substance Act (CSA). Both of those pills are only available via prescription only. All contraband was stored and processed in accordance with MSP policy.    Soon after, we began our commute to the Golden Ring Barrack located at 8908 Kelso Drive, Essex, MD 21221 for processing. While traveling to the Golden Ring Barrack, the white male, began to become disorderly and threatened to jump out of the vehicle while in motion. Out of my peripheral vision, I observed the white male make a spontaneous movement and successfully removed his seatbelt. I ordered him to stop moving and attempted to put his seatbelt on. The subject then leaned his body weight forward in an attempt to hinder me from doing so. The white male then stated that I would have to shoot him. I pulled over onto the right shoulder of I-695E, Charles Street, Baltimore County, Maryland. At that time, the white male attempted to open the car door and I held him with my right arm and left arm in a manner consistent with a soft empty hand technique with a reasonable amount of force. At that time, I told him to stop and he did not listen.    Soon after, he continued to try to exit the vehicle, I held him within the vehicle and requested additional units. The white male headbutted the right side of my chin with his head as I held him down on the seat. The white male, then tried to switch his hands to the anterior side of his body and even stood up on the right-front seat. I pushed his feet off the seat using an open hand in a sweeping motion by utilizing my right hand with an open palm in a manner consistent with a hard empty hand technique. While holding the male subject, he threatened to bite me and I ordered him not to and informed him that would be assault. He continued to obstruct by forcefully attempting to exit the vehicle. Secondly, the white male then began to kick the front-right door of my assigned patrol vehicle against the guardrail, kicked the fixed radar unit within my vehicle, opened the glove box with his foot and broke it, and then pulled all the radio wires. As a result, my patrol vehicle sustained damage to its front right passenger side door resulting in paint chips, dents, and the door not properly closing without force. The entire time I am attempting to keep the suspect in my vehicle to prevent his escape. I used muscling techniques and attempted to hold on to him as best as I could from the driver seat of my vehicle while he continued to try and exit the vehicle. Throughout his attempted escape he was able to maneuver his handcuffs in front of him by standing up in the seat and looping his hands under his legs. To prevent inadvertent injury to the suspect I held his arms and shorts while he pulled away causing injuries to himself and his wrists. Soon after, Baltimore County officers arrived on the scene and extracted him from the vehicle. I grabbed his legs and held them down as county officers removed the handcuffs to place them back around his back. Soon after, he was placed in Baltimore Countys transport van 603. During transport, the white male damaged Baltimore Countys transport van 603 ultimately causing the county unit to stop to retrieve the piece plex glass that he had damaged. At that time, Baltimore County officers removed the white male from within the transport van to retrieve the plex glass and prevent self-harm.    Soon after, the white male subject informed units he was having trouble breathing therefore, medical services were requested. While waiting for medical to arrive on the scene, the white male threatened to bite TFC. Howard #7278, threatened to disarm police officers on the scene and then headbutted TFC. Howard is on his left arm with his head. Medic #11 transported the white male subject to GBMC (ref. run # 2313552030). While at the hospital, the white male provided medical staff with the name of Mark Jonathan DOB: 10/07/2000. I requested a query over the radio on that name to which Dispatch informed me that name and date of birth did not have a return. Then I tried, Mark Johnson DOB: 10/07/2000, and again, no return. Later, the white male informed me his real name was Mark Anthony Miller (W/M DOB: 10/07/2000). Dispatch informed me over the radio that the subject had an open warrant through Worcester County, Maryland for Trespass: Private Property. Miller was discharged from the GBMC with discharge instructions and an after-visit summary. Thereafter, he was compliant until he arrived at the Golden Ring Barrack. While at the Golden Ring Barrack, Miller became disorderly and flushed the toilet within the cell over twenty times in a row. Soon after, he discontinued flushing and began to bang on the cell door and yell.    Later, Miller was transported to GBMC, for a second time. It was suspected that Miller was having a withdrawal episode. GBMC hospital staff deemed Miller had a drop in his glucose levels due to improper nutrition. Miller was given a meal and discharged from GBMC with discharge instructions. Miller was then transported back to the Golden Ring Barrack for processing.    During the Use of Force once compliance was given force was immediately stopped.  All events occurred in Baltimore City and Baltimore County, Maryland.  I request this case be OPEN pending service. An arrest warrant through Baltimore City and Baltimore County has been issued for Miller and is currently on file at the Golden Ring Barrack.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 04:53:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 07:50:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lora</LastName>
            <FirstName>Miguel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7207</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Iman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5709</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lora</LastName>
            <FirstName>Miguel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7207</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lora</LastName>
            <FirstName>Miguel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7207</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506764</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>15</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15575</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/15/2023 15:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 21:56:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:50:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506764</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>16</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16995</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/15/2023 15:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 21:56:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:50:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506764</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>17</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16996</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/15/2023 15:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 21:56:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:50:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506764</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>20</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>15</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/15/2023 15:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 09:00:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:50:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506764</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>21</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>15</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0600</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/15/2023 15:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0600</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 09:17:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:50:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506764</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>22</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>15</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 1020</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>A</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/15/2023 15:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>A</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 1020</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 09:36:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:50:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506764</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>23</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>15</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1425</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/15/2023 15:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1425</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 09:45:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:50:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506764</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>24</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>15</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1661</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/15/2023 15:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1661</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 09:55:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:50:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506764</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>25</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>15</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1662</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/15/2023 15:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1662</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:03:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:50:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506764</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>26</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>11</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3 4025</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/15/2023 15:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3 4025</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:12:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:50:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506764</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>27</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1564</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/15/2023 15:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1564</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:49:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:50:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 21:56:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:51:20</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377224</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>MILLER</LastName>
               <FirstName>MARK</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ANTHONY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/07/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/16/2023 21:55:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>MILLER</LastName>
               <FirstName>MARK</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ANTHONY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/07/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/16/2023 21:55:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:51:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:51:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PE</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:51:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:51:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 01:51:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:08:38</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377879</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Howard #7278</LastName>
               <FirstName>TFC.</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 01:16:43</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T120</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Howard #7278</LastName>
               <FirstName>TFC.</FirstName>
               <SLastName>H630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T120</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 01:16:43</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:08:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:08:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:08:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 01:52:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:09:37</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377881</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lora #7207</LastName>
               <FirstName>TFC</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 01:52:17</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T120</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lora #7207</LastName>
               <FirstName>TFC</FirstName>
               <SLastName>L600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T120</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 01:52:17</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:09:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:09:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:09:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 09:49:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 09:49:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240012775</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>Department of Maryland State Police</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 01:15:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:15:15</UpdatorDate>
         <BusinessAddress>
            <AddressId>322444</AddressId>
            <StreetNumber>7749</StreetNumber>
            <StreetName>Washington</StreetName>
            <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
            <City>Jessup</City>
            <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
            <Zip5>20794</Zip5>
            <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            <Longitude>-76.779499</Longitude>
            <Latitude>39.174096</Latitude>
         </BusinessAddress>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153356</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>VI</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:38:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:38:37</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FM5K8ARXHGC35242</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>XPL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLU</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8CN0882</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>LF</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehicleValue>1000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 01:24:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:52:42</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>P-339374</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249171</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>4.6</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 01:24:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:46:39</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>P-339374</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>561</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249172</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>P</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>2</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 01:24:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:46:39</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>P-339374</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>561</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249173</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>P</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/31/2023 13:09:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/31/2023 13:09:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/15/2023 13:02:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 13:09:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:54</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>  On Wednesday, May 31st, 2023, I obtained a preliminary estimate referencing the damage to MSP Unmarked vehicle R39 caused by Miller.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 13:10:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 13:11:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Iman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5709</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lora</LastName>
            <FirstName>Miguel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7207</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/13/2023 13:39:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/13/2023 13:39:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/15/2023 13:02:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 13:39:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:54</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On Sunday, August 13th, 2023. At approximately 1339 hours, I (TFC Lora #7207) attached a copy of the issued arrest warrants for Miller.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 13:40:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 13:40:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Iman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5709</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lora</LastName>
            <FirstName>Miguel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7207</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/14/2023 07:25:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/14/2023 07:25:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/15/2023 13:02:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 07:25:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:54</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On Monday, August 14th, 2023, at approximately 0727 hours, I (TFC Lora #7207) attached the lab results regarding the seized drugs in this case.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 07:26:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 07:28:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Iman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5709</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lora</LastName>
            <FirstName>Miguel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7207</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>