<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-014597</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/25/2023 01:16:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/25/2023 01:16:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/25/2023 01:02:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/25/2023 01:02:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Car stop. DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 01:16:57</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/16/2023 23:20:43</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MACBETH WAY/ SYKESVILLE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>691864</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 01:17:00</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 00:51:37</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>691864</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Macbeth</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Sykesville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.95263</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.39998</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>5936-6043 MACBETH WAY / 6234-6323 SYKESVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/25/2023 01:16:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/25/2023 01:16:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/06/2023 15:12:53</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 01:16:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:27</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was captured on body worn and in car camera.  ATTACHMENTS: METERS printouts Citations Notice to appear DUI processing packet  DRIVER: Jamie Lynn Wingate  W/F  03/11/1988 6555 Abraham Ct Sykesville, MD  NARRATIVE: Vehcile in Motion On 04/25/2023, at approximately 0102 hours, I was on patrol in the town of Sykesville, MD. I was conducting routine traffic enforcement on MD32 in the area of MD26. I was stopped at a red light in the right southbound lane and observed a grey Hyundai Santa Fe bearing MD registration 2EH7982 in the left southbound lane. I requested a routine registration check on the status of the registration. I learned that the registration was expired and suspended for a multitude of reasons. The registration expired on 10/31/2022 and was suspended for an insurance lapse (10/18/2022) as well as failure to comply with the VEIP as of 04/14/2023.  As such, I decided to conduct a traffic stop. After the light turned green, we proceeded through the intersection with MD26 and continued south on MD32 towards MacBeth Way. At the intersection with MacBeth Way, the vehicle got into the left turn lane. As it did so, the passenger side of the vehicle was over the solid white line separating the left turn lane from the southbound lanes. After slowing, the vehicle turned left up MacBeth Way.  Almost immediately I activated my emergency lights. However, the vehicle accelerated somewhat aggressively for approximately 3 seconds, making no indication that the operator saw me. I found this odd as my lights are extremely bright and the night was dark but otherwise clear. Finally, the vehicles right turn signal activated and the vehicle came to a stop.At that time I exited my vehicle and made contact with the driver, later identified by MD drivers license as Jamie Lynn Wingate.  Operator Contact I introduced myself and requested the operators license and registration.Immediately upon making contact with Wingate I detected a strong odor of alcoholic beverage coming from her person. While Wingate started looking for the requested items, I began to converse with her. I asked where she was headed to and learned that she was on her way home. I then asked where she was coming from. Wingate did not answer me and kept looking for her documents. I asked a second time and Wingate said that she was coming from a friends house. I asked if Wingates address on her license was current and learned that she had just moved to Sykesville. She seemed to stop looking for her registration during this time and it appeared as though Wingate was struggling to divide her attention between two tasks. I again asked for her registration and asked for proof of insurance as well. A few moments later Wingate provided me a registration card and the title to her vehicle. I again had to focus her on obtaining the document for which I had asked.  She was alone in the car. I also noted that her eyes were bloodshot and glassy. As Wingate spoke with me she was slurring her speech and her speech seemed labored. I also noted that Wingate seemed to be having mood swings. At one point when discussing the registration status, Wingate became emotional and started crying. She seemed to start hyperventilating. Moments later she seemed to calm down and returned to a normal state. Based on my training, knowledge, and experience as a law enforcement officer for over 10 years, I know that these observations can be indicators of impairment.  As Wingate looked for proof of insurance, I asked more about her evening. She said that her friends house is in Eldersburg and that she was at a moms night. She added that she was regretting it now. I found this comment strange and I interpreted it as though Wingate knew she should not be driving. When asked why she seemed to stumble over her answer and said that she shouldnt have taken this car before trailing off. I watched as Wingate pulled open a Progressive application on her cellphone before closing it and opening another, unrelated app. Again, it appeared as though her focus, memory and divided attention were poor.  I asked Wingate about her alcohol consumption. She initially shook her head no and said none. I repeated her answer in a tone to suggest disbelief and Wingate looked up from her phone and looked at me. When she looked up, her face reminded me of the look a child would give when they are asking for something or want pity. She did not answer me. She looked away and I asked again how much she had consumed. Wingate dropped her hands to her lap and took what appeared to be a defeated posture before saying something to the effect that it was not fair and that the first time she had drank in two weeks. She seemed to be talking to herself. She later said that she did not know and that she does not normally drink but admitted that she drank tonight. She then started crying and said something like she was so close to her home. It appeared as though she was asking me to let her go and ignore the fact that she had been drinking. I tried to calm her down and in conversation she said that there were 5 people at the moms night and that they had about 2 bottles of wine.  Again, Wingate became emotional and worked up. I tried to calm her down but, as she cried, she said something to the effect that she was going to jail. Then she said something to the effect that she was going to lose her security clearance and her job. I again tried to calm Wingate. I told her to remain in the vehicle and calm down while I returned to my car.  After returning to my car, I conducted routine checks on the status of Wingates license. I learned nothing of note. I then returned to Wingate with the intention of asking her to perform SFSTs. Once back with Wingate, I asked if she was willing to do some tests to make sure she was okay to drive. She asked if she could just walk and that she lives right there. I told Wingate that if she was okay to drive, I didnt care how she got home. I again asked if she was willing to do some test to make sure she was okay. She once again asked me if she could just walk home. When I told her no, she started to cry and tell me she is a single mom and will lose her job. She became much more emotional so I made the decision to have Wingate exit the vehicle.  She opened the door and stepped out. As she did so she stood by the door jam and I observed he rock back and forth on her feet. Her balance seemed poor as her weight shifted from her toes to her heels. After adjusting herself, she moved toward the back of her car as directed, though I had to reiterate the directive numerous times. Once at the back of her vehicle, I asked Wingate if she was willing to do the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, explaining that I could not force her to do them. She shook her head no and said something that I could not understand as her speech was so slurred and mumbled. I asked for clarification and Wingate said that she was not wiling to do SFSTs.  At that time, based on the numerous psychophsyical observations I had made and my training, knowledge, and experience, it was clear that Wingate was intoxicated by alcohol and that it was impairing her ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. She was therefore taken into custody for DUI. She was searched incident to arrest, handcuffed and placed in the front of my car.  A brief search of Wingates vehicle revealed two, small Fireball Whiskey containers, both of which were mostly empty, in the center console. I did not locate anything else of note while searching for fruits of the crime. I secured Wingates vehicle.  Wingate was then transported to the Westminster State Police Barrack. We remained in the vehicle in the parking lot while I played the audio version of the DR15 Advice of Rights available through the MVA website. I provided Wingate a paper copy to follow along as the audio played and I sat with Wingate to ensure there were no issues. At the conclusion at 0205 hours, Wingate agreed to an evidentiary test. Wingate was then transported to the Westminster City Police Department. At 0230 hours Wingate provided a sample of her breath as evidence, showing .18 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  Wingate was issued the appropriate paperwork before being released.  All events occurred in Carroll County.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 01:05:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/28/2023 02:12:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pettis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6498</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McCarty</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cade</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6579</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phelps</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7210</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/25/2023 01:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/25/2023 01:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/25/2023 01:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/25/2023 01:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/25/2023 01:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16604</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/25/2023 01:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16626</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/25/2023 01:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16624</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/25/2023 01:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19123</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/25/2023 01:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:59:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:20</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375416</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Wingate</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jamie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/11/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13270564E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/27/2023 00:58:04</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W523</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Wingate</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jamie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/11/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13270564E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>W523</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/27/2023 00:58:04</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6555</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Abraham</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Eldersburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21784</Zip5>
               <Zip4>6118</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.953436</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.394438</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:59:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:59:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:59:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 00:55:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152392</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 01:03:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 01:03:15</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HYUN</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SANTAFE</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2eh7982</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>