<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-006760</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/21/2023 22:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/21/2023 22:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/21/2023 18:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/21/2023 18:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Broken down vehicle that was left on I-495 was stolen. Vehicle was last seen by owner on 02/21/2023 at 1800 hours.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/21/2023 22:08:44</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5682</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/11/2023 13:09:38</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>STV</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>639860</AddressId>
      <City>MDC175</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/21/2023 22:48:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/22/2023 18:02:46</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>639860</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>I-495</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.86462</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.95623</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/21/2023 22:08:41</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/21/2023 22:08:41</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>Y</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/11/2023 13:09:39</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/21/2023 22:08:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>CASE NUMBER: 23-MSP-006760  SCENE PROCESSING A written statement from the victim was taken at the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack. A check of the alleged theft area yielded no results of the victims vehicle.  SUSPECT Unknown.  State of Maryland Trooper Harris #7179, (301)-345-3101 10100 Rhode Island Avenue, College Park, Maryland 20740  VICTIM / COMPLAINANT Oladipo Olukayode Aniyikaiye (301)-523-7982 DOB: 05/30/1984 4905 Vista Green Lane, Lanham Seabrook, Maryland 20706  CHARGES CR 7-105 : Motor Vehicle / Unlawful Taken  Stolen Property: 2017 Black Jeep Wrangler Unlimited  Total Value: $26,218.00  Narrative: On February 21st, 2023 at 2208 hours (10:08 PM), I, Trooper Harris #7179, responded to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack to take a report of a stolen vehicle. Upon my arrival, the complainant, Oladipo Aniyikaiye (DOB 05/30/1984), submitted a written statement to the barrack. Aniyikaiye said in the statement that his Jeep Wrangler broke down on the inner loop of I-495 in the area of US Route 50 at around 1800 hours (6:00 PM). Aniyikaiye left the vehicle and called for a tow truck to retrieve the vehicle at a later time. Some time later, the tow company contacted Aniyikaiye and advised him that they could not locate his vehicle. Aniyikaiye then checked the area at around 2100 hours (9:00 PM) and realized that his vehicle was stolen and was nowhere to be found.  After learning this information, I checked the area of the last known location of the vehicle. I could not locate the said vehicle. I contacted Aniyikaiye via telephone to inquire for further information. Aniyikaiye told me that his vehicle was smoking, which caused him to leave the vehicle on the side of I-495. Aniyikaiye also said he left the vehicle unlocked prior to him leaving the area. Aniyikaiye advised that he has only 1 set of keys to the vehicle that no one else has access to, no current loan on the vehicle and no GPS tracking devices on the vehicle that he is aware of. Aniyikaiye also advised that the vehicle has no distinguishing markings such as bumper stickers, paint, or stripes on the vehicle. The vehicle also has a removable top and a spare tire mounted on the rear of the vehicle. Aniyikaiye does not have any potential suspect information.  I then conducted a METERS check of the VIN plate of the vehicle which returns to a different name than Aniyikaiye. Further questioning of Aniyikaiye revealed that he purchased the vehicle out of an auction in Virginia in January of 2023 and was provided Virginia temporary tags. Aniyikaiye could not provide information on the Virginia registration. I ran the VIN through Virginia with negative results. Its concluded that the Jeep has unknown temporary registration tags through Virginia.   With this information, I advised Aniyikaiye that he needs to complete the title transfer from the old owner to his name so the vehicle can be entered into NCIC as a stolen vehicle since Aniyikaiye is currently not the registered owner. Aniyikaiye said he is going to the MVA on February 22nd, 2023 to complete the title transfer.  After I contacted Aniyikaiye via telephone, I e-mailed him the case number as well as a victim witness pamphlet. I also advised him to email myself or notify the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack of any relevant information on the case.  On February 22nd, 2023, I ran the VIN through METERS and verified that the vehicle is now registered to Aniyikaiye in Maryland. After learning this information, the vehicle was entered as stolen through NCIC on 02/22/2023.  I then contacted Aniyikaiye again to inquire more about the vehicle. As of 02/22/2023, Aniyikaiye is unaware of any Internet / WiFi, GPS tracking devices, or E-ZPass on the vehicle. Aniyikaiye also said that he only left the vehicle registration information and office paperwork in the vehicle. Prior to concluding the phone conversation, I advised Aniyikaiye to notify me if he becomes aware of any GPS devices on the vehicle as well as the Virginia registration information.  I conducted a search through the Regional Automated Property Information Database (RAPID) with negative results. I used the Alerts option in the RAPID system in order to retrieve alerts in my email regarding the vehicle. I then utilized the Law Enforcement Information Exchange (LInX) system to run the VIN through the system with negative results. I am using the Watch List option in LInX to receive alerts in my email regarding the vehicle. I am currently in contact with the Virginia Fusion Center to retrieve a possible temporary tag for the vehicle since I cannot utilize the Maryland Fusion Center for License Plate Reader (LPR) queries until I get a tag number.  I request this case to be open pending investigation. All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/21/2023 23:52:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7179</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/22/2023 22:51:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Long</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5477</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harris</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bruce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7179</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496157</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0480</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/21/2023 21:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/21/2023 22:50:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7179</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/21/2023 22:50:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/21/2023 22:52:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369776</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Aniyikaiye</LastName>
               <FirstName>Oladipo</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Olukayode</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/30/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/21/2023 22:51:49</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>O431</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Aniyikaiye</LastName>
               <FirstName>Oladipo</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Olukayode</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/30/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>A520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>O431</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/21/2023 22:51:49</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4905</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Vista Green</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Lanham</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20706</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.828215</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.956516</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>523</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7982</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/22/2023 17:53:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/22/2023 17:53:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/22/2023 17:53:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/22/2023 17:53:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150097</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>ST</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/22/2023 17:54:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7179</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/22/2023 17:54:07</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>7</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C4HJWDG3HL598329</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>WRG</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>TM</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehicleValue>26218</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/28/2023 02:56:30</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/28/2023 02:56:30</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/11/2023 13:09:39</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 02:56:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On February 22nd, 2023, I contacted the Virginia Fusion Center via e-mail to inquire about the vehicles possible Virginia temporary registration. On February 24th, 2023, I was contacted by the Virginia Fusion Center and was notified that there was no record of the vehicle at the Virginia Department of Motor Vehicles.  On February 28th, 2023, I conducted a search of Craigslist utilizing the VIN that encompasses a 250-mile radius from Silver Spring, Maryland and got negative results. Another search for a 2017 Jeep Wrangler on Craigslist yielded no results matching the description of the vehicle.  On the same date, I conducted a Google search of the VIN and came across an auction website called PLC Group containing the vehicle with the same VIN number. The website shows that the vehicle was listed for auction on 02/20/2023, 1 day prior to the reported date of theft. Pictures of the vehicle are included on the website. The auction website stated the auction is closed without a specified date and time. The auction website also said the vehicle was located at Bel Air Auto Auction located in Maryland.  The car insurance for the vehicle was effective on 01/31/2023, according to the insurance identification card. I then contacted Progressive insurance via telephone. The insurance representative told me that Aniyikaiye requested for insurance coverage on 01/31/2023 and that there was no lien listed on the insurance file.   On February 28th, 2023, I received a report from the Maryland Coordination and Analysis Center (MCAC) for information on the VIN. From the report, CARFAX reported that the last activity prior to the vehicle being reported stolen was the vehicle passed a safety inspection on 09/06/2023 in Lanham, Maryland.   On March 3rd, 2023 I made another follow-up phone call to Aniyikaiye. He advised me that he was unable to provide me with GPS tracking information for the Jeep. Aniyikaiye said that he got the vehicle through a friend named Paul but could not provide me with a last name. Paul apparently buys and sells cars from auctions and he happens to sell this vehicle to Aniyikaiye. Aniyikaiye also advised me he was possibly provided fake paper tags on the vehicle since Paul could not provide the temporary registration information to Aniyikaiye. I questioned Aniyikaiye further on where the vehicle was possibly purchased from. Aniyikaiye could not provide any dealership information since he bought the vehicle off of Paul. Aniyikaiye also said any documents that he had brought to the MVA were not returned to him.  On March 7th, 2023, I contacted Bel Air Auto Auction with a phone number of 410-879-7950. I got in touch with Dylan Lewis who ran the VIN number. He advised me that the vehicle had never gone on the property in the past. Lewis also stated that it was previously auctioned in 2020 by a credit union but could not provide what auction the vehicle was at. I had also asked if Lewis was familiar with the PLC Group website, the site that the vehicle was listed for auction on. Lewis said he was not familiar with that website.  That same day, I contacted Aniyikaiye to attempt to retrieve documents that were requested on March 3rd with no success. Aniyikaiye stated that he did not have the proof of purchase in his possession and he was trying to contact Paul to get copies with no success. I had also contacted MCAC again in an attempt to get copies of the documents that should be on file with the MVA. I was advised by MCAC that it would be a delayed process for my request since there is only one police investigator assigned to the MVA.  I request this case to remain open pending further investigation and transfer to Trooper Stewart #7590 </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7179</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 02:57:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7179</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 12:05:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Heath</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4437</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harris</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bruce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7179</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/26/2023 08:02:02</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/26/2023 08:02:02</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/11/2023 13:09:39</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5532</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/26/2023 08:02:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement - 2023 Validation</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 05/09/23, computer inquiries were run through the Virginia Motor Vehicle Administration files, the Prince Georges County Impound files, NCIB VIN Edit and a nationwide inquiry was run utilizing the VIN.  On 05/09/23 at approximately 0844 hours, telephone contact was attempted with the complainant Oladipo Aniyikaiye which was unsuccessful. On the same day at approximately 0857 hours, an email was sent to the address on the witness statement which went unanswered. A certified letter was sent to the address on the report.  The NCIC Stolen Vehicle entry remains active and this investigation is suspended pending the development of any new information or the vehicle is recovered.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5532</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/26/2023 08:02:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5532</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/26/2023 08:02:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Heath</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4437</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wilson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jessica</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5532</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/11/2023 07:39:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/11/2023 07:39:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/11/2023 13:09:39</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/11/2023 07:39:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On May 4, 2023, I, Tpr. R. Stewart #7590 made contact with Adrian St. Michael, an investigator with Progressive Insurance Group on the phone. Mr. St. Michael was assigned the investigation for the insurance company in reference to this case for the claim filed by Oladipo Aniyikaiye, the alleged victim. Mr. St. Michael advised he would be meeting with the legal team of Progressive Insurance to discuss his investigation/findings and the possibility of criminally charging Aniyikaiye. On 5/7/23 I, followed up with Mr. St. Michael with an e-mail. On 5/15/23 Mr. St. Michael responded and advised the following: Legal finished their review and decided that Oladipo Aniyikaiye has failed to cooperate fully with our investigation and we are denying his claim for payment. At this juncture, we do not have enough evidence to say he committed insurance fraud. After speaking with D/Sgt. Heath about this case, I requested Mr. St. Michaels case file to review and add to this case file. I received no response from Mr. St. Michael and followed up with a second e-mail to Mr. St. Michael approximately a month later, and again received no response. I respectfully request this case be closed, due to no further investigative leads and lack of response from potential victim, being the insurance company. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/11/2023 07:40:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/11/2023 07:40:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zinn</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5682</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stewart</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7590</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>