<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002408</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/20/2023 09:13:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/20/2023 09:13:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/20/2023 09:10:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/20/2023 09:10:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Warrant Service for Dujuan Satterfield which resulted in a Firearms Violation.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 09:13:21</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3355</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 11:16:17</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>681177</AddressId>
      <City>MDC103</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 09:13:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 11:32:14</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>681177</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>5753</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Hazelwood</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Baltimore City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.531084</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.339614</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/20/2023 09:13:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/20/2023 09:13:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40N</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/23/2023 12:17:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 09:13:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6039</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 10:29:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On January 19, 2023, TFC. Hadley of the Maryland State Police - Maryland State Apprehension Team / US Marshals - Capital Area Regional Fugitive Task Force, was requested by the Baltimore City Police Department to assist with locating and apprehending a fugitive, identified as Dujuan Keandre Satterfield, B/M, DOB: 06/20/1996. Satterfield was wanted through the Baltimore City Police Department for Robbery and related offenses (2B02465101). These charges stem from an incident where Satterfield allegedly assaulted his ex-girlfriend and stole her car keys.  Upon being assigned the fugitive investigation, Task Force members conducted an in-depth background investigation into Satterfields family, friends, associates, social media, and pattern of life. During the course of the investigation, Task Force members identified an updated address of 5753 Hazelwood Cir, Apt D, Baltimore MD 21206 for Satterfield. Task Force members confirmed with the Hazelwood Homes leasing office that Satterfield was on the only person on the lease at that address. Task Force members also identified a 2008 gray Acura TL with expired Maryland temporary registration registered in his name. Task Force members conducted a check of the vehicles VIN and discovered it re-registered through Virginia under registration, UCJ4682.  On January 19, 2023, Task Force members were conducting covert surveillance at Satterfields residence when they observed him pull into the apartment complex in his gray Acura TL bearing Virginia registration, UCJ4682. Satterfield parked in front of 5753 Hazelwood Circle and exited his vehicle. Satterfield escorted his two (2) little kids from out of his vehicle and into his residence at 5753 Hazelwood Circle.  On January 20, 2023, in the early morning hours, after Task Force members confirmed Satterfields vehicle was parked at location, responded to the 5753 Hazelwood Cir Apt D in attempt to locate and apprehend Satterfield. Task Force members established a perimeter around the residence and began knocking and announcing their presence. After a brief period of time, the front door was opened by Satterfield who was apprehended without incident. Satterfield looked to have just woken up and was only wearing boxer briefs. Satterfield advised the only other occupants in his residence were his two (2) little kids.  Due to Satterfield needing to be clothed and his unattended children, Task Force members entered into the residence and conducted a protective sweep before they could render it safe to address these issues. During the protective sweep, Task Force members first opened and cleared the closest door in the main living room, which was directly adjacent to the front door. Task Force members know closets to be a common area where people try to hide and conceal themselves. Upon opening of the closet door, Task Force members observed in plain view, a black handgun, propped up on the closet shelf against a cardboard box. In order to render the room safe, Task Force members secured the handgun and cleared it of all live ammunition. As Task Force members did this, they observed the serial number on the top right side of the handgun obliterated. The serial number was observed to have been repeatedly scraped over until it was difficult to read, and all black paint was removed. The firearm was a Smith  Wesson MP Shield, .45 Cal. (SN:HDV4618). There was a round in the chamber and seven (7) rounds in the magazine for a total of eight (8) rounds. Task Force members were able to obtain the firearms serial number when it was read at a specific angle and in proper lighting.  When Satterfield saw Task Force members securing the firearm he openly stated that it was his firearm from when he was in the service. Satterfield then stated he bought the firearm in its current condition at a pawn shop in New Port, Virginia back in 2018. Task Force members discovered the pawn shop to be Warwick Trading Company. Multiple attempts to make contact with the pawn shop were made but were unsuccessful. A Google search of Warwick Trading Company revealed it to be temporarily closed. Satterfield stated he did not have any of the paperwork for when he purchased the firearm.  A check through the Maryland Gun Center revealed Satterfield to NOT be prohibited from possessing a firearm and to have no firearms registered in his name. A check of the firearm revealed it NOT to be registered or stolen. The firearm was seized and stored at the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack under Property Held (P-339309).  Satterfield was transported to the Baltimore City Police Northeast District to be interviewed and processed.  On January 23, 2023, TFC Hadley applied for criminal charges in reference to the obliterated serial number and a criminal summons was issued for Satterfield. At 0715 hours that same morning, Satterfield was served the criminal summons and provided a copy.  Later that day, Task Force members received the ATF E-Trace report for the firearm. The report confirmed that Satterfield purchased the firearm from Warwick Trading Company (15674 Warwick Blvd, Newport News, VA 23602) (FFL: 15414373) on 04/06/2018. A copy of the report has been attached.  I request this case be closed. All events occurred in Baltimore City, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6732</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 09:26:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6732</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 11:35:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hadley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jack</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6732</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Vanhoy</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3355</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hadley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jack</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6732</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40N</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hadley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jack</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6732</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491791</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1612</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/20/2023 09:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1612</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6732</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 10:37:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6732</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 10:53:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6732</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 10:37:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:04</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366708</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Satterfield</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dujuan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Keandre</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/20/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16477468E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>01/20/2023 13:24:28</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S361</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Satterfield</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dujuan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Keandre</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/20/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16477468E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S361</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/20/2023 13:24:28</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5753</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hazelwood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>D</SubNumber>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21206</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.530389</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.339495</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>534</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0870</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6732</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 11:34:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:43</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6732</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 11:34:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:43</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6732</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 10:37:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6732</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 10:37:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6732</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 11:29:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6732</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 11:29:51</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Smith &amp; Wesson M&amp;P Shield .45 Cal w/ 8 rounds</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>MSPPI</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <SerialNumber>HDV4618</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>242066</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>BLK</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>Smith &amp; Wesson</Make>
         <Model>M&amp;P Shield</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/06/2023 14:18:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/06/2023 14:18:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/07/2023 10:29:59</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP1174</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 14:18:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 10:30:01</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>TEST FIRE   On February 21, 2023, I, D/Sgt. Douglas Forrester # 1174 of the Maryland State Police completed a test-firing of the following firearm by firing two test shots with the firearm. I am currently assigned to the Golden Ring Barrack located at 8908 Kelso Drive, Essex, MD 21221. I can be contacted by email at douglas.forrester@maryland.gov or by phone at 410-780-2706.   Make: Smith  Wesson  Model: MP 45 Shield  Caliber: 45 cal.  Serial Number: Serial number damaged (partial HDV4618)   I certify that this firearm is operable and capable of being fired. The test shots have been forwarded to the Maryland State Police Firearm/Toolmark Unit for NIBIN database entry and storage. I attended the MSP Forensic Buddy training and successfully completed a competency test. I successfully completed recertification on December 14, 2022.  See attached Maryland State Police OTS Firearm Test Fire Certificate Form MSP 21-30.  The firearm will be submitted to the MSP FSD for serial number restoration. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP1174</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 14:19:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/06/2023 14:24:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burton</LastName>
            <FirstName>Graham</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Forrester</LastName>
            <FirstName>Douglas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1174</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>