<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-018664</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/25/2023 18:40:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/25/2023 18:40:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/25/2023 18:08:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/25/2023 18:08:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Unknown subject broke the glass storm door on a side entrance to the residence via an unknown mechanism of damage.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 18:40:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4993</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 22:56:01</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>MDOP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>695262</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 18:40:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/26/2023 17:01:02</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>695262</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1702</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Crestwood</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Salisbury</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.551628</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.360268</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/25/2023 18:40:00</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/25/2023 18:40:00</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>Y</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/26/2023 18:25:36</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 18:40:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:52:50</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Location: 1702 Crestwood Circle Salisbury MD 21804  Scene Description: Single Story single family residence. Property had a driveway located on the right side of the property The driveway ran alongside the residence. Parked in the driveway was a black Dodge pickup truck. The truck was parked alongside the residence in front of the side door. The right side door to the residence was a exterior metal door that was equipped with a white aluminum/glass pane storm door. The door had dual glass panes that made up the face of the door. The lower pane of glass was shattered by an unknown object/means. The location of the Dodge pickup truck obscured the doorway from the roadway/ neighboring properties.  Scene Processing: I took photographs of the damage to the storm door. I also attempted to locate any objects or projectiles that could have caused the damage to the glass, however I was unable to locate anything. The photographs taken will be uploaded to Veri-Pic.  Neighborhood Check: The property located to the right of 1702 Crestwood Circle was under renovation. I was advised by Bailey that the resident at 1701 Crestwood Circle, the residence directly across from his, leaves for work earlier than he does and was not home, noting the absence of the subjects pickup truck. I was given phone numbers for the neighbors who reside at 1622 Mt Hermon Rd. and 1701 Crestwood Circle  On 5/26/2022 I made contact with Jordan Planzer via telephone, he advised me that he had left and driven by the residences on Crestwood Circle around 2pm on 5/25/23 and did not observe anything out of the ordinary. He did note that random people will sometimes pull into the neighborhood, mistaking Crestwood Circle for another nearby street.  Jordan Planzer 1622 Mt Hermon Rd Salisbury MD 21804 410-430-0678  I attempted to contact Brad Wilmer, who resides at 1701 Crestwood Circle via telephone, however I was unable to make contact with him.  Brad Wilmer 1701 Crestwood Circle Salisbury MD 21804 443-365-0266  BWC Footage: https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=451b2e890d674be4b0712c8adaa1aa13partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  Narrative: On 5/25/2023 @ 1808hrs, I S/Tpr Shelter responded to 1702 Crestwood Circle Salisbury MD 21804 for the report of a Malicious Destruction of Property.  Upon my arrival, I made contact with a male subject outside the residence. I was able to identify the subject as James Bailey. He advised me that he had returned from work to discover his neighbors chain-link fence gate to be open and upon walking up to his residence, saw that the glass portion of the storm door on a side entrance to his residence had been shattered. Bailey advised me he resides at 1702 Crestwood Circle and had left for work at around 0805am. He said that when he returned home around 17:15hrs, He pulled into his driveway and saw that the chain link gate to the fence on his neighbors property, 1700 Crestwood Circle was open. He said that as he walked up his driveway, which is located adjacent to the property line, he saw that the glass storm door on the right side entrance to his residence was shattered. Upon inspecting the damaged door, I observed that the lower glass pane was shattered and falling out of the frame. I was unable to observe any impact marks on the actual residence door or any objects or projectiles on the ground or on the door frame that would have caused the damage. Bailey advised that he checked his residence and all the doors and windows were secure and locked. Bailey said that when he left for work, the door was not broken. Bailey did not have any security cameras that would have captured the incident. Bailey also added that the Dodge pickup in his driveway that was parked alongside his residence had been parked in the same location all day.   I then made contact with the owner of 1700 Crestwood Circle, whom I identified as Jane Antinori. She advised me that she had left the residence to go to Newport News Va with her daughter at around 0830-0900 hours and when she left her chain-link gate to her yard was open. She advised that she had her lawn care company come the day prior to cut her grass, and it is possible that the gate may not have been fully latched and managed to be opened by the wind at some point during the day. Antinori advised that she arrived back at the residence around 1820hrs where she met with Bailey. Antinori said that she checked her property and it was secure. She also added that she contacted her neighbor, Jordan Planzer who resides at the residence to the right of her property (1622 Mt. Hermon Rd Salisbury MD 21804), and he advised that he had driven by the property around noon and the gate was shut. It was suggested that possibly while the lawn care company was mowing Antinoris yard, a rock or object could have been kicked up and struck the door on Baileys residence and the glass later broke due to stress.   Both Bailey and Antinori advised that the neighborhood is fairly quiet and that no one has any quarrels with either of them.  I was unable to determine the means in which the storm door could have been damaged and provided Bailey with this case number for insurance purposes. I advised Bailey that due to the lack of evidence this case would ultimately be suspended. I took photographs of the damage to the door and they will be uploaded to Veri-Pic  At this time I have no further leads to pursue or evidence that could lead to the identification of a suspect(s)  I request this case be SUSPENDED  ALL EVENTS OCCURRED IN WICOMICO COUNTY MD      </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/26/2023 17:05:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5979</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/26/2023 17:44:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mareck</LastName>
            <FirstName>Keven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3258</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shelter</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5979</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508097</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3 4025</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/25/2023 18:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3 4025</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 20:15:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5979</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 20:15:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>64</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/26/2023 17:02:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:23</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378096</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bailey</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/16/1959 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/26/2023 17:02:41</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bailey</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/16/1959 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/26/2023 17:02:41</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1702</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Crestwood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.551628</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.360268</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>726</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4912</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/26/2023 17:02:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>71</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/26/2023 17:03:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>299767</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Antinori</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jane</FirstName>
               <DOB>02/05/1952 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/08/2021 11:47:09</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A535</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Antinori</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jane</FirstName>
               <DOB>02/05/1952 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>A535</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/08/2021 11:47:09</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1700</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Crestwood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21801</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.55146</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.36058</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>880</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5506</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/08/2021 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/26/2023 17:03:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5979</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/26/2023 17:04:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5979</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/26/2023 17:04:39</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>White metal/glass storm door</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>555</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>200</PropertyValue>
         <Value>200</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249415</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>WHI</PrimaryColor>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>