<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-032572</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/16/2023 16:02:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/16/2023 16:02:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/16/2023 15:21:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/16/2023 15:21:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Rape</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/16/2023 16:02:55</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/18/2023 10:45:46</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>RAP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>HOWARD CO GENERAL</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>509980</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/16/2023 16:02:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 14:29:54</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>509980</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>8450</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Dorsey Run Rd</StreetName>
         <City>Jessup</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20794</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.795226</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.139981</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>Clifton T. Perkins Hospital</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/16/2023 16:02:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/16/2023 16:02:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>50</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/18/2023 10:45:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/16/2023 16:02:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments:  -MVA printouts -Howard County Sexual Assault Report  Suspect:  Darryn Xavier Thomas DOB: 09-22-1988  Victim:  Christopher Sambula DOB: 09/12/1999  Neighborhood Check:  N/A  Narrative:    On September 16, 2023 at approximately 1528 hours, Lieutenant Branham contacted the Maryland State Police Waterloo Barrack to report a possible sexual assault between two patients that occurred at the Clifton T. Perkins Detention facility. Lt. Branham advised the Waterloo Barrack that the victim and suspect were transported by Clifton T. Perkins personnel to Howard County General hospital. I (ST Morgan #6068) responded to Howard County General Hospital to contact the victim and suspect. I arrived at Howard County General hospital and spoke with Jena Britton. Jenna Britton is the on-call forensic nurse in charge of the suspect and victim. Britton informed me that the victim, Christopher Sambula D.O.B 09/12/1999, was treated and transported back to Clifton T. Perkins. The suspect, Darryn Xavier Thomas D.O.B 09/22/1988, was at the hospital and being guarded by Clifton T. Perkins personnel. Britton conducted a physical and completed a sexual assault kit on Sambula. Britton advised me that Thomas was uncooperative and was refusing any DNA testing. Britton completed a Sexual Assault Forensic Examination Report, and it is attached to the report.    In the Sexual Assault Forensic Examination Report, Brittion recorded a statement of the events from Sambula, it is included in her report. Sambulas stated the following to Britton. I was sleeping, and I woke up to my bunk mate rubbing lotion on my rectum. This has never happened before but, he just became my bunk mate a day ago. I tried to get him off of me and I couldnt. He was holding me down. I was on my stomach with my leg coming down from the top bunk. He sodomized me for three minutes, and he ejaculated inside my rectum. Sebula denied being in pain at that time. Subula also stated to Britton, I was bleeding in my rectum, but I have been having this for the last two weeks because I have been eating toothpaste because it gets me high. I bleed in my stool when I wipe.   CPL. Zakery Null of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division was contacted by the Maryland State Police Waterloo Barrack, and responded to Clilfton T. Perkins to interview the victim and assume the investigation.  All events occurred in Howard County, Maryland.    I request this case be forwarded to CED for investigation. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6068</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/16/2023 18:08:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6068</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/16/2023 19:09:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Krysiak</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1955</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Morgan</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6068</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522025</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1102 SS</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>15</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/16/2023 15:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1102 SS</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6068</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/16/2023 19:25:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6068</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/16/2023 19:25:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6068</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/16/2023 17:51:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 14:29:54</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>387983</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Thomas</LastName>
               <FirstName>Darryn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Xavier</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/22/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>I</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>09/16/2023 17:50:36</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Thomas</LastName>
               <FirstName>Darryn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Xavier</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/22/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>I</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>T520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/16/2023 17:50:36</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>8450</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Dorsey Run</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Jessup</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20794</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.7952266</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.1399817</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6068</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/16/2023 17:51:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6068</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/16/2023 17:54:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 14:29:54</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>146296</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sambula</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/12/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/09/2017 11:17:38</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S514</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sambula</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/12/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S514</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/09/2017 11:17:38</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>8450</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Dorsey Run</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Jessup</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20794</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>10710</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Brookemeade</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Williamsport</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21795</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.799369</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.608709</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>347</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>485</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1229</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/09/2017 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6068</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/16/2023 19:32:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/20/2023 17:07:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/20/2023 17:07:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/18/2023 10:45:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/20/2023 17:07:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Suspect:    Thomas, Darryn Xavier     B/M DOB: 09/22/1988      Victim:    Sambula, Christopher     B/M       Evidence:    Bedding from crime scene  Bedding from quiet room  Stolen Property:    Due to the nature of the incident no stolen property is reported.  Scene Processing:    SAFE Kit was completed. Interviews were completed. Bedding stored per MSP policy.   Neighborhood check:     Due to the nature of the incident no neighborhood check was conducted.   Witness information:    Sander, Jermanie     B/M      Additional Information:    No additional information was collected at this time.   Training and Experience: I am a certified Police Officer in the State of Maryland With over 40 hours of training in DUI detection at the Maryland State Police Academy. The training included classroom instruction, practical application, alcohol workshops, written testing and practical application examination. During my time as a Maryland State Trooper I have arrested over 50 impaired drivers and have been trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE). Additionally, I have been recognized by the Maryland State Highway Safety Office for my Impaired Driving Enforcement. I have attended Street Narcotic Investigation Training as well as Gang Identification and awarenessprovided by the Maryland State Police. I have also attended 40 hours of Basic Criminal Investigator School provided by the Maryland State Police. I have attended an8 hours of 4th Amendment Search and Seizure Training presented by the Honorable Judge Wahlen. Furthermore, I have completed Total Traffic Stops, a drug interdiction course presented by the Northeast Counter Drug Training Center. I also completed the Heroin Interdiction Initiative hostedby Washington-Baltimore High Intensity Drug Trafficking Area and Anne Arundel County Police Department, presented by Maryland State Police Proactive Criminal Enforcement Team. During my time as a Maryland State Trooper I have arrested over 60 drug related offenses and assisted on many more. Additionally, I am a certified RADAR/LIDAR Operator in the State of Maryland. Furthermore, I have completed a 24 hour, Interview and Interrogation with Forensic Analysis. Additionally, I am certified in CastViz;CastViz is a analytical tool produced by the Federal Bureau of Investigations to map and analyze cellular data. During my time as a Maryland State Trooper I have investigated crimes such as Burglaries, Robberies, Assaults, Computer Crimes, Fraud, Theft, Drugs, Traffic offense, Threats of Violence, Weapon Offenses, Rapes, and other crimes which required traditional investigative efforts to include surveillance, interviews, evidence collection, title 3 wire taps; as well as non-conventional investigative methods such as social media use, electronic surveillance and analysis, and computer investigations.  Narrative:   On September 16, 2023, I, Corporal Z. Null 6149 of the Maryland State Police - Criminal Enforcement Division, was contacted by the Maryland State Police Waterloo Barrack in reference to a rape. It was learned that a suspect detained at Clifton T. Perkins Hospital anally raped the victim who is also detained at Clifton T. Perkins Hospital.    Trooper Morgan responded to Howard County Medical Center to investigate the incident. Upon Trooper Morgans arrival it was learned the victim, who was identified as Sambula, Christopher (B/M), was transported to the Hospital for a SAFE Exam, but prior to his arrival was transported back to Clifton T. Perkins Hospital. It was also learned that the suspect, identified as Thomas, Darryn Xavier (B/M DOB: 09/22/1988), was at Howard County Medical Center. Trooper Morgan attempted to speak to Thomas, but Thomas was uncooperative. Additionally, Thomas would not allow a SAFE Examiner to conduct an examination.    Based on the totality of the investigation and the allegations, D/SGT Collier and I responded to Clifton T. Perkins Hospital to conduct additional follow up.    Myself and D/SGT Collier made contact with LT. Nolan Ross, Maryland Department of Health - Correctional Officer for Perkins Hospital. LT. Ross facilitated the MSP investigators needs on Saturday, September 16, 2023, at Perkins Hospital. LT. Ross was present during our interviews of Sambula and the third roommate/potential witness identified as, Sanders, Jermaine (B/M). LT. Ross recommended MSP investigators contactLT. Branham, Clifton Perkins Hospital Police Department,to obtain (1). Clifton Perkins Hospital reports, (2). Patient/inmate information, (3). Correctional officer reports and (4). Surveillance of the patient/inmates door, wing hallway, nurses station and lobby. LT. Ross said the incident occurred in room number113.According to LT. Ross, Sambula came out of his room around midnight on Saturday, September 16, 2023, and told the nurses station that he had been raped/sodomized.  We thenmet with Perkins Hospital Medical Doctor,Dr. Malika Waseem. Dr.Wassemsaid she was the on-call doctor when the Sambula reported the incident. Dr. Waseem said Sambula and Thomas are under the care of the same Perkins Hospital Psychiatrist,Dr. Zhang. Dr. Wasseem said Sambula disclosed the following:    The Victim shares his room with the Suspect and a third roommate/potential witness. Three patients/inmates per room.  The Victim said the Suspect began rubbing lotion on the Victims anus.  The Victim said he verbally and physically triedto stop the Suspect but the Suspect continued.  The Victim said the Suspect pushed him down, and he sodomized him for approximately 3 minutes.  Several hours later, the Suspect claimed hed been raped and demanded an offsite examination.Due to the several hours long gap in time before the Suspect claimed rape, Dr. Waseem and LT. Ross doubted this was true and thought potentially the Suspect could be attempting to cover up his culpability.The Suspect claimed he didntcome forward with this information right away because he was embarrassed and didntwant to tell anybody.  Investigators spoke with Sambula. The interview was recorded by my body worn camera; however, at some point during the interview he asked if we could audio record only; therefore, the body worn camera was deactivated and the audio recorder was turned on. Highlights from the interview are as follows:    Sambula said he shares room # 113 withThomas and Sanders. Sambuladescribed Thomasas a tall, black, guy in his thirties. Sambulasaid he did not feel comfortable speaking with investigators about Sanders because Sanders was still in the facility. Sambulasaid Sanders was not in the room when the rape/sodomy occurred.  Sambula saidhis bed is in-between Thomas bed-(right side of the room) and Sanders bed-(left side of the room).  Sambula said he did not previously have any type of relationship with Thomas or Sanders. Sambulasaid he heard Thomashad a problem with another man and Perkins Hospital Staff transferred Sambulato room # 113 on Friday, September 15, 2023. Sambulasaid he had notbeen in the room for even 24 hours, before he was raped/sodomized.  Sambula said he was sleeping in his bed when he felt Thomastouching his rectum with his hands/fingers. Sambulasaid Thomaswas rubbing lotion on his anus. Sambulasaid he moved and told Thomasto stop; however, Thomassaid Let me see something real quick and continued.  Sambula said ThomasSodomized him for approximately three-(3) minutes and ejaculated while inside him. Sambulasaid he tried to get Thomasoff of him; however, Thomasdug his thumbs into Sambulasback pinning him down. Sambulasaid Thomas held him down the entire time.  Sambula said he was lying on his stomach sleeping in his bed prior to the incident. Sambulasaid he was wearing a white t-shirt but was naked from the waist down when the incident took place. Sambulasaid he was sleeping with a sheet over top of his naked bottom before Thomasbegan assaulting him by straddling over top of him.  Sambula said their third roommate/Sanders was not in the room when the rape/sodomy took place.  Sambula said after the assault he put his pants on without underwear and walked to the bathroom closest to his room where he cleaned himself up. After cleaning himself Sambulawalked to the nurses station and reported the rape/sodomy. Sambulasaid he reported the crime to an Asian, Male, Nurse and was moved to a separate, Quiet room.  Sambula said he hasntbeen back to his room since the incident. Sambulasaid there was no semen on his white t-shirt or inside his pants. Sambulawas not sure if there was semen on his bedding since he hadnot been back to his room.  When Sambulawas asked if it was possible Thomascould have thought the encounter was welcomed, Sambulaindicated the possibility, Thomascould have interpreted him sleeping naked from the waist down as an enticement. Sambulareminded investigators that he told Thomasto stop and also physically attempted to stop Thomasaction.  Sambulatold investigators everything he told them was the truth.Investigators told Sambula he could ask LT Ross at any time to get a hold of them on his behalf or trust LT. Ross to assist him with issues moving forward. Sambulasaid he was taking 3 kinds of medication to help with his Focus and anxiety. When asked what punishment Thomasshould receive, Sambulasaid it wasnt his job to determine that.  Investigators then spoke to the third roommate/Sanders. The interview was recorded on my body worn camera. Highlights from interview are as follows:    Sanders said he was not in the room when the crime occurred.Sanders said the crime would not have occurred if he was present.Sanders said investigators could check surveillance footage, and it would show that he was speaking with another man, Keith Johnsonin the lobby area when he saw Sambula report the crime to the nurses station.Sanders said he kind of overheard some of the report to the nurses station. Sanders said hes never had an issue with Thomasand has never seen or heard Thomasattempt sexual contact with any patients/inmates.  Sanders said Sambulahad only been in room # 113 for oneday.    I requested the bedding from Clifton Perkins Hospital to seize as evidence. LT Ross arranged from the bedding from room #113 and the quiet room to be brought to myself.    Based on the investigation thusfar, D/SGT Collier and I left Clifton Perkins Hospital and transported the bedding the Maryland State Police Waterloo Barrack for processing. The evidence was packaged per MSP Policy and placed in storage pending additional follow up.    This case remains open and will be transferred to TFC Hussey for additional follow up.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/20/2023 17:15:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/28/2023 14:31:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Whitmore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6094</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Null</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zakery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6149</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522025</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4 3600</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>15</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/16/2023 15:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4 3600</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/20/2023 17:13:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/20/2023 17:13:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522025</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>15</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/16/2023 15:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/20/2023 17:14:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/20/2023 17:14:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/20/2023 17:17:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/20/2023 17:17:08</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Bedding recovered from victims bed</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>333</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>254303</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>WHI</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>WHI</SecondaryColor>
         <Quantity>0</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6149</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/20/2023 17:17:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6149</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/20/2023 17:17:08</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Bedding recovered from quiet room</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>333</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>254304</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>WHI</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>WHI</SecondaryColor>
         <Quantity>0</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/29/2023 14:06:40</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/29/2023 14:06:40</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40C</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/18/2023 10:45:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6913</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 14:06:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments: -Maryland Department of Health Police report -Howard County General Hospital Sexual Assault Forensic Examination Report -Clifton T. Perkins Hospital Center Sambula Subpoena -Clifton T. Perkins Hospital Center Thomas Subpoena -Unserved DNA search warrant for Darryn Xavier Thomas -Unserved search warrant inventory report and return -Served DNA search warrant for Darryn Xavier Thomas -Served search warrant inventory report and return  Suspect: -Darryn Xavier Thomas, AA/M, DOB: 09/22/1988  Victim: -Christopher Sambula, AA/M, DOB: 09/12/1999  Evidence: -Two (2) DNA swabs from Darryn Xavier Thomas -SAFE kit  Narrative:  Since the incident, Thomas has been transported to the Prince Georges County Department of Corrections located at 13400 Dille Drive, Upper Marlboro, MD 20772 in reference to Prince Georges Circuit Court case number CT220899X.  On 09/18/2023, I responded to Johns Hopkins Howard County Medical Center and met Jena Britton who conducted the SAFE exam. I retrieved the SAFE kit and the SAFE report, the SAFE kit was transported to the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie barrack.  On 09/22/2023, investigators responded to Prince Georges County Department of Corrections located at 13400 Dille Drive, Upper Marlboro, MD 20772 to serve a DNA search warrant on Thomas. Thomas advised that we were not getting his DNA. Thomas was explained that the search warrant was signed by a judge, Thomas advised he didnt care if the search warrant was signed by God, that we were not getting his DNA. Thomas made a death threat to one of the investigators during the brief interaction with him. Due to Thomas being highly agitated, investigators decided to attempt the DNA search warrant on a later date.  On 09/27/2023, investigators responded to Prince Georges County Department of Corrections and served a DNA search warrant on the suspect. The two (2) DNA swabs from the Thomas and were packaged and processed per MSP policy and brought to the Glen Burnie barrack.  On 09/28/2023, Clifton T. Perkins Hospital Center was served two subpoenas. On 10/12/2023, Beverly L. Todd, R.H.I.T. Health Information Management Services requested two separate subpoenas for Thomas and Sambulas records.  On 10/16/2023, Clifton T. Perkins Hospital Center was served two separate subpoenas for Thomas and Sambula. The first subpoena included patient/inmate information for Darryn Xavier Thomas-(Patient ID#:14917) (Suspect), Perkins Hospital reports regarding the incident, and surveillance of the patient/imates door, wing hallway, nurses station, and lobby. The second subpoena included, patient/inmate information for Christopher (christofer) Sambula-(Patient ID#:14093 or 14903), Perkins Hospital reports regarding the incident, and surveillance of the patient/imates door, wing hallway, nurses station, and lobby.  On 09/28/2023, the SAFE kit and DNA swabs were sent to the crime lab for analysis.  This case remains open, pending laboratory analysis and retrieval of subpoenas.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6913</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 14:08:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6913</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/17/2023 11:46:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Null</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zakery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6149</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40C</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hussey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6913</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6913</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 14:29:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6913</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 14:29:20</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Two (2) DNA swabs from Darryn Xavier Thomas</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>DNA</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>254705</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>2</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6913</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 14:29:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6913</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 14:29:20</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) SAFE kit</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>3</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>254706</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>