<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-018474</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/24/2023 09:28:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/24/2023 09:28:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/24/2023 09:28:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/24/2023 09:28:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Possession/Distribution of Child Pornography</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 09:28:14</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6001</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 12:17:38</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>CAC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>697111</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 09:28:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/27/2023 16:19:22</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>697111</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>103</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Austin</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21811</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/24/2023 09:28:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/24/2023 09:28:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>Y</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/03/2023 10:56:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 09:28:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:14</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Initial Report</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report:   Initial Report  Narrative:  On Wednesday, May 24, 2023, I S/T Garrett Dick #6158 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region received NCMEC CyberTip #161605184. The CyberTip, generated by Dropbox, Inc, indicated that a subject uploaded child pornography to the internet.The CyberTip did not record or denote a time the child pornography was uploaded by the Dropbox user account. I viewed the uploaded child pornography which depicted the following:  One video approximately one (1) minutes and forty (40) seconds in length depicting a pubescent female (approximately fourteen (14) years old) wearing a blue bathing suit and white bathing suit bottoms. As the video plays the female takes her top off, exposing her breasts and utilizes her hands to manipulate her breasts. As the video continues the females bottoms are off and the camera shows a close up of her utilizing her hands to manipulate her vagina and digitally penetrate her anus.  Dropbox, Inc provided the following Uploaded File information: Filename: Video 31.08.15 18 50 31.mp4 MD5: 268a58045ad68250174647948bb375c9  Dropbox, Inc provided the following suspect account information for the user account that uploaded the child pornography as described above related to the NCMEC CyberTip:  Email Address: beachbum92278@gmail.com (Verified 08-03-2020 20:21:38 UTC) Screen/User Name: Janice Righs ESP User ID: 3404743808 IP Address: 73.250.196.17 (Login) 02-20-2023 22:11:08 UTC IP Address: 73.250.196.17 (Login) 02-22-2023 02:02:40 UTC IP Address: 168.67.1.131 (Login) 05-04-2023 19:21:22 UTC  It should be noted that the information received by Dropbox , Inc., related to the suspect account showed that the suspect account of beachbum92278@gmail.com was created on August 3, 2020.    A subpoena was sent to Comcast Cable requested subscriber information for Comcast IP address, 73.250.196.17 assigned on 02-20-2023 @ 22:11:08 UTC. On 5/30/2023 Comcast Cable sent back a subpoena response that provided the following information;  Subscriber Name: Matt Powell Service Address: 103 Austin Circle, Berlin, Maryland, 218111056 Billing Address: 103 Austin Circle, Berlin, Maryland, 218111056 Telephone #: (410) 726-8308 Type of Service: Internet Account Number: 8299410160035550 Account Status: Active IP Assignment: Dynamically Assigned E-mail User Ids: mp719@comcast.net    A search warrant is forthcoming for the suspect Dropbox, Inc account.  Case OPEN. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 08:39:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6158</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 09:28:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6158</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507907</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0300</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/24/2023 09:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0300</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 12:01:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6158</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 12:01:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 12:01:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6158</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 12:01:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/13/2023 11:06:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/13/2023 11:06:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/03/2023 10:56:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/13/2023 11:06:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:14</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Dropbox Search Warrant</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report:   Dropbox Search Warrant  Narrative:   On Thursday, June 1, 2023, I S/T Garrett Dick #6158 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region authored a Dropbox search warrant on the following Dropbox, Inc account;  Email: beachbum92278@gmail.com Screen/Username: Janice Righs ESP User ID: 3404743808    The search warrant was reviewed and signed by the honorable Judge Karen M. Dean of the Wicomico County Circuit Court. On Friday, June 2nd, 2023, I served the search warrant upon Dropbox, Inc via their online portal.  Case OPEN, pending search warrant results. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/13/2023 11:10:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6158</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/13/2023 12:17:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6158</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/25/2023 10:08:43</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/25/2023 10:08:43</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/03/2023 10:56:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/25/2023 10:08:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:14</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Dropbox results</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of supplemental Report:   Dropbox Results   Narrative:   I, S/T Garrett Dick #6158 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region have previewed the Dropbox Inc results in this investigation and observed several files of potential CSAM. I will be meeting with Doctor Wehberg on 9/8/2023 to have her view the images and videos to identify the ages of the children in the videos and pictures from the Dropbox account.  Case OPEN</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/25/2023 10:09:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6158</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/25/2023 10:15:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6158</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/25/2023 10:18:50</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/25/2023 10:18:50</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/03/2023 10:56:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 10:18:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:14</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Dropbox Review with Dr. Wehburg </NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report:   Dropbox Review with Dr. Wehburg  Narrative:   On Friday, September 9, 2023, I S/T Garrett Dick #6158 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region met with Dr. Wehburg, a pediatric doctor who assisted in aging the children in the suspect Dropbox Account in this investigation. I opened the Dropbox download that was received upon execution of the suspect Dropbox account, beachbum92278@gmail.com, ESP User ID: 3404743808. I began by opening the file labeled 13-17 Teen Vids and observed the following:  1. Filename:710ea920-9d43-4ba2-91ae-c624d2bcef07.mp4 Length: 1 minute 59 seconds. Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately fourteen (14) years old. The female begins stripping in the video and exposes her breasts.  2. Filename:2014-11-22_15-26-45_828..mp4 Length: 3 minutes 50 seconds. Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately fourteen (14) years old. The female is not wearing a shirt and her breasts are exposed as she is sexually licking a red cylinder shaped object. The female then proceeds to spit saliva on her breast and begins rubbing her nipples. The female then proceeds to expose her vagina and begins inserting the red cylinder shaped object in her vagina.  3. Filename:a732e8a9-b893-4ddf-b7ee-24aa25a5d3be.mp4 Length: 1 minute 31 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting a prepubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately 12-13 years old. The female is nude from the waist down and laying on the floor inserting an unknown object into her vagina.  4. Filename:a37697af-7ad9-42a4-b647-7b36aff9b97d.mp4 Length: 1 minute 6 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately fourteen (14) years old. The female is naked from the waist down and is inserting a unknown black object in her anus. The vagina is exposed and she is utilizing her fingers to manipulate her vagina as she inserts the unknown object in her anus.  5. Filename:Bg2.mp4 Length: 22 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting a pre-pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately 10-12 years old utilizing her fingers to manipulate her vagina.  6. Filename:c28afc37-3e99-4e00-980d-fb6a666a2f73.mp4 Length: 1 minute 31 seconds. Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately fifteen (15) years old. The female is initially wearing a purple bra and white/pink/grey underwear. The female begins to take her underwear off and expose her buttocks, and the takes her bra off and exposed her breasts.  7. Filename: Ct.mp4 Length: 2 minutes Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately fourteen (14) years old. The female is initially wearing only underwear but quickly takes them off and exposes her breasts and vagina. Later in the video the female sits on her bed and begins utilizing her fingers to manipulate her vagina.  8. Filename: Ct02.mp4 Length: 15 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately fourteen (14) years old. The female is nude from the waist down and is bending over exposing her anus and vagina. The female is utilizing a black beaded object to penetrate her anus.  9. Filename: Ct09.mp4 Length: 1 minute 37 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately thirteen (13) years old. The female initially is wearing a blue tank top and blue pants but begins to strip until shes fully nude. The females breasts, vagina, and buttocks are exposed, and the female begins dancing and using her fingers to manipulate her vagina.  10. Filename: Ct909.mp4 Length: 50 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately thirteen (13) years old. The female is initially wearing a white tank top and grey pants. The female takes her tank top off and exposes her breasts and then begins taking her grey pants off. The female proceeds to take her pink underwear off and expose her vagina and buttocks.  11. Filename: cuti.mp4 Length: 14 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately thirteen (13) years old. The female is fully nude with her breasts exposed and is using a vibrating device to manipulate her vagina.  12. Filename:d9ee1015-45ab-45b7-ba56-c63dd0853dc6 (1).mp4 Length: 52 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately fourteen (14) years old. The female is lying face down on her bed exposing her buttocks and vagina, while inserting a hairbrush in and out of her vagina.  13. Filename:e87ac59f-fafa-4caa-8de9-9c9adacf6c0d.mp4 Length: 32 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately 12-13 years old. The female is initially wearing a black bra and purple/blue underwear. The female takes her bra off exposing her breasts and then takes her underwear off and exposes her buttocks and vagina.  14. Filename:f3fd5906-2098-4dc0-9b6c-d32dcf5d9bc7.mp4 Length: 51 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately fourteen (14) years old. The female is seated on the floor wearing a pink top and nude from the waist down. The female is utilizing her fingers to manipulate her vagina while sexually moaning.  15. Filename:f5b8073c-746b-45db-a906-a52136daf072.mp4 Length: 52 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately 13-14 years old. Initially the female is wearing a gren bra and blue underwear but a short time later the female takes her underwear and bra off exposing her breast and vagina before finally sitting down, and the female begins using her fingers to manipulate her vagina.    For the next five videos I opened the folder listed as 1  16. Filename: 3 girls showing tits.mp4 Length: 2 minutes 5 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting three pubescent females under the age of sixteen (16) approximately 12-14 years old. The females all lift there shirts and expose their breasts to the camera.  17. Filename: 341.mp4 Length: 3 minutes 13 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately 15 years old. The female is initially wearing a white shirt, red skirt, and pink underwear. The female begins rubbing her breasts and vagina through her shit and underwear before taking them off and exposing her vagina and then breasts. The female then sits on a chair and begins utilizing and orange object to penetrate her vagina.  18. Filename: 349.mp4 Length: 1 minute 3 seconds. Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately 12-13 years old wearing a white Mickey Mouse t-shirt. The female pulls her shirt down and exposes her breasts to the camera.  19. Filename: 357.mp4 Length: 24 minutes Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately 14-15 years old. The female is wearing a pink baggy sweatshirt and lifts it up exposing her breasts. The female eventually takes her sweatshirt off and is seen wearing a black bra and black underwear. The female proceeds to take her bra off and begins massaging her breasts in a sexual manner. Finally the female pulls her underwear down and starts to expose and manipulate her vagina.  20. Filename: 360.mp4 Length: 3 minutes and 52 seconds Description: One (1) video depicting a pubescent female under the age of sixteen (16) approximately thirteen years old. Initially the female is wearing a white dress and a tan bra. The female proceeds to take her bra off and expose her breasts, and then lift her dress up and expose her buttocks.    The Dropbox contained several other child sex abuse material but for charging purposes these videos were selected and described.  Case OPEN pending residential search warrant of the suspect residence.     </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 10:19:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6158</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/27/2023 16:21:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6158</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/03/2023 10:41:18</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/03/2023 10:41:18</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/03/2023 10:56:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 10:41:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:14</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Google Subpoena </NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report:   Google Subpoena  Narrative:   On Tuesday, October 3, 2023, I S/T Garrett Dick #6158 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region served a subpoena upon Google LLC reference obtaining subscriber information for GMAIL account, beachbum92278@gmail.com. Once Google responds a supplement detailing the results with documented.  Case OPEN.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 10:42:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6158</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 10:43:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6158</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>5</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/31/2023 13:38:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/31/2023 13:38:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/01/2023 07:26:10</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/31/2023 13:38:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/01/2023 07:26:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Google Subpoena Results </NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: Google Subpoena Results  Narrative:   On 10/18/2023, I S/T Garrett Dick #6158 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region received Google subpoena results back in reference to the suspect email address documented in the NCMEC Cyber-Tip. Google provided the following information;  Google Account ID: 771333377792 Name: Matt Powell Given Name: Matt Family Name: Powell e-Mail:beachbum92278@gmail.com Created on: 2017-04-03 21:17:38 Z Last Upload Date: 10-07-19:27:36 Z  Account Recovery e-Mail. map719@gmail.com  IP Activity: Time Stamp: 2023-05-05 17:43:03 Z IP Address: 2600:1003:b028:eb26:b013:533c:9cbf:d7af Activity Type:Login Time Stamp: 2023-05-05 17:10:21 Z IP Address:168.67.1.131 Activity Type:Login Time Stamp: 2023-05-05 IP Address: 2600:1003:b028:eb286:b013:533c:9cbf:d7af Activity Type:Login  The IP address listed in IP activity, 168.67.1.131 was also documented as a login in the NCMEC Cyber-Tip.    Case OPEN pending search warrant on 103 Austin Circle, Berlin, Maryland on 11/2/2023.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/31/2023 13:40:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6158</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/31/2023 14:15:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6158</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>6</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/03/2023 10:27:29</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/03/2023 10:27:29</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/08/2023 09:39:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/03/2023 10:27:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/08/2023 09:39:30</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Residential SW 103 Austin Circle</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: Residential SW 103 Austin Circle  Evidence:   One (1) Red iPhone in red case   One (1) black HP Laptop S/N: CND72653V6   One (1) white iPhone in clear case   One (1) black iPhone   One (1) pink iPhone SE   One (1) pink iPhone model A1532   One (1) gold USB flash drive with Ejing 128GB with lightning adapter   One (1) black USB flash drive with 1TB USB 3.0 printed in silver   One (1) USE flash drive with MicroSD USB 2.0 printed in silver   One (1) gray and silver SanDisk USB Flash Drive with lightning adapter   One (1) HP Computer tower S/N: 3CR224023V with power cord   One (1) silver Verbatim USB flash drive   One (1) silver Attache USB flash drive 16GB   One (1) silver Kingston 256MB USB flash drive   One (1) blue Panasonic 256MB SD Card   One (1) space gray iPad with keyboard   One (1) SLOANE black and silver USB flash drive   One (1) blue USB flash drive   One (1) Onn. 128 GB micro SD card with adapter   One (1) WYZE 32 GB black micro SD card with adapter  AXON LINK: https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=c041ac4190d9499790660a8509e5c9d9partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  Narrative:   On Thursday, November 2, 2023, I S/T Garrett Dick #6158 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region [CEDER] accompanied by other members of CEDER executed a residential search warrant upon 103 Austin Circle, Berlin, Maryland. Matthew Powell [hereinafter referred to as Matthew] opened the front door after I made several knocks and announces. The residence was cleared by members of CEDER and the only other person present at the residence was Powells daughter identified as Kyleigh Powell [hereinafter referred to as Kyleigh]. One hundred and twenty-five (125) digital images were taken during the execution of the search warrant, and later uploaded to VeriPic in accordance with MSP policy. During the execution of the search warrant the following items were located, documented and seized;  One (1) Red iPhone in red case   One (1) black HP Laptop S/N: CND72653V6   One (1) white iPhone in clear case   One (1) black iPhone   One (1) pink iPhone SE   One (1) pink iPhone model A1532   One (1) gold USB flash drive with Ejing 128GB with lightning adapter   One (1) black USB flash drive with 1TB USB 3.0 printed in silver   One (1) USE flash drive with MicroSD USB 2.0 printed in silver   One (1) gray and silver SanDisk USB Flash Drive with lightning adapter   One (1) HP Computer tower S/N: 3CR224023V with power cord   One (1) silver Verbatim USB flash drive   One (1) silver Attache USB flash drive 16GB   One (1) silver Kingston 256MB USB flash drive   One (1) blue Panasonic 256MB SD Card   One (1) space gray iPad with keyboard   One (1) SLOANE black and silver USB flash drive   One (1) blue USB flash drive   One (1) Onn. 128 GB micro SD card with adapter   One (1) WYZE 32 GB black micro SD card with adapter    At approximately 0611 hours [6:11 a.m.] I attempted to conduct an audibly and visually recorded interview with Matthew, however he declined to speak with me. I read Matthew the search warrant which was captured audibly and visually. At approximately 0619 hours [6:19 a.m.] I spoke with Kyleigh and read her a Maryland State Police form 78 (consent to search and seize) and explained to her that if she provides written consent, for me to preview her cell phone and verify her cellular phone contained no CSAM. Kyliegh provided written consent for me to search and preview her iPhone 11, and I did not find any CSAM on the phone. Kyleigh was immediately given her iPhone 11 back, and she left the residence.    Matthew was provided copies of the search warrant, search warrant return, and inventory, and then myself and CEDER investigators exited the residence and responded to the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack with the seized evidence which was processed and stored in accordance with MSP policy.  Case OPEN.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/06/2023 12:19:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6158</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/07/2023 08:29:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6158</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>7</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/06/2023 09:56:49</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/06/2023 09:56:49</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/08/2023 09:41:08</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 09:56:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/08/2023 09:41:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Interview of Laura Powell</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report:   Interview of Laura Powell  AXON LINK: https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=4d5de306146541ea8bbb93201e1b9df6partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  Narrative:   On Monday, November 6, 2023, I S/T Garrett Dick #6158 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region conducted and audibly and visually recorded interview with Laura Powell [hereinafter referred to as Laura] concerning the investigation. The interview was conducted in the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack interview room. Below is a synopsis of the interview and not a transcript therefore some paraphrasing may be used;   Laura was shown the Cyber-Tip and the details listed on it concerning suspect information.  Laura was shown the listed suspect email address, beachbum92278@gmail.com, and advised the numbers 92278 are Matthew Powells [hereinafter referred to as Matthew]birth date.  Laura was shown the Google subscriber information which listed a backup email account of: map719@gmail.com which Laura positively identified as Matthews email account.  Laura also identified the email address listed by Comcast, which was MP719@comcast.net, and added that 719 is their daughtersbirth date.  Laura and Matthew have been divorced since 2021, and Matthew lives with only his daughter at 103 Austin Circle, Berlin, Maryland.  Laura added that Matthew has a girlfriend that may stay with him.  Laura was aware of Matthew watching pornography but not child pornography.  Case OPEN</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 09:57:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6158</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/07/2023 09:16:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6158</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>8</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/07/2023 09:17:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/07/2023 09:17:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/08/2023 09:41:38</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/07/2023 09:17:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/08/2023 09:41:39</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Authorization of Device Search Warrant</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report: Authorization of Device Search Warrant  Narrative:   On Thursday, December 7, 2023, I S/T Garrett Dick #6158 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region finalized the device search warrant to have the seized devices in this investigation forensically analyzed. I sent a copy of the search warrant to Assistant States Attorney Pamela Correa of the Worcester County States Attorneys Office for review. Upon completed of the search warrant review I will send the warrant to a judge and complete a supplemental report.  Case OPEN.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/07/2023 09:19:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6158</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/07/2023 09:21:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6158</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>9</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/05/2024 12:17:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/05/2024 12:17:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 12:17:37</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 12:17:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 12:17:38</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Device Search Warrant Review</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report:   Device Search Warrant Review  Narrative:   On Thursday, January 24, 2023, I S/T Garrett Dick #6158 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region sent the device search warrant to the Honorable Judge Abigail Marsh, Judge of the Wicomico County District Court for review. Upon signature of the search warrant I will complete a Digital Forensic Request to the Maryland State Police Forensic Lab and update this case,  Case OPEN.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2024 12:17:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6158</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 09:19:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6158</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>