<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-030364</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/28/2023 18:46:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/28/2023 18:46:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/28/2023 18:33:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/28/2023 18:33:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>CIVIL DISPUTE COMPLAINT</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/28/2023 18:46:17</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4199</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 11:39:58</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>CDT</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>705288</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/28/2023 18:46:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 00:48:12</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>705288</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>30494</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Broad</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Princess Anne</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.694462</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.205352</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/28/2023 18:46:13</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/28/2023 18:46:13</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>09/13/2023 11:39:58</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/28/2023 18:46:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4199</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 11:39:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack X Tpr. B. Salgueiro, IBM 7370 Field Operation Bureau August 28, 2023   Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle:X-4is an unmarked 2021 Ford Explorer equipped with an MVR system and body-worn camera. Type of Report: Civil dispute Complainant: Martina Mikeal Harmon (DOB: 05-15-1974 B/F) Suspect/interviewed: Deshell Johnson (DOB: 07-17-1997 B/F)     Troopers Training/Experience:  * Trained in Human Trafficking through the Federal Bureau Of Investigations (FBI) and Maryland State Police (MSP)  * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).  *Trained and certified with the Somerset County Crisis Intervention Team (CIT).  *Trained and certified in Mental Health First Aid through the National Council for Mental Well-being.  * Trained and certified to operate Radar and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  * NHTSA certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E).  * Attended multiple NHTSA-certified cannabis impairment detection workshops.    Narrative:  This report has been prepared based upon the observations of this trooper and/or those of other troopers relative to the offense(s). The facts contained herein are intended solely to give the prosecuting authority a basic understanding of the facts pertaining to this case. The facts contained herein are not intended to be an exhaustive recitation of the facts pertaining to pretrial or trial issues. Instead, this trooper anticipates that during the pretrial proceedings, in this case, the prosecutor will take the opportunity to interview this trooper in order to ascertain any and all relevant facts which might be the subject of this troopers testimony during court proceedings.   On 8/28/2023 at 1833 hours, I, Tpr. Salgueiro #7370 was dispatched to a report of a possible domestic dispute between two female subjects at30494 Broad Street, Princess Anne, Maryland. I responded to the scene and made contact with the complaint identified as Martina Mikeal Harmon (DOB:05-15-1974 B/F). Harmon advised me that approximately 30 minutes prior to my arrival she was watching over her sons daughter. Allegedly the daughter had braids that had just been placed in her hair. The daughters mother identified as Deshell Johnson (DOB:07-17-1997 B/F) was upset at the complainant because she allowed the child to get these braids. The complainant advised that Johnson then left30494 Broad Street but shortly returned to the residence and forced her way inside. After the complainant advised Johnson that law enforcement was en route, she left the residence with her daughter. Both parties were cooperative on scene and advised they would respond to the Somerset County Commissioners Office to file paperwork. Both parties were advised of the case number for this report and given my name and badge number. I was able to remain on scene until both parties separated, and cleared without incident.  I request this case be closed due to no further investigative leads on this case.  All events did occur in Somerset County Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/04/2023 23:20:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7370</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/10/2023 15:58:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Revel</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7146</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barkley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ivan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4199</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Salgueiro</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7370</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>