<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-023777</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/02/2023 20:30:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/02/2023 20:30:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/02/2023 20:02:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/02/2023 20:02:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Car stop. DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 20:30:27</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/03/2023 10:16:39</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>SYKESVILLE RD/ BOLLINGER MILL RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>545380</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 20:30:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 19:35:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>545380</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Sykesville</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Finksburg</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.924605</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.448964</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4600-4600 SYKESVILLE RD / 1996-2014 BOLLINGER MILL RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4548-4599 SYKESVILLE RD / 2000-2020 BOLLINGER MILL RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4497-4499 SYKESVILLE RD / 1996-2018 BOLLINGER MILL RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/02/2023 20:30:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/02/2023 20:30:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/19/2023 10:55:46</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 20:30:27</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was captured on body worn and in car camera.  ATTACHMENTS: METERS printout DUI Processing packet Citations Notice to appear  DRIVER: Carolann Shapre  W/F  09/17/1969 1809 Emory Rd Reisterstown, MD  NARRATIVE: Vehicle in Motion On 07/02/2023, at approximately 2000 hours, I was on patrol in the town of Sykesville, MD. I was conducting routine traffic enforcement on MD32. 07/02/2023 was the Sunday before Independence Day. I was traveling north in the area of the Freedom Elementary School when I observed a white Ram pickup truck ahead of me. The truck was also driving north and I took note of the vehicle because it appeared as though the vehicle crossed over the double yellow center line. The truck was about a quarter mile ahead of me, so I accelerated to catch up. As I was catching up to the vehicle, I noted that the vehicle appeared to be drifting within its lane.  I got directly behind the truck in the area of MD32 and Pine Knob Rd. As we continued north, I watched as the vehicle drifted from the right edge of the lane to the left edge - from fog line to yellow center line. The steering inputs seemed sudden and jerky. In the area just north of Pine Knob Rd., for example, I watched as the truck drifted over the solid white fog line and into the shoulder. About one third of the truck was in the shoulder for approximately 2 seconds before the truck drifted back to a position in the northbound travel lane. Shortly thereafter and in rapid succession, the truck drifted from being over the white fog line, to touching the double yellow center and back to the white line multiple times.  While crossing the bridge over Liberty Reservoir, in a perfectly straight stretch of road, the vehicle drifted to the left such that the drivers side tires were covering the yellow center lines. The vehicle stayed there for approximately 2 seconds before drifting to, and crossing over, the white fog line. It remained over the white fog line through the start of a right-hand curve before drifting to the center line once again. AS the road straightened, the vehicle continued to bounce back and forth.  Based on the observations I had made, I decided to stop the truck. Not only had it committed a traffic violation, I also know from my training, knowledge and experience that the behavior could be indicative of impaired driving. However, due to the roadway, I was forced to wait a short distance until a safe location became available. During that time, I continued to make observations. In the area of Arlington Rd., MD32 curves to the left. I watched as the trucks drivers side tires were covering the yellow double center line through the corner. Just north of this location, the truck navigated another left corner. I watched as the trucks drivers side tires were completely over the double yellow through the duration of this corner. Due to roadway dynamics, visibility is very poor for southbound (oncoming) traffic and I watched as the truck made a sudden correction to a position completely in the northbound lane in the face of southbound traffic. The roadway straightens on the north side of this corner and I watched as the truck once again drifted over the center line such that the drivers side tires were completely covering the line.  At that time I was able to activate my emergency lights and siren to conduct a traffic stop. There area of the stop was the north side of Bollinger Mill Rd. This section of MD32 has a small acceleration lane in addition to the northbound travel lane providing excellent space to stop. Additionally, there were two driveways and a large parking lot. The vehicle pulled to the right and slowed, but did not stop. Although it could have maneuvered into the first driveway and parking lot, it then accelerated and pulled forward. It ultimately came to a stop in the shoulder of the roadway, though the drivers rear corner was still partially in the road. I took note of the slow stop because based on my training, knowledge and experience I know that it can be indicative of impaired driving.  Operator Contact I then made contact with the driver, later identified by MD drivers license as Carolann Sharpe. Sharpe was already getting her license but I introduced myself and requesting her documents. I watched as Sharpe got her license and quickly dropped it within the truck. I watched as Sharpe tried to find it. She opened the drivers door so I offered to help her find it. I observed mouthwash in the drivers side door pocket, which I found out of place. I learned that Sharpe was on her way home from getting dinner and could smell a strong odor of fried chicken emanating from within the truck. I learned that Sharpe had been at a fundraiser earlier in the day.  While speaking with Sharpe, I detected a faint odor of alcoholic beverage coming from her breath. I also noted that her speech was slurred and labored. Her eyes were also very bloodshot and glassy. I told Sharpe the reason for the stop and she attributed the poor operation to trying to eat while she was driving. I asked Sharpe about her drinking history. She said that she had one glass of wine and added that she was keto, presumably referring to her diet. She estimated starting drinking around 4:30 or 5 pm and said that she finished drinking around 6:30pm. I asked again what alcohol she had consumed during that time. She said she had one crush. Seeing that this was a different answer from when she was asked moments ago, I asked for clarification. Sharpes response was something to the effect that it was a wine crush. I again asked for clarification and Sharpe said that she had one crush. She said that it was a lime crush and that someone had made it for her and served it in a plastic cup. During this time I watched as Sharpe drank from her water bottle, which I found strange to do in the middle of a short conversation.  I instructed Sharpe to remain in the truck. I returned to my car and conducted routine checks on the status of Sharpes license and registration. I learned that Sharpe had been charged with DUI in January 2021. I learned nothing else of note. While in my vehicle, I also observed Sharpe open and close her drivers side door a couple of times. I returned to Sharpe moments later with the intention of asking her to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  When I returned to Sharpe, I could a fresh wet spot on the ground near the drivers side front tire. I could also see a blue liquid on the trucks step which appeared consistent with the mouthwash I had seen in the door pocket. I concluded that Sharpe had used mouthwash while I was conducting checks in my vehicle. I found the timing to be odd and got the impression that she was trying to mask the odor of alcoholic beverage from her breath.  I asked Sharpe about the liquid on the ground but she denied using the mouthwash. She said that she is self-conscious about having a denture and that food often gets stuck in the denture. Sharpe said that she uses the mouthwash to clean the denture, but when asked directly if she rinsed or used mouthwash, she said that she had not. Even if she had merely rinsed her denture with the mouthwash, I found the timing to be strange. However, not to push the issue, I decided to move past it. I directed Sharpe to exit the vehicle. She said something like lord have mercy and exited. I noted that Sharpe held onto the truck with both hands as she got down before walking to the back of her truck as directed.  SFSTs Once there I told Sharpe I wanted to make sure she was okay to drive. She immediately said something like Im fine, and, been there done that. I reiterated that I merely wanted to verify that and asked if she was willing to go through Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. She said sure. At that time I got Sharpe into the starting position for the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test. I conducted a pre-screening medical assessment. I learned that Sharpe had no recent head injuries. She reported having a lower back injury from a horse back riding incident in 2021. Sharpe said that she had broken her back and that while she is no longer going to traditional physical therapy, she participates in horse back riding therapy regularly. I asked her to gauge where she was in her recovery but would not answer, instead asking something like do you ever really recover from a back injury. Sharpe had been cooperative up to that point but seemed to start becoming more uncooperative; her mood seemed to swing. Sharpe reported no other lower extremity issues. She said that she was wearing contact lenses (non-colored). Sharpe said that she was pre-diabetic and while she was not taking insulin, she was prescribed a pill to address her pre-diabetes. Sharpe said that she does not check her sugars and is not on any other drugs or medications.  At that time, I explained the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test in detail. I demonstrated when applicable and ensured that Sharpe had no questions and understood the test prior to beginning. Before beginning, I checked for resting nystagmus, equal pupil size and equal tracking. I saw no issues. During the test I observed 6 out of 6 possible clues. Specifically I observed lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees. I also observed Vertical Gaze Nystagmus. It should be noted that during this test, Sharpe asked if I was looking for the jumping and told me that she is married to a cop.  The next test I attempted to administer was the Walk and Turn Test. I directed Sharpe into the starting position so that I could explain the test, but she asked if I realized that she was married to a cop and had zero balance. I was unclear as to the relevance of who she was married to, though it seemed as though she expected that to affect my decision-making. Sharpe went on to address her bad balance and said that she had weak ankles and bad balance. She told me that she has been ice skating her whole life and that was why she rode horses, in order to work on her balance. I attempted to explain that it was a totality of the circumstances, but Sharpe asked me if I knew that no one could do this, referring to standing in the starting position. I had been standing in the starting position the entire time and reminded her that I was standing in the same position in which I wanted her to stand. She merely reiterated that she had poor balance.  Sharpe ultimately tried to get into the starting position, though appeared unsteady as she did so. She was unable to maintain her balance, stepping out of position. At one point her shoulders shook side to side as she tried to maintain balance. I explained the test in detail, demonstrating when applicable. I asked Sharpe if she had any questions before beginning. She indicated she did not have any questions but when I asked if she understood the test, she said she did not. I asked if she wanted me to explain the test once more. She said yes. I then explained the test, demonstrating when applicable, in its entirety once again. I then asked Sharpe if she had any questions. She said she did not. When I asked if she understood the test, Sharpes response was not really.  I asked how I could make it any more clear, as I had explained and demonstrated the test twice but each time she reported having no questions but not understanding the test. Her response was try again. It became clear that Sharpe was becoming more uncooperative. I told Sharpe that if she did not want to do SFSTs that I could not force her to do them. I got the feeling that Sharpe was playing games and I told her that we were not going to do that. I started to explain the test once more but Sharpe interrupted me, saying something to the effect that her dilemma was that she knows she has poor balance and that I was asking her to do something she knew that she could not do.  Although I tried to explain that I was merely trying to ensure that she understood the test, Sharpe was focused on making it know that she has had limitations since childhood based on her balance. I asked Sharpe numerous times if she was willing to try the test. Each time I asked for a clear yes or no response from Sharpe, she instead said that she was concerned that she would not do well as a result of lifelong balance issues. I therefore made the decision to move past the Walk and Turn and ask Sharpe if she was willing to perform the One Leg Stand. Sharpe immediately reiterated her concerns and it became very clear that she was not willing to perform SFSTs. I directed Sharpe to the front of my vehicle. There I offered her the chance to take a PBT. Sharpe declined and asked if she could just go home.  At that time, based on the totality of the circumstances, it was clear that Sharpe was not capable of operating a motor vehicle safely as a result of alcohol impairment. She was therefore taken into custody for DUI. Sharpe was handcuffed, the handcuffs were checked for tightness and double locked. She was searched incident to arrest, yielding nothing of note. Sharpe was placed in my vehicle and transported to the Westminster State Police Barrack for processing. There I read the DR15 Advice of Rights in its entirety. At 2118 hours, Sharpe agreed to take an evidentiary test. She was transported to the Westminster City Police Department for testing. At 2155 hours Sharpe provided a sample of her breath as evidence, showing .12 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  Sharpe was issued the appropriate paperwork before being released to a sober party. I request this case be closed.  All events occurred in Carroll County.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/11/2023 02:29:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/12/2023 05:28:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pettis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6498</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McCarty</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cade</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6579</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phelps</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7210</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513216</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/02/2023 20:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513216</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/02/2023 20:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513216</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/02/2023 20:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513216</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/02/2023 20:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513216</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/02/2023 20:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513216</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/02/2023 20:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513216</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/02/2023 20:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513216</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16616</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/02/2023 20:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>53</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:41:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:02</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>294720</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sharpe</LastName>
               <FirstName>Carolann</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/17/1969 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.16666504E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>01/17/2021 19:31:24</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S610</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C645</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sharpe</LastName>
               <FirstName>Carolann</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/17/1969 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.16666504E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S610</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C645</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/17/2021 19:31:24</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1809</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Emory</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Reisterstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21136</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.8592929</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.522849</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>908</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5599</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/17/2021 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:41:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:41:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:41:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 19:38:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>120326</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 19:44:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 19:44:25</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/17/2021 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3C6TR5FT3GG191928</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2016</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>R25</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5EK5184</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicMonth>11</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>