<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-023678</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>64</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/01/2023 23:52:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/01/2023 23:52:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/01/2023 23:19:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/01/2023 23:19:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/01/2023 23:52:53</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3039</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/03/2023 01:41:39</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>699627</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/01/2023 23:52:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 01:39:30</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>699627</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>21</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I70 Eb</StreetName>
         <City>Clear Spring</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.8643</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.65045</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/01/2023 23:52:49</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/01/2023 23:52:49</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>64</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/03/2023 01:41:40</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/01/2023 23:52:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:39</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> margin-left:10px; padding:0in 0in 0in 0in"&gt;THIS INCIDENT WAS CAPTURED ON BWC AS WELL AS O-19s IN CAR CAMERA WITH FUNCTIONING AUDIO AND VIDEO  Defendant: Wayne Robert Charles Salmon Jr Date of Birth 02/16/1996 Date of arrest: 07/01/2023 Time of arrest: 2352 hours.  DUI # 23-070  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING  * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)    The vehicle was not observed in motion for this incident.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)   On July 1, 2023, at approximately 2319 hours, I responded to Eastbound Interstate 70 in the area of the 21 mile marker for the report of a collision.    Upon arrival, I observed a dark blue Nissan Rogue bearing Maryland registration 6DZ5647. The Rogue was running, sitting stationary on the left shoulder facing Westbound on the Eastbound side of Interstate 70. EMS personnel on scene advised no collision had taken place. I contacted the driver, and sole occupant of the vehicle, who I identified by his Maryland Drivers license as, Wayne Robert Charles Salmon Jr (W/M 02/16/1996). I observed Salmon to be seated in the drivers seat, with his seat belt still buckled. Salmon advised he was coming from Berkley Springs, West Virginia, and was very tired. Salmon advised he completed a U turn in the middle of the roadway, and pulled over on the shoulder so he would not fall asleep while driving. As I spoke with Salmon, I detected the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy, and his speech to be slurred. Salmon advised he was coming from a float trip in Berkley Springs, and had then stopped at a bar for some food before continuing on his drive home. I asked Salmon how much he had to drink at which time he initially advised none Salmon then advised he had consumed two (2) 12 oz Bud light alcoholic beverages at approximately 1000 hours on the day of the stop, while on his float trip. Salmon advised he had then consumed one Michelob Ultra alcoholic beverage while eating dinner. Salmon advised he had consumed the Michelob Ultra at approximately 2100 hours, on the day of the stop. I asked Salmon to submit to the Standardized Field Sobriety tests (SFSTs) which he subsequently agreed to.  I asked Salmon the following: Injuries: Salmon advised he had broken his right foot 7 years prior to the stop, and it became stiff if he stood on it for long periods of time. Medication: NO glasses/contacts: Salmon was wearing corrective lenses at the time of personal contact.  Pre-arrest screening (PHASE 3)   The SFSTs were performed on the left shoulder of Eastbound Interstate 70.The surface was wet due to recent rainfall, and free from any obvious debris. The area where theSFSTs were performed on a level surface. There was no rainfall while the SFSTs were completed. All forward facing emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Salmon appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible signs of injury.  HORIZONAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6 Of 6 CLUES OBSERVED)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. My pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Salmons eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. I observed Salmon to have equal pupil size, and equal tracking. Salmon verbally advised he understood the directions for the test.  Lack of smooth pursuit- Present in both eyes Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation- Present in both eyes Onset Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees- present in both eyes  Walk and turn (4 of 8 clues observed)   margin-left:10px; padding:0in 0in 0in 0in"&gt;Prior to Salmon performing the test I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Salmon was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Salmon was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until instructed to begin. Salmon was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. Salmon was instructed to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on hisfeet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Salmon was explained and I demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and planted, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around to his left. Salmon was again explained, and I demonstrated a second series of nine (9) steps were to be completed identically to the first series. Salmon was instructed that once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed. Keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. Salmon verbally advised he understood the directions for the test.  Instructional Phase  Salmon started too soon before being advised to begin the test during the instructional phase.     First set of nine steps: Salmon missed heel to toe contact by more than  inch on step three and six. Salmon stepped off line on step 8 Salmon raised his arms more than approximately 6 inches from his body in an attempt to maintain his balance on step 8.    Second set of nine steps: Salmon missed heel to toe contact by more than  inch on step 1.  One leg stand (2 of 4 clues observed)  Prior to Salmon performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be completed. Salmon was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down at his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Salmon verbally stated he understood the directions for the test. Salmon raised his right foot for the test.   Seconds 1-10 Salmon raised his arms more than approximately six inches away from his body in an attempt to maintain his balance Salmon swayed from side to side while balancing.  Seconds 11-20 No clues observed  Seconds 21-30 No clues observed  Salmon agreed to a PBT with a result of .09 BrAC. Salmon removed a piece of gum from his mouth, prior to submitting to the PBT.   ARREST    margin-left:10px; padding:0in 0in 0in 0in"&gt;Based on the following, I had reason to believe Salmon was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:    margin-left:10px; padding:0in 0in 0in 0in"&gt; *Admission to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to driving *My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety testing *Bloodshot eyes *Watery eyes *Slurred Speech  * Performing a U turn on a one-way roadway (Eastbound Interstate 70) and parking on the shoulder facing the opposite direction of traffic flow.     salmon was placed under arrest at approximately 2352 hours. Prior to placing Salmon in my patrol vehicle, I conducted a search of his person which revealed no contraband. I also checked Salmons mouth and found it was free of any foreign substances. Salmon was transported to the Maryland State Police Hagerstown Barrack. Once at the Hagerstown Barrack, Salmon was read and given to read a copy of the DR-15 advice of rights while seated directly to my right. Salmon agreed to submit to the intoximeter test On July 2, 2023, at approximately 0024 hours.  Intoximeter results:  Salmonsubmitted to the Intoximeter test on July 2. 2023, at approximately 0031 hours administered by Sgt. Kulina #3039 with a result of .09 BrAC.  Salmon signed and received all appropriate paperwork, was issued the appropriate traffic citations, and released to a sober driver  CASE STATUS:   I respectfully request this case be closed by arrest.   All events occurred in Washington County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 01:40:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6783</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 01:40:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>64</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Socks</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6504</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>64</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>O'Neal</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6746</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>64</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kulina</LastName>
            <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>64</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derek</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6783</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513117</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/01/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 01:50:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6783</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 01:51:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513117</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/01/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 01:50:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6783</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 01:51:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513117</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/01/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 01:50:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6783</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 01:52:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 01:50:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:57</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>381461</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Salmon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Wayne</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Robert Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/16/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>07/02/2023 01:47:23</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S455</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Salmon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Wayne</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Robert Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/16/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>S455</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/02/2023 01:47:23</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 01:52:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 01:52:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 01:50:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6783</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 01:50:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>