<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-034823</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/04/2023 11:49:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/04/2023 11:49:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/04/2023 11:46:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/04/2023 11:46:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Jaclyn Folk entered the barrack wishing to report a rape which occurred 15+ yrs ago.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 11:49:24</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 10:11:06</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>RAP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>602728</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 11:49:27</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 14:02:25</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>602728</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>145</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Sunset Ridge</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>McHenry</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21541</Zip5>
         <Zip4>1188</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-79.3377324</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.5584129</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/04/2023 11:49:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/04/2023 11:49:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/27/2023 10:12:27</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 11:49:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 16:27:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 10/4/2023, Jaclyn Folk, W/F, DOB 11/16/1987 responded to the McHenry Barrack to report an alleged rape which occurred fifteen or more years ago.  I was asked by the duty officer if I could speak with Ms. Folk concerning the allegations. Ms. Folk was taken to the McHenry Barrack conference room and she asked that I do not record our interview. She also demanded that I turn off my cell phone because she did not want anyone listening in on the conversation. I could tell Folk was paranoid and I calmed her down. I advised her I would not turn off my cell phone due to being on-call and I needed to record the interview for note taking purposes. I advised her the recording is not public information. Folk agreed to having the interview recorded and I immediately started recording.  Prior to starting the interview, Folk went into an explanation how she is no longer afraid of men and will not be put down by men telling her that she is not good enough. She continued on how she used to be the best female aviator for the FAA (Federal Aviation Administration) and she was terminated due to holding in secrets for the last fifteen years. She advised she is not an alcoholic nor is she on illicit drugs. However, she has recently been released from rehab and is working with a doctor that has prescribed every known medication for depression and anxiety disorder that exists (these were her own words). She stated her doctor told her to go home and rest for the next month.  Everytime I would ask her about being an airline pilot, she would divert to another subject. She stated she was raped numerous times throughout her life. She stated many of the Captains within the airline industry had raped her throughout her career, however, she did not wish to speak about those incidents.  Folk only wanted to speak of two incidents which occurred when she was approximately sixteen (16) years old. She stated the first incident occurred at Frostburg State University and she was drinking alcoholic beverages with some friends. She stated she became intoxicated and was eventually raped by a person named Kellen Baumgardner. She could not give any descriptive details other than it occurred in her best friends apartment.  The other incident occurred by the same individual located at an address on White Rock Road in Friendsville, Maryland. Folk stated she was raped after drinking alcoholic beverages with some friends and Baumgardner raped her while she was on her period. She once again could not provide any further details. She stated she knew Baumgardner from high school and was fed up with staying silent.  I asked Folk why she was coming forward now. Folk stated she received a text message from Baumgardner approximately two weeks ago. Baumgardner is apparently in some continuing education program with a mutual friend of Folk. She alleges the two people had been speaking and her name came up during the conversation. She advised that Baumgardner is a chemical engineer and started rattling off places he has been and names of relatives. I eventually advised Folk to stay on track and tell me information relating to the alleged rape.  Folk then makes mention of a friend she helped who was also raped when this person was a child. She mentioned no names but made statements that she helped this person come forward and this individual was able to take his godfather for all he had. I advised Folk this has nothing to do with this investigation. She felt it was important because it was a case which was also not reported for numerous years.  I was not sure if Folk wanted me to investigate this as a rape or if she was just looking to be heard and have the incident documented. I advised Folk that physical evidence was needed. She immediately gestured to her body with her hands and said, My body is the physical evidence. I advised her the difficulties with a case that is reported numerous years after the fact. I advised her its possible to attempt a controlled telephone call. I explained it to her and she got out of her chair and said she would go get her cell phone from the car and be right back. I left the recorder on as I exited the room and retrieved an MSP 177. The telephone call was attempted with negative results.  Folk stated she would like me to shut down her social security number because she believes someone is using it. I advised her to contact the Social Security Administration because I cannot have her SSN shut down. She then asked for a protective order against anyone with the last name Baumgardner. I advised her how to obtain a peace/protective order and explained she needed to be a little more narrow on the person she needs protected from. She stated she wants one against everyone with the last name Baumgardner in Garrett County. She also wanted me to guarantee her safety as she lives in and moves about Garrett County. I advised her that is impossible because people who have full-time body guards are not guaranteed to be safe. Folk stated she understood.  After listening to Folk for approximately one hour, I asked her again if she wanted me to make contact with Baumgardner. She asked that I contact him and tell him that Folk is okay and a grown woman that can hold her own and she is not afraid of men. I asked her again if this is all she wants as far as an investigation. She stated she would only like this to be put in a report so when she is cleared to get her job back as an airline pilot under the FAA, they will understand her PTSD.  I asked once again when was the last time she flew as an airplane. She stated, Let me give you his number. She provided Kellen Baumgardners telephone number and refused to answer any questions pertaining to her former career as a pilot.  I advised Folk I would obtain a case number for her records and she asked me if I could look up her DUI case number from a couple of months ago. I advised her I was only dealing with the issue at hand and I was not looking up her case number for the recent DUI.  As I was asking for a case number to be generated, I was advised troopers have been at her address at least three or four times in the past week for check welfare and for an emergency petition. These incidents will be looked into, further.  At this time, Folk stated she is coming back to the McHenry Barrack tomorrow to meet me because she has documentation. I asked her if it pertains to the allegations and she said she would just like to show me documentation which could help clarify a few things. She will be arriving around 0930 on October 5, 2023.  OCTOBER 5, 2023  At approximately 0937 hours, Ms. Folk responded to the McHenry Barracks. I recorded my interaction with her on my audio recorder.  I met Folk in the barrack lobby and sat her down in the barrack conference room. She did not have any details or information to provide. She stated she was going home to rest and would like me to keep the investigation open. She stated she would like to meet with me again next Wednesday. I advised her I would not be available. She then asked to meet with someone I trust. I explained to her, its best to continue the investigation with one investigator since I already know the story she is bringing forward. Folk stated she would send me her schedule and continue this after a couple of weeks. She further explained this will give her the opportunity to uncover information from the past that could assist in this investigation.  OCTOBER 25, 2023  At approximately 0930 hours, Ms. Folk came to the McHenry Barrack for a scheduled interview. This interaction was recorded with an audio reorder and my issued Axon body camera.  Folk stated she would like for the investigation to stop due to her being able to move on with her life. She stated she will not obtain a peace order against Kellen Baumgardner and will continue working with her therapist concerning what took place numerous years ago.  I advised Folk the case would be closed and could be reopened if she desired to pursue this incident any further. The interview ended and Folk exited the barrack.  At this time, this case will be closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 14:03:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5177</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/26/2023 08:46:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ross</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3572</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Romanchak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5177</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524281</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1102</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/04/2023 11:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1102</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/25/2023 15:08:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5177</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/25/2023 15:08:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 14:05:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/25/2023 15:09:20</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>314349</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Folk</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jaclyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Deanne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/16/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.17213406E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>07/21/2021 11:07:22</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J245</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Folk</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jaclyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Deanne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/16/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.17213406E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>F420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J245</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/21/2021 11:07:22</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>145</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sunset Ridge</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>McHenry</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21541</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1188</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.3377324</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.5584129</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>697</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5580</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/21/2021 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/25/2023 15:09:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 14:11:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 14:11:38</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389547</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Baumgardner</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kellen</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/04/2023 14:08:58</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B526</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K450</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Baumgardner</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kellen</FirstName>
               <SLastName>B526</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K450</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/04/2023 14:08:58</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>616</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2259</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/04/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 14:11:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>