<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-035063</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40I</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/06/2023 11:01:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/06/2023 11:01:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/06/2023 11:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/06/2023 11:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Possession CDS / Not marijuana</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 11:01:54</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 12:55:56</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>549937</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 11:01:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 11:01:55</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>549937</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>10534</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Baltimore National</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PIKE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Myersville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.576807</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.521082</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/06/2023 11:01:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/06/2023 11:01:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40I</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>01/03/2024 12:54:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 11:01:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 12:54:57</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> On 10/6/2023 at approximately 0630 hours, members of the Frederick HIDTA, Western Region Investigations and the Western Region Gun Unit executed a search and seizure warrant at 10534 Baltimore National Pike, Myersville Maryland. Entry was made without incident of injury and two occupants were located inside the residence. The main target of the investigation was identified as Brian Kelly Motz. Cpl. Mills with the Western Region Investigations, authored the search warrant forevidence related to fraud and crimes of theft.  Motz was interviewed by Cpl. Mills and Motz requested to speak to his lawyer before answering any further questions. During the search of the residence Motz was asked where the keys for his car were due to the fact that the car was locked inside the garage. Motz advised, the car keys were in his bag that was on the kitchen counter. Trooper Potivn, held up a dark-colored bag that looked like a file / computer bag and asked this one. Motz said, yes that was the bag confirming the bag that Trooper Potvin was holding.     Located inside the bag were the keys to the BMW that Motz owns. Also located within the bag was a clear plastic bag containing two smaller plastic bags. Those two bags contained a white powder that was consistent with cocaine. Due to M/Tpr. Hoods training and experience as a Maryland State Trooper he was able to identify the substance as suspected cocaine. Due to Motz wanting to speak to his lawyer no questions were asked of Motz pertaining to the suspected cocaine. The cocaine was seized and transported to the Frederick State Police Barracks for processing. The total weight of the suspected cocaine was 8.7 grams.  M/Tpr. Hood was contacted later on 10/6/2023 by Motzs attorney and asked to speak to M/Tpr. Hood about the suspected cocaine. M/Tpr. Hood advised the attorney that it would be best to set a time for a meeting regarding Motzs CDS related charges.  M/Tpr. Hood as not heard anything from Motz or his attorney regarding the meeting as of October 13th 2023  All the above events occurred in Frederick County Maryland.  I request this case remain open pending charges.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/11/2023 10:35:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 12:53:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40I</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hood</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daryl</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5345</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>