<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-017484</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/17/2023 03:16:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/17/2023 03:16:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/17/2023 02:32:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/17/2023 02:32:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>05/17/2023 07:11:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>DUI# 23-061 James Albert Watson 3rd. DOB: 12/24/1979 White/Male was involved in a motor vehicle collision with a parked vehicle on southbound interstate 95 north of Maryland Route 32 right shoulder.Watson 3rd was arrested for DUI, second offense.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 03:16:19</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5372</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/28/2023 13:22:54</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>southbound 95 n/o MD Route 32</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>699157</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 03:16:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 17:42:04</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>699157</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>I-95 N/O MD32</StreetName>
         <City>Jessup</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20794</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>S</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-76.81791</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.16179</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/17/2023 03:16:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/17/2023 03:16:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>50</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 10:49:30</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 03:16:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 19:56:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI# 23-061 MSP marked Unit A-4 is equipped with an in-car camera and body camera recording device. Interactions/Interviews were captured/recorded.  Defendant: James Albert Watson 3rd Date of Birth: 12/24/1973  Date of Arrest: 05/17/2023 Times of Arrest: 0315 DL: W-325-367-041-974 DUI #: 23-061 2nd DUI Offense  *********Related reports ACRS: 23-MSP-017484 **********  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: * Graduated with distinction from the University of Maryland Institute of Advanced Law Enforcement Studies, DUI Institute, Session XIII. I am trained by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration to administer standardized field sobriety tests. I am a certified Radar and Lidar operator. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On Wednesday, May 17, 2023 at approximately 0233 hours, I, STPR. Dugue #5832 with the Maryland State Police, currently assigned to the Waterloo barrack was dispatched to southbound Interstate 95, north of Maryland Route 32 in Columbia, Howard County, Maryland for a multiple vehicle collision.   Upon my arrival, I observed on the right shoulder of the highway, a parked White GMC Sienna pickup with no registration plate that was attached to U-Haul flat bed with Kansas registration plates, 650572 and the U-Haul was towing a Honda CR-V. I further observed, approximately 150 feet south of my location a black Dodge Ram pickup with a Maryland registration plate, 3EK2313 against the guardrail with severe front end damage. The combination airbags of the Dodge Ram were deployed. I observed the flat bed U-Haul and the blue Honda CR-V unattended with severe rear end and left side damage.   Howard County EMS and Fire Department were already on scene and lane number four was closed. Upon my initial investigation on scene, I found out that the black Dodge Ram was traveling on southbound Interstate 95, north of Maryland Route 32 and failed to drive within the single lane of traffic, crossed onto the right shoulder of the highway and struck the three vehicles that were parked on the right shoulder.  I further observed a Caucasian male that was collecting personal items inside the Dodge Ramp pickup.   Howard County EMS personnel made contact with the male and on his well-being. At approximately 0310 hours, the Caucasian male signed a waiver and refused to be transported to the hospital, Howard County EMS run #23-15340.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I contacted the caucasian male, and identified him by his Maryland drivers license as James Albert Watson 3rd, DOB: 12/24/1973 W/M. I introduced myself and explained to him that I was there for the collision investigation. Watson 3rd stated that he was the driver of the Dodge Ram pickup. I asked what happened. Watson 3rd immediately stated that while he was traveling in lane number four, he saw three vehicles that were parked in traffic lanes, he had nowhere to go, and collided with the vehicles. At that point, I walked toward the vehicles that were parked, and I clearly showed Watson 3rd the vehicles were not parked in lanes of traffic. The vehicles were clearly inside the white line of the right shoulder area. I further advised him these vehicles had been parked there for several hours before he collided with them. While I was speaking with Watson 3rd, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I observed Watson 3rd to have glassy and bloodshot eyes. Watson 3rd s speech was slurred.  I asked Watson 3rd if he consumed any alcoholic beverages earlier. Watson 3rd stated he had some drinks around 10 PM the night before. I asked him what kind of drinks that he had consumed. Watson 3rd stated he had two shots of Makers Mark whiskey. Iasked Watson 3rd tosubmit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, to which he consented.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of southbound Interstate 95, north of Maryland Route 32 on the right shoulder. The surface was dryand free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 74 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of patrol vehicles headlights, spotlight, and my flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three phases of the tests.Watson 3rdwas wearing a black sweater and a blue pair of jeans. I asked the following questions:  Medical Conditions - No Injuries  No Medication No   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS(6/6 clues observed) 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes  WALK AND TURN( 4/8) Watson 3rd was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in the position until told to begin. Watson 3rd was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Watson 3rd was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Watson 3rd was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Watson 3rd was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Watson 3rd was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, touch heel to toe on every step, and count each step out loud. I asked if he understood the test, and he stated, Yes.  Instructional Stage: 1.) Lost balance  feet broke apart on one (1) occasionand remained with both feet next to each other.  Walking Stage (1st Nine): 1.) Missed heel to toe by more than 1/2 inch on step number 2. 2.) Stops walking- Watson 3rd stopped walking on step number two. 3.) Actual Step Taken- Watson 3rd took 8 steps instead the nine steps he was instructed to take.  Turn: No Clues   Walking Stage (2nd Nine) 1.) Missed heel to toe by more than 1/2 inch on step number 8.  ONE LEG STAND(3 of 4 clues were observed) Prior to performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Watson 3rd was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Watson 3rdwas asked if he understood the test and instructions to which he stated, Yes. Watson 3rddecided to raise his right foot.  Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10: No clues   Seconds 10-20: Watson 3rd put his foot down on count 1013. Watson 3rd swayed on count 1018.  Watson 3rd used both arms away from his body more than 6 inches for balance on count 1018  Seconds 21-30: No clues  PRELIMINARYBREATHTEST: Iexplained and offered Watson 3rda preliminary breath test to which Watson 3rd refused.  ARREST:  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Watson 3rd was driving a motor vehicle under the influenceof alcohol:  * Vehicle damage/collision against parked vehicles  * Eyes glassy and bloodshot *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating Watson 3rddrivers breath and person. * Slurred speech * Repeated instructions needed * Observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests  At approximately 0315 hours, Watson 3rd was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol and transported to the MSP Waterloo barracks for further processing. I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Watson 3rd beginning with his arrest. A preliminary search of Watson 3rd was conducted on scene and it revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. I observed Watson 3rd from the time of arrest until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. Also, no oral piercings were observed.  Upon arrival at the barrack, at approximately 0350 hours, I played audibly the DR-15 Advise of Rights on the MVA website through my in-car computer. Watson 3rdagreed to submit to the breath test.The test was administered by Sgt. Clark ID# 5290. The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of.17 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath approximately 0406 hours. Watson 3rd was charged accordingly, Watson 3rd Maryland drivers license was confiscated to be returned to the Motor Vehicle Administration. Watson 3rdwas laterreleased to his wife from the barracks without incident.  2nd DUI offense  Assist Trooper: TFC Shiveler and Sgt Clark.  Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Howard County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/26/2023 11:00:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 18:30:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shiveler</LastName>
            <FirstName>David </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6683</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dull</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6466</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>DuGue</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jose</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5832</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506911</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/17/2023 02:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 09:10:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 17:22:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506911</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/17/2023 02:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/04/2023 21:42:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 17:21:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506911</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/17/2023 02:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/04/2023 21:43:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 17:22:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506911</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/17/2023 02:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/04/2023 21:45:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 17:24:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506911</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/17/2023 02:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/04/2023 21:46:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 17:44:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506911</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/17/2023 02:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/04/2023 21:47:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 17:24:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>48</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>C</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 09:23:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377515</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Watson</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/24/1974 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>05/20/2023 09:22:03</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W325</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Watson</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/24/1974 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>W325</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/20/2023 09:22:03</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>367</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4586</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 22:39:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 22:39:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 22:39:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 22:39:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 18:13:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>381044</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cantoral duarte</LastName>
               <FirstName>Elmar de jesus</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/20/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/27/2023 18:12:39</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E456</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cantoral duarte</LastName>
               <FirstName>Elmar de jesus</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/20/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E456</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/27/2023 18:12:39</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>277</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8748</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 18:13:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/04/2023 21:39:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/04/2023 21:39:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154560</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>VI</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/26/2023 15:58:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/26/2023 15:58:08</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>UU</VIN>
         <VehicleStyleCode>FB</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TR</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>KY</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>650572</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleValue>5000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154559</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AC</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 18:14:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 18:14:38</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JHLRE48717C093222</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2007</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CR-V</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4H</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>N/A</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleValue>5000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154596</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AC</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 18:17:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 18:17:00</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3GTU2UEC0EG317804</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SRA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>PK</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4eb1395</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>4</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleValue>5000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153207</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 18:28:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 18:28:09</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C6SRFHT7LN357075</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>R15</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>PK</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3EK2313</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleValue>1500</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/27/2023 18:41:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/27/2023 18:41:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>50</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 10:49:30</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 18:41:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 19:56:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attached Approved ACRS report</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5832</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 18:42:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5832</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 18:42:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dull</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6466</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>DuGue</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jose</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5832</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>