<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-021306</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/14/2023 08:13:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/14/2023 08:13:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/14/2023 07:34:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/14/2023 07:34:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect was alleged to have pointed a handgun at the victim during a road rage incident. The handgun was recovered and the suspect was transported to the St. Mary's County Detention Center.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 08:13:34</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2362</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/01/2023 12:39:35</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>THREE NOTCH RD/ PEGG RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>141098</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 08:13:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/21/2023 14:47:05</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>141098</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Three Notch</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Lexington Park</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.51992000000007</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.303790037594545</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>RCAC 5</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>22000-22126 THREE NOTCH RD / 22146-22149 PEGG RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/14/2023 08:13:31</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/14/2023 08:13:31</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>Y</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/22/2023 17:26:15</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 08:13:35</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2362</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/01/2023 12:39:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-car camera operational, T-25. BWC utilized.  SCENE PROCESSING:  I responded to a call for a traffic complaint involving a firearm. Both vehicles stopped in separate parking lots until police arrived. The investigation revealed the suspect pointed a firearm at the victim while they were traveling on the roadway. The suspect stated there was a firearm in the vehicle. The firearm, magazine, ammunition, and holster located during the investigation were packaged in accordance with MSP policy and held at the MSP Leonardtown Barrack as evidence.   Photographs of the firearm, magazine, ammunition, and holster were taken. All pictures have been attached to this report and uploaded to Veri-Pic. The Maryland Gun Center was contacted and a copy of their report is attached to this report.   PHYSICAL EVIDENCE:  The firearm, magazines, and ammunition were captured on Property Record P-340306. A MSP Form 67, Chain of Custody/Lab, and a MSP form 63, Property Record, were completed and attached to the weapons packaging. One Gun Box containing the following:   Item A: One (1) Black handgun, Glock 43x Serial Number: BSRX030  Item B: One (1) black handgun magazine, 9mm  Item C: Eight (8) rounds of 9mm ammunition   A MSP Form 67, Chain of Custody/Lab, was completed and attached to this report for the holster. Evidence Bag containing the following:    Item A: One (1) Black Warriorland gun holster   A MSP Form 67, Chain of Custody/Lab, was completed and attached to this report for the flash drive. Evidene Bag Containing the following:    "&gt;Item A: One (1) Black SanDisk flash drive containing seven (7) 9-1-1 audio clips   The following has been attached to this report.    One (1) Maryland Gun Center Report  Seven (7) digital photographs  One (1) MSP Form 76 Witness Statement  One (1) Maryland State Police OTS Firearms Test Fire Certificate  NARRATIVE:  On June 14, 2023 at approximately 0734 hours, I, Tpr. Pettyjohn #7329 was dispatched to the area of Maryland Route 235 (Three Notch Road) at Macarthur Boulevard, California, St. Marys County, Maryland for a traffic complaint involving a gun. The victim called 9-1-1 and reported the suspect was hitting his brakes and pointed a gun at her multiple times. The suspect called 9-1-1 as well, to report the victim was trying to run him off the road and yelling unknown things at him.  At approximately 0737 hours, I arrived at the Shell gas station located at 22141 Three Notch Road, Lexington Park, St. Marys County, Maryland 20653 and met with the victim Rasheeha Octavia Butler (B/F DOB: 10/17/1998). Butler was identified by her MVA photograph.  At the same time the suspect Michael Lopez Rodriguez (H/M DOB: 07/10/1975) called 9-1-1 and reported the incident. Deputys from the St. Marys County Sheriffs Office stopped out with Rodriguez at the Bank of America located at 21800 N Shangri La Dr Unit 22, Lexington Park, St. Marys County, Maryland 20653. Rodriguez was identified by his MVA photograph.  I asked Butler what happened and she said while traveling on Maryland Route 235 (Three Notch Road) passing MacArthur Boulevard a black Audi displaying Maryland registration 7DT1193 brake checked her. Butler stated she went to pass the vehicle on the left and got in front of the vehicle. Butler stated when she went to pass the vehicle Rodriguez pulled out a small black handgun and pointed it at her. Butler stated Rodriguez continued to point the gun at her when she moved in front of his vehicle. Butler stated she then moved over to the passenger side of Roriguezs vehicle. Butler advised Rodriguez pointed the gun at her and waved it around in the car. Butler stated she then turned into the Shell to avoid Rodriguez because she feared for her life. I asked Butler what the firearm looked like and she stated It looks like yours but smaller. It should be noted Butler was referring to my agency issued firearm which is a black Glock 17. I asked Butler what hand Rodriguez had the firearm in and she stated right. Butler showed me a picture she took of Rodriguez sitting in his vehicle during the incident. In the picture Rodriguez was talking on a cellphone in his right hand and the window was not open. No weapons were observed in the picture. The picture was uploaded to this report. I asked Butler if she knew the person in the other vehicle, Butler stated shes never seen him before.    Tpr. Baden #7152 then asked Butler if she would be willing to complete a written statement, and she stated Yes. Butler completed a MSP Form 076, Written Statement and a copy of the form have been attached to this report.  Around the same time of the incident, Mathew Charles Ayre (W/M DOB:12/22/1986) called the barrack and stated he saw both vehicles driving aggressively but stated the silver Jeep was making more aggressive movements. Ayre stated the driver of the Audi was holding a black cell phone in his hand. Ayre saw no weapons and nothing thrown from the vehicle.    On June 19, 2023 at approximately 1600 hours I contacted Ayre to ask him questions about the incident. I asked Ayre what he saw, and he stated the driver of the Jeep was driving aggressive and seemed like she was trying to run the Audi off the road. Ayre stated it seemed like the Audi was trying to stay behind the Jeep and avoid the situation. I asked Ayre if he saw anything in the driver of the Audis hands and he stated he was not able to see inside the vehicle because the windows were tinted. I asked Ayre if he knew any of the individuals in the two vehicles and he stated he did not know either person.  I then arrived at the Bank of America to speak with Rodriquez and get his side of the story. I asked Rodriguez what happened. Rodriguez stated there was a silver Jeep passenger vehicle tailgating him while on Fairgrounds Road, Maryland Route 4, and Maryland Route 235. Rodriguez stated he hit his brakes to get the vehicle to back off. Rodriguez stated the vehicle then passed him and immediately cut him off slamming on the brakes. Rodriguez stated the vehicle hit the brakes 3 more times. Rodriguez stated he was afraid the driver of the vehicle would do something to injure him so he proceeded to retrieve his firearm from his safe underneath the passenger seat with his right hand. Rodriguez stated the vehicle drove beside the right side of his car and rolled the driver side window down and began yelling at him. Rodriguez stated he did not hear what was said due to his window being closed and being on the phone. I asked Rodriguez how Butler would have seen the firearm. Rodriguez stated when he was getting his firearm from the safe, he went to put his hands back on the steering wheel with the firearm in his right hand, and had the gun pointed at the ceiling of the car while in the holster. Rodriguez stated he then proceeded to move the firearm onto the seat beside his right leg. Rodriguez sat in the car and acted out how he grabbed the gun out of the safe and transitioned the gun to the steering wheel and to his right leg. I asked Rodriguez if he took the gun out of the holster and he stated it stayed in the holster the whole time.    I asked Rodriguez where the firearm was inside the vehicle and he stated it was in the safe under the passenger seat. Rodriguez stated I could use the key fob he provided to open the safe. A black Glock 43x handgun (Serial #BSRX030) was recovered from Rodriguezs vehicle. The handgun was secured in the holster in a locked safe under the passenger side seat. The handgun was loaded with eight rounds (8) with one in the chamber. The handgun was transported back to the Leonardtown Barrack for processing.  It should be noted Rodriguez has a valid handgun permit through Maryland (Permit #22HGP105904).  At approximately 0826 hours, Rodriguez was read his Miranda Rights and decided to invoke his rights.    At approximately 0835 hours, I placed Rodriguez under arrest for First Degree Assault, Second Degree Assault, and Firearm Use in a Felony/Violent Crime. Rodriguez was transported to the St. Marys County Detention Center where he was held pending a hearing with the District Court Commissioner. Rodriguez did not speak about the incident in the car and kept apologizing. Rodriguez stated, Im so confused right now, I just ended my military career, I thought was nothing, defending myself. Rodriguez also stated,  I was afraid for my life and was defending myself. As we were pulling into the sallyport of the detention center Rodriguez stated, Im so sorry officer. It should be noted as I well leaving the detention center Rodriquez apologized again.    On June 14, 2023 at approximately 0927 hours, the Maryland Gun Center was contacted. A check through MAFSS showed there were no firearms registered to Rodriguez.   On June 14, 2023 at approximately 1300 hours, S/T DiToto #5416, test fired the weapon seized during this investigation. The test fire occurred at the Leonardtown Barrack in the presence of Tpr. Pettyjohn #7329. The firearm is operable and capable of being fired. The test shots have been forwarded to the Maryland State Police Firearm/Toolmark Unit for entry and/or storage in the National Integrated Ballistic Information Network (NIBIN).    On June 21, 2023 I received seven (7) audio clips of 9-1-1 calls that were made by Rodriguez and Butler. The audio clips were downloaded on a flash drive and submitted as evidence.    On the audio clip from June 14, 2023 at approximally 0729 hours Butler stated when she called 9-1-1, I have a car a BMW or an Audi pulling a gun on me in the road, he has a gun and hes pulling it out on me he just showed it in the car. Butler also stated, He has a navy tag I think hes in the navy, but he did pull a gun on me. The dispatcher asked for a description of the vehicle and Butler stated, Now he wont get next to me, hes a white male about 40 years old, its an Audi car its an A6, Im getting a picture now.    At approximally 0731 hours, Butler stated Hes on the phone though, Ill get a picture. The dispatcher asked Butler if she was able to get herself to safety and Butler stated Im safe, hes not going to pull the trigger, hes not stupid. Butler also stated, Think your going to scare someone with a fucking gun, you stupid bitch.    At approximately 0732 hours Butler stated, The tag is 7DT1193, I am by the Shell, and he is still going straight, I am getting away from him, I just had to get a picture.    At approximally 0733 hours the dispatcher asked Butler to describe the weapon and Butler stated, It was like a Glock, it was a handheld one, it was black.    On June 14, 2023 at approximally 0731 hours Rodriguez called 9-1-1 and stated, Im on the road Route 235 towards PAX River Naval Air Station, I have a silver Jeep Cherokee that is trying to run me of the road, it is a black female, and shes acting like a maniac. Rodriguez also stated, She has a camera on my face and has an attitude like she wants to kill me. The dispatcher asked for the tag number and and he stated, Her tag number is 5FA6062, I am in a black Audi A6. The dispatcher asked what the other vehicle was doing to Rodriguez and he stated,  Shes been tailgating me since Fairgrounds Rd and Route 4 and when we got on Route 235 I was trying to get out of her way and she completely sped up and slammed on her breaks in front of me, I am afraid of what this woman is going to do to me. Rodriguez also stated, I am licensed concealed carry civilian, and I have my weapon with me right now, Im scared for my life right now.    All above events occurred in St. Marys County Maryland </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 15:36:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7329</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 17:18:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Baden</LastName>
            <FirstName>Craig</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7152</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oles</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5857</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pettyjohn</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7329</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510741</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1420</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/14/2023 07:34:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1420</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 15:07:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7329</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/14/2023 15:07:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510741</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/14/2023 07:34:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 15:09:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7329</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/14/2023 15:09:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510741</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 5299</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/14/2023 07:34:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 5299</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 15:11:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7329</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/14/2023 15:11:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 15:13:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:04</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>149011</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>BUTLER</LastName>
               <FirstName>Rasheeha</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Octavia</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/17/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/02/2017 06:11:58</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B346</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>BUTLER</LastName>
               <FirstName>Rasheeha</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Octavia</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/17/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B346</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/02/2017 06:11:58</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>14656</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Oaks</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Charlotte Hall</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20622</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.80176</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.502589</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>542</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4890</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/02/2017 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/21/2023 15:02:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/21/2023 15:02:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>47</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 15:19:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:20</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>379835</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Rodriguez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lopez</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/10/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/14/2023 15:18:26</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R362</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Rodriguez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lopez</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/10/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R362</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/14/2023 15:18:26</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>23674</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Jm Gough</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Leonardtown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20650</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3786</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.671343</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.31841</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/21/2023 15:02:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/21/2023 15:02:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/21/2023 15:02:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>36</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 16:25:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>380301</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ayre</LastName>
               <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/22/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/19/2023 16:25:29</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ayre</LastName>
               <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/22/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>A600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/19/2023 16:25:29</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>27745</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Old Village</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Mechanicsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20659</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.729886</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.435521</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>526</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0771</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/21/2023 14:48:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 15:11:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7329</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/14/2023 15:11:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154133</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/21/2023 14:54:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7329</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/21/2023 14:54:29</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WAUGFAFC3GN086550</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2016</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>AUDI</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>A6</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7DT1193</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154134</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>VI</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/21/2023 14:54:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7329</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/21/2023 14:54:48</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C4PJLDB8LD614462</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CHK</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5FA6062</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 15:31:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7329</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/21/2023 14:52:44</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Black Glock 43x</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>MSPPI</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <SerialNumber>BSRX030</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>250430</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>BLK</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>Glock</Make>
         <Model>43x</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 15:33:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7329</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/14/2023 15:33:34</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>8 rounds of 9mm Ammunition</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>424</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>250431</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>8</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 15:34:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7329</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/14/2023 15:34:49</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One black 9mm magazine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>611</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>250432</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>Glock</Make>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7329</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/14/2023 15:35:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7329</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/14/2023 15:35:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One black gun holster</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>505</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>250433</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>Warriorland</Make>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/28/2023 10:45:43</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/28/2023 10:45:43</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>Y</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/28/2023 12:30:41</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP2362</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 10:45:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2362</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/01/2023 12:39:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Narrative:  On 7/25/2023 the suspect,Michael Lopez-Rodriguez, H/M, DOB-7/10/75 contacted the Leonardtown Barrack to request the firearm that was seized from the initial incident be returned to him. On 7/26/2023 I conducted a check ofsecure case search. While reviewing, I observed that all three charges initially filed against Lopez-Rodriguez on 6/14/2023 were entered as Nolle Prosequi. On 7/27/2023, I responded to the States Attorneys Office (District Court) to check if the case was being transferred to the Circuit Court for felony prosecution. I was advised the case was not being transferred, and its final disposition was made in the District Court. I then contacted Christina Robey, the criminal assistant to ASA J. Maylor (Circuit Court) regarding this case via telephone. Robey advised the entire case file to include the B.W.C footage was reviewed by ASA Maylor. After the review, ASA Maylor determined that no charges should be pursued against Lopez-Rodriguez. Robey advised since no further action was occurring, the firearm could be released back to Lopez-Rodriguez.  After obtaining that information, I completed the Gun Center Request Form regarding a prohibited check for Lopez-Rodriguez. The prohibited checked was conducted by Investigator J. Reininger # 2663 (MDGC #-202305488). The check revealed that Lopez-Rodriguez was NOT prohibited from possessing any firearms. On 7/27/2023 at approximately 1300 hours, I contacted Lopez-Rodriguez via telephone to advise him I could return his firearm to him. Lopez-Rodriguez responded to the Leonardtown Barrack on 7/27/2023 at 1445 hours. Upon his arrival, I returned Items A-C(Firearm, Magazine, Rounds) from the attached PH # P-340306. I also released Item A- holster from a separate, related MSP Form # 67, Chain of Custody. Lopez-Rodriguez signed all and received copies of both MSP Forms # 67 and the Property Record. Lopez-Rodriguez advised since his initial arrest, he received a letter form the Licensing Division advising his wear and carry permit has been revoked. Lopz-Rodriguez advised since receiving that letter he has mailed his permit back to the Licensing Division. The firearm and ammunition were placed into a locked box/safe prior to Lopez Rodriguez departing from the Leonardtown Barrack.  No further action.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP2362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 10:47:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP2362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/28/2023 11:14:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5920</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Murphy</LastName>
            <FirstName>Shawn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2362</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>