<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-035117</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/06/2023 18:18:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/06/2023 18:18:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/06/2023 17:52:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/06/2023 17:52:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI ARREST OF OSVALDO CARDONA CORTEZ</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 18:18:26</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6047</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/08/2023 04:47:23</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>709195</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 18:18:27</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:20:35</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>709195</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Meteor</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Cambridge</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21613</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>HWY</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.065709</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.563869</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/06/2023 18:18:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/06/2023 18:18:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/08/2023 04:47:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 18:18:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 16:27:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>CASE NUMBER: 23-MSP-035117 INVESTIGATING TROOPER: Trooper First Class M. Mowbray #7119 NATURE OF CALL: Traffic Stop, DWI SCENE PROCESSING: Scene processing was conducted with the following results;   Intox EC/IR Information Sheet  MSP Form 32 - Alcohol Information Report  DR-15  Advice of Rights (Alcohol Concentration Test)  DR-15A  Officers Certification and Order of Suspension  Intox EC/IR Test Record Print Out  MSP Form 102  PBT Advice of Rights  MVA Print-Out  Copy of all Citations  Photocopy of Drivers Identification  One (1) digital photograph of Osvaldo Cardona Cortez  INCIDENT FOOTAGE: FOOTAGE LABELED 23-MSP-035117 ON AXON EVIDENCE  INCIDENT CAPTURED BY A MOBILE VIDEO RECORDER I-12 EQUIPPED WITH AN MVR I-12 Mobile Video Recorder (Outward Facing): partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=e54d5c2dec1a46b89c077f6db96c84dfpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 I-12 Mobile Video Recorder (Inward Facing): partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=d9fec060d3634d60b04809ea683a7052partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=43a297fa4e3646ff93fbfe8c0e1f3999partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  INCIDENT CAPTURED WITH BODY WORN CAMERA TFC M. Mowbray #7119: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=c34f2c09644d482e900ce5b447692a47partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  CAMERA SYSTEM / CAD SYSTEM The camera system is manufactured by Axon. The in-car; outward facing camera is activated when the emergency lights are activated in the patrol car or if manually activated by the user. The camera will go back in time and start the recording thirty (30) seconds before the camera is activated. This event is called a 30 second pre-record. The body worn camera (BWC); attached to the front of the Trooper, is also activated when the emergency lights are activated or manually by its user. The camera will record the previous sixty (60) seconds prior to the camera activation. The camera system does not have a date and time stamp on the video itself. The system records the date and time in the metadata. The time only records the hour and minute when the camera starts the recording. Therefore, the timeline below will start with a time that was recorded from the cameras metadata and then show the duration of the video. The in-car camera and body worn camera footage remains the best depiction of the events surrounding the traffic stop. However, in order to obtain an exact time of a specific event, the reader will have to add the length of duration from the start of the video that was recorded in the metadata. Although times are recorded by other means such as the Delta Plus system that prints a time stamp on the warning, citation or safety equipment repair order this time is only when the traffic enforcement button is activated by the Trooper. This date/time is usually started shortly after making contact with a violator and upon return to the patrol vehicle. Other programs such as Caliber RMS incident and CAD reports will show a timestamp, but this time depends on when the Police Communications Operator or Trooper activates the incident within the CAD system. The two aforementioned examples of the recording of time will almost always be different than the in-car camera system due to all of the systems utilizing different internal clocks.  DUI FOLDER NUMBER: 23-58-207 DEFENDANT:  Osvaldo Cardona Cortez DOB: 12/20/1983 8210 New Hampshire Avenue, Apartment 202, Silver Spring, Montgomery County, Maryland 20903 SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER: YES DATE OF ARREST: 10/06/2023 TIME OF ARREST: 1818 hours  CERTIFICATIONS AND TRAINING:    Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration on May 30, 2019  Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) on January 30, 2020  Trained and certified to operate the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) through the Maryland State Police  I am trained in the detection and recognition of controlled dangerous substances through the Maryland State Police Academy  Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police  Trained and certified to operate Maryland Coordination and Analysis Center License Plate Readers since August 2019  Maryland State Police Conducting the Complete Traffic Stop: Criminal Interdiction Training  Trained in Advanced Collision Investigations by the Maryland State Police  Attended and completed the Maryland State Police Cannabis Impairment Detection Workshop  ASSIGNMENT: On Friday, October 6, 2023, I, Trooper First Class M. Mowbray #7119, of the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack, was assigned to road patrol duties in Dorchester County, Maryland. The Maryland State Easton Barrack is responsible for enforcing and investigating all criminal and traffic related crime within Dorchester, Talbot and Caroline counties. My duties include but are not limited to: enforcing the criminal and motor vehicle laws of the State of Maryland, issuing traffic citations and warnings, investigating traffic accidents, investigating and completing criminal investigations, interviewing witnesses, victims and suspects and writing field reports.   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On October 6, 2023, at approximately 1740 hours the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack Duty Officer relayed a be-on-the-lookout, or BOLO, for a white work van traveling westbound on U.S. Route 50 (Ocean Gateway) in the area of Vienna driving erratically.  At approximately 1750 hours I was on patrol operating my unmarked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle I-12; a 2022 Ford Explorer, traveling westbound on U.S. Route 50 near the intersection of Woods Road. At that time I observed a white 2014 Ford E-350 bearing Maryland registration 7FA5318 traveling westbound directly in front of me in lane one. As the Ford approached the intersection of Woods Road I observed it to unsafely change from lane one to lane two, causing a white tow truck to have to apply its brakes to allow for a safe following distance. I then observed the Ford cross from lane two to lane three by over a tires width then drift back into lane two as it passed the intersection of Woods Road. As I continued to follow the Ford, I observed it to, again, drift from lane two to lane three by over a tires width then drift back into lane two as it passed the Cambridge Marketplace on two separate occasions. As the Ford approached the intersection of Crusader Road, I observed it to drift from lane two to lane three by a tires width, failing to maintain its lane on a third occasion. After the Ford passed the intersection of Crusader Road I observed it to drive between lane two and lane three for what I could estimate as 100 feet before positioning itself in lane three. I then immediately initiated a lawful traffic stop of the vehicle by activating my emergency equipment which consists of red, blue, and white strobe lights and siren. The Ford continued westbound drifting into a standing concrete curb as it slowed at the intersection of Meteor Avenue. The Ford then made a right turn onto Meteor Avenue driving directly into oncoming traffic, failing to drive on the right half of roadway when required. The vehicle that was stopped at the red light at the intersection of Meteor Avenue and U.S. Route 50 was forced to reverse to avoid the Ford striking the front of it. The Ford then turned left into the parking lot of Exxon.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Ford from the drivers side and made contact with the driver; identified as Osvaldo Cardona Cortez (DOB: 12/20/1983) [hereinafter identified as Cortez], as he was seated in the drivers seat. I then introduced myself, advised the occupants that encounter was being audibly and visually recorded and advised the driver the reason for the traffic stop. I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I requested Cortez to provide me with his drivers license to which he replied; No have. Cortez then provided with his Guatemalan identification card. I observed Cortez eyes to be bloodshot and glassy, indicative of the consumption of alcoholic beverages. After Cortez provided me with a copy of his identification card I asked him if he had anything to drink prior to operating the motor vehicle to which he replied; Uh, no.  I then returned to my patrol vehicle and began conducting checks of Cortez and the Ford and relayed all pertinent information to the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack Emergency Dispatcher.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) I then returned to the Ford and requested the Cortez exit his vehicle and submit to the battery of Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, to which he complied. I then instructed Cortez to walk to the front of the Ford, to which he complied.  I then began Standardized Field Sobriety Tests; which yielded the following results;  The test was performed on the asphalt parking lot of Exxon. The surface was dry, level and free from any debris. Lighting consisted of daylight. My front red/blue lights were deactivated, and spotlight was pointed downward prior to the test. The weather was clear, day time, and 78 degrees Fahrenheit. Cortez was wearing tennis shoes, blue jean and a red t-shirt. As Cortez continued to speak with me, I detected the same odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person and noticed his speech to be slurred. I asked Cortez if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages prior to operating a motor vehicle to which he stated; I had one drink. I then inquired with Cortez to estimate the time he stopped consuming the beverages to which he stated; Five minutes ago. I then asked Cortez what type of beers he consumed to which he stated; Modelo.  When asked if Cortez had any physical disabilities, medical issues and/or on any medications that would prevent him from successfully completed the tests(eyes/balance), by asking the following medical screening questions; Q: Have you ever had a concussion? A: No. Q: Do you wear glasses or corrective lenses? A: No. Q: Are you on any current medications? A: Oh, yes, for diabetes, thats it.  Q: Have you ever had any surgeries? A: No. Q: Do you have any issues with your eyes that would affect your vision? A: My eyes, no, thats fine. Q: Do you have any issues that would affect your balance? A: Thats fine.   The first test administered was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test. I held an ink pen 12-15 inches in front of Cortez face and slightly above eye level. Cortez was checked to ensure that his eyes could track the pens movement equally. Additionally, I ensured there was no resting nystagmus and that his pupils were equal in size.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6 of 6 Clues) (EYE COLOR: Hazel) 1.) LACK OF SMOOTH PURSUIT - Yes - 1 clue 2.) DISTINCT AND SUSTAINED NYSTAGMUS AT MAXIMUM DEVIATION - Yes - 1 clue 3.) ONSET OF NYSTAGMUS PRIOR TO 45 DEGREES - Yes - 1 clue VERTICAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS - Not present  WALK AND TURN (4 of 8 Clues) Prior to Cortez performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Cortez was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Cortez was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in that position until instructed to begin. Cortez was advised to take nine (9) heel to toe steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Cortez was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, Cortez was advised to conduct a turn by taking a series of small steps in a counterclockwise manner keeping his lead foot planted. Cortez was explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Cortez was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed.   Instructional Stage: 1. CANNOT KEEP BALANCE  - Yes, Cortez lost balance during this stage - 1 clue 2. STARTS TOO SOON - No Walking Stage (1st Nine): 3. STOPS WALKING - No 4. MISSES HEEL TO TOE - No 5. STEPS OFF LINE - Yes, stepped off of the line on step(s) 3 - 1 clue 6. RAISES ARMS - Yes, on step(s) 7, 8 and 9 - 1 clue 7. ACTUAL NUMBER OF STEPS (9) - No, Cortez took 10 steps - 1 clue Walking Stage (2nd Nine): 3. STOPS WALKING - No 4. MISSES HEEL TO TOE - No 5. STEPS OFF LINE - Yes, stepped off line on step 1 -1 clue 6. RAISES ARMS - Yes, on step(s) 1, 2, 3 and 4 - 1 clue 7. ACTUAL NUMBER OF STEPS (9) - Yes Turn: 8. IMPROPER TURN - No, proper  ONE LEG STAND (3 of 4 Clues) Prior to Cortez performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Cortez was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot and to count out loud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two) and so on until instructed to stop.  Leg raised: Right 1. PUTS FOOT DOWN - Yes, Cortez put his foot down on during second(s) 0-10 - 1 clue 2. USES ARMS FOR BALANCE - Yes, Cortez used his arms for balance during second(s) 0-10, 11-20 and 21-30 - 1 clue 3. SWAYS - Yes, Cortez swayed during seconds 0-10, 11-20 and 21-30 - 1 clue 4. HOPS - No  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST RESULTS: The Preliminary Breath Test was offered to Steven at the scene. I advised Cortez of the State of Maryland Preliminary Breath Test Advisement of Rights prior to the test. Result: .16  METERS/NCIC CHECKS: After conducting checks of Cortez via the National Crime Information Center (NCIC) and Maryland Electronic Telecommunications Resource System (METERS); it was learned that Cortez did not possess a valid drivers license in the State of Maryland or any other State.  ARREST: Based on the following, I had reason to believe Steven was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol. - Driver failure to obey a properly placed traffic control device - Driver failing to maintain lane - Strong odor of alcohol emanating from his breath and person - Admission to consuming an alcoholic beverage prior to operating a motor vehicle - Eyes bloodshot and glassy - My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests  ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) CHARGES/RELEASE Due to Cortez poor performance on the battery of the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, he was placed under arrest at 1818 hours for driving under the influence. While seated in the passenger seat of my patrol vehicle, I played the DR-15 Advice of Rights (Alcohol Concentration Test) Spanish Audio provided by the State of Maryland at 1823 hours as I sat to his left. Cortez was also provided with a copy of the DR-15 to read along, which was placed in front of him. Cortez agreed to submit to the chemical alcohol concentration test at 1837 hours. Cortez mouth was checked at to ensure it was free from any foreign objects. Cortez was transported to the Cambridge Police Department; located at 8 Washington Street, Cambridge, Dorchester County, Maryland 21613 where he was processed per Maryland State Police policy. After the observation time was completed, Sergeant E. Howard #0317 of the Cambridge Police Department administered the Alcohol Concentration Test at 1905 hours, where an insufficient sample was obtained due to Cortezs lack of effort to provide one.  ALCOHOL CONCENTRATION TEST RESULT: INSUFFICIENT SAMPLE/REFUSED  Osvaldo Cardona Cortez was charged with the following offenses; TA 21-902 (A)(1)(I): DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL (5FT0V1Z) TA 21-902 (B)(1)(I): DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL (5FV0V1Z) TA 16-101 (A)(1): DRIVING MOTOR VEHICLE ON HIGHWAY WITHOUT REQUIRED LICENSE AND AUTHORIZATION (5FW0V1Z) TA 21-901.1 (A): RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OF PERSONS AND PROPERTY (5FX0V1Z) TA 21-901.1 (B): NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON (5FY0V1Z) TA 21-309 (B): DRIVER CHANGING LANES WHEN UNSAFE (5FZ0V1Z) TA 21-201 (A)(1): DRIVER FAILURE TO OBEY PROPERLY PLACED TRAFFIC CONTROL DEVICE INSTRUCTIONS (5G00V1Z) TA 21-301 (A): FAILURE TO DRIVE RIGHT OF CENTER (5G10V1Z) TA 16-112 (C): FAILURE OF INDIVIDUAL DRIVING ON HIGHWAY TO DISPLAY LICENSE TO UNIFORMED POLICE ON DEMAND (5G20V1Z)  Cortez was released to await a sober ride from the Maryland State Police Cambridge Detachment at 2127 hours.  Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Dorchester County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/15/2023 21:13:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/15/2023 21:36:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Del Vecchio</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mowbray</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7119</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524576</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/06/2023 17:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 5FT0V1Z</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524576</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/06/2023 17:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 5FV0V1Z</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524576</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/06/2023 17:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 5FW0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19731</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524576</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/06/2023 17:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 5FX0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524576</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/06/2023 17:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 5FY0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524576</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15558</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/06/2023 17:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 5FZ0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15558</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524576</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/06/2023 17:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 5G00V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524576</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/06/2023 17:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 5G10V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524576</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/06/2023 17:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 5G20V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:27:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:27:29</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389742</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cardona Cortez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Osvaldo</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/20/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/06/2023 18:55:38</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C635</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>O214</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cardona Cortez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Osvaldo</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/20/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C635</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>O214</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/06/2023 18:55:38</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>8210</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>New Hampshire</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>202</SubNumber>
               <City>Silver Spring</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20903</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.9871905</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.993718</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>619</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0268</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:27:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:27:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:27:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:27:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:24:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157805</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 20:28:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:28:17</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FTSE3EL2EDA73661</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>EC3</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7FA5318</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>