<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-024498</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/08/2023 21:18:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/08/2023 21:18:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/08/2023 21:10:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/08/2023 21:10:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 21:18:16</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/15/2023 03:14:57</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY/ RIDDLE LN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>587051</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 21:18:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/08/2023 21:18:17</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>587051</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.154957</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.340754</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 E/O GLEN RIDDLE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 /  RIDDLE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>50 WB/ RIDDLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 / RIDDLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11317-11541 OCEAN GTWY / 10001-10003 RIDDLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11316-11542 OCEAN GTWY / 10001-10003 RIDDLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11317-11541 OCEAN GTWY / 10005-10015 RIDDLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/08/2023 21:18:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/08/2023 21:18:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/15/2023 02:40:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 21:18:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:29:38</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Jason Robert Usilton Maryland SOUNDEX: U-2430373-745-164  Breath Test Result: .refused DUI Citation # 64B0T5Y DUI Tape #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-024498 (Axon View XL Software)  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. * Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.). * Completed and graduated from the DUI Institute. * Completed and graduated from the SFST Instructor school  NARRATIVE -PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION- On July 08, 2023 at approximately 2110 hours, I (TFC. S. Shubert #6944), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating unmarked MSP vehicle V-08 in the area of westbound US 50 east of Riddle Lane, Ocean City, Worcester County, Maryland.   At that time, I observed gold GMC Sierra bearing Maryland registration (803Z91) traveling westbound on US 50 directly in front of my patrol vehicle.    I observed the gold GMC Sierra to follow a dark blue Chevrolet Tahoe too closely. I observed the gold GMC to be less than half a car length behind the dark blue Chevrolet Tahoe.I also observed the gold Sierra passenger side tires cross the right merge lane dotted white line by approximately one foot and drift back into lane two. I observed the gold GMC Sierra make a lane change to travel westbound US 50 in lane one.   I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop. As soon as I activated my emergency equipment, I observed the driver side tires cross the left solid yellow shoulder line by approximately two feet. I observed the driver side tires touch the grass. This driving behavior continued for approximately 100 feet.    The gold GMC Sierra then drifted to the right shoulder of the roadway and abruptly stopped.   -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT- I exited my patrol vehicle and made contact with the driver via the driver side door. I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle. I informed the driver the reason for the traffic stop and requested his drivers license and registration card. The driver stated I didnt think so. I also observed the driver to display a dazed/expression look on his face. I also observed his speech to be slurred. The driver was identified through his Maryland drivers license as Jason Robert Usilton. Ustilton grabbed a Pepsi can and attempted to put a cuzzi on the can. However, had a difficult time doing so. Usilton also lit a new cigarette an attempt to eliminate the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Usiltons breath and person. Ustilton then stepped out of his vehicle an attempt to locate his drivers license. I asked Usilton to step back into the vehicle and Usilton stated Calm down you got me. Usilton then grabbed his flip flops and attempted to put them on. I observed Usilton to use his right hand against the door for balance when putting his flip flops on. Usilton then attempted to walk away stating I am going to deny everything. Your going to tow my vehicle and I am just going to walk away. I am going to deny everything. Tow my truck and I have nothing else to say.    -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING- STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs) Usilton refused to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety test.   -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING- ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Usilton was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.  * Slurred speech *lethargic movements  *Dazed/expression look on face *unable to maintain balance.   I placed Usilton under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 2114 hours on July 08, 2023. At this time, I observed Usilton to have a lit cigarette on his mouth. I asked Usilton to spit it out and Usilton refused. I had to remove the cigarette out of his mouth and put it on the ground. I then observed mints in his mouth. I asked two times for Usilton to spit out his mints. I visually inspected the inside of Usiltons mouth for any foreign objects and none were found. Usilton then stated Well I have 18 months hanging over my head so I dont care.   The Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack advised that Usiltons driving status is suspended and the registration on the gold GMC Sierra was also suspended.  ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) Usilton was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Usilton was given his Advice of Rights via the audio version of the DR-15 Form. Usilton then stated I am not signing anything or giving blood. Just take me to jail. Goodnight guys. I placed a copy of the DR-15 in front of Usilton. Once the DR-15 was completed being played Usilton stated that he understood his Advice of Rights. At approximately 2140 hours, refused to submit to the Intoximeter test.   Usilton started to place his feet on my dash and windshield. I advised for Usilton to put his feet down and Usilton stated Go ahead and beat me up. I need it. I asked five times for Usilton to put his feet down. Usilton stated Oh this bothers you doesnt it. I gently placed my hand on Usiltons legs and told him to put his legs on the floor. Usilton did as I requested. Usilton continued to state It bothers you when I do that Doesnt it. Just beat me up. Usilton then put his feet back on my dash. Due to Usilton not cooperating, I requested Ocean City Police Department in reference to a cage vehicle.   Ocean City Police Department arrived on scene and officer Laval #8613 and PSA Foy #9715 opened the door to the cage vehicle. Usilton entered the cage vehicle with no assistance. Officer Laval left the scene and was en route to the Ocean City Police Department where I would be processing Usilton. Officer Laval made a U-turn at the intersection of westbound US 50 at Riddle Lane. I observed Officer Laval make a wide and slow U-turn to travel on eastbound US 50. Once the OCPD cage vehicle proceeded to travel eastbound, I observed the patrol vehicle to drift to the right shoulder of the roadway and stop. I exited my patrol vehicle and observed Officer Laval open the rear door to the cage vehicle. Usilton then stated You were going 70 MPH and I fell off the seat. I was never restrained and I am going to sue every one of you. I am going to take all of your pensions. I asked Usilton if he needed EMS to respond and Usilton stated Yes. I asked Usilton if we could do anything to help and Usilton stated No. I need a Paramedic. Not you. I continued to detect the strong odor emitting from within the cage vehicle. I also observed Usiltons speech to be slurred. I asked Usilton where he was injured Usilton stated Well I hit my head so my head hurts, my neck hurts, my back hurts, my legs hurt. Well I guess I hurt everywhere. I observed no apparent signs of physical injury. I did observe Usilton hit his head once on the aluminum cage. Usilton was attempting to react what happened during his fall.  Ocean City EMS arrived on scene (EMS Run #23-02971). Usilton requested to be transported to the hospital. Ocean City EMS transported Usilton to Atlantic General Hospital (AGH). Once arriving at AGH The ER doctor checked Usilton. The ER doctor did not admit Usilton due to him not having any injuries. Usilton was discharged. Usilton then requested an MRI and CT scan. AGH advised to receive a CT scan or MRI Usilton would submit a blood sample. But the ER doctor stated that Usilton does not show any signs for a CT scan or MRI. Usilton stated I aint giving you anything. I disagree with you. I need another doctor. Once AGH issued Usilton the discharge papers. I transported Usilton to the Ocean City Police Department for processing.   During transport I observed Usilton to move his wrist behind his back. I advised to Usilton that the handcuffs will hurt more if you move more. Once arriving at OCPD, Usilton stated Oh my wrists are numb because of the handcuffs. I need to go back to the hospital. Ocean City EMS arrived back on scene (EMS Run #23-07086531). Usilton requested to return to the hospital but he wanted to go to Tidal Health Hospital not AGH. EMS advised they could not transport Usilton to Tidal Health due to him not meeting the criteria to be transported there. Usilton then stated I hope you dont have anything going on tomorrow with your kids or your fat wife at home. We are going to be doing this all night. As soon as they release me, we will come right back here and I will get EMS to take me back to the hospital. After 10 or 11 hours you wont have any evidence.   Once arriving at AGH, Usilton continued to be loud within the ER. Usilton also continued to stated If they release me we are going to Tidal Health next. AGH discharged Usilton. While walking to my patrol vehicle. I had my hand on Usiltons left arm. As we were approaching my patrol vehicle Usilton stated Oh no. and bumped me pushing myself and him into the rear of my patrol vehicle. Usilton then freely fell to the ground. I asked Usilton to get up four times. Usilton stated You cant pick up a 200-pound man. Im not getting up. Myself and Cpl. Ruiz fireman carried Usilton. I grabbed his upper body and Cpl. Ruiz grabbed his feet. We carried him approximately 8 feet and gently placed him back on the ground. I again, asked Usilton to stand up. Usilton stated Since you all were nice I will get up. Usilton then freely entered into my patrol vehicle.   While Usilton was in my patrol vehicle. Usilton stated Lets go over there so you can beat me up, I know you want to. I am going to get a sweaty attorney so I can take all of your pension. You are so aggressive and you need to find another career, you are not fit for this job. Youre such a dog.  I then transported Usilton to Tidal Health Hospital. I released Usilton to the care of Tidal Health Hospital.   PROCESSING I observed no physical signs of injury. During my interaction with Usilton, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person, observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy, lethargic movements, slurred speech, loud and rambling, un cooperating with myself and others orders.  I was able to locate a picture from Usilltons Facebook showing that he was at Seacrets bar approximately 5 hours prior to being placed under arrest.  CHARGES Usilton was charged with the following citations: 1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (64B0T5Y) 2. Driving While Impaired By Alcohol (64C0T5Y) 3. Negligent driving(64D0T5Y) 4.Driving on suspended license (64F0T5Y) 5.Failure to display drivers license (64G0T5Y) 6. Failure to display registration card (64H0T5Y) 7. Driving on suspended registration (64J0T5Y) 8. Driver failure to obey designated lanes (64K0T5Y) 9. Driver followed vehicle too close (64L0T5Y)  Case closed by arrest. All events occurred in Worcester County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 19:27:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/14/2023 19:42:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513938</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/08/2023 21:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 18:04:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/14/2023 18:05:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>42</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 18:04:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:14</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>282876</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Usilton</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Robert</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/03/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/13/2020 17:54:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>U243</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Usilton</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Robert</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/03/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>U243</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/13/2020 17:54:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>20872</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Nanticoke</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Bivalve</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21814</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.893338</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.292778</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>506</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Forest</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Fruitland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21826</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1308</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.6296511</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.3291664</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>302</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>519</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7173</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/13/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 18:07:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 18:07:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 18:04:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/14/2023 18:04:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155122</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 18:10:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/14/2023 18:10:19</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2003</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SRA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GLD</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GLD</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>803Z91</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>