<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-039676</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/10/2023 03:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/10/2023 03:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/10/2023 02:41:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/10/2023 02:41:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/10/2023 03:08:45</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/27/2023 01:12:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>25 MM CAPITAL BELTWAY SB, COLLEGE PARK</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>712647</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/10/2023 03:08:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/11/2023 06:06:02</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>712647</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>25</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm Capital Beltway Sb College</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PARK</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.9189935</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0185155</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/10/2023 03:08:41</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/10/2023 03:08:41</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/26/2023 17:16:01</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/10/2023 03:08:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSPQ031</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 11:32:01</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>HELLAMS, EUGENE JR. // 23-MSP-039676 // 0PQ0Y2X  Defendant: Hellams, Eugene Jr. Incident Number: 23-MSP-039676 DUI Folder: 23-272 Date of Offense: 11/10/2023 Arresting Officer: Tpr. Fleming #7439 Breath Technician: N/A Subsequent Offender: No  Q-13 IS EQUIPPED WITH AN IN CAR CAMERA THE EVENT WAS AUDIBLY AND VISUALLY RECORDED  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On November 10th, 2023, at approximately 0241 hours, I, Trooper Fleming #7439 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, was on patrol in the area of southbound 495 at 95, College Park, Prince Georges County, Maryland. I was in full uniform operating a marked patrol vehicle Q-13. The incident was audibly and visually recorded on my body worn camera and Q-13s in-car camera. I observed a black Subaru Forester bearing the Maryland registration 34971CG travelling at a high rate of speed in lane one. I moved approximately two car lengths directly behind the vehicle to better observe the vehicle. I matched my speed with the vehicle and paced the vehicle travelling at approximately 87 mph. The vehicle drifted to the left side of lane one and then jerked back to the right. The right side wheels of the vehicle drifted over the white dotted lines into lane two. The vehicle then drifted back into lane one. Once again, the right side of the vehicle drifted to the right side of lane one. The right side wheels of the vehicle touched the white dotted lines between lane one and lane two I activated my emergency lights and initiated a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle pulled over to the right shoulder of southbound 495 at 201. The vehicle immediately braked and began to move towards the right shoulder, despite there being a large, clear shoulder area on the left. As the vehicle began to enter lane four, the vehicle stopped braking. The vehicle then braked again. As the vehicle entered the right shoulder the vehicle again stopped braking. The vehicle took an unusually long amount of time to come to a complete stop (approximately 55 seconds from the time I activated my emergency lights). I exited my patrol vehicle to make contact with the driver.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I made a passengers side approach to the vehicle. I informed the driver of the reason for the traffic stop. I informed the driver the traffic stop would be audibly and visually recorded. I made contact with the driver who I later identified as Hellams, Eugene Jr. (1/M, DOB: 02/01/1977) via his Maryland Drivers License. I asked Hellams for his drivers license. Hellams took an unusually long amount of time to find his drivers license (approximately 60 seconds from the time I asked). Hellams first checked his pocket book, then his small bag, before locating his drivers license in his phone case. I observed that there was a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from within Hellamss vehicle. Hellamss eyes were bloodshot and glassy. Hellamss speech was slurred. Hellamss movements were slow. I asked Hellams if he had anything to drink before leaving; Hellams stated he had one beer.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) An additional police unit arrived on scene. I asked Hellams to perform field sobriety in order to rule out alcohol as a contributing factor. Hellams agreed to perform field sobriety. The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of southbound 495 at 201. The shoulder area was level and dry. Hellams appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. Upon separating Hellams from his vehicle, I observed a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath and person. I asked Hellams the following questions: Drugs/Medication  Hellams stated he took medication for nerves in his back. Hellams stated that he takes this medication daily and it should not affect his ability to drive. Physical Injuries  Hellams stated he does not have any physical injuries that should affect his ability to walk in a straight line or stand on one foot. Glasses or Contacts  Hellams stated he regularly wore glasses. Hellams was removed his glasses for the HGN test.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 Clues Observed) The test was explained. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus. The stimulus was held approximately 12-15 inches from Hellamss eye, slightly above eye level. Hellams was instructed to look straight ahead, keep his head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. Hellamss pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Before beginning the test, I asked Hellams if he understood my instructions, to which he confirmed. Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Additional Observations  Resting gaze nystagmus was not present. Vertical gaze nystagmus was not present.  WALK AND TURN TEST (6/8 Clues Observed) The test was explained and demonstrated. Hellams was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Hellams was then instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and remain in that position until told to begin. Hellams was advised to take nine steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line, and take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Hellams was instructed to complete the second series of nine steps in the same heel to toe fashion. Hellams was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, to count every step out loud, and once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Hellams if he understood, and he confirmed that he did. Instructional Phase  Cannot Keep Balance  Hellams could not remain balanced with his right foot directly in front of his left foot touching heel to toe while the walking stage of the test was being demonstrated and given instructions for. Hellams broke the starting position on at least two occasions. Walking Stage (First Nine Steps)  Misses Heel-Toe  On all nine of his first nine steps, Hellams missed heel to toe by more than one half inch. Steps Off Line  On all nine of his first nine steps, Hellams stepped off line by more than one half inch. Raises Arms  On all nine of his first nine steps, Hellams raises his arms greater than six inches from his body. Improper Turn - Hellams turned by stepping with both feet. Walking Stage (Second Nine Steps) Misses Heel-Toe  On all nine of his second nine steps, Hellams missed heel to toe by more than one half inch. Steps Off Line  On all nine of his second nine steps, Hellams stepped off line by more than one half inch. Raises Arms  On all nine of his second nine steps, Hellams raises his arms greater than six inches from his body. Actual Number of Steps  Hellams stepped eight times. Additional Observations  ONE-LEG STAND TEST (3/4 Clues Observed) The test was explained and demonstrated. Hellams was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch the raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two, etc.), and not put his foot down until the end of the test. I asked Hellams if he understood the test, and he confirmed. Seconds 1-10 Raises Arms  Hellams would raise his arms greater than six inches from his body during this period. Seconds 11-20 Raises Arms  Hellams would raise his right arm greater than six inches from his body during this period. Sways  Hellamss body would sway from the left and right greater than two inches upon losing his balance. Hops  Hellams would hop on one foot in an attempt to regain his balance once during this period. Seconds 21-30 Raises Arms  Hellams would raise his right arm greater than six inches from his body during this period. Sways  Hellamss body would sway from the left and right greater than two inches upon losing his balance and putting his foot down.  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST While on scene, I informed Hellams of his Preliminary Breath Rights. Hellams was offered a PBT, to which he agreed. Preliminary Breath Test Results: .127 ARREST Based on the totality of circumstances, I concluded Hellams was driving a motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol. Hellamss inability to maintain within his traffic lane while driving. Hellams was travelling at approximately 87 mph in a 55 mph zone The unusual long amount of time Hellams took come to a complete stop The unusual long amount of time Hellams took to find his drivers license The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on Hellamss breath and person. Hellamss eyes were bloodshot and glassy. Hellamss slurred speech. Hellamss slow movement. Hellamss admission to recently consuming alcohol. HGN (6/6), WAT (6/8), OLS (3/4) On November 10th, 2023, at approximately 0303 hours, I placed Hellams under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack. A search incident to arrest of Hellamss person was conducted. The search of Hellamss person was negative. I transported Hellams to the College Park Barrack. Hellams was played the DR-15 Advice of Rights English recording provided by MVA. Hellams was provided with a copy of the DR-15 to read along as well. At approximately 0340 hours, Hellams agreed to take an alcohol concentration test.  20 MINUTE OBSERVATION I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Hellams beginning with his arrest. A preliminary search of Hellams was conducted on scene and it was revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. I observed Hellams from the time of arrest until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by Cpl. Williams #6099 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Hellams had a result of .13 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath on November 10th, 2023 at 0403 hours. Intoximeter Result: .13 BrAC Hellamss vehicle was towed by HH Towing. I processed Hellams and transported him to his residence at 7814 Cloister Pl, Greenbelt, MD 20770. I released Hellams to Tabron Hellams, Jobena Renae (1/F; DOB: 01/25/1977).  Hellams was issued the following citations. TA - 21-902(a1i) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL TA - 21-902(b1i) DRIVING VEH. WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL TA - 21-902(a1ii) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL PER SE TA - 21-901.1(a) RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OF PERSONS AND PROPERTY TA - 21-901.1(b) NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON TA - 21-201(a1) DRIVER FAILURE TO OBEY PROPERLY PLACED TRAFFIC CONTROL DEVICE INSTRUCTIONS TA - 21-801.1 EXCEEDING POSTED MAXIMUM SPEED LIMIT: 87 MPH IN A 55 MPH ZONE TA - 13-401(h) DRIVING VEHICLE ON HIGHWAY WITH SUSPENDED REGISTRATION TA - 13-411(f) DRIVING VEHICLE ON HIGHWAY WITH EXPIRED REGISTRATION PLATE ISSUED BY ANY STATE  The defendant was issued copies of the following documents: -Citations (listed above) -DR-15 Advice of Rights -DR-15a Order of Suspension -MSP 33 Notification to Defendant of Result of Test for Alcohol Concentration All documents were forwarded to the Prince Georges County, State Attorney Office. All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/26/2023 16:23:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/26/2023 17:04:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Richards</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jerrell</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7514</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Aaron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fleming</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sierra</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7439</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529144</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/10/2023 02:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 02:48:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/11/2023 02:48:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>46</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 03:20:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/11/2023 06:05:31</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392610</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hellams</LastName>
               <FirstName>Eugene</FirstName>
               <DOB>02/01/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>11/10/2023 05:43:54</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hellams</LastName>
               <FirstName>Eugene</FirstName>
               <DOB>02/01/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>H452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/10/2023 05:43:54</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7814</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Cloister</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Greenbelt</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20770</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3030</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.871229</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.988696</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 03:20:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 03:20:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 03:20:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 03:20:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 02:48:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/11/2023 02:48:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>