<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-006256</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/17/2023 22:22:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/17/2023 22:22:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/17/2023 21:18:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/17/2023 21:18:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 22:18:39</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0392</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 13:30:44</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>482358</AddressId>
      <City>MDC244</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 22:18:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/06/2023 10:01:22</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>482358</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>301</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Crain</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Upper Marlboro</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20772</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-76.81038000000018</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.75671003801608</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>9401-9699 CRAIN HWY / 9961-9999 ROSARYVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/17/2023 22:18:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/17/2023 22:18:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/07/2023 12:32:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/17/2023 22:18:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car (L-42) and Body Worn Camera Operational.   Defendant: Frederick Bobby Settles-Peck   Date of Birth: 02/10/1983  Date of Arrest: 02/17/2023  Time of Arrest: 2218 Hours    DUI:  23-056  Certificate and Training:  Trained in Administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) through the Maryland State Police (MSP) and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA)  Soundex:  A67306554/Virginia  Narrative: VEHICLE IN MOTION (Phase 1):  On February 17, 2023, at approximately 2122 hours, the College Park Barrack Police Communication Operator (PCO) dispatched a complaint of a Black Dodge Ram 1500 driving Northbound Crain Highway south of Pennsylvania Avenue traveling north in the southbound lanes with inadequate illumination, no lights at all from the vehicle were displayed.  At approximately 2130 hours, I arrived in the area where the vehicle was last seen. Upon my arrival to the location, the PCO advised the complainant stated the suspect vehicle made a U-turn at Village Drive West, Upper Marlboro, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20772 was now traveling southbound. The U-turn from the suspect vehicle ultimately caused another vehicle to swerve out of the lane where it collided with another vehicle traveling in the same direction. However, the suspect vehicle was not involved in the accident.  At approximately 2137 hours, I, Trooper G. Olds #7581 of the Maryland State Police, currently assigned to the Forestville Barrack was on duty in my marked patrol vehicle traveling southbound Crain Highway at Heathermore Boulevard, Upper Marlboro, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20772, where I observed the vehicle bearing Maryland registration 6EK8662. I observed the suspect vehicle in lane 2 where it crossed over the dotted lane divider lines by more than a half a car length, nearly striking a vehicle traveling in lane 1. I activated my emergency equipment to conduct a traffic stop on the vehicle, southbound Crain Highway at Rosaryville Road, Upper Marlboro, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20772. After approximately 30 seconds to a minute, the suspect eventually came to a slow stop in lane 2.   PERSONAL CONTACT (Phase 2):  Upon contact with the driver, I made a driver side approach where I observed the vehicle was occupied one time. I identified the driver by his Virginia drivers license as Frederick Bobby Settles-Peck (B/M DOB: 02/10/1983.) While talking to Settles-Peck, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I observed Settles-Peck eyes to be glossy and bloodshot. While talking to Settles-Peck I asked had he consumed any alcoholic beverages to which he stated, Yes, two glasses of Bourbon. I asked Settles-Peck if he would perform the voluntary Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) to which Settles-Peck agreed to perform.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (Phase 3):  Prior to performing the SFSTs, I turned off my front facing emergency lights and turned away my spotlight, I asked Settles-Peck to stand with his feet and legs together and his arms down by his sides, advising him to not move from this position until I instructed him to do so. I ask Settles-Peck if he was taking any medication or has any injures which would hinder him from performing the tests, to which Settles-Peck advised he did not.   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) 6 out of 6 clues observed:  Before performing HGN, I instructed Settles-Peck to follow my stimulus with his eyes and his eyes only without moving his head, neck, or shoulders. I asked Settles-Peck if he understood the instructions I gave him to which he advised he understood. While performing HGN, Settles-Peck exhibited equal pupil size in both eyes and resting nystagmus was not present. Settles-Peck did not follow the stimulus as instructed. Settles-Peck would move his head multiple times after he was advised not to multiple times. Settles-Peck was unable to complete this portion of the SFSTs satisfactorily.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit:  Settles-Peck showed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus:  Settles-Peck showed distinct and sustained nystagmus in both eyes.  Onset (of) Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees:  Settles-Peck showed onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.  Vertical Gaze Nystagmus:  Settles-Peck did not show vertical gaze nystagmus.  Walk and Turn (WAT) 7 out of 8 clues observed:  Before performing WAT, I instructed Settles-Peck to imagine there was a straight line in front of him and to place his right foot in front of his left foot touching heel to toe with his arms down by his sides. It should be noted Settles-Peck could not get into the instructional phase position. Settles-Peck was falling off balance while attempting to get into position. Settles-Peck had to be held up to get into the instructional phase by Trooper J. Barlow #7186 and Trooper R. Miller #7332 prior to giving instructions to the test. Settles-Peck was unable to get into the instructional phase position without losing balance and was instructed to stand with his legs and feet together. I instructed Settles-Peck not to move from this position until I instructed him to do so. I instructed Settles-Peck to take nine (9) heel to toe steps down the imaginary straight line, looking down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I instructed Settles-Peck once he got to his 9thstep to leave his lead foot planted, take a series of small steps turning around, and to take 9 more heel to toe steps back down the imaginary straight line. I instructed Settles-Peck once he starts the test not to stop the test until he completed the test. I asked Settles-Peck if he understood the instructions to which he advised he understood. I demonstrated how the test should be performed, taking three (3) steps, simulating 9, turning around, and not stopping once I started the test. I asked Settles-Peck if he understood the demonstration to which he advised he did. I instructed Settles-Peck to begin the test.  Instructional Phase:   Settles-Peck was unable to maintain balance in the Instructional Phase.   Walking Stage (1st Series):  Settles-Peck missed heel to toe steps during the whole series.  Settles-Peck raised his hands approximately six inches from his sides.  Settles-Peck stepped of line by more than one half inch during his seventh step.  Settles-Peck took the improper number of steps totaling 10 steps.   Turn:  Settles-Peck made an improper turn by not keeping his lead foot planted and taking a short series of steps to turn as instructed.  Walking Stage (2nd Series):  Settles-Peck missed heel to toe steps during steps 1-9.  Settles-Peck raised his hands approximately six inches from his sides.  Settles-Peck stopped walking for approximately ten second after his improper turn.  One Leg Stand (OLS) 3 out of 4 clues observed:  Before Performing the OLS, I instructed Settles-Peck to stand with his legs and feet together and arms by his sides. I instructed Settles-Peck not to move from the position until instructed to do so. I instructed Settles-Peck to lift the leg of his choosing approximately six inches off the ground. I instructed Settles-Peck to look down at the raised leg and count out loud in the manner of one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-three and so on until instructed to stop. I asked Settles-Peck did he understand the instructions to which he advised he understood. I demonstrated how the test should be performed and asked Settles-Peck if he understood to which he advised he did. I asked Settles-Peck which leg is he going to raise to which he advised his right leg. I instructed Settles-Peck to begin the test. At second fifteen Settles-Peck out his foot down and stopped performing the test. He did not resume the test.  Puts Foot down:  Settles-Peck put his foot down on seconds 1,3,4,6,8.  Uses arms to balance:  Settles-Peck used his hands to balance during seconds 1-30  Sways:  Settles-Peck Swayed during the seconds 1-30.  Hops:  Settles-Peck did not hop.  Arrest:    Failure to maintain right of center  Operating vehicle without rear reflectors  Glossy eyes  Bloodshot eyes  The strong odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from his person   margin-left:8px"&gt;The observations during the SFSTs   Preliminary Breath Test:  .22BrAC  At approximately 2217 hours, Settles-Peck was advised of his Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) rights and offered a PBT. Settles-Peck agreed to take the PBT with the results of .22BrAC. At approximately 2218 hours, Settles-Peck was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. Settles-Peck was searched prior to being placed in my marked patrol vehicle to be transported to the Forestville Barrack. Settles-Peck was provided a digital copy of the Advice of Rights (DR-015) from the mva.maryland.gov website to follow along while I read the form from the same website and its entirety.   Intoximeter Test:  .26BrAC  Having been read the DR-015, at approximately 2218 hours, Settles-Peck agreed to take the Intoximeter Test. At 2327 hours, Settles-Peck took the Intoximeter Test, with the results of .26BrAC. The test was administered by Sgt T. Estrin #6052.  Settles-Peck was charged with DUI/DWI and other traffic related incidents.  Settles-Peck vehicle was released to his wife, Nickia, Danielle King (B/F DOB:09/24/1988)  Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/04/2023 20:23:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/06/2023 10:07:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ortiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Angel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5858</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ware</LastName>
            <FirstName>Traevon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7467</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Reily</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7338</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Skutovas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robertas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7332</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Landis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dwayne</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5082</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Olds</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7581</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495651</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 21:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 22:59:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 23:43:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495651</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 21:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:00:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 23:43:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495651</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 21:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:01:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 23:44:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495651</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 21:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:02:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 23:45:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495651</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 21:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:07:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 23:44:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495651</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 21:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17272</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:25:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 23:25:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495651</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 21:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:37:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 23:37:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495651</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 21:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:38:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 23:38:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495651</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 21:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:39:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 23:39:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495651</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17034</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 21:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17034</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:41:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 23:41:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495651</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16631</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/17/2023 21:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16631</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:42:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 23:42:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:21:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:44</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369958</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Settles-Peck</LastName>
               <FirstName>Frederick</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Bobby</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/10/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/23/2023 23:18:19</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S342</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F636</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Settles-Peck</LastName>
               <FirstName>Frederick</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Bobby</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/10/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S342</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F636</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/23/2023 23:18:19</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>8016</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hayfield</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Clinton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20735</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1905</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.852604</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.776956</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:56:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:56:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:56:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:56:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 22:59:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 22:59:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150170</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7581</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 23:50:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7581</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 23:50:27</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C6SRFFT8LN147362</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>RM1500CWCB</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6EK8662</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>11</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>