<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011566</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/31/2023 23:14:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/31/2023 23:14:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/31/2023 23:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/31/2023 23:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI//K9 Scan</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/31/2023 23:14:11</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0343</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/09/2023 12:32:13</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>1678 AUGUSTINE HERMAN,ELKTON</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>689264</AddressId>
      <City>MDC146</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/31/2023 23:14:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 00:58:37</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>689264</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1678</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Augustine Herman Elkton</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.8037245833333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.54479125</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/31/2023 23:14:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/31/2023 23:14:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/09/2023 12:31:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/31/2023 23:14:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:25</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>F-45 MVR equipped In Car/Body worn camera was operational.   Defendant: Toni Marie Didonna  Date of Birth: 03/2/1988 Date of Arrest: 03/31/2023 Time of Arrest: 2313 hours FL DL # D350813885820 DUI #: 23-058 (North East)  TRAINING CERTIFICATES:  I am trained by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration to administer standardized field sobriety tests and advanced roadside impaired driving tests.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1):  On March 31, 2023, at approximately 2300 hours, I, TFC Rafer #6709, of the Maryland State Police, was on patrol in the area of N/B Rt 213 N/O Spears Hill Rd. While traveling N/B, I observed a black Chevrolet Truck (MD  7FE2600) travel over the center lane divider line, and fail to stay to the right of the center lane.  Due to the truck driving being unable to maintain its lane, I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):  Upon contact with the driver, I immediately detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle. I identified the driver by her Florida ID as Toni Marie Didonna (DOB 3/2/1988 W/F). While speaking with Didonna, she failed to look in my direction, and continued to look to her right while speaking. This indicated to me she was attempting to conceal her breath. Didonna appeared to be lethargic and slow in her movements.  I questioned Didonna how much she had to drink and she stated, Not that much. I requested a specific number of alcoholic beverages, and she replied, I wasnt at any bar if thats what youre asking. Didonna then looked at me, and observed she had bloodshot eyes.  Upon my second vehicle approach, Didonna had lit a cigarette. I had Didonna step out of the vehicle, and walk to the front of vehicle.  I asked Didonna the following question, On a scale, one to 10, 10 being the drunkest youve ever been and one being the least drunk youve ever been, what number would you say you are? Didonna replied, Uh, I would never get into the, the car if I was drunk. If I was drunk that I didnt think I could drive, I would never get in the car. I never do that. Ok. Alright.  While speaking with Didonna outside of the vehicle, I detected a strong odor of alcohol emitting from her breath. I questioned Didonna if she would conduct standard field sobriety test, and she stated, I think Im gonna pass, yes.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):  The surface was dry, essentially level, appeared to be free from obvious debris, and the weather was clear. Lighting conditions were nighttime hours and consisted of my flashlight. Didonna appeared to be in good physical condition and displayed no visible injuries.  I asked Didonna the following questions:  Glasses or Contacts- Yes. Medical Conditions- None. Injuries- None. Medication- Prozac in the morning.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Didonnas eyes. DIDONNA was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes. DIDONNAs pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Lack of Smooth Pursuit- Present in both eyes  2) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation- Present in both eyes 3) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees- Present in both eyes    Didonna moved her head and continued to snap her eyes forward, failing to follow my instructions. I requested Didonna reach out and touch the tip of my pen, in order to confirm she was able to see the stimulant, which she successfully did.  When I continued the test, Didonna continued to stare forward.   WALK AND TURN (5/8 clues observed)  Prior to DIDONNA performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. DIDONNA was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and heel touching toe. DIDONNA was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in that position until told to begin the test. DIDONNA was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. DIDONNA was instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keeping her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, DIDONNA was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to the left to turn completely around. DIDONNA was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. DIDONNA was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keeping her hands down by her sides, look down at her feet, and count aloud each step. I asked DIDONNA if he understood the test and she stated, yes sir.  Instructional Stage:  Lost balance: No  Kept her arms wrapped around herself   Starts too soon: No  Walking Stage (1st Nine):  Total steps taken: 10  Stops mid test: Yes  Steps off line: Yes  Misses heel to toe: Yes  Raises arms: No  Turn  Did not complete, ended test after 10 steps   Didonna stopped and stated, Is it necessary at this point? I stated yes, and asked her id she thought she failed, and Didonna replied, Yes because I dont have good balance.   Didonna then began her last nine steps.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  Total steps taken: 9  Stops mid test: No  Steps off line: Yes  Misses heel to toe: Yes  Raises arms: No   ONE LEG STAND (4/4 clues observed): raised left foot.  Prior to DIDONNA performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. DIDONNA was instructed to stand with her feet together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of her choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised he was to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. DIDONNA was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, Yes sir.  Counting and Balancing Stage:  1-10: Raised arms, Swayed, Hops, Put foot down  Didonna ended the test prior to being told.      PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST:  Refused.   ARREST:  Based on the following, I had reason to believe DIDONNA was driving/attempting to drive a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from her breath and person. *Admitting to consuming alcohol  *Eyes bloodshot/Slow uncoordinated movements. *Clues during standardized field sobriety testing.  Due to the number of observations, I concluded DIDONNA was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 2313 hours, I placed DIDONNA under arrest for driving/attempting to drive while under influence of alcohol. While at the North East Barrack I read Didonna her DR-15 Advice of Rights at 2354 hours, which he refused.  20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD:  DIDONNA was given copies of all pertinent paperwork. DIDONNA was released from the Maryland State Police North East Barrack to a valid and sober operator.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6709</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/05/2023 10:07:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6709</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/05/2023 10:07:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nagovich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Valentine</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6919</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jones</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7445</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Black</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0343</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rafer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Luke</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6709</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500969</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/31/2023 23:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6709</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 01:02:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6709</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 01:02:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6709</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 01:10:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373139</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Didonna</LastName>
               <FirstName>Toni</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Mari</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/02/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/01/2023 01:06:59</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D350</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Didonna</LastName>
               <FirstName>Toni</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Mari</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/02/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D350</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/01/2023 01:06:59</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>410</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Pfalzgroff</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Millington</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.864085</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.258236</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6709</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 01:10:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6709</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 01:10:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6709</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 01:02:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6709</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 01:02:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>