<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013449</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/15/2023 23:47:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/15/2023 23:47:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/15/2023 23:11:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/15/2023 23:11:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DWI ARREST OF FRANCIS JOSEPH BROGLIE III</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 23:47:44</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/24/2023 11:17:29</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>E NEW MARKET-ELLWOOD RD/ PEA HILL RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>666017</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 23:47:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 02:37:06</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>666017</AddressId>
         <StreetName>East New Market Ellwood </StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>East New Market</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21631</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.91314</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.625778781792945</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/15/2023 23:47:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/15/2023 23:47:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/15/2023 03:24:10</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 23:47:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:30</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>CASE NUMBER: 23-MSP-013449 INVESTIGATING TROOPER: Trooper First Class M. Mowbray #7119 NATURE OF CALL: Traffic Stop, DUI, DWI SCENE PROCESSING: Scene processing was conducted with the following results;   Intox EC/IR Information Sheet  MSP Form 32 - Alcohol Information Report  DR-15  Advice of Rights (Alcohol Concentration Test/Drug or CDS Test)  DR-15A  Officers Certification and Order of Suspension  Intox EC/IR Test Record Print-Out  MSP Form 102  PBT Advice of Rights  MVA Print-Out  Copy of all Citations  Photocopy of Drivers Identification  One (1) digital photograph of Francis Joseph Broglie 3rd  INCIDENT FOOTAGE: INCIDENT CAPTURED BY A MOBILE VIDEO RECORDER I-39 EQUIPPED WITH AN MVR FOOTAGE LABELED 23-MSP-006987 ON AXON EVIDENCE Dash Camera: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=1d00dfe4942248dd877d7544b5094a06partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 In-car Camera (Transport to MSP Cambridge): partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=61aff370275142f394df0bbaf1d42496partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 INCIDENT CAPTURED WITH BODY WORN CAMERA TFC M. Mowbray #7119: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=053b6386f7ed4b44bc5b53fb95e400afpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  CAMERA SYSTEM / CAD SYSTEM The camera system is manufactured by Axon. The in-car; outward facing camera is activated when the emergency lights are activated in the patrol car or if manually activated by the user. The camera will go back in time and start the recording thirty (30) seconds before the camera is activated. This event is called a 30 second pre-record. The body worn camera (BWC); attached to the front of the Trooper, is also activated when the emergency lights are activated or manually by its user. The camera will record the previous sixty (60) seconds prior to the camera activation. The camera system does not have a date and time stamp on the video itself. The system records the date and time in the metadata. The time only records the hour and minute when the camera starts the recording. Therefore, the timeline below will start with a time that was recorded from the cameras metadata and then show the duration of the video. The in-car camera and body worn camera footage remains the best depiction of the events surrounding the traffic stop. However, in order to obtain an exact time of a specific event, the reader will have to add the length of duration from the start of the video that was recorded in the metadata. Although times are recorded by other means such as the Delta Plus system that prints a time stamp on the warning, citation or safety equipment repair order this time is only when the traffic enforcement button is activated by the Trooper. This date/time is usually started shortly after making contact with a violator and upon return to the patrol vehicle. Other programs such as Caliber RMS incident and CAD reports will show a timestamp, but this time depends on when the Police Communications Operator or Trooper activates the incident within the CAD system. The two aforementioned examples of the recording of time will almost always be different than the in-car camera system due to all of the systems utilizing different internal clocks.  DUI FOLDER NUMBER: 23-58-075 DEFENDANT:  Francis Joseph Broglie 3rd  DOB: 12/06/1964 6645 Pine Top Road, Hurlock, Dorchester County, Maryland 21643 SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER: NO DATE OF ARREST: 04/15/2023 TIME OF ARREST: 2347 hours  CERTIFICATIONS AND TRAINING:    Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration on May 30, 2019  Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) on January 30, 2020  Trained and certified to operate the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) through the Maryland State Police  I am trained in the detection and recognition of controlled dangerous substances through the Maryland State Police Academy  Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police  Trained and certified to operate Maryland Coordination and Analysis Center License Plate Readers since August 2019  Maryland State Police Conducting the Complete Traffic Stop: Criminal Interdiction Training  Trained in Advanced Collision Investigations by the Maryland State Police  ASSIGNMENT: On Saturday, April 15, 2023, I, Trooper First Class M. Mowbray #7119, of the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack, was assigned to road patrol duties in Dorchester County, Maryland. The Maryland State Easton Barrack is responsible for enforcing and investigating all criminal and traffic related crime within Dorchester, Talbot and Caroline counties. My duties include but are not limited to: enforcing the criminal and motor vehicle laws of the State of Maryland, issuing traffic citations and warnings, investigating traffic accidents, investigating and completing criminal investigations, interviewing witnesses, victims and suspects and writing field reports.   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On April 15, 2023, at approximately 2308 hours I, Trooper First Class M. Mowbray #7119 of the Maryland State Police, was on patrol operating my marked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle I-39; a 2021 Ford Explorer, traveling southbound on Maryland Route 16 (East New Market Ellwood Road) near the intersection of Maryland Route 14 (Academy Street). At that time, I observed a green 2000 Ford Mustang, bearing Maryland registration JKD505, traveling northbound approaching my location appearing to be traveling over the posted speed limit of 35 miles per hour. I activated the front antenna of my Kustom Signals Golden Eagle II radar unit (MSP Serial #: 50003412) in opposite direction fastest moving mode and obtained an audio and visual confirmation of the speed of 47 MPH in a posted 35 MPH zone. As the Ford continued northbound I observed it to have an inoperable right registration plate light causing inadequate rear plate illumination; rendering it not clearly legible from a distance of 50 feet to the rear.   I initiated a U-turn and proceeded to follow the Ford as its continued northbound and entered the 45 MPH zone, continuing to appear to be traveling over the posted speed limit of 45 miles per hour. I activated the front antenna of my Kustom Signals Golden Eagle II radar unit in same direction moving mode and obtained an audio and visual confirmation of the speed of 47 MPH in a posted 45 MPH zone.  I immediately initiated a lawful traffic stop of the vehicle by activating my emergency equipment which consists of red, blue, and white strobe lights. The Ford continued northbound at a slow pace and took one minute and six seconds (1:06) to come to a stop near the intersection of Pea Hill Road, an unusual amount of time to pull over and to the right for an emergency vehicle.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Ford from the passengers side and made contact with the driver; identified by Maryland drivers license as Francis Joseph Broglie 3rd (DOB: 12/06/1964) [hereinafter identified as Broglie], as he was seated in the drivers seat. I introduced myself and informed Broglie that the traffic stop was being audibly and visually recorded. I requested that Broglie provide me with the required documents (i.e. Drivers license and vehicle registration), to which he complied. I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Broglies breath and person. While Broglie was retrieving his vehicle registration I observed a clear plastic cup with a lemon within the cupholder with condensation around the cup. Broglie stated; This is my water, just to let you know its water and lemon, thats all I have. While Broglie was retrieving his vehicle registration I inquired if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages prior to operating a motor vehicle to which he replied; I was out at my friends house earlier, that was all. I then asked Broglie to elaborate on his response by asking him, again, if he consumed any alcoholic beverages prior to operating a motor vehicle to which he replied; It was earlier around nine oclock. While speaking with Broglie, I observed his speech to be slurred and his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy, indicative of the consumption of alcoholic beverages.  I then returned to my patrol vehicle and relayed the information to the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack Emergency Dispatcher.   METERS/NCIC CHECKS: After conducting checks of Broglie via the National Crime Information Center (NCIC) and Maryland Electronic Telecommunications Resource System (METERS); it was learned that he possessed a valid drivers license in the State of Maryland.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) I requested that Broglie exit his vehicle and submit to the battery of Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, to which he complied and stated Yes sir, I am exhausted. I have had a day. I then instructed Broglie to walk to the front of the Ford, to which he complied. I then conducted a pat down of Broglies person due to safety precautions.   I then began Standardized Field Sobriety Tests; which yielded the following results; The test was performed in front of the Ford on the asphalt roadway of Pine Street. The surface was dry, level and free from any debris. Lighting consisted of headlights and my flashlight. My front red/blue lights were deactivated, and spotlight was pointed downward prior to the test. The weather was clear, evening time, and 63 degrees Fahrenheit. Broglie was wearing black shoes, black pants and a blue polo. As Broglie continued to speak with me, I detected the same strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I also observed his speech continued to be slurred. I asked Broglie about the consumption of alcoholic beverages prior to operating a motor vehicle to which he replied; I came home and I enjoy sitting outside and I had my happy hour. Broglie explained that while enjoying his happy hour he was contacted by his place of employment in regard to an emergency that occurred with the walk-in freezers and coolers and that he volunteered to return to work to take care of the issue. Broglie then stated; I stopped into Johnnys (Johnnys Tavern, a known local business that frequently sells alcohol) to see what was going on, and I sat in the parking lot, I looked at my phone for a little bit, and I decided theres no reason for me to go in there. I then asked Broglie to estimate what time he had consumed his last alcoholic beverage to which he replied; Home at nine oclock). I then inquired with Broglie as to what the alcoholic beverage he consumed to which he stated; Titos, Titos and Diet Coke. I inquired with Broglie as to the amount of alcoholic beverages he consumed prior to operating a motor vehicle to which he replied; Two, three.   When asked if Triggs had any physical disabilities, medical issues and/or on any medications that would prevent him from successfully completed the tests(eyes/balance), by asking the following medical screening questions; Q: Are you on any current medications? A: Yes, Fluoxetine, a blood pressure medicine, Nexium and Claritin. Q: Have you ever had a concussion? A: Yes, twenty years ago. Q: Do you wear corrective lenses or contacts? A: I do wear glasses at work.  The first test administered was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test. I held an ink pen 12-15 inches in front of Broglies face and slightly above eye level. Broglie was checked to ensure that his eyes could track the pens movement equally. Additionally, I ensured there was no resting nystagmus and that his pupils were equal in size.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6 of 6 Clues) (EYE COLOR: Brown) 1.) LACK OF SMOOTH PURSUIT - Present in both left and right eyes - 2 clues 2.) DISTINCT AND SUSTAINED NYSTAGMUS AT MAXIMUM DEVIATION - Present in both left and right eyes - 2 clues 3.) ONSET OF NYSTAGMUS PRIOR TO 45 DEGREES - Present in both left and right eyes - 2 clues VERTICAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS - Not present   WALK AND TURN (6 of 8 Clues) Prior to Broglie performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Broglie was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Broglie was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in that position until instructed to begin. Broglie was advised to take nine (9) heel to toe steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Broglie was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, Broglie was advised to conduct a turn by taking a series of small steps in a counterclockwise manner keeping his lead foot planted. Broglie was explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Broglie was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed.  Instructional Stage: 1. CANNOT KEEP BALANCE  - Yes, Broglie lost balance during this stage on two occasions - 1 clue 2. STARTS TOO SOON - No Walking Stage (1st Nine): 3. STOPS WALKING - Yes, Broglie stopped at step 3 the began to start over - 1 clue 4. MISSES HEEL TO TOE - Yes, Broglie missed heel to toe on step(s) 4, 5 and 8  - 1 clue 5. STEPS OFF LINE - Yes, Broglie stepped off of the line on step(s) 3 - 1 clue 6. RAISES ARMS - Yes, Broglie raised his arms on his first step(s) 1, 2 and 3 - 1 clue 7. ACTUAL NUMBER OF STEPS (9) - No, Broglie took a total of 12 steps - 1 clue Walking Stage (2nd Nine): 3. STOPS WALKING - No 4. MISSES HEEL TO TOE - Yes, Broglie missed heel to toe on step(s) 2 and 6 - 1 clue 5. STEPS OFF LINE - Yes, Broglie stepped off of the line on step(s) 7 - 1 clue 6. RAISES ARMS - Yes, Broglie raised his arms on step(s) 4, 5 and 6 - 1 clue 7. ACTUAL NUMBER OF STEPS (9) - Yes Turn: 8. IMPROPER TURN - No, proper  ONE LEG STAND (3 of 4 Clues) Prior to Broglie performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Broglie was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot and to count out loud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two) and so on until instructed to stop. Leg raised: Right 1. PUTS FOOT DOWN - Yes, Broglie put his foot down on second(s) 0-10, and 11-20 - 1 clue 2. USES ARMS FOR BALANCE - Yes, Broglie raised his arms for balance on second(s) 0-10 and 11-20 - 1 clue 3. SWAYS - Yes, Broglie swayed on second(s) 0-10, 11-20 - 1 clue 4. HOPS - No  ALPHABET TEST (F-T): Broglie was asked what his highest level of education was to which he replied; GED. Broglie was also asked if he was familiar with the alphabet. Broglie was asked to recite the alphabet starting with the letter F and ending with the letter T. Broglie agreed to perform the Alphabet Test with the following results: F, G, F, T, F, G, F, T, IS THAT CORRECT?, G, F, T, CORRECT?  NUMBERS TEST (59-36):  Broglie was asked if he was familiar and comfortable with counting numbers backwards. He was instructed to count backwards from 59 to 36. Broglie agreed to perform the test with the following results: 59, 58, 57, 56, 56, 55, 54, 53, 52, 51, 50, 49, 48, 47, 46, 45, 44, 43, 42, 41, 40, 39, 38, 37, 36.  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST RESULTS: The Preliminary Breath Test was offered to Broglie at the scene. I advised Broglie of the State of Maryland Preliminary Breath Test Advisement of Rights prior to the test. Result: .13  ARREST/ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)/ADVICE OF MIRANDA RIGHTS Based on the following, I had reason to believe Broglie was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of a Controlled Dangerous Substance: - Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Broglies breath and person - Eyes glassy and bloodshot - Slurred speech - Admission to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to operating a motor vehicle - Driver failing obey the maximum posted speed limit  - My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests  Due to Broglies poor performance on the battery of the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, he was placed under arrest at 2347 hours for driving under the influence. While seated in the passenger seat of my patrol vehicle, I played the DR-15 Advice of Rights (Alcohol Concentration Test) English Audio provided by the State of Maryland at 2352 hours as I sat to his left. Broglie refused to submit to the chemical alcohol concentration test at 0005 hours. Broglie was transported to the Maryland State Police Cambridge Detachment; located at 829 Fieldcrest Road, Cambridge, Dorchester County, Maryland 21613 where he was processed per Maryland State Police policy.  ALCOHOL CONCENTRATION TEST RESULT: REFUSAL  It should also be noted that Broglie was polite and cooperative during the entire encounter.   Broglie was provided copies of his paperwork released to a sober individual at 0041 hours.   Francis Joseph Broglie 3rd was charged with the following offenses; TA 21-902 (A)(1)(I): DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL (4SD0V1Z) TA 21-902 (B)(1)(I): DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL (4SF0V1Z) TA 21-901.1 (A): RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OF PERSONS AND PROPERTY (4SG0V1Z) TA 21-901.1 (B): NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON (4SH0V1Z) TA 21-801.1: EXCEEDING POSTED MAXIMUM SPEED LIMIT: 47 MPH IN A POSTED 35 MPH ZONE (4SJ0V1Z) TA 22-204 (F): DRIVING VEHICLE WITHOUT ADEQUATE REAR REGISTRATION PLATE ILLUMINATION (4SK0V1Z) SERO 65*: TAG LIGHTS (S0V1Z1Y9)  Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Dorchester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 14:32:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/30/2023 14:36:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Del Vecchio</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mowbray</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7119</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502856</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 23:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4SD0V1Z</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502856</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 23:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4SF0V1Z</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502856</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 23:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4SG0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502856</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 23:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4SH0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502856</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 23:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4SJ0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502856</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17023</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 23:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4SK0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17023</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>58</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 02:41:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:29</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374714</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Broglie</LastName>
               <FirstName>Francis</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Joseph</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/06/1964 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.09420564E8</SSN>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>04/19/2023 02:25:18</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B624</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F652</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Broglie</LastName>
               <FirstName>Francis</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Joseph</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/06/1964 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.09420564E8</SSN>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>B624</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F652</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/19/2023 02:25:18</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6645</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Pine Top</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hurlock</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21643</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3267</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.925797</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.656329</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>521</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7348</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 05:39:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 05:39:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 05:39:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 05:39:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 02:40:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152128</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 02:42:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 02:42:11</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FAFP42X9YF299557</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2000</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MUS</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRN</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>JKD505</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>