<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008942</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/11/2023 02:24:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/11/2023 02:24:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/11/2023 02:11:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/11/2023 02:11:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>BOLO LOOKOUT LEADING TO DUI/DWI TRAFFIC STOP (TAG LIGHT PC)</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 02:24:13</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2864</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 21:39:46</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>CRISFIELD HWY/ OCEAN HWY</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>547225</AddressId>
      <City>MDC580</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 02:24:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 23:58:27</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>547225</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Crisfield</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westover</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>HWY</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.700997</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.136955</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>8998-9273 CRISFIELD HWY / 9152-9273 OCEAN HWY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 CRISFIELD HWY / 0-0 OCEAN HWY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/11/2023 02:24:10</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/11/2023 02:24:10</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/20/2023 21:37:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 02:24:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:15</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p align="center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; Princess Anne Barrack &amp;ldquo;X&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; Tpr. B. Salgueiro, IBM 7370&lt;br /&gt; Field Operation Bureau&lt;br /&gt; March 11th, 2023&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;X-4&amp;nbsp;is an unmarked 2021 Ford Explorer equipped with an MVR system and body-worn camera.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Type of Report:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;DUI/DWI arrest&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Driver/Defendant:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Katrina Murphy Bigelow&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Sex:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Female&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Race:&lt;/strong&gt; White or Caucasian&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Date of Birth:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;03/27/77&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Maryland SOUNDEX&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;B240461615244&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breath Test Result:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;REFUSED&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;DUI Citation #&lt;/strong&gt;: 26V0XC3&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Troopers Training/Experience:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;* Trained in Human Trafficking through the Federal Bureau Of Investigations (FBI) and Maryland State Police (MSP)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Trained and certified to operate Radar and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * NHTSA certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Attended multiple NHTSA-certified cannabis impairment detection workshops.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This report has been prepared based upon the observations of this trooper and/or those of other troopers relative to the offense(s). The facts contained herein are intended solely to give the prosecuting authority a basic understanding of the facts pertaining to this case. The facts contained herein are not intended to be an exhaustive recitation of the facts pertaining to pretrial or trial issues. Instead, this trooper anticipates that during the pretrial proceedings, in this case, the prosecutor will take the opportunity to interview this trooper in order to ascertain any and all relevant facts which might be the subject of this trooper&amp;rsquo;s testimony during court proceedings.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NARRATIVE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On 03/11/2023 at approximately 0210 hours, I (Tpr.B.Salgueiro #7370), was on duty officially as a Maryland State Trooper operating an unmarked MSP vehicle X-4. At approximately 0211 hours, I was notified by the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack that a concerned citizen contacted the barrack advising there was a dark in color square body vehicle driving southbound in the northbound lanes of U.S. Route 13 south of Revells Neck Rd. I was traveling northbound on U.S. 13 in the area prior to the lookout being relayed through the barrack. I observed the suspect vehicle appear to have just been traveling opposite of the correct lane direction of traffic (Photo references will be attached to this report to further explain my observations) when turning onto Crisfield Hwy (413) traveling horizontally across both lanes one(1) and lane two(2) at an extremely slow speed and riding the clearly marked road lines when it reached Hwy 413. I then continued northbound on U.S. Route 13 and made a U-turn at Revells Neck Rd to travel southbound in an attempt to make contact with the vehicle. As I turned onto Hwy 413 I observed the same vehicle, a black 2014 Toyota Scion bearing MD registration (1EZ9844) that was turning onto Hwy 413 parked on the right shoulder of the roadway prior to Sam Barnes Rd. I observed the vehicle to have one rear tag light inoperable and as I made an initial slow pass by the vehicle I observed the driver to be slumped over to the center console of the vehicle and the lights and engine still running. I then turned around and got behind the vehicle to conduct a traffic stop for the inoperable tag light and to check on the welfare of the driver. As I approached the vehicle the driver still appeared to be slumped over the center console and appeared to be on her cell phone. I was able to get the driver&amp;#39;s attention, and she turned towards me and said &amp;quot;oh fuck&amp;quot;. The driver advised me she was heading to Ocean City for the Saint Patrick day parade and had been driving there from Baltimore, Maryland. As she spoke, the strong odor of alcoholic beverage was present from her breath and the interior of the vehicle, of which she was the sole occupant. The driver then made the statement &amp;quot;we both know how this is gonna end right&amp;quot; as she attempted to locate her license and registration. I watched the driver look through an assortment of cards as she passed her driver&amp;#39;s license multiple times. The driver then looked me in the eyes and said &amp;quot;can I be honest with you&amp;quot; to which I replied &amp;quot;what&amp;#39;s that&amp;quot; and she stated, &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ve been drinking&amp;quot;. I then asked the driver for her registration and as she reached over to the front passenger side of the vehicle I observed multiple empty and full 50ML bottles of Fireball Cinnamon Whisky spread across the front passenger floorboard and front passenger seats of the vehicle. The driver then handed me an assortment of papers as I advised her to shut the vehicle off and exit the vehicle, to which she complied.&amp;nbsp;As the driver, now identified as Katrina Murphy Bigelow (DOB: 03-27-1977 W/F) exited the vehicle she attempted to close the driver door and stumbled backward having to catch her footing so as not to fall. I then explained to Bigelow that if she wanted to I would run her through SFST&amp;#39;s. Bigelow stated &amp;quot;yeah I&amp;#39;ve been drinking, I&amp;#39;m not a lair&amp;quot; as I spoke. Bigelow then agreed verbally that she would perform SFST. My emergency lights were not on at any point during SFST&amp;#39;s. Before tests were conducted, Bigelow multiple times swayed from left to right and eventually leaned back on the hood of the vehicle in an attempt to keep her balance as she spoke with me. As she continued to speak, the distinct smell of an alcoholic beverage was still present on her breath. After conducting HGN on Bigelow, she stated &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m a drinker, I&amp;#39;ve never done one fucking drug a day in my damn life&amp;quot;. I then asked Bigelow what she had consumed today, and she stated &amp;quot;Fireball, yeah&amp;quot;. Before I was able to conduct WAT tests Bigelow began to talk about her family and her foster parents. I then told Bigelow &amp;quot;I understand&amp;quot; to which she became extremely agitated by my statement and pointed directly at me and said&amp;quot; you don&amp;#39;t actually understand what the fuck I&amp;#39;m talking about&amp;quot;, she continued to show extremely varied levels of anger, and aggression throughout my interaction with her which was all captured on my body-worn camera. I then attempted to advise Bigelow that she had to get into the instructional position for the WAT test. Bigelow stumbled to her right-hand side over three times before stating &amp;quot;Of course, I can&amp;#39;t&amp;quot; along with stating &amp;quot;just take me to jail, why are we doing this&amp;quot;. She ultimately refused to conduct WAT testing and I began explaining the OLS test. The test was explained to Bigelow, and she stated &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; when asked if she understood, and when she began the test, immediately swayed to her left almost falling, and stated, &amp;quot;fuck this, just take me to jail&amp;quot;. I then was able to place Bigelow in custody for DUI/DWI without incident at 0223 hours. After Bigelow was placed safely into the front passenger seat of my police vehicle, I returned to her vehicle to lock and secure it at her verbal request. As I was securing the vehicle I observed ten empty 50ML bottles of&amp;nbsp;Fireball Cinnamon Whisky in plain view. At approximately 0230 hours I transported Bigelow less than 3 miles to the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack for processing. While driving to the barrack Bigelow made multiple statements like &amp;quot;what I&amp;#39;m most embarrassed of is that I was caught&amp;quot;. While driving to the barrack my vehicle now had the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage. While processing Bigelow at the barrack, multiple times she became extremely belligerent with me and my supervisor. She called my supervisor multiple names like &amp;quot;Captain America&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Lieutenant Dangle&amp;quot; along with displaying both of her middle fingers to him whenever he was facing away from her. Bigelow was advised her right via a DR-15 placed in front of her and the MVA audio version and refused the test at 0256 hours. While Bigelow awaited a ride, her mood changed multiple times. She kicked the cell door, threw cups of water provided to her across the cell, and at one point began to bang her head against the cell wall. When asked the reason for these outbursts, Bigelow stated &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m cold&amp;quot;. She was removed from the cell for her safety and I remained with her in the intoximeter room to calm her down. At 0625 hours Bigelow was released to a sober driver that was found to have a suspended license through Maryland, and they awaited another driver to pick them up from the barrack.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Lookout called in about a vehicle matching the suspect vehicle traveling the wrong-way on northbound U.S. 13.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. My observation of the vehicle as it appeared to be driving under the posted speed limit and was halfway in the roadway and halfway on the shoulder.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Upon contact with the driver, I made the following observations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. I exited my patrol car and observed the driver was on the phone and slumped over the center console.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;2. The driver was wearing a hoodie&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. Upon my request for a driver&amp;#39;s license and registration card, the driver appeared disoriented as she attempted to located these items.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 4. I observed multiple opened and empty alcoholic beverages on the front passenger seat.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 5. There was a strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 6. Slurred speech as the driver spoke with me.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 7. The driver&amp;#39;s own verbal admission to driving &amp;quot;drunk&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 8. The manner in which the driver stumbled as she attempted to exit the vehicle and close the door.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;The driver advised the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. The driver stated she was driving to Salisbury to meet her foster parents to attend the Saint Patrick&amp;#39;s day parade in Ocean City the next day.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. The driver was not injured and not in need of medical attention.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. The driver admitted to consuming alcohol.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 4. Driver admitted she knew she was &amp;quot;wrong&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;I continued to make the following observations:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.&amp;nbsp;The driver produced a valid Maryland Provisional License and current registration card.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. The driver was identified as&amp;nbsp;Katrina Murphy Bigelow (DOB: 03-27-1977 W/F)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 4. I asked Bigelow to exit the vehicle and walk to the front of it, and she complied.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;While interacting with Bigelow, I made the following observations:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. I could smell the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;strong odor of alcoholic beverage&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;emanating from her breath and person as she spoke.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. Bigelow had&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;glassy and bloodshot&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. Bigelow displayed a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;glazed look/expression&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;on her face as she interacted with me.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 4. Bigelow appeared unsteady on her feet, her body swaying to the left and right as she spoke with me. I informed Bigelow that I wanted her to perform field sobriety tests which she agreed to submit to.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 5. Abrupt mood changes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of Hwy 413. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions were my vehicle&amp;#39;s headlights and handheld flashlight. I asked Bigelow if she had any significant medical issues with her eyes, arms, or legs which would prevent her from performing the field sobriety tests or if she had taken any medication prior to driving. Bigelow responded: &amp;ldquo;No&amp;rdquo;. Bigelow appeared to be in generally good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries, limps, or limb ailments. Bigelow later stated she was deaf in her left ear.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Bigelow displayed a lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. Bigelow displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. Bigelow displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**WALK AND TURN: Not conducted**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Bigelow was unable and unwilling to attempt this test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**ONE LEG STAND: Not conducted**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Bigelow was unable and unwilling to attempt this test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**PBT RESULTS**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; PBT was not offered to&amp;nbsp;Bigelow.&lt;br /&gt; .&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Bigelow was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *The multiple times&amp;nbsp;Bigelow stated she had consumed alcohol.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Glazed look/expression on her face.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * My observed signs of impairment as she performed field sobriety tests.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I determined that Bigelow was impaired by the presence of an alcoholic beverage in her system that adversely affected her ability to perform most of the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests properly can also adversely affect the person&amp;#39;s ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. I placed Bigelow under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0223 hours on 03/11/2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Bigelow mouth to check for foreign objects and none were found.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bigelow was provided her Advice of Rights via the audio MVA version of the DR-15 Form along with a paper version to assist her in understanding the DR-15. At the conclusion of the audio version, Bigelow stated that she understood her Advice of Rights and refused to submit to a breath test at approximately 0256 hours.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;TRANSPORT&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; During transport to Princess Anne Barrack for processing. The odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Bigelow continued to be strong. Upon arrival at the Barrack, Bigelow was placed in the intoximeter room for processing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELEASE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bigelow was released to a sober driver at approximately 0625 hours on 03/11/2023.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CHARGES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bigelow was charged with the following citations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. 26V0XC3 DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. 26W0XC3 DRIVING VEH. WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3.&amp;nbsp;26X0XC3 DRIVING VEH. W/O ADEQUATE REAR REG. PLATE ILLUMINATION&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 4.&amp;nbsp;26Y0XC3 NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 5.&amp;nbsp;26Z0XC3 DIRECTING AND PERMITTING HWY. VEH. OPERATION CONTRARY TO LAW&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Somerset County, MD.&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 01:14:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7370</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 14:40:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Revel</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7146</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Salgueiro</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7370</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498341</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 02:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 00:23:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7370</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 00:23:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498341</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 02:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 00:23:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7370</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 00:23:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498341</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17023</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 02:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17023</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 00:23:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7370</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 00:23:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498341</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 02:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 00:23:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7370</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 00:23:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498341</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 02:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17272</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 00:23:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7370</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 00:23:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 00:33:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:42</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371414</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>BIGELOW</LastName>
               <FirstName>KATRINA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MURPHY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/27/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/13/2023 00:29:28</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K365</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>BIGELOW</LastName>
               <FirstName>KATRINA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MURPHY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/27/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K365</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/13/2023 00:29:28</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 00:33:39</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 00:33:39</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 00:23:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7370</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 00:23:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150814</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7370</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 01:11:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7370</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 01:11:48</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SCI</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1EZ9844</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>