<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012446</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/07/2023 22:59:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/07/2023 22:59:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/07/2023 22:42:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/07/2023 22:42:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 23:00:01</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 09:09:25</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MD-100 EB TO RITCHIE NB / RITCHIE HWY</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>689997</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 23:00:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 21:36:47</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>689997</AddressId>
         <StreetName>E/B MD-100</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Glen Burnie</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21061</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.613955</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.138848</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1-110 MD-100 EB TO RITCHIE NB / 0-0 RITCHIE HWY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/07/2023 22:59:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/07/2023 22:59:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/14/2023 22:14:33</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 23:00:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUI #: P-23-032&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CASE #: 23-MSP-012446&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEFENDANT: Brittney Maria Celano (MD C-450-098-585-234)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WITNESS: Andrew Patrick Morrissette (MD-10273051259) &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*THIS INCIDENT WAS RECORDED ON MY IN-CAR AND BODY WORN CAMERA SYSTEMS*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NARRATIVE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;On April 7, 2023, at approximately 2242 hours I, Trooper Keller #7360 was on routine patrol in my unmarked MSP vehicle P-14. I responded to a report of a reckless vehicle operation and possible impaired driver traveling on southbound I-97 near Dorsey Road. The complainant, later identified as Andrew Patrick Morrissette (W/M DOB: 03/12/1984), was following the suspect vehicle providing updated location and vehicle motion details to MSP Glen Burnie dispatchers. Dispatch relayed the information to me via radio. Dispatch advised multiple times that the vehicle was failing to maintain their lane and nearly causing multiple collisions. Following the updated locations, I first observed the suspect vehicle, a gray Nissan Rouge bearing Maryland registration 9ET6664, traveling in lane two of eastbound MD-100 prior to Oakwood Road.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 1 &amp;ndash; VEHICLE IN MOTION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Immediately upon positioning behind the Nissan, I observed the vehicle slowly drift left and cross over the lane division line into lane one, leaving only its passenger side tires in lane two. The maneuver caused a pickup truck, traveling beside me in lane one to abruptly activate his brake lights. The Nissan corrected back into lane two and then began hugging the rightmost portion of the lane. While passing the Oakwood road exit I observed the Nissan cross over the solid white line at the gore area with both passenger side tires. The vehicle corrected and moments later again crossed over the right white fog line with approximately half the width of the vehicle. While following the Nissan I was maintaining a consistent distance while traveling at approximately 35 MPH in a posted 55 MPH zone. I activated my emergency lights to conduct a traffic stop on the vehicle. After receiving no reaction for approximately 10 seconds, I utilized my siren to alert the driver while their vehicle was again partially traveling on the right shoulder. The Nissan activated their right turn signal and brake lights and stopped on the right shoulder past Oakwood Road.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 2 &amp;ndash; PERSONAL CONTACT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Upon my drivers side approach to the Nissan, I observed a white female driver who was the sole occupant of the vehicle. The driver, later identified as Brittney Maria Celano (W/F DOB: 03/23/1996) by her Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license, stated that she was traveling from happy hour at the Crafty Crab restaurant and was &amp;ldquo;just trying to get home&amp;rdquo;. Celano stated that she has a new address in Rosedale and that was her destination. Celano&amp;rsquo;s direction of travel was inconsistent with her destination. Given information provided to me through dispatch, Celano traveled from southbound I-97 to eastbound MD-100 while being followed by the complainant, Morrissette. Celano was travelling well south and in the opposite direction of her destination.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I asked Celano why she was failing to maintain her lane and she stated that she was &amp;ldquo;tired&amp;rdquo;. I then asked her how much sleep she had the night prior. Celano stated that she woke up at 8 a.m. for work and after getting off at 5 p.m. went to the restaurant for happy hour. Celano stated that while at the restaurant she had consumed one Margarita, adding that it was approximately the size of a &amp;ldquo;solo cup&amp;rdquo;. While speaking with Celano and collecting her documentation I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from inside the passenger compartment of the vehicle. Celano&amp;rsquo;s speech was heavily slurred and slow and her eyes were bloodshot. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 3 &amp;ndash; PRE-ARREST SCREENING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Based on my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, I suspected Celano was impaired by alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. Celano agreed to submit to standardized field sobriety testing. The tests were performed on the right shoulder in an area that was level and free of debris. The weather was clear and the test began at approximately 2247 hours. Celano advised me that she was not on any medications, had no present injuries, removed her eyeglasses for HGN testing and wore them for the remainder of the tests. Celano also confirmed that she could see my stimulus (pen) in front of her face.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instructions: Celano was told to stand with her feet together and her arms down at her side. A stimulus (ink pen) was held approximately twelve to fifteen inches from Celano&amp;rsquo;s face, and she was asked to follow the stimulus with her eyes only and to not move her head. Prior to beginning the test, I asked Celano if she understood the instructions. Celano answered yes. I initially checked for equal pupil size, resting nystagmus, and equal tracking. I next checked for lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees. Lastly, I checked for vertical gaze nystagmus. Both eyes were checked twice for each clue.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results: 6/6. VGN present. &lt;/strong&gt;Celano had brown colored eyes. Both pupils were equal in size and equally tracking the stimulus. Resting nystagmus was not present. Nystagmus was observed in each eye during all three observations. Vertical gaze nystagmus was present indicating high level of alcohol in Celano&amp;rsquo;s system, specifically for her person. While completing the test Celano lost track of the stimulus multiple times. I observed her swaying side to side approximately 4 inches during the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;WALK AND TURN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instructions: Celano was told to stand with her right foot in front of her left foot in a heel to toe manner. She was told to stay in that position and keep her arms at her side until being told to begin the test. I asked Celano if she understood and she answered yes. I began explaining and demonstrating the test. Celano was instructed to take nine heel to toe steps on a straight, imaginary line. On the ninth step, she was instructed to leave her lead foot planted and take a series of small steps to turn 180 degrees. Celano was told to then take an additional nine heel to toe steps back down the same imaginary line. She was told to gaze down at her feet, count the steps out loud, keep her hands at her side, touch heel to toe on every step, and to not stop walking until the test is complete. I asked Celano if she understood the instructions before beginning and she answered yes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results: 8/8. &lt;/strong&gt;While assuming the starting position Celano continually placed her right foot in the rear instead of her left as instructed. I repeated the instruction and demonstration of the starting position three times before she corrected her footing. While explaining the test Celano began walking forward prior to being told to begin. Prior to beginning her first set of steps Celano attempted to answer a phone call on her smart watch. I advised her that the person calling can wait and to begin the test when ready. Celano lost balance twice while in the starting position. After the second time she made no attempt to get back in the position until it was time for the first set of steps.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;On the first set of steps, Celano initially took eight steps and then stopped walking attempting to turn off her smartwatch. Celano did not count any of her steps out loud as instructed. I advised Celano to continue as instructed. Celano continued walking in the same direction and made no attempt to turn. On the first set of steps, Celano completed 19 steps before I stopped her and asked her how many I had advised her to take. Celano stated 9. I then asked her how many steps she had taken and she stated, &amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t count because I was worried about my mom&amp;rdquo;, who had been calling her. I asked Celano if she was having difficulty dividing her attention between two tasks and she stated, &amp;ldquo;yeah, I know&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I advised Celano that now that she has finished the first set of steps to continue in the way I had instructed. Celano again began walking in the same direction until I told her to stop. Celano did not complete the turn or second set of steps as instructed due to her inability to follow instructions. During the first set of steps, Celano maintained approximately 2 inches between her heel and toe on all steps. On steps 4 and 6 Celano stepped off line to the right, crossing her left foot over her right, and lifted her left arm approximately 7 inches to maintain balance. On both instances, Celano had to reset her footing to continue walking.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ONE LEG STAND&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instructions: Celano was instructed to stand with her feet together and her hands at her side while I explained the instructions and demonstrated the test. Celano was told to raise either foot of her choice approximately six inches off the ground while keeping it parallel to the ground. She was told to begin to count, one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-three...etc. Celano was instructed to continue counting until I told her to stop. She was told to gaze down at her feet, to count out loud, to keep her arms at her side, and to not put her foot down. I then asked if Celano understood the instructions and she answered yes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results: 4/4.&lt;/strong&gt; Celano chose to lift her left leg for the test. For the first 7 seconds of the test Celano lifted both arms approximately 12 inches from her sides to maintain balance. I advised her to keep her hands down at her side and she complied. I observed Celano swaying side to side approximately 4 inches for the entirety of the test. At 13 seconds, Celano leaned to the right, again lifted her arms, and began hopping on her right foot to maintain balance. Celano dropped her foot to the ground at approximately 18 seconds, 21 seconds, and 27 seconds. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Celano was offered a roadside Preliminary Breath Test (PBT). Celano refused the test. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Based on my observations and my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, Celano was placed under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol at approximately 2259 hours. Following the arrest, I asked Celano if she had a phone in the car I could retrieve prior to securing her vehicle. Celano stated it was in her pocket, although I observed it mounted to the vehicle&amp;#39;s dashboard. I secured Celano in my patrol vehicle and transported her to the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie barrack for processing. During transport, Celano was generally quiet, occasionally asking questions about the upcoming process. I explained the process to Celano including her being able to contact a sober ride home following processing. Moments later Celano asked, &amp;ldquo;Will I be able to call someone once we get there&amp;rdquo;. I again advised Celano that she would be able to make a call for a ride after the paperwork regarding the incident was completed. While speaking with Celano in my vehicle, there was a strong odor of alcohol emanating from her breath and her speech was consistently slow and slurred. We arrived at the barrack at approximately 2319 hours. While exiting my vehicle Celano was crying. I escorted Celano into the barracks DWI room and she was provided a copy of her DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along as I read the form out loud in its entirety. After reading the form I answered basic questions Celano had by pointing out the answered within the form. I asked Celano if she understood the form and she answered yes. At approximately 2334 hours, Celano refused to submit to the intoximeter test. &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Celano was placed in a temporary holding cell while the remainder of the paperwork and citations were completed. Her license was confiscated and forwarded to the MVA along with a DR-15A Order of Suspension.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DISPOSITION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;At approximately 0027 hours on April 8, Celano was released to the custody of her fianc&amp;eacute;. Celano was provided with all appropriate paperwork and citations from the incident. I asked Celano if she knew the location of her vehicle to retrieve it at a later time and she stated &amp;ldquo;yeah&amp;rdquo;. I asked her what roadway her vehicle was on and she stated that she did not know. Celano was provided with the location of her vehicle along with the documentation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FURTHER INVESTIGATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;On April 8, 2023, at approximately 1900 hours, I contacted witness Andrew Morrissette via phone call. Morrissette stated that while traveling on eastbound I-695 near MD-295 he observed multiple vehicles ahead of him abruptly activating their break lights and maneuvering around a gray colored Nissan SUV. Morrissette stated that he observed the vehicle partially traveling on the left shoulder with its right turn signal activated. He stated he observed the vehicle slowly drift over to the right appearing to continue eastbound on I-695, but then followed the vehicle and contacted 911 once he observed the Nissan travel to the left through the solid white lines of the gore area to continue onto southbound I-97. Morrissette stated that while following the vehicle south on I-97 its speeds fluctuated drastically and it was operating erratically while traveling &amp;ldquo;all over the road&amp;rdquo;. Morrissette stated that the Nissan left the roadway and traveled onto the shoulder multiple times nearly coming in contact with multiple vehicles, concrete barriers, and a motorcycle who had to maneuver out of the Nissans path. Morrissette stated that he followed the Nissan off the MD-100 exit in which it originally was taking the ramp to continue westbound but &amp;ldquo;at the last second&amp;rdquo; turned left through the gore area to travel eastbound. Morrissette stated that he again watched the vehicle failing to maintain travel in lane two and drift left in front of a red Chevrolet pickup truck which &amp;ldquo;locked its brakes&amp;rdquo; to avoid an accident. Morrissette added that while on MD-100 multiple vehicles including a motorcycle had to maneuver around the Nissan to avoid a collision. Morrissette stated that he does not have a dash camera or video footage from the incident.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7360</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 18:58:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7360</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 00:11:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CVED</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Donaldson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5015</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Litz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Simon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7362</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wiest</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4939</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Keller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brady</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7360</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501849</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 22:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7360</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 18:55:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7360</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 18:55:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7360</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 18:57:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:26</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373780</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Celano</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brittney</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Maria</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/23/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 16:18:32</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C450</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B635</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Celano</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brittney</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Maria</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/23/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C450</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B635</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 16:18:32</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5090</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Silver Oak</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Rosedale</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21237</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3395</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.47578</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.374478</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>904</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3798</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7360</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 18:57:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7360</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 18:57:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7360</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 18:57:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7360</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 18:57:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7360</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 21:43:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373795</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Morrissette</LastName>
               <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Patrick</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/12/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 21:42:56</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M623</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A536</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Morrissette</LastName>
               <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Patrick</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/12/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M623</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A536</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 21:42:56</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>624</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Oakland Hills</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>402</SubNumber>
               <City>Arnold</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21012</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.472106</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.046162</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>903</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0277</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7360</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 21:43:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7360</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 21:43:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7360</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 18:55:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7360</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 18:55:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151761</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7360</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 18:57:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7360</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 18:57:55</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5N1AT2MV1KC774235</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>RGE</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9ET6664</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>