<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011587</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/01/2023 02:02:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/01/2023 02:02:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/01/2023 01:48:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/01/2023 01:48:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI arrest of Billy Gene Jackson III.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 02:02:05</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/15/2023 00:17:16</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY/ OCEAN EXPY</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>586954</AddressId>
      <City>MDC108</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 02:02:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 21:18:28</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>586954</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>EXPY</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.269659</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.36862</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>8621-8625 OCEAN GTWY / 1-151 OCEAN EXPY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50 COMING UP ON 90</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50 BETWEEN 90 AND 346</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>8627-8897 OCEAN GTWY / 102-104 OCEAN EXPY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>8628-8898 OCEAN GTWY / 2-100 OCEAN EXPY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>8621-8625 OCEAN GTWY / 106-152 OCEAN EXPY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>8251-8619 OCEAN GTWY / 1-151 OCEAN EXPY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>8600-8626 OCEAN GTWY / 2-100 OCEAN EXPY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/01/2023 02:02:03</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/01/2023 02:02:03</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/15/2023 00:07:27</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 02:02:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:47</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Billy Gene Jackson III&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Maryland SOUNDEX: J-250-089-275-929&lt;br /&gt; Breath Test Result: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#f1c40f"&gt;0.12&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DWI Citation #: 4LP0J79&lt;br /&gt; DWI MVR/Body Cam #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-011587 (Axon View XL Software).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;TROOPER CERTIFICATES / TRAINING / SPECIAL ASSIGNMENTS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;1. Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; 2. Certified SFST Instructor.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 3. Chemical Breath Test Operator.&lt;br /&gt; 4. Graduate of the University of Maryland&amp;#39;s DUI Institute.&lt;br /&gt; 5. Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; 6. Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.).&lt;br /&gt; 7. Trained in Cannabis Impairment Detection (Maryland State Police).&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 8. Assigned to the Berlin Barrack &amp;quot;V&amp;quot; Special Enforcement Team (focusing exclusively on DUI enforcement) from October 2017 - June 2022.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;NARRATIVE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;-PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION-&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 04-01-2023 at approximately 0148 hours, I (Corporal J. Ruiz #6312), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating marked MSP vehicle V-14 in the area of Maryland Route 90 westbound at Coastal Highway (Ocean City). I was stationary on the right shoulder area prior to the Assawoman Bay Bridge, monitoring all westbound traffic exiting Ocean City onto MD Route 90. I was operating stationary radar. The in-car Kustom Golden Eagle II (MSP Serial #50010806) front radar antenna was activated and had been checked before (and later after) my shift and appeared to be functioning properly. At that time, I observed a truck traveling westbound approach my location at what appeared to be a high rate of speed. I made the following observations on the same vehicle:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;MD ROUTE 90 PRIOR TO THE ASSAWOMAN BAY BRIDGE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. The area between Coastal Highway and the beginning of the Assawoman Bay Bridge is a posted &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;40 MPH zone&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. As the vehicle continued traveling westbound, a speed of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;61 MPH&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; in a posted 40 MPH zone was captured as the vehicle entered the influence of the radar beam.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;I safely entered the roadway and followed the same truck. There were four (4) sedans between my patrol vehicle and the truck. I was able to close in on the same truck on MD Route 90 near Mile Marker 7.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;BETWEEN MILE MARKER 7 AND THE U.S. ROUTE 113 EXITS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. The vehicle&amp;rsquo;s right tires &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;crossed&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (1 tire width) the solid white line into the right shoulder area on &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;five (5) occasions&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane each time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;MARYLAND ROUTE 346 UNDERPASS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 4. The vehicle&amp;rsquo;s right tires &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;crossed&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt; the solid white shoulder line on two (2) occasions. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane each time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 5. The vehicle&amp;rsquo;s left tires &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;crossed&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; the solid yellow center double line on one (1) occasion. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ADDITIONAL OBSERVATIONS&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 6. The vehicle failed to maintain proper lane position due to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;pronounced and excessive weaving&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (alternately moving toward one side of the lane and then the other) during the entire duration of my observations.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 7. Total distance traveled was approximately 9.70 miles.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;DWI INDICATORS / REASON FOR STOP&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHSTA) published a &amp;quot;The Visual Detection of DWI Motorists&amp;quot; booklet in March 2010. The research revealed that DWI cues related to problems in maintaining proper lane position include:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Weaving&lt;br /&gt; 2. Weaving across lane lines&lt;br /&gt; 3. Drifting&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All of the above DWI indicators were exhibited by the same truck prior to my initiating a traffic stop.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;TRAFFIC STOP&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I activated the emergency lights to my patrol vehicle, initiating a traffic stop on U.S. Route 50 westbound just west of the MD Route 90 overpass. The vehicle was a silver 2013 Ford F-150 bearing Maryland Registration 4DA7527.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;-PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT-&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the driver via the driver side door, and I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop and requested the driver&amp;rsquo;s license and the registration card to the vehicle. I noticed what appeared to be law enforcement credentials (gold badge and identification card) laying on the driver&amp;rsquo;s lap. The driver was identified as Billy Gene Jackson III by his Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license. I asked Jackson where he was traveling from, and he responded: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Uh, we went to Seacrets&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. I asked Jackson where he was traveling to, and he replied: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Uh, goin&amp;rsquo; home&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. I asked Jackson how much he had to drink earlier in the evening, and he advised: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Uh, I had a Pain In The Ass&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As Jackson spoke, I made the following observations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. I intentionally observed his eyes to be &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;glassy and bloodshot&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Jackson.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I later returned to the Ford and requested Jackson exit the vehicle and walk to the front of it, to which he complied. While at the front of the vehicle, I continued to speak with Jackson. I asked Jackson again where he was traveling from, and he stated: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Comin&amp;rsquo; from Seacrets, sir&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. I asked Jackson who he was employed with, and he replied: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Maryland Natural Resources Police&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. I asked Jackson how long he had been employed with the agency, and he responded: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;3 and a half years&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. I asked Jackson how many total alcoholic beverages he had consumed prior to driving, and he advised: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not a big drinker. So, like a had a Pain In The Ass and like a, some other drink I don&amp;rsquo;t know they got me. I haven&amp;rsquo;t got out man much because, um, my grandmother passed and my mom passed&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. When asked at approximately what time he had finished consuming his last drink prior to driving, Jackson stated: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Imma say at least about an hour&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. As Jackson spoke, I smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I informed Jackson that I wanted him to perform field sobriety tests which he agreed to submit to.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;-PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING-&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder area. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and vehicle headlamps. Weather was clear and approximately 50 degrees. I asked Jackson if he had any significant medical issues with his eyes, arms, or legs which would prevent him from performing the field sobriety tests or if he had taken any medication prior to driving. Jackson responded: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;No, sir&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Jackson appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries, limps, or any limb ailments.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Jackson was wearing a black windbreaker, black jeans, and black/gray/orange athletic-type shoes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Jackson displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. Jackson displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. Jackson displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**WALK AND TURN: 2 of 8 clues**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Jackson missed heel-to-toe on steps 1 and 9 during the first series. Jackson missed heel-to-toe on step 2 during the second series. All misses were of more than half an inch.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. Jackson was unable to maintain a straight line and stepped off the line on all steps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**ONE LEG STAND: 2 of 4 clues**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Jackson&amp;rsquo;s body swayed to the left and right on counts 16 and 19.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. Jackson put his left foot down on counts 16, 18, and 19.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ADDITIONAL TESTING&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**ALPHABET TEST**:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Jackson advised that he was a high school graduate and that he was capable of reciting the English alphabet and numbers. I instructed Jackson to recite from the letter &amp;#39;F&amp;#39; to the letter &amp;#39;S&amp;#39;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Jackson recited in the following manner: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;A-B-C-H-I-K-A-B-C-D-E-F-A-B-C-D-A-B-C-D-F-G-H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P-Q-R-S&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**COUNT TEST**:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I instructed Jackson to count backwards from 36-19.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Completed satisfactorily.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Jackson the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Jackson submitted to a preliminary breath test with a reading of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#f1c40f"&gt;0.134&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; BrAC.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ARREST&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Jackson was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;* Driving vehicle in a negligent manner which caused it to commit 8 lane violations in addition to traveling above the posted speed limit and excessive weaving &amp;ndash; &lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#f1c40f"&gt;DRIVING SKILLS IMPAIRED&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Admission to consuming more than one (1) alcoholic beverage prior to operating a motor vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * PBT result of 0.134 BrAC.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I determined that Jackson was impaired by the presence of an alcoholic beverage in his system that adversely affected his ability to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests properly can also adversely affect the person&amp;rsquo;s ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. I placed Jackson under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0201 hours on 04-01-2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Jackson&amp;rsquo;s mouth for any foreign objects and none were found. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Jackson was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Jackson was given his Advice of Rights via the audio version of the DR-15 Form (played through the patrol vehicle&amp;rsquo;s Bluetooth speakers). At the conclusion of the audio version, I verbally re-explained the driver&amp;rsquo;s license sanctions and penalties (section printed in red) to Jackson. Jackson stated that he understood his Advice of Rights and agreed to submit to a breath test at approximately 0219 hours on 04-01-2023.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;TRANSPORT&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Jackson was subsequently transported to the Berlin Barrack for processing. During transport, the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Jackson continued to be strong.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;**INTOXIMETER RESULT**:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to the breath test, I observed Corporal M. Shockley #4814 visually check the inside of Jackson&amp;rsquo;s mouth for any foreign objects. None were found.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The breath test was administered by CPL Shockley at approximately 0244 hours on 04-01-2023, and two (2) sufficient samples of Jackson&amp;rsquo;s breath were obtained. The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#f1c40f"&gt;0.12&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;RELEASE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Jackson was released from the Berlin Barrack to a sober driver (Captain M. Corbin of the Maryland Natural Resources Police) at approximately 0342 hours on 04-01-2023.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CHARGES&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Jackson was charged with the following citations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (4LP0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 2. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol Per Se (4LQ0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 3. Driving Vehicle While Impaired By Alcohol (4LR0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 4. Speed: 61 MPH In A Posted 40 MPH Zone (4LS0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 5. Failure To Obey Designated Lane Directions (4LT0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 6. Failure To Drive Right Of Center (4LV0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 7. Negligent Driving (4LW0J79)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 21:24:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 19:03:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500990</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/01/2023 21:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 21:17:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 21:21:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500990</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/01/2023 21:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 21:17:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 21:21:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500990</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/01/2023 21:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 21:17:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 21:20:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500990</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/01/2023 21:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 21:17:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 21:20:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500990</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/01/2023 21:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 21:17:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 21:19:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 21:17:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:21</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373187</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Jackson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Billy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Gene</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/06/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14111303E8</SSN>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>04/01/2023 20:31:58</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Jackson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Billy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Gene</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/06/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14111303E8</SSN>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>J250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/01/2023 20:31:58</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>29880</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Brighton</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Delmar</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21875</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.576219</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.434093</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>859</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2185</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 21:22:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 21:22:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 21:18:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 21:18:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151543</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 21:23:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 21:23:53</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FTFW1EF1DFD43544</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>F-150</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4DA7527</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>10</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>