<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000979</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/09/2023 00:22:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/09/2023 00:22:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/09/2023 00:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/09/2023 00:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI//DWI (6LR0MF8-6M30MF8)</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 00:22:20</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 21:52:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I695 / HARFORD RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>582504</AddressId>
      <City>MDC501</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 00:22:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 20:23:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>582504</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I695</StreetName>
         <City>Parkville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.5306</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.38798</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL BTW XT 30 AND 31 RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL @ 31 B</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 0-0 HARFORD RD RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L I695 / 9058-9098 HARFORD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IL @ EXT 31</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL @ HARFORD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IL PT HARFORD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IL LS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I695 / 9059-9099 HARFORD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L I695 @ HARFORD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL PT PERRING RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L  HARFORD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OUTER LOOP //  HARFORD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 9046-9056 HARFORD RD RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL BTWN 30B AND 31 RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL@ PUTTY HILL LS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 9046-9056 HARFORD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L I-695 AT HARFORD ROAD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L @ HARFORD RD   RIGHT SHOULDER</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 9059-9099 HARFORD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L AT  HARFORD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IL @ 31 C</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L I-695 PRIOR TO HARFORD ROAD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL PT HARFORD RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L @  HARFORD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL BTWN HARFORD AND PERRING RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 OL / 0-0 HARFORD RD RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 0-0 HARFORD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L I-695 AT HARFORD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 9058-9098 HARFORD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L 695 @ 31B</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>L BTWN HARFORD AND BEL AIR RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 9045-9057 HARFORD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/09/2023 00:22:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/09/2023 00:22:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/23/2023 21:52:32</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 00:22:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:23:06</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>TFC Wilson #6512&lt;br /&gt; Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; Golden Ring Barrack&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Assigned patrol vehicle, unmarked unit R-21, and I are equipped with an Axon camera. This stop was recorded.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; APPLICABLE CERTIFICATIONS &amp;amp; TRAINING&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *October 24-28, 2022: Certified EC/IR II Breath Test Operator&lt;br /&gt; *May 7, 2020: Traffic Safety Specialist - Program Designation I&lt;br /&gt; *September 23-27, 2019: Basic Criminal Investigation&lt;br /&gt; *February 22, 2017: A.R.I.D.E. (16 hours)&lt;br /&gt; *Certified Preliminary Breath Test Operator&lt;br /&gt; *September 1-4, 2014: USDOT NHTSA DWI Detection and SFST Course&lt;br /&gt; *June 23, 2014-December 12, 2014: Maryland State Police Academy, Class 142, Treasurer&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;_____________________________________________________________________________ &lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Defendant:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cordova Sanchez, Isahi&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Address:&lt;br /&gt; 427 Shirley Manor Rd&lt;br /&gt; Reisterstown, MD 21136&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Vehicle:&lt;br /&gt; MD 5FF9751&lt;br /&gt; Toyota Corolla (white)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; DUI# 23-023&lt;/div&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Vehicle in Motion:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On 01/08/2023 at approximately 2358hrs I, TFC Wilson #6512, was on routine patrol on the outer loop north of I-95 prior to Belair Rd. At the that time, I observed a white Toyota Corolla entering the outer loop I-695 from the I-95 ramp at an apparent high rate of speed which appeared to be above the posted speed limit of 55 mph. I knew this due to my training in speed estimates as well as my current speed being approximately 65 mph and the vehicle was consistently pulling away.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I began to increase speed in effort to obtain an accurate speed of the Toyota using RADAR. I observed the Toyota merge all the way left using its left turn signal lamp to maneuver to lane 1. Once in lane 1, the Toyota entered my RADAR&amp;rsquo;s field on influence as I closed the distance toward it. I detected a high-pitched Doppler tone and observed the speed of 85 mph in a clearly posted 55 mph zone. A speed limit speed with this posted speed was observed on the right portion of the roadway after this speed was obtained.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;As I was within distance to observe the Maryland registration of 5FF9751, I observed the Toyota slow and its interior map lamp was on. As the Toyota continued in lane 1, its left turn signal was still activated, and I observed it swerving from side to side within the lane. Just past the onramp for Belair Rd, the Toyota&amp;rsquo;s driver side tires crossed onto the left solid yellow line which separates the left shoulder. The Toyota the appeared to jerk the wheel back toward the center of the lane. After this occurred, the Toyota began increasing speed and the map light was turned off.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The Toyota was observed quickly approaching another vehicle in lane 1. I anticipated the Toyota to conduct a lane change so I merged to lane 2 with more than enough distance to allow for the Toyota to safely make the lane change as well. I then observed the Toyota increasing close distance to the other vehicle which appeared to be a white sedan. I observed the Toyota was behind the white sedan so close, well within 1 car length, that its headlamps had a glaring reflection of the rear of the it. I then observed the white sedan begin to proceed right toward lane 2 just as the Toyota was attempting to change lanes to lane 2 with its right turn signal now activated. Thankfully the Toyota did not collide with the white sedan and diverted back to lane 1 to pass it. The Toyota then kept the right turn signal activated as it continued to drive in lane 1.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;After observing these violations which were directly jeopardized the safety of other operators, I maneuvered my patrol vehicle into lane 1 directly behind the Toyota and activated my emergency equipment at approximately 0000hrs on 1/09/2023. The Toyota brake lamps activated, but it continued in lane 1 without immediately yielding. The Toyota then began to slowly merge right and then stopped on the right shoulder prior to Harford Rd.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I then exited my patrol vehicle and contacted the Toyota on the passenger side front window.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Personal Contact:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I observed the Toyota was occupied by 3 subjects. A driver, front passenger, and one rear passenger. I introduced myself, advised the stop was being recorded, and the reason for the stop. The driver advised he was heading home. While at the vehicle, I detected an overwhelming odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from within the vehicle. I observed the driver had glassy and bloodshot eyes. I asked if the driver consumed any alcohol and he indicated yes. I asked the driver for his license. He advised he didn&amp;rsquo;t have one or have any form of identification. I then went to the driver side of the Toyota to obtain his information and speak with him further. The driver provided a name and date of birth of Isahi Cordova Sanchez (H/M DOB 12/08/1996). Cordova Sanchez advised that he lived at 427 Shirly Manor Rd, Reisterstown. While speaking with him, I detected an overwhelming odor of an alcoholic beverage. I asked Cordova Sanchez who owned the car, and he advised &amp;ldquo;his friend.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I returned to my patrol vehicle and conducted routine check via METERS/NCIC. It revealed the vehicle was registered to Cordova Sanchez. Records also indicated Cordova Sanchez had no record of a license. I then attempted to further identify Cordova Sanchez by conducting checks using law enforcement databases including LINX. A LINX record revealed Cordova Sanchez was arrested by US Customs and Border Protection for an immigration violation on 3/17/2016. A booking photograph was viewed in which I utilized to positively identify Cordova Sanchez.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I also requested a back-up unit to respond to assist with my intention to ask Cordova Sanchez to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Officer&amp;rsquo;s from the Baltimore County Police Department arrived shortly afterwards.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Cordova Sanchez was asked to exit the vehicle and complied. While outside the vehicle, I detected strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I asked Cordova Sanchez to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. He began to tell me that he consumed two beers and today was his &amp;ldquo;birthday.&amp;rdquo; This was later clarified that he was celebrating his birthday. He then went on to tell me that his birth is 12/08/1996 and the &amp;ldquo;plate&amp;rdquo; on the vehicle was his friend&amp;rsquo;s, but car was his. Cordova Sanchez was asked again if he wanted to perform SFSTs. He advised &amp;ldquo;no.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Pre-Arrest Screening:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Initially refused SFSTs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Arrest:&lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had probable cause to arrest Cordova Sanchez for DUI:&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Cordova Sanchez driving his Toyota at 85mph in a clearly posted 55mph zone.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Cordova Sanchez failing to maintain the lane of travel and swerving.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Cordova Sanchez following a white sedan well within 1 car length and nearly getting into a collision.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Overwhelming odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Cordova Sanchez&amp;rsquo;s vehicle, breath, and person.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Cordova Sanchez refusing to submit to SFST&amp;rsquo;s roadside.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cordova Sanchez was arrested at 0017hrs. He was searched incident to arrest including and oral cavity check. Cordova Sanchez was placed in the front seat of my patrol vehicle. His phone and keys were obtained from his vehicle. The two other occupants were provided courtesy rides off of the roadway. Cordova Sanchez&amp;rsquo;s vehicle was locked and secured.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cordova Sanchez was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack for processing. While interacting with Cordova Sanchez, I observed he knew some English but there was some difficulty during communication. I requested a Spanish speaking Trooper/Officer to assist. During transport, I began to play the Spanish language version of the DR-15 provided by the MVA Information for Law Enforcement website&lt;br /&gt; (https://mva.maryland.gov/Pages/police.aspx). Once at the barrack, the audio as paused and Cordova Sanchez was directed to the DUI processing room. A secondary search was completed then he was allowed to utilized the restroom in cell 2. Once finished he was directed back to the DUI processing room, provided a paper copy of the DR-15 and directed to the back of the form where Spanish is written. The audio resumed until completion. After the DR-15 was read, I then contact Gabriella #394656 from Language Line Solutions to assist. Cordova Sanchez was read Advice of Miranda Rights and agreed to waive his rights.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked Cordova Sanchez if he would like to submit to SFSTs. He agreed. Utilizing Gabriella to provide translation, SFSTs were conducted in the DUI processing room and hallway beside the room. The barrack is a climate controlled with standard room lighting. The floors are level and consist of a tile-like material.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cordova Sanchez was asked about the following:&lt;br /&gt; Glasses/Contacts: No&lt;br /&gt; Medications: None&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Injuries: None. Cordova Sanchez did indicate something was wrong was with his vision which but did not elaborate and advised he was ok. Cordova Sanchez advised he had no problems driving. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Cordova Sanchez appeared to be in good health.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS TEST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; His eyes were checked and they displayed equal tracking and his pupils were equal sizes. Cordova Sanchez was instructed to follow the stimulus with his eyes only, keeping his head still. After stating that he understood the instructions, Cordova Sanchez attempted this test. No resting nystagmus was observed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The results of this test displayed 6 of the 6 possible clues.&lt;br /&gt; - A lack of smooth pursuit in the left eye&lt;br /&gt; - A lack of smooth pursuit in the right eye&lt;br /&gt; - A distinct and sustained nystagmus in the left eye at maximum deviation&lt;br /&gt; - A distinct and sustained nystagmus in the right eye at maximum deviation&lt;br /&gt; - An onset of nystagmus in the left eye prior to 45 degrees.&lt;br /&gt; - An onset of nystagmus in the right eye prior to 45 degrees.&lt;br /&gt; The test revealed the presence of vertical nystagmus.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;WALK AND TURN TEST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cordova Sanchez was instructed to put his left foot on the line and his right foot in front of it with his right heel touching the toe of his left foot. He was instructed to stand in this manner with his hands to his sides until the test instructions were completed and the test demonstrated. Cordova Sanchez was instructed not to begin the test until told to start. He was instructed to take nine steps along the line in a heel-to-toe manner. After the ninth step he was to stop and turn around keeping his lead foot on the ground, taking several small steps with the other foot to turn around. After turning around, he was to take nine steps in a heel-to-toe manner back along the line, in the direction he had come from. Cordova Sanchez was further instructed to watch his feet at all times while walking, keep his arms down to his side, and to count his steps out loud. After the test was demonstrated Cordova Sanchez stated that he understood the instructions and was instructed to begin the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The results of this test displayed 5 of the 8 possible clues:&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;He was unable to maintain his balance in the instructed position by using the wall for support&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;After the turn, he leaned back and stopped briefly to regain balance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On the second series of 9 steps, he did not touch heel-to-toe on step 1.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On the second series of 9 steps, he stepped off the line on step 1.&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;He used his arms throughout the test for balance.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND TEST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cordova Sanchez was instructed to stand with his feet together and arms at his sides during the test. Cordova Sanchez was asked not to begin the test until instructed. He was instructed to raise the leg of his choice by approximately 6 inches off the ground. While holding that position, he was to keep his leg straight and count out loud starting at one thousand one (one thousand one, one thousand two, one thousand three, &amp;hellip;) and so forth until instructed to stop (after 30 seconds). The test was demonstrated to Cordova Sanchez.&lt;br /&gt; After he indicated understanding the instructions, Cordova Sanchez attempted the test and raised his right leg.&lt;br /&gt; The result of this test displayed 4 of the 4 possible clues:&lt;br /&gt; - Swayed during the test&lt;br /&gt; - Used arms for balance&lt;br /&gt; - Hopped in order to remain on one foot&lt;br /&gt; - Put foot down once during the test (After approximately 10 seconds)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After SFSTs were performed, Cordova Sanchez was asked to review the DR-15 and if he had any questions. He was then asked if he wanted to submit to an alcohol concentration test. He refused to submit at approximately 0117hrs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cordova Sanchez was issued a DR-15A and appropriate citations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While completing paperwork, Cordova Sanchez advised he consumed approximately 4-5 beers at an establishment in Baltimore, but he couldn&amp;rsquo;t recall the name. Cordova Sanchez advised he is from Mexico and that he used to be a police officer there.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cordova Sanchez was provided with copies of all paperwork and released at approximately 0202hrs to Francis Sifontes Mejia from the MSP Golden Ring Barrack.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cordova Sanchez was polite and cooperative throughout this investigation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I request this case to be closed by arrest.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; All event occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 05:59:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 22:40:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Twardowski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wilson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gregory</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6512</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490357</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/09/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490357</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/09/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490357</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/09/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490357</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/09/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490357</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/09/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490357</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15566</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/09/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490357</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/09/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490357</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/09/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490357</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15558</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/09/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490357</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15546</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/09/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:56:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365707</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>CORDOVA SANCHEZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>ISAHI</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/08/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/09/2023 22:51:13</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C631</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>CORDOVA SANCHEZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>ISAHI</FirstName>
               <DOB>12/08/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C631</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/09/2023 22:51:13</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>427</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Shirley Manor</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Reisterstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21136</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.819633</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.459471</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>905</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1613</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:56:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:56:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:56:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 22:49:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148460</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 23:10:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 23:10:35</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>COA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5FF9751</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>