<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-006290</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/18/2023 03:15:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/18/2023 03:15:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/18/2023 02:35:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/18/2023 02:35:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>On Saturday, February 18th, 2023 at approximately 0235, I, TFC Mohr #6743, assigned to the Maryland State Police, Waterloo Barracks was on patrol in the area of N/B I-95 and Gorman Road. I observed a gray Toyota Tacoma traveling above the posted speed limit of 65 miles per hour, specifically, 94 miles per hour in a 65 mph zone. I stopped the Toyota after making our way toward the rest area. I interviewed the driver and detected impairment. SFST's were performed poorly by the driver and he was arrested for DUI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 03:15:37</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5372</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/01/2023 13:57:57</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>319826</AddressId>
      <City>MDC182</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 03:15:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/20/2023 20:21:06</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>319826</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>N</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>I-95 REST AREA</StreetName>
         <City>Laurel</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/18/2023 03:15:33</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/18/2023 03:15:33</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>50</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/20/2023 23:55:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 03:15:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:20</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The below incident was recorded on an in-car camera system, &amp;ldquo;A-5&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;TFC Mohr is equipped with a body-worn camera (AXON Body 3 No. 00016805)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scene Processing&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Due to the nature of the incident, scene processing was not conducted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evidence Processing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Due to the nature of the incident, evidence processing was not conducted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Training/Knowledge/Experience for TFC Mohr:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Proficiency in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST&amp;rsquo;s) per National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) Manual-Gained during Maryland State Police (MSP) Academy (Class 145, 2016)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;NHTSA Certified SFST Instructor- Gained through MSP CTAU (June 2021).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Advanced Roadside Impairment Detection and Enforcement (ARIDE) Trained in 2017 through MSP Chemical Test for Alcohol Unit (CTAU).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Attendee of 2019 DUI Conference through Maryland Highway Safety Office.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Over 100 DUI Arrests involving Alcohol impairment, Controlled dangerous substances impairment or both.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Over five years of active law enforcement officer duties including, but not limited to, traffic safety, DUI detection and DUI apprehension&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Certified Traffic Safety Specialist- gained in 2018.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Certified Preliminary Breath Test Operator-Through MSP CTAU and the Office of the Chief Medical Examiner (2016).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suspect&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lamberto Bautista Bacho&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hispanic male&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;DOB: 09/17/1984&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Address:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;41 Travis Court&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Gaithersburg, Maryland 20879&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;FIRST TIME DUI OFFENSE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Narrative:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;PHASE I, VEHICLE IN MOTION: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On Saturday, February 18, 2023 at approximately 0235 hours, I, Trooper First Class (TFC) Mohr #6743, assigned to the Maryland State Police (MSP), Waterloo Barracks, was on routine patrol in the area of Interstate 95 and Gorman Road in Laurel, Howard County, Maryland. I was working stationary laser enforcement, focused on northbound traffic, south of Gorman Road. I was operating MSP unit &amp;ldquo;A-5&amp;rdquo;, a black, un-marked Ford Explorer equipped with red and blue electronic lights along with a siren. I was dressed in the uniform of the day while on patrol. I am trained and certified in using a LIDAR speed-measuring device. I was operating a Kustom Signals Pro Laser III device, which I am trained and certified to use. At the above time and location, I was stopped in a crossover, out of the travel portion of the highway. My headlights and taillights were on. I observed a gray Toyota Tacoma, displaying Maryland registration, &amp;ldquo;7FC0775&amp;rdquo;, traveling toward my location and had appeared to be traveling over the posted speed limit of 65 miles per hour. I utilized the LIDAR unit, &amp;ldquo;Set 6&amp;rdquo;, to confirm my suspicion that the Toyota was traveling at a speed above 65 miles per hour. I captured a readout on the LIDAR unit: 94 miles per hour, at 939 feet away from my position. The Toyota passed my location in the crossover while in lane one. I got behind the Toyota, activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the Toyota. The Toyota came to a stop just inside the northbound Rest Area off I-95.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;PHASE II, PERSONAL CONTACT:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I exited my patrol vehicle and approached the driver&amp;rsquo;s side of the Toyota. I made contact with the driver, seated in the front seat. He was the sole occupant. I identified myself, stated that our conversation was being recorded and stated the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver for his license and he provided it. I identified the driver by his Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license as Lamberto Bautista Bacho, Hispanic male, DOB: 09/17/1984. He stated that he was trying to get home and was not having a good [day]. I could identify that he was wearing a green, paper wristband during our conversation. I returned to my patrol vehicle and radioed the driver&amp;rsquo;s information to the MSP Waterloo Barracks. A MILES/METERS/MVA check revealed that Bautista Bacho&amp;rsquo;s driver&amp;rsquo;s license and privilege was suspended through Maryland. The license plates on Bautista Bacho&amp;rsquo;s vehicle were also showing suspended. I also radioed for another unit to assist me. TFC Amoh #7037 arrived on scene at approximately 0256 hours. I made a second approach to the Toyota after I saw Bautista Bacho&amp;rsquo;s hand out the driver&amp;rsquo;s window. He stated he needed to urinate and I advised him that he should excuse himself to the right side of the entrance of the rest area, unseen by the public. Upon conclusion, I asked him to remain outside the vehicle to have a conversation with me about his license. I informed him that his license was suspended and that his registration plates were also suspended. He stated that the funds were mainly coming from his business account and seemed aware of the issue. During my conversation with him, I could detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath, in an ambient environment with vehicles passing by. I asked him where he was coming from and he stated that he was coming from a nightclub. I asked him when he consumed his last drink and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Thirty minutes ago.&amp;rdquo; I asked him how many drinks he had consumed and he said, &amp;ldquo;Five vodka and cranberry.&amp;rdquo; I advised Bautista Bacho that I was going to ask him to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST&amp;rsquo;s). He agreed to cooperate with the tests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;PHASE III, PRE-ARREST SCREENING:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The tests were performed in front of Bautista Bacho&amp;rsquo;s vehicle. Ambient light was provided by several streetlights and vehicle headlamps. I used a flashlight as well. The weather was cold with minimal wind conditions. There was no precipitation present at the time of the tests. The roadway was dry and the testing surface (asphalt) was flat and clear of any debris. I asked Bautista Bacho several questions pertaining to his medical history. He stated he was a cancer survivor and had been taking some medications previously, but was not taking them currently. He did not speak of any injuries sustained prior to beginning the tests. He wore a black leather jacket, with white jeans and black boots. The tests were explained in English, which Bautista Bahco understood.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;During the HGN test, he displayed &lt;strong&gt;four out of six possible clues of impairment.&lt;/strong&gt; No VGN was detected. Equal pupil size was verified and both eyes tracked the stimulus equally.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;He lacked smooth pursuit of the stimulus in both eyes. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;He had distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Walk and Turn:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prior to the WAT, I explained and demonstrated the entirety of the test. During the test, he displayed &lt;strong&gt;two out of eight possible clues of impairment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;During the instructional stage, he failed to keep his right foot in front of his left foot, touching heel to toe while I explained the test. He broke the stance three times before I instructed him to begin. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;During the first series of steps, he took 16 steps instead of the instructed nine. During the second series of steps, he took 18 steps instead of the instructed nine. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;One Leg Stand:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;During the OLS, he displayed one out of &lt;strong&gt;four possible clues of impairment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;During counts 1-4, he kept both his arms above his pants, greater than six inches. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I offered Bautista Bacho a preliminary breath test, which he agreed to take. His result was a .11 BrAC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;ARREST:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Based upon the above observations to include: erratic driving behavior, inability to follow instructions, the admission to consuming alcohol prior to driving, obvious divided attention during SFST&amp;rsquo;s and the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath, I placed Bautista Bacho under arrest for driving a vehicle while under the influence of alcohol at 0315 hours. He was handcuffed and secured in the front seat of my patrol vehicle. A search incident to arrest revealed no weapons or contraband. His Toyota was secured prior to responding to the barracks for continuation of the process. Upon arrival at the barracks, Bautista Bacho remained polite and cooperative. He was read his DR-15, Advice of Rights at 0348 hours and refused to submit to an intoximeter examination. A ride was summoned for him to be released from the barracks. Upon his release, Bautista Bacho received copies of his traffic citations, a DR-15A, Order of Suspension, and traffic citations appear notice for the District Court of Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Case closed by arrest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;All events occurred in Howard County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 21:26:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/20/2023 22:14:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Amoh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7037</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mohr</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6743</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gailor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zinnah</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1086</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mohr</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6743</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mohr</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6743</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495685</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 02:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 20:24:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/20/2023 20:26:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495685</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 02:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 20:26:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/20/2023 20:26:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 20:24:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:44</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369444</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bautista Bacho</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lamberto</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/17/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>9.44389889E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>02/18/2023 05:36:36</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B323</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L516</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bautista Bacho</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lamberto</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/17/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>9.44389889E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>B323</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L516</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/18/2023 05:36:36</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>41</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Travis</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Gaithersburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20879</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3316</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.214967</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.161596</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>717</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>781</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5781</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 20:28:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 20:28:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 20:28:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 20:28:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 20:24:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/20/2023 20:24:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149949</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/20/2023 20:28:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/20/2023 20:28:47</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3TMDZ5BN7KM058992</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>TAC</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7FC0775</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>8</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>