<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-010252</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/22/2023 01:41:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/22/2023 01:41:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/22/2023 01:23:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/22/2023 01:23:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI TS</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/22/2023 01:41:36</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 08:18:11</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I97 SB,GLEN BURNIE, 21061</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>688076</AddressId>
      <City>MDC421</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/22/2023 01:41:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/22/2023 03:09:35</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>688076</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I97 Sb</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GLN</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.6408026666667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.1692105</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/22/2023 01:41:33</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/22/2023 01:41:33</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/24/2023 01:19:10</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/22/2023 01:41:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*This stop was captured on in-car and body worn camera*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUI #: P-23-029&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CASE #: 23-MSP-010252&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUSPECT: Kass, Adam Richard (W/M DOB: 12/15/1973)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VICTIM: Society&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NARRATIVE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;On March 22, 2023 at approximately 0120 hours, I was on duty and in uniform operating unmarked MSP vehicle P-11. I was on routine patrol in the area of W/B I-695 at S/B I-97, Anne Arundel County, Maryland, when I first observed the suspect vehicle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 1 &amp;ndash; VEHICLE IN MOTION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;As I was traveling in lane 3, I observed the suspect vehicle traveling directly ahead of my location. As I was approaching the rear of the vehicle, I observed it drift slowly to the right causing the passenger side tires to cross the solid white shoulder line. The vehicle then quickly corrected back into lane 3 as I continued to follow the vehicle onto the ramp from W/B I-695 to S/B I-97. As the vehicle began to navigate the curve of the ramp, I observed the vehicle slowly drift to the left causing approximately half of the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s width to cross the solid yellow shoulder line before abruptly jerking to the right back to center. Shortly after correcting back to the center and while still attempting to navigate the long curve of the ramp, the vehicle again drifted to the left causing both driver side tires to cross the solid yellow shoulder line and then immediately and abruptly swerved back to the right. Almost instantly after correcting back to the right, the vehicle again drifted to the left once again causing half of the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s width to cross the solid yellow shoulder line as we then approached the merge point for S/B I-97.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; As the vehicle came to the bottom of the ramp and was preparing to merge, it suddenly began to drift to the right causing both passenger side tires to then cross the solid white shoulder line on the right, and then slowly correcting back to center merging. After merging into what was then lane 1, the vehicle activated its turn signal to change lanes into lane 2. After changing lanes into lane 2, the suspect vehicle deactivated its turn signal and continued in lane 2 for 1-2 seconds before slowly drifting to the right, across lane 3, and causing both passenger side tires to cross onto the right shoulder. While traveling in lane 3, the suspect vehicle continued to rock back and forth several times while also causing both passenger side tires to cross onto the right shoulder on another three occasions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; As we then began to pass Wellham Avenue, I changed lanes into lane 2 and attempted to pull alongside the suspect vehicle and made observations of the driver. As I was attempting to pull alongside the driver, I observed he did not appear to be distracted by any other object or person in the vehicle, and was staring straight ahead while leaning slightly forward. After making brief observations of the driver and beginning to slow my speed again to get back behind the suspect vehicle, it also slowed its speed. While I was continuing to slow my speed to allow the vehicle to pass, I continued to observe the vehicle rocking back and forth in lane 3, causing the vehicle to cross into both lane 2 and the right shoulder on at least one occasion for each. At one point while slowing my speed, I was traveling approximately 40 MPH lane 2 of I-97, a 65 MPH highway, and the suspect vehicle was continuing to slow its speed. At the time, there was no other traffic in our immediate area and I had to abruptly apply my brakes for the suspect vehicle to pass my location. At that time, I changed lanes into lane 3 behind the suspect vehicle and activated my emergency equipment to conduct a lawful traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle was a green Kia Sportage bearing Maryland registration 1BV1029. The vehicle came to a slow stop on the right shoulder of S/B I-97 at Cromwell Park Driver, Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 2 &amp;ndash; PERSONAL CONTACT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;I made a passenger side approach to the vehicle and made contact with the driver and sole occupant of the vehicle. When I approached the vehicle, I immediately observed the driver appeared disoriented, taking him several seconds to roll down the window after he acknowledged my presence. When making my initial contact with the driver, he denied swerving and stated that he was &amp;ldquo;OK.&amp;rdquo; When I continued to ask the driver about his driving behavior, he continued to claim that he was not swerving and also denied slowing his speed to avoid passing me. As I spoke with the driver, I also immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I further observed the driver&amp;rsquo;s speech was thick and heavily slurred, and the driver appeared covered in glitter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;After asking the driver for his license and registration, I continued asking the driver questions to divert his attention. While the driver was looking for his wallet, I asked where he was coming from that night. The driver fumbled over his words and hesitating answering simply stating, &amp;ldquo;Baltimore.&amp;rdquo; When I attempted to clarify with the driver, he eventually stated that he was coming from a &amp;ldquo;club&amp;rdquo; in Baltimore City, but did not state which one. As the driver reached into his back pocket to retrieve his wallet, he began to press down on the gas causing the engine to loudly rev. When I asked the driver to remove his foot from the gas, he denied ever pushing on the gas pedal. After providing his driver&amp;rsquo;s license, the driver forgot to provide his registration card and had to be reminded. The driver&amp;rsquo;s movements were slow and lethargic, he appeared drowsy, and he had droopy eyelids with glossy eyes. When I asked the driver how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed that night, he denied drinking all together even after being confronted about the indicators of impairment I had observed. The driver was identified by his Maryland issued driver&amp;rsquo;s license as Adam Richard Kass (W/M DOB: 12/15/1973).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 3 &amp;ndash; PRE-ARREST SCREENING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Based on my observations and conversations with Kass, I asked him to exit his vehicle to perform standardized field sobriety tests and confirm he could safely operate a motor vehicle. When I initially asked Kass to exit his vehicle, he refused and questioned if he had to. Kass had to be instructed three times to exit his vehicle before he finally complied. As Kass exited his vehicle, he used the door to lift himself out of the vehicle, and then used the side of the vehicle as a crutch as he walked to the front of the vehicle. I further observed Kass was taking slow and deliberate steps while slightly wobbling as he walked and bumping into his driver side mirror. After reaching the front of his vehicle, Kass stumbled forward slightly toward the grass before I directed him where to stand. Kass agreed to submit to standardized field sobriety tests. The tests were performed on the right shoulder in front of Kass&amp;rsquo; vehicle where the ground was level and free from debris. Kass stated that he did not wear contacts or glasses, did not have any vision problems, and did not take any medications. Kass also again denied consuming any alcoholic beverages. When I asked Kass about injuries or impairments that affected his balance or ability to walk, Kass stated that he had an undiagnosed pain in his back that he struggled to explain and claimed that he had been dealing with for a long time. Kass was informed that he did not have to perform the tests if he did not feel comfortable performing them. The weather at the time of testing was clear and approximately 40 degrees Fahrenheit. Kass was wearing a zipper jacket and under shirt, jeans, and laced sneakers at the time of testing. While standing outside the vehicle with Kass, I continued to detect the heavy odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person, and observed he was wobbling and swaying in place.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instructions: The subject is told to stand with their feet together and their arms down at their side. A stimulus (ink pen) is held approximately twelve to fifteen inches from the subjects&amp;rsquo; face, and they are asked to follow the stimulus with their eyes only and not to move their head. Prior to beginning the test, I ask the subject if they understand the instructions. I initially check for equal pupil size, resting nystagmus, and equal tracking. I next check for lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees. Finally, I check for vertical nystagmus. Both eyes are checked twice for each clue.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Results: &lt;strong&gt;6/6&lt;/strong&gt;. Kass had brownish eyes that were glossy and watery. Both pupils appeared normal and equal in size. Both eyes were tracking equally and resting nystagmus was not present. All clues were present and distinct with a very early onset of nystagmus. Vertical gaze Nystagmus present. Kass attempted to anticipate the movement of my pen and attempted to move his head, but was corrected and was able to finish the test. Kass was also wobbling and swaying in place while I was performing the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;WALK AND TURN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instructions: The subject is told to stand with their right foot in front of their left foot in a heel to toe manner. They are told to stay in that position and keep their arms at their side until being told to begin the test. I ask to make sure they understand and then begin explaining and demonstrating the test. The subject is instructed to take nine heel-to-toe steps on a straight, imaginary line. On the ninth step, they are instructed to leave their lead foot planted and take a series of small steps to turn 180 degrees. They are then told to take an additional nine heel to toe steps back down the same imaginary line. They are told to watch their feet, count their steps out loud, keep their hands at their side, touch heel to toe on every step, and to not stop walking until the test is completed.&amp;nbsp; I then ask if they understand the instructions before having them begin the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Results:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cannot Keep Balance: &lt;/strong&gt;Kass stumbled out of the instructional stage almost immediately after being placed in it. Kass initially blamed a slope on the ground, but I instructed him to stand on the level part of the surface and even stood in the instructional position in the same direction I was asking him to with no difficulty. Kass stumbled out of the instructional position multiple times until he stopped trying as I was giving instructions and stood normally. At one point, Kass lost his balance and stumbled back and to his left as if he was going to fall over before he caught himself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Missed Heel-to-toe: &lt;/strong&gt;Kiss missed heel-to-toe on all steps of both sets of steps, crossing his feet as he walked.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steps off Line: &lt;/strong&gt;Kass stepped off line multiple times as he was walking crooked towards the grassy median. On the 5&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; step of the first set of steps, Kass stumbled to his right and crossed his legs to the point where he was now walking on a separate line that he was originally. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incorrect Number of Steps:&lt;/strong&gt; Kass took 10 steps on the first set of steps rather than 9 as instructed. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improper Turn:&lt;/strong&gt; Kass spun on both feet rather than taking small steps as instructed.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raises Arms:&lt;/strong&gt; Kass would swing his arms and raise them greater than 6 inches as he would stumble.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other:&lt;/strong&gt; Extremely uncoordinated. Slow and deliberate steps. I observed Kass&amp;rsquo; had a very unsteady walk with very wobbly legs, appearing as if he was going to fall over several times. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total Clues: 6/8&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ONE LEG STAND&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instructions: The subject is instructed to stand with their feet together with their hands at the side while I explain the instructions and demonstrate the test. They are told to raise either foot of their choice approximately six inches off the ground. They are told to begin to count, one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-three&amp;hellip;etc. They are told to continue counting until I tell them to stop. They are told to watch their feet, to count out loud, to keep their arms at their side, and to not put their foot down. I then ask if the subject understands the instructions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Results:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Put Foot Down:&lt;/strong&gt; Kass lost his balance several times throughout the test, putting his foot down on multiple different occasions. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sway:&lt;/strong&gt; Kass was swaying his arms, leg, and body throughout the entire test. On multiple occasions, Kass would begin to lean to his right towards his vehicle and almost fall over before reaching out to his car and catching himself with his right hand. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Uses Arms to Balance:&lt;/strong&gt; Kass raised his arms from his body greater than 6 inches during the entire test as he would sway and lose his balance. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other:&lt;/strong&gt; Kass began the test by standing on his right foot and raising his left foot. Kass also chose to face the median with his back towards the roadway as he performed the test. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total Clues: 3/4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;While on scene, Kass was asked if he would submit to a preliminary breath test. I am certified by the Maryland State Police and the State of Maryland Office of the Chief Medical Examiner to conduct preliminary breath tests with the use of the Alco Sensor. This is the approved preliminary breath test for the State of Maryland. Kass refused to submit to the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Based on my observations and my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper and Drug Recognition Expert, I placed Kass under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0141 hours. Kass remained quiet, polite, and cooperative during my entire interaction with him. Kass was secured in my vehicle to be transported to the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack for further processing. Kass&amp;rsquo; vehicle was secured on the right shoulder, and his personal belongings were transported to the Barrack with him including his cell phone, wallet, and keys. When conducting a mouth check, I had to explain to Kass several times how to hold his tongue away from his teeth, but he still had a very difficult time following instruction. Kass was quite for the entire ride to the Barrack. We arrived at the Barrack at approximately 0151 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; After arriving at the Barrack, Kass was escorted to the Barrack DUI processing room. While walking through the Barrack, Kass was stumbling over his own feet at one point and began to fall over where I had to pull him upward by his arm. Kass was provided a copy of his DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along as I read the form in its entirety. While I was reading the form, Kass kept his copy on the table to his right while looking down at the form and appearing to be following along. After reading the form, Kass stated that he understood the form and did not have any questions. Kass refused to submit to an alcohol concentration test at approximately 0205 hours. At the time, a certified intoximeter operator was on duty and available with a working instrument.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DISPOSITION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;After completing the appropriate paperwork, Kass was given the opportunity to call for a sober driver to pick him up from the Barrack. Kass was able to eventually contact his brother who had agreed to pick him up. Kass was secured in a temporary holding cell while I completed the remaining paperwork. While in the cell, Kass was observed sleeping on the bench majority of the time. When Kass&amp;rsquo; brother arrived at the Barrack, Kass struggled standing up straight and was observed leaning against the cell wall while struggling to put his shoes and belt on properly. Kass was released from the Barrack to his brother after being charged accordingly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 04:52:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 01:18:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Keller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brady</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7360</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harris</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bruce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7179</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bigham</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4826</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499652</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/22/2023 01:23:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/22/2023 03:08:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/22/2023 03:10:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>49</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/22/2023 03:08:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372192</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Kass</LastName>
               <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Richard</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/15/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/22/2023 02:46:23</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A350</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Kass</LastName>
               <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Richard</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/15/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>K200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A350</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/22/2023 02:46:23</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2445</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Blue Spring</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>UNIT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>104</SubNumber>
               <City>Odenton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21113</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2542</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.718388</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.062984</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>320</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1937</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/22/2023 03:10:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/22/2023 03:10:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/22/2023 03:09:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/22/2023 03:09:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>