<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012402</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/07/2023 15:39:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/07/2023 15:39:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/07/2023 15:07:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/07/2023 15:07:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Devin Smith was stopped for a traffic violation and was found to be DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 15:39:18</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5162</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/29/2023 10:25:12</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>610843</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 15:39:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 16:14:48</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>610843</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Three Notch</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Mechanicsville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20659</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>CT</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.71369</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.426539</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/07/2023 15:39:16</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/07/2023 15:39:16</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/24/2023 08:12:32</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 15:39:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:10</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;This stop was audibly and visually recorded utilizing the Axon Digital Recording System installed in U-24 as well as my BWC. This stop was also captured on Tpr. Quinn&amp;rsquo;s #7583, Tpr. Baden&amp;rsquo;s #7152, and Tpr. Esuma&amp;rsquo;s #7574 BWC.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Smith, Devin Michael&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 06/04/1996&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 04/07/2023&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 1539&lt;br /&gt; License#: MD-10272884785, MD&lt;br /&gt; DUI #: 23-033&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On April 7&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;, 2023 at approximately 1515 hours, the St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s County Emergency Communications Center dispatched a call for a traffic complaint. ECC advised a Gray Volkswagen Jetta bearing Maryland registration, &amp;ldquo;8CE0122&amp;rdquo;, was currently northbound on MD Rt. 235 in the area of Tom Hodges Drive and was driving in an erratic manner. ECC obtained further information from multiple callers that the vehicle had exited the roadway and proceeded to drive in the median of the roadway. The vehicle proceeded northbound on MD Rt. 235 and the last known location was Oakville Road. I located the vehicle just south of MD Rt. 6, confirmed the registration, and observed the vehicle in lane 1. The vehicle crossed over the solid yellow line almost running into the median prior to making an unsafe lane change in front of a dark gray work van. The work van was forced to swerve into the shoulder to avoid being hit. The Jetta proceeded to enter lane 2 and ended up crossing the solid white shoulder line with both of its passenger side tires completely crossing the line. The Jetta proceeded to enter back into lane 2 and quickly entered lane 1 once more. The vehicle proceeded to cross over the solid yellow line and drove into the grass median. Both of the driver&amp;rsquo;s side tires completely left the roadway and had entered into the grass median just north of MD Rt. 6. At that time, I decided to conduct a traffic stop by activating my emergency equipment to include my lights and sirens. The vehicle proceeded into the shoulder area where in continued northbound at approximately 40 miles per hour. The driver of the vehicle put his hand out of the driver side window and signaled he was going to be pulling onto Valley Wood Court. The vehicle came to a stop on a concrete median barrier on Valley Wood Court.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Tpr. Quinn and I made contact with the driver of the vehicle. The driver was unable to provide a license or identification card, however, he was later positively identified as Devin Michael Smith, (B/M, DOB: 06/04/1996). While speaking with Smith, I noticed he was extremely lethargic, had extremely bloodshot eyes, his speech was heavily slurred, and he could barely keep his eyes open. When asked about his driving, he stated he was on his phone texting. Smith was unable to keep his eyes open while speaking with me and had to lean backwards in order to see me. Smith was asked to step out of the vehicle and he proceeded to walk to the front of my vehicle. Smith was then administered Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The evaluation was performed in the roadway adjacent to the traffic stop.&amp;nbsp;The surface was dry, level, and free of any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of the daylight. My patrol vehicle&amp;#39;s forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Smith appeared to be in good physical condition. When Smith&amp;nbsp;was asked about any pre-existing medical conditions, injuries, or if he took any medication, he stated he had Sickle Cell Anemia, smokes Cannabis, and his left eye was a &amp;ldquo;lazy eye&amp;rdquo;.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (0/6 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Smith&amp;rsquo;s&amp;nbsp;eyes. Smith&amp;nbsp;was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. The following clues were observed:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - NOT present in right or left eye.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2.) Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation- NOT present in right or left eye.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3.) Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees- NOT present in right or left eye.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While performing the HGN test, Smith had difficulty keeping his eyes open.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walk And Turn (7/8 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Prior to Smith&amp;nbsp;performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Smith was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Smith was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Smith was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step. Smith was to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Smith was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Smith was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Smith was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keeping his hands down by his side, looking down at his feet, and counting each step out loud. Smith stated that he understood the instructions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 1.) Failure to Maintain Balance (broke heel to toe prior to beginning test 1 time, failed to get back into position)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 1.) Missed heel to toe on steps 2 and 5.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 2.) Stepped off line on steps 2 and 7.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 3.) Stopped walking on step 6&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 4.) Raised arms on step 7.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 5.) Incorrect number of steps (7 instead of 9)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Turn:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Turn completed incorrectly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 1.) Missed heel to toe on steps 4 and 6.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 2.)&amp;nbsp;Stopped walking on steps 3 and 4.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;One Leg Stand (4/4 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Prior to Smith performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Smith was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, keep his hands at his sides, to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two), and to continue the test until told to stop. Smith stated he understood the instructions. Smith then lifted his right leg.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Nothing to report&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 1.) Used arms for balance on 1-4 seconds.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 2.) Put foot down on 4 and 6 seconds.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 3.) Swayed entire time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 1.) Used arms for balance on 11-13 seconds.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 2.) Put foot down at 13 seconds.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 3.) Swayed entire time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; It should be noted that Smith switched from standing on his left foot to standing on his right foot after 13 seconds.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;1.) Hops on 25-27 seconds.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;3.) Swayed entire time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Three more tests were then conducted. The Lack of Convergence, Modified Romberg Test, as well as the finger to nose test were conducted.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lack of Convergence:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Smith was instructed to stand with his feet together with his hands down by his side while the test was being conducted. I instructed that I would be making a series of circles with my stimulus (pen) and that Smith would have to keep his eyes on the tip of my stimulus without moving his head. Smith was instructed to follow the stimulus with his eyes and eyes only. I then instructed Smith that I would be bringing the stimulus towards his nose, however I would not be touching his nose. Smith stated that he understood the instructions. I then conducted two circles approximately 12&amp;quot; away from Moore going in a counter-clockwise manner and then brought the stimulus towards Smith&amp;rsquo;s nose until it was approximately 1&amp;quot; away from the bridge of his nose. I then repeated that one more time. While conducting the test, Smith showed the lack of convergence and was unable to follow the stimulus.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Modified Romberg Test:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Smith was instructed to once again stand with his feet together with his hands by his sides. I instructed Smith that when told to, he would close his eyes, tilt his head back at a 45 degree angle, and was told that he would estimate the passing of 30 seconds in his head. Smith was instructed that once the estimation of 30 seconds had passed, he would then open his eyes, bring his head back down, and say stop. I then told Smith that he could start whenever he was ready. Smith tilted his head back and closed his eyes. While in that position, I observed Smith swaying back and forth as well as side to side. While looking at Smith eyes, I observed him to have eyelid tremors. I also observed Smith&amp;rsquo;s legs to begin to bend during the test. Smith&amp;rsquo;s estimation of 30 seconds took 17 seconds.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Finger to Nose Test:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Smith was instructed to stand with his feet together and to put his hand out at a 45 degree angle with his point finger out. I instructed that when told to do so, Smith would use the tip of his pointer finger to touch the tip of his nose and that he would return his arm down to the starting position. I instructed to Smith that I would be telling him either &amp;quot;left&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;right&amp;quot; and that was what finger would be touching the tip of his nose. I then showed Smith the tip of my finger as opposed to the pad of my finger. Smith stated that he understood the instructions and I began the test.&amp;nbsp;The following are the clues I observed:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Left) Searched for nose, touched nostril&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Right) Searched for nose, touched nostril&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Left) Searched for nose, touched nostril&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Right) Searched for nose, touched upper lip&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Right) Nothing observed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Left) Turned head towards left arm to assist&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ARREST&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Based on the following, I had reason to believe Smith was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of a controlled dangerous substance:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; *Inability to maintain a single lane of travel.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; *Lack of awareness of vehicles around him.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; *Inability to maintain his vehicle on the roadway.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; *Extremely slurred speech.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; *Lethargic movements while trying to obtain license and registration.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*Clues observed during the standardized field sobriety tests.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; *Eyelid&amp;nbsp;and body tremors.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; *Swaying back and forth.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; *Lack of convergence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; *Admittance to using melatonin and Cannabis prior to me stopping him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Smith was arrested for driving under the influence of CDS approximately 1539 hours.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Smith was transported to the Maryland State Police Leonardtown Barrack for processing.&amp;nbsp;Smith was read the DR-15, Advice of Rights, in English via the MVA website. At the conclusion of reading the DR-15, Smith agreed to take the breath test at 1556 hours. The test was conducted by Sgt. Oles at 1620 hours and resulted in a BrAC of .00&amp;nbsp;grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. Smith was asked to submit to a Drug Recognition Expert&amp;#39;s test. Smith agreed to take the test. TFC Backus #6648 responded to the barrack and conducted his evaluation of Smith. Please refer to TFC Backus&amp;rsquo; report (23-002-0022) for his findings. TFC Backus then gave Smith the opportunity to submit to a blood kit in which he agreed to take. Smith was transported to MedStar St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s Hospital where the staff conducted the blood draw. The blood kit utilized was T-178 and was sent to CTAU on 4/7/2023.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Smith was released from the Barrack and given his pertinent paperwork.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;All events occurred in St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I request this case remain open pending blood results.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 18:24:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6719</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 23:20:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Baden</LastName>
            <FirstName>Craig</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7152</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Esuma</LastName>
            <FirstName>Smith</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7574</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Quinn-Edwards</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kire</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7583</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bauer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6719</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5920</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bauer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6719</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bauer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6719</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501805</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>08</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 15:39:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 16:12:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6719</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 16:15:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501805</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>08</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 15:39:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 16:12:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6719</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 16:15:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501805</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>08</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 15:39:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 16:12:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6719</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 16:16:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 16:12:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:29</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>249548</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>SMITH</LastName>
               <FirstName>DEVIN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MICHAEL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/04/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.9063579E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>10/21/2019 10:18:04</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>SMITH</LastName>
               <FirstName>DEVIN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MICHAEL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/04/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.9063579E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/21/2019 10:18:04</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>8620</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Broomes Island</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Broomes Island</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20615</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.54311</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.416299</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1894</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Parkers Creek</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Port Republic </City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20676</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.532234</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.51887</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1705</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Dalrymple</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Sunderland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20689</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.575034</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.653022</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>449</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9464</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 16:17:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 16:17:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 16:17:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 16:12:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6719</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 16:12:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151762</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 16:18:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6719</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 16:18:55</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3VWSP69M13M162098</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2003</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>VOLK</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>JET</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8CE0122</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/22/2023 17:58:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/22/2023 17:58:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/24/2023 08:12:32</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6648</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 17:58:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:10</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Date and time of Offense:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;04/07/2023 1507 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Location:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Three Notch Road &amp;amp; Valley Wood Court Mechanicsville, MD 20659&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Suspect:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Devin Michael Smith (B/M DOB 6/4/1996)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Narrative:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On April 7, 2023 at approximately 1625 hours, I, TFC. R. Backus #6648 with the Maryland State Police, a Drug Recognition Expert (#36475), responded to the State Police Barrack in Leonardtown, in order to conduct a NHTSA/IACP 12 Step Drug Influence Evaluation. After completing my evaluation, it is my opinion, as a Drug Recognition Expert, the driver of the vehicle was under the influence of Cannabis, impaired, and unable to operate a vehicle safely. The driver voluntarily agreed to submit to a blood kit. A copy of my completed report is attached.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Case open pending results of the bloodkit.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All events occurred in St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s County.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6648</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 18:00:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6648</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 18:03:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oles</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5857</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Backus</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6648</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/16/2023 21:56:21</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/16/2023 21:56:21</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/24/2023 08:12:32</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/16/2023 21:56:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:10</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On August 16th, 2023, Devin Smith responded to the Maryland State Police Prince Frederick barrack where he made contact with Cpl. Davis #5829 in reference to the blood kit results. On August 8th, 2023, the Forensic Toxicology Analysis Report revealed that the blood kit that was administered by TFC Backus #6648 on April 4th, 2023 revealed that Smith&amp;#39;s blood tested positive for Benzoylecgonine, Carboxy-THC, Delta-9-THC, and Fentanyl. Smith was issued a copy of the blood results as well as his traffic citations charging him with DUI and multiple other traffic violations. A copy of the results and the citations have been attached to this supplemental report.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/16/2023 21:57:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6719</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/16/2023 22:08:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oles</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5857</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bauer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6719</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501805</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>2</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/16/2023 22:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/16/2023 22:08:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6719</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/16/2023 22:08:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501805</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>2</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/16/2023 22:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/16/2023 22:08:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6719</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/16/2023 22:09:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501805</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>2</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/16/2023 22:09:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6719</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/16/2023 22:09:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6719</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/16/2023 22:09:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>