<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009907</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/19/2023 02:45:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/19/2023 02:45:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/19/2023 02:25:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/19/2023 02:25:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI arrest of Shaun Michael Barlow.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 02:45:37</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/31/2023 07:11:09</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN EXPY/ RACETRACK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
      <City>MDC108</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 02:45:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 19:30:56</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>EXPY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.170578</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.38053</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 E/O 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB/ 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 PRIOR 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MERGING OFF OF 90 INTO OCEAN PINES</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB BETWEEN BRIDGE AND OCEAN PINES EXIT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB PAST 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11083-11086 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1296-1352 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/19/2023 02:45:33</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/19/2023 02:45:33</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/30/2023 18:22:50</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 02:45:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Shaun Michael Barlow&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Maryland SOUNDEX: MD-10272362615&lt;br /&gt; Breath Test Result: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#f1c40f"&gt;0.09&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DWI Citation #: 4LH0J79&lt;br /&gt; DWI MVR/Body Cam #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-009907 (Axon View XL Software).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;TROOPER CERTIFICATES / TRAINING / SPECIAL ASSIGNMENTS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;1. Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; 2. Certified SFST Instructor.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 3. Chemical Breath Test Operator.&lt;br /&gt; 4. Graduate of the University of Maryland&amp;#39;s DUI Institute.&lt;br /&gt; 5. Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; 6. Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.).&lt;br /&gt; 7. Trained in Cannabis Impairment Detection (Maryland State Police).&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 8. Assigned to the Berlin Barrack &amp;quot;V&amp;quot; Special Enforcement Team (focusing exclusively on DUI enforcement) from October 2017 - June 2022.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;NARRATIVE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;-PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION-&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 03-19-2023 at approximately 0225 hours, I (Corporal J. Ruiz #6312), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating marked MSP vehicle V-14 in the area of Maryland Route 90 westbound near Mile Marker 7 (Ocean Pines). I was traveling westbound and &amp;ndash; at that time &amp;ndash; I observed a small SUV also traveling westbound. Though there were two (2) vehicles in front me, I could clearly observe the following on the same vehicle:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;BETWEEN MILE MARKER 7 AND THE MARYLAND ROUTE 589 EXIT&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. The vehicle&amp;rsquo;s left tires were &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;directly on top&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; of the solid yellow line near the center guardrail on &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;three (3) occasions&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. The vehicle &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;abruptly swerved&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; back into the westbound lane each time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. The vehicle&amp;rsquo;s right tires &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;crossed&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (1 tire width) the solid white line into the right shoulder area on one (1) occasion. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;MARYLAND ROUTE 589 OVERPASS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. The vehicle&amp;rsquo;s right tires were &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;directly on top&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; of the solid white shoulder line on one (1) occasion. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ADDITIONAL OBSERVATIONS&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 4. The vehicle failed to maintain proper lane position due to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;pronounced and excessive weaving&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (alternately moving toward one side of the lane and then the other) during the entire duration of my observations.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 5. Total distance traveled was approximately 1.65 miles.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;DWI INDICATORS / REASON FOR STOP&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHSTA) published a &amp;quot;The Visual Detection of DWI&lt;br /&gt; Motorists&amp;quot; booklet in March 2010. The research revealed that DWI cues related to problems in maintaining proper lane position include:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Weaving&lt;br /&gt; 2. Weaving across lane lines&lt;br /&gt; 3. Drifting&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All of the above DWI indicators were exhibited by the same SUV prior to my initiating a traffic stop.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;TRAFFIC STOP&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I activated the emergency lights to my patrol vehicle, initiating a traffic stop on MD Route 90 westbound just west of MD Route 589. The vehicle was a blue 2014 Honda CR-V bearing Maryland Registration 9FF5960.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;-PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT-&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the driver via the driver side door, and I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop and requested the driver&amp;rsquo;s license and the registration card to the vehicle. The driver was identified as Shaun Michael Barlow by his Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license. I asked Barlow where he was traveling from, and he responded: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;From Ocean City&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. I asked Barlow how much he had to drink earlier in the evening, and he responded: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Uh, I&amp;rsquo;ve only had a beer or two&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As Barlow spoke, I made the following observations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. I intentionally observed his eyes to be &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;glassy and bloodshot&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. Barlow displayed a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;glazed look/expression&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; on his face as he interacted with me.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Barlow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I later returned to the Honda and requested Barlow exit the vehicle and walk to the front of it, to which he complied. While at the front of the vehicle, I continued to speak with Barlow. I asked Barlow again where he was traveling from, and he stated: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Uh, Seacrets&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. I asked Barlow where he was traveling to, and he replied: &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Salisbury&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;. I asked Barlow how many total alcoholic beverages he had consumed prior to driving, and he advised: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Probably 4 beers. 4 beers and maybe 1 shot&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. When asked at approximately what time he had finished consuming his last drink prior to driving, Barlow advised: &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Maybe 1&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. As Barlow spoke, I smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I informed Barlow that I wanted him to perform field sobriety tests which he agreed to submit to.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;-PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING-&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder area. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and vehicle headlamps. Weather was clear and approximately 30 degrees. I asked Barlow if he had any significant medical issues with his eyes, arms, or legs which would prevent him from performing the field sobriety tests or if he had taken any medication prior to driving. Barlow responded: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;I do have anemia, and I have had surgery on my left eye for [unintelligible]. And I am supposed to wear glasses&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Adderall, Clonidine, Seroquel&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Barlow appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries, limps, or any limb ailments.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Barlow was wearing a black/white print sweatshirt, blue jeans, and black/gray athletic-type shoes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Barlow displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. Barlow displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. Barlow displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**WALK AND TURN: 5 of 8 clues**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Barlow could not maintain his balance during the Instruction Phase. Barlow&amp;rsquo;s feet broke from the start position on two (2) occasions, and he stumbled to his right each time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. Barlow missed heel-to-toe on step 2 during the first series. Barlow missed heel-to-toe on steps 1, 2, 5, 7, 8, 9, and 10 during the second series. All misses were of more than half an inch.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. Barlow did not complete the turn in a satisfactory manner, simultaneously pivoting both feet to his left which was contrary to my instructions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 4. Barlow took 10 steps during the second series, which was contrary to my instructions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 5. Barlow was unable to maintain a straight line and stepped off the line on all steps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**ONE LEG STAND: 3 of 4 clues**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Barlow&amp;rsquo;s body swayed to the left and right on counts 6, 7, 9, 10, and 11.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. Barlow put his right foot down on count 9.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. Barlow raised his left arm for balance (higher than 6&amp;rdquo; to his side) on count 11.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ADDITIONAL TESTING&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Alphabet and Count Tests completed satisfactorily. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Barlow the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Barlow submitted to a preliminary breath test with a reading of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#f1c40f"&gt;0.12&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; BrAC.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ARREST&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Barlow was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;* Driving vehicle in a negligent manner which caused it to commit 5 lane violations in addition to excessive weaving &amp;ndash; &lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#f1c40f"&gt;DRIVING SKILLS IMPAIRED&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Glazed look/expression on face.&lt;br /&gt; * Admission to consuming more than one (1) alcoholic beverage prior to operating a motor vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * PBT result of 0.12 BrAC.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I determined that Barlow was impaired by the presence of an alcoholic beverage in his system that adversely affected his ability to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests properly can also adversely affect the person&amp;rsquo;s ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. I placed Barlow under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0244 hours on 03-19-2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Barlow&amp;rsquo;s mouth for any foreign objects and none were found. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Barlow was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Barlow was given his Advice of Rights via the audio version of the DR-15 Form (played through the patrol vehicle&amp;rsquo;s Bluetooth speakers). At the conclusion of the audio version, I verbally re-explained the driver&amp;rsquo;s license sanctions and penalties (section printed in red) to Barlow. Barlow stated that he understood his Advice of Rights and agreed to submit to a breath test at approximately 0311 hours on 03-19-2023.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;TRANSPORT&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Barlow was subsequently transported to the Berlin Barrack for processing. During transport, the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Barlow continued to be strong.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;**INTOXIMETER RESULT**:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to the breath test, I observed Sergeant B. Walls #3805 visually check the inside of Barlow&amp;rsquo;s mouth for any foreign objects. None were found.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The breath test was administered by SGT Walls at approximately 0338 hours on 03-19-2023, and two (2) sufficient samples of Barlow&amp;rsquo;s breath were obtained. The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#f1c40f"&gt;0.09&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;RELEASE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Barlow was released from the Berlin Barrack to a sober driver at approximately 0357 hours on 03-19-2023.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CHARGES&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Barlow was charged with the following citations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (4LH0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 2. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol Per Se (4LJ0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 3. Driving Vehicle While Impaired By Alcohol (4LK0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 4. Failure To Drive Right Of Center (4LL0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 5. Failure To Obey Designated Lane Directions (4LM0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 6. Negligent Driving (4LN0J79)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 20:26:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 20:37:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phillips</LastName>
            <FirstName>Riley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7211</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Drew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/24/2023 19:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 19:30:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 19:32:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/24/2023 19:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 19:30:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 19:32:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/24/2023 19:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 19:30:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 19:31:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/24/2023 19:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 19:30:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 19:31:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 19:30:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:45</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372454</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shaun</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/27/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 19:24:17</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shaun</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/27/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 19:24:17</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6121</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Ruth</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.51010454541915</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.359152160546735</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>735</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5722</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 19:33:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 19:33:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 19:31:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 19:31:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151239</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 19:35:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 19:35:50</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2HKRM4H59EH6387678</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CR-V</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9FF5960</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>