<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-003769</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/30/2023 09:47:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/30/2023 09:47:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/30/2023 09:43:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/30/2023 09:43:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Sexual Child Abuse</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 09:47:47</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 08:46:26</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SAS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>7198 DUSTIN  DR</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>682347</AddressId>
      <City>MDC229</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 09:47:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/30/2023 10:08:24</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>682347</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>7198</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Dustin</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Sharpsburg</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/30/2023 09:47:46</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/30/2023 09:47:46</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>02/06/2023 08:45:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 09:47:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 08:45:57</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 1/26/2023, I, Sgt, Angermeier was notified by Washington County CPS on an incoming case of alleged child sex abuse. The alleged victim, Sophia Houck, 9 YOA, reported to two of her friends that her brother&amp;#39;s Kaden Ledezma, 13 YOA, DOB:10/8/2009, and John (JT) Marshall III, 18 YOA, DOB:8/31/2002, told her to &amp;quot;suck his balls&amp;quot; for $100 and she did it. Sophia also disclosed that 2 days ago her brother JT, asked her to suck his balls and she did it. Sophia advised this has been going on &amp;quot;a long time.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 1/30/2023 at approximately 1254 hours, Case Worker Amber Kelly conducted a forensic interview with Sophia at the Washington County CAC. I was present for the interview as well as CAC Supervisor Rachel Mazloum.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; BELOW IS THE INTERVIEW NOTES BY CPS SUPERVISOR RACHEL MAZLOUM. TO SEE THE FULL DETAILS OF THE INTERVIEW, SEE THE RECORDED INTERVIEW ON CD.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker began by orienting Sofia to the interview room and process. She began to build rapport. Sofia likes to play Roblox, play with her dogs, and watch movies. Worker completed narrative practice regarding the last time Sofia played with her dog Mia. Sofia was able to provide detail but was soft spoken and needed prompting to be able to give a full narrative. Sofia did appear developmentally appropriate.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker inquired about household members. She lives with her mom (Emily), grandma (Dee), grandma&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend (Mike), and Shelby. With her mom she watches movies and goes shopping. Sofia cooks dinner with her mom. She feeds the animals with Mike. She plays video games with Shelby.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker provided an open invitation. Sofia did not know why she was present to talk. She denied anyone talking to her about the interview. Worker brought up the topic of body safety. Worker presented the anatomically correct drawings of the male and female. Worker had her point to where the bathing suit covers. She labelled the vagina as the &amp;ldquo;bug&amp;rdquo;, penis the &amp;ldquo;private part&amp;rdquo;, the buttocks the &amp;ldquo;butt&amp;rdquo;. Worker asked if anyone touched her in her bug. She shook her head &amp;ldquo;no&amp;rdquo;. Worker asked if anyone has had her touch the boy&amp;rsquo;s private part and she shook her head &amp;ldquo;no&amp;rdquo;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker asked about siblings. She listed JT, Lexi, Bentley, and Bailey. She sees them at her dad&amp;rsquo;s house. She last saw JT and Bentley last weekend at dad&amp;rsquo;s house. She played tag with JT and Lexi. They rode bikes together. After this they played on their phones. She sleeps on the couch at her dad&amp;rsquo;s house. Bailey sleeps on the other couch and JT sleeps on the air mattress. Kaden is another of her siblings who lives at her grandfather&amp;rsquo;s and they have the same mother.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; She talked about playing Fortnite at her grandfather&amp;rsquo;s house with JT.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker exited the interview room to speak to observers and re-entered. Worker asked about touches Sofia likes. Sofia likes hand shakes. She likes high fives. Worker asked about touches she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like. She was quiet for an extended period of time. She noted liking hugs from her brothers, sisters, and parents. There is no one she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like hugs from. She said she would like a high five from her brother. Worker asked if there was a touch from her brother that would make her uncomfortable and she shook her head.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker asked what she likes to do with Kaden. She likes to stay the night with him and watch movies. She colors with him. She sees him on the weekends when she spends the night at her grandfather&amp;rsquo;s. She sleeps in her grandfather&amp;rsquo;s girlfriend&amp;rsquo;s daughter&amp;rsquo;s bunks. She slept over there last the weekend before she stayed at her dad&amp;rsquo;s. They shot their BB guns together. They watched a movie together and went to bed. The next day they played Fortnite together. She denied there being anything she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like to do with Kaden. Worker asked if anything with Kaden has ever made her uncomfortable and she shook her head &amp;ldquo;no&amp;rdquo;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker asked about JT. Sofia likes to play on the phone with him. She doesn&amp;rsquo;t like to ride a 4wheeler with him, since he almost makes her fall off. There is nothing else she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like to do with him. She likes to take his dog on a walk.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker exited the interview room again to speak to observers and then re-entered. Worker reviewed that no one should see or ask to see the parts of the body covered by a bathing suit. Sofia denied anyone touching her in these areas. She noted she could tell her mom. She denied ever having to tell anyone about them touching her areas or asking her to touch their areas.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The interview was ended after reverting to a neutral topic.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to no disclosure of abuse, this case is closed as unfounded.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Washington County, MD.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5544</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 09:00:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5544</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 09:52:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Angermeier</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5544</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>09</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5544</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 10:09:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:09</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>367599</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Houck</LastName>
               <FirstName>Sofia</FirstName>
               <DOB>07/18/2013 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/30/2023 10:09:35</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S100</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Houck</LastName>
               <FirstName>Sofia</FirstName>
               <DOB>07/18/2013 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S100</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/30/2023 10:09:35</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7198</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Dustin</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Sharpsburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5544</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/30/2023 10:09:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>