<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-006389</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/18/2023 21:30:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/18/2023 21:30:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/18/2023 21:08:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/18/2023 21:08:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Vehicle was a lookout for an impaired driver. The driver was stopped, preformed SFST's and arrested.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 21:30:55</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 12:11:30</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>129736</AddressId>
      <City>MDC305</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 21:30:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/18/2023 23:04:12</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>129736</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2551</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>BALTIMORE</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>FINKSBURG</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.90470659544425</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.508919312809844</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>HILLENDALE TRAILER PARK #72</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>HILLENDALE TRAILER PARK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/18/2023 21:30:52</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/18/2023 21:30:52</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/23/2023 04:08:18</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 21:30:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:03</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;DUI Case #23-024&lt;br /&gt; This stop was captured on AXON body worn camera and in-car camera.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TRAINING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TEST&amp;#39;s CERTIFIED&lt;br /&gt; A.R.I.D.E (Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement) CERTIFIED&lt;br /&gt; STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY CERTIFIED INSTRUCTOR&amp;nbsp;CERTIFIED&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;DRIVER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Morgan Ashley Pellegran&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;W/F&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;DOB: 10/13/1992&lt;br /&gt; 31 Grant St.&lt;br /&gt; Baltimore, MD 21202&lt;br /&gt; 337-278-9640&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;WITNESS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Deborah Clinton&lt;br /&gt; 410-340-8655&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Phase #1 - Vehicle in Motion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On February 18, 2023, at approximately 2108 hours, I, TFC Adle was operating MSP marked patrol vehicle G-42 in the area of Old Westminster Pike at Sandymount Road when the Westminster Barrack advised that they had a caller behind a vehicle who they believed was under the influence. The Westminster Barrack advised the vehicle was headed eastbound on Route 140 approaching Reese Road. The barrack described the vehicle as a white Toyota 4-Runner bearing Louisiana registration &amp;quot;WNR2576&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp; I then proceed to Route 140 to locate the vehicle. As I was driving in the direction of the vehicle, the barrack advised that the vehicle had a hard time maintaining its lane numerous times according to the caller. Shortly after the lookout was broadcasted, TFC Perrell advised that he was behind the white Toyota 4-Runner matching the lookout. TFC Perrell began making observations of the vehicle&amp;#39;s driving behaviors and made a traffic stop shortly thereafter on eastbound Route 140 west of Route 91, see his supplement.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I spoke with the 911 caller, Deborah Clinton on 2/19/2023 by telephone. I asked Mrs. Clinton to describe the vehicle&amp;#39;s driving behaviors. Mrs. Clinton advised that she pulled out behind the white Toyota 4-Runner from Royer Road onto eastbound Rt. 140. She stated that she immediately observed the vehicle drift from lane two into lane one by half the car width then back into lane two. Mrs. Clinton stated that she thought the vehicle was going to change lanes however the vehicle did not have its blinker on and did not stay in the lane it drifted into. Mrs. Clinton stated that as the vehicle continued eastbound she observed the vehicle drift over the solid white line that separates lane two from the shoulder. She stated that between WMC Drive and Route 31 the vehicle drifted from lane two into lane one causing a vehicle that was in lane one to slam on their brakes to avoid a collision. Mrs. Clinton stated that she called 911 and advised what she observed. She stated that from the time she got behind the vehicle till the time the Trooper made a traffic stop on the vehicle she observed the 4-Runner drift over the dotted white line separating lanes several times.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Phase #2 - Personal Contact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with TFC Perrell, and took over the business needs of the traffic stop. While TFC Perrell was completing routine checks on the information the driver provided I made a driver&amp;#39;s side approach on the vehicle and contacted the driver. The driver was later identified by her Louisiana driver&amp;#39;s license as Morgan Ashley Pellegran. I introduced myself and asked Ms. Pellegran if she had her insurance for the vehicle. Ms. Pellegran advised that she did not have a physical copy but had a copy on her phone. As Ms. Pellegran began to speak, I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from her breath. I asked&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran where she was coming from tonight, and she stated &amp;quot;um, I&amp;#39;m from Baltimore.&amp;quot; I then asked again, where are you coming from tonight, and she stated &amp;quot;Baltimore.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran then stated that she was at Liberty Mountain Skiing. I asked&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran where she was headed to, and she stated &amp;quot;Baltimore.&amp;quot; To clarify I stated that you&amp;#39;re coming from Baltimore, and she replied, &amp;quot;yeah.&amp;quot; I know through my experiences that she was headed the wrong direction to be coming from Baltimore City.&amp;nbsp; I asked&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran how much she had to drink (alcoholic beverages) tonight because her eyes were bloodshot and glassy, and she stated &amp;quot;just a little bit.&amp;quot; I asked&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran what she had to drink, and she stated &amp;quot;beers.&amp;quot; I again asked&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran if she had proof of her insurance and she stated that it was on her phone. I asked who her insurance was through, and she stated Geico.&amp;nbsp;While I was asking&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran these questions I observed her to stop looking for her insurance on her phone and pause to think of the answer. I know through my training, knowledge, and experiences that this is a possible sign of impairment due to her inability to divide her attention. I instructed Ms. Pellegran to continue looking up her insurance as I returned to my vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I made a second approach on the vehicle and asked Ms. Pellegran to step outside her vehicle so I could separate her from the odor of an acholic beverage that I was detecting. Once outside the vehicle I asked Ms. Pellegran why she was drifting over the roadway. Ms. Pellegran stated that she was on speakerphone with her friend. I again detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from her breath.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on her driving and my personal contact with her, I asked Mrs. Pellegran&amp;nbsp;if she would perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests in which she agreed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Phase #3 - Pre-Arrest Screening&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I asked&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran about the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Medications - No&lt;br /&gt; Contacts - No&lt;br /&gt; Eyeglasses - No&lt;br /&gt; Head Trauma - No&lt;br /&gt; Shoes - Okay to walk in&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I am trained through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Transportation Safety Administration in administrating Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Weather conditions were clear, and the tests were performed on a smooth surface free of any debris.&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran chose to wear a pair of white sneakers.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus - 6 of 6 clues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test.&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran was turned away from my patrol lights.&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran was instructed to place her arms by her side and her feet together. My pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Ms. Pellegran &amp;#39;s eyes. Ms. Pellegran was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Ms. Pellegran&amp;#39;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I asked&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran if she understood my instructions, and she acknowledged he did.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; - Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; - Onset of Nystagmus Prior to Reaching 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I had to instruct Ms. Pellegran to not move her head once. I asked Ms. Pellegran what kind of beer did she consume, and she stated a &amp;quot;PBR.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Walk and Turn - 5 of 8 clues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Before Ms. Pellegran started performing the test she was placed in an instructional position. I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted.&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran was instructed to place her left foot on an imaginary line and to put her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe.&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran was instructed to place her hands down at her side and to remain in the position until told to begin.&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran was advised to take nine (9) steps on an imaginary straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. She was to keep her hands down at her side, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step,&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran was demonstrated and explained to keep her lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around.&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran was again explained and demonstrated the second series of steps to be performed identically to the first series.&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran was advised once she started the test, she was not to stop until the test was finished. I asked&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran if she understood all of my instructions in which she acknowledges she did.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *INSTRUCTIONAL POSITION *&lt;br /&gt; -Broke instructional position to maintain her balance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *WALKING PHASE*&lt;br /&gt; First 9 Steps&lt;br /&gt; -Stepped offline on step nine&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Turn completed incorrectly&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Second 9 Steps&lt;br /&gt; -Stepped offline on step four and five&lt;br /&gt; -Missed heel to toe on steps eight and nine&lt;br /&gt; -Incorrect number of steps, she took ten total steps&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;One Leg Stand - 3 of 4 clues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Before&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran started performing the test she was placed into an instructional position, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted.&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran was instructed to stand with her feet together and hands down to her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. She was instructed not to begin the test until she was instructed to start, and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately six (6) inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, keep her toe pointed forward, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand two, one thousand three...) and to continue the test until told to stop (30 seconds). Ms. Pellegran was asked if she understood the test and the instructions given in which she acknowledged that she did.&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran chose to perform the test with her right foot raised.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *BALANCE AND COUNTING STAGE*&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10&lt;br /&gt; -Sways&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20&lt;br /&gt; -Puts Foot Down&lt;br /&gt; -Sways&lt;br /&gt; -Hopping&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30&lt;br /&gt; -Puts Foot Down&lt;br /&gt; -Sways&lt;br /&gt; -Hopping&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I&amp;nbsp;offered&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran the preliminary breath test in which she accepted. The results were .14.&amp;nbsp; Based on my observations I believed Ms. Pellegran was unable to operate the vehicle safely, and she was placed under arrest for driving under the influence at 2126 hours.&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran&amp;#39;s vehicle was towed by Rockdale towing per her request.&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran was transported to the Westminster Barrack. While en route to the Barrack my patrol vehicle filled with the odor of an alcoholic beverage. At the Westminster Barrack,&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran was provided a copy and read in its entirety the DR15 Advice of Rights form. Ms. Pellegran stated she understood the form and agreed to take the alcohol concentration test at 2149 hours. Sgt. Newill #5358 administered the test on the certified instrument (#011733). The test results revealed Ms. Pellegran&amp;#39;s&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;breath specimen contained an alcohol concentration of .16 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&amp;nbsp;Ms. Pellegran was issued citations and other appropriate paper and released to a sober driver.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I respectfully request this case be CLOSED by arrest.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 23:08:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6906</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 17:25:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Perrell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Curtis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7140</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Adle</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6906</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Karas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5562</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Adle</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6906</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Adle</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6906</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495785</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 23:01:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6906</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/18/2023 23:03:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495785</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 23:01:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6906</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/18/2023 23:03:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495785</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 23:01:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6906</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/18/2023 23:03:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>30</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 23:01:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:50</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369498</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Pellegran</LastName>
               <FirstName>Morgan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ashley</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/13/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>4.38850576E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>02/18/2023 22:51:41</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P426</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M625</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Pellegran</LastName>
               <FirstName>Morgan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ashley</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/13/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>4.38850576E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>P426</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M625</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/18/2023 22:51:41</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>31</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Grant</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21202</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.6128643</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.2882665</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>337</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>278</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9640</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 23:05:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 23:05:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 23:05:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 23:01:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6906</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/18/2023 23:01:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149971</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 23:07:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6906</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/18/2023 23:07:06</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>1997</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>4RN</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>LA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>WNR257</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>