<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013399</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/15/2023 20:31:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/15/2023 20:31:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/15/2023 15:55:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/15/2023 15:55:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>2nd degree burn on male subject.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 16:07:11</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5162</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/11/2023 09:33:39</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>690807</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 16:07:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/15/2023 20:33:50</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>690807</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1425</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Gregg</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Lusby</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20657</Zip5>
         <Zip4>2971</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.476077</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.354672</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/15/2023 16:07:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/15/2023 16:07:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>05/11/2023 09:33:39</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 16:07:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5162</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/11/2023 09:33:39</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This incident was captured utilizing the agency-issued AXON body-worn camera assigned to Trooper P. Hernandez #7266.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On April 15, 2023, at approximately 1556 hours, the Calvert County Emergency Control Center broadcasted a call to assist the fire department on a call involving a male subject on fire at, 1425 Gregg Dr, Lusby, MD 20657.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Upon arrival, at approximately 1602 hours, I made contact with one of the medics on-scene, and he advised the wife of the subject who caught fire was on-scene.&amp;nbsp;I made contact with a female subject who was later identified as, Barbara Jean Dehenzel (W/F DOB: 01/30/1958) by her Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license. I asked Dehenzel what happened, and she advised she was not on-scene to witness the incident. Dehenzel advised &amp;quot;Paul&amp;quot; witnessed the incident. &amp;quot;Paul&amp;quot; (W/M DOB: UNK) stated the male subject was working on a vintage vehicle. &amp;quot;Paul&amp;quot; advised the male subject had a can of gas, and he poured it into the carburetor, which backfired and threw the male subject back, causing him to catch on fire. &amp;quot;Paul&amp;quot; advised he grabbed a towel and attempted to put out the fire, but the male subject threw himself on the ground and began rolling on the grass, which eventually put-out the fire. While looking at the vehicle, I observed a can of starter fluid sitting in the engine bay of the vintage vehicle. I also observed a red gas container that was approximately ten feet away from the rear end of the vehicle. I did not detect any odors of gasoline in the area, but I did notice a small patch of burnt material that was next to the vehicle. The burnt material appeared to be burnt hair.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; It should be noted that &amp;quot;Paul&amp;quot; left the scene before I could gather his information.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; After speaking with Dehenzel and &amp;quot;Paul&amp;quot;, I asked the medic on-scene if he knew where the male subject was going to be transported, and he stated the male subject was going to be transported to the burn center at, the Washington Hospital Center located at,&amp;nbsp;110 Irving St NW, Washington, DC 20010. The male subject was transported by &amp;quot;Medic 101&amp;quot; with the &amp;quot;Calvert Advanced Life Support.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I went back to speak with Dehenzel, and I asked Dehenzel what her relationship was with the male subject who was transported to the hospital and, she advised he was her boyfriend. I asked Dehenzel for her boyfriend&amp;#39;s information, and she identified him as, Kelly Charles Higgs (W/M DOB: 08/27/1957).&amp;nbsp;I asked Dehenzel to describe what happened, and she stated that she was not on-scene to observe what had occurred. Dehenzel advised she only knew that Higgs was working on the engine of his vintage vehicle. Dehenzel stated Higgs was adding gasoline to the carburetor, which in-turn backfired and caused Higgs to back away from the vehicle while holding a can of gasoline. The gasoline spilled on Dehenzel&amp;#39;s skin and caught fire. Dehenzel stated Higgs dropped to the ground and began rolling on the grass in an attempt to stop the fire. The medic on-scene advised the male subject suffered 2nd degree burns to his chest, neck, and face area. I asked Dehenzel if she was the person who called 911, and she stated &amp;quot;no.&amp;quot; Dehenzel advised the medics were on a call down the street, and they happened to notice Higgs on fire. The medics arrived on scene and immediately provided medical attention.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It should be noted that I was unable to make contact with Higgs, since he was already in the ambulance at the time of my arrival.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I asked Dehenzel if she knew where &amp;quot;Paul&amp;quot; lived, and she pointed at the house across from her residence. I attempted to locate &amp;quot;Paul&amp;quot; at, 1432 Gregg Dr, Lusby, MD 20657, but I was unable to locate him. I went back to Dehenzel&amp;#39;s residence to take photographs of the vehicle. The vehicle involved in the incident is a black French vintage vehicle&amp;nbsp;that was parked in front of the house. I asked Dehenzel if she knew any information about the vehicle, and she stated &amp;quot;no.&amp;quot; I also asked Dehenzel if there was any paperwork that identified the vehicle, and she stated that she did not have any paperwork or documents for it. I approached the vehicle to see if there were any damages to it, but there were no damages caused by the fire. I was not able to identify the year, make, or model of the vehicle. Dehenzel advised that the vehicle is only used as a display model at car shows. Based on my observations, the vehicle did not appear to be able to start. The vehicle appeared to be worked on, and was getting ready for a car show in the upcoming weeks, according to Dehenzel. I did not observe any keys belonging to the vehicle, and Dehenzel had no other information regarding the vehicle. I proceeded to take photographs of the vehicle (see attachments / uploaded to VeriPic). There is a metal plate on the engine bay of the vehicle, which read &amp;quot;Societe Belge Des Automobiles Citroen S.S Bruxelles.&amp;quot; It also listed the chassis and motor number. The Chassis number is &amp;quot;2490550,&amp;quot; and the motor number is &amp;quot;AG05822.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; After taking a look at the vehicle, I provided Dehenzel the case number, along with my information, and advised her to give the Maryland State Police Prince Frederick Barrack a call if she had any questions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On May 9, 2023, at approximately 1541 hours, I contacted Higgs via telephone in regard to his recovery process. Higgs advised the burn center treated him amazingly. Higgs stated the medical attention was excellent, but he did not like being at the hospital for several days. Higgs advised he released himself from the burn center, but agreed to go back for several follow-up appointments until fully recovered. Since I was unable to see Higgs at the time the incident occurred, I asked him where he obtained his burns. Higgs stated 19% of his body obtained burns, to include his right hand. I asked Higgs if he had feeling in his hand, and stated he obtained nerve damage, but he was slowly gaining feeling and movement of his hand and fingertips. Higgs also advised he will be starting therapy on Thursday, May 18, 2023. Higgs stated he is recovering and doing well, and is shocked by how well his skin looks after the burns. Higgs was very thankful for the follow-up.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Case closed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; All events occurred in Calvert County, MD.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 20:42:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7266</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/10/2023 23:07:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hunt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kemery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5162</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5829</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hernandez-Miguel</LastName>
            <FirstName>Pavel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7266</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>65</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 20:39:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:28</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374393</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Higgs</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kelly</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/27/1957 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/15/2023 20:38:51</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Higgs</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kelly</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/27/1957 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/15/2023 20:38:51</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4665</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Huntingtown</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Huntingtown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20639</Zip5>
               <Zip4>8512</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.627485</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.625993</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>968</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6253</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>E</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 20:39:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 20:39:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>65</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 20:41:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:28</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374394</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dehenzel</LastName>
               <FirstName>Barbara</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jean</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/30/1958 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/15/2023 20:41:17</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D524</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B616</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dehenzel</LastName>
               <FirstName>Barbara</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jean</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/30/1958 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D524</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B616</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/15/2023 20:41:17</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1425</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Gregg</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Lusby</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20657</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2971</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.476077</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.354672</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>474</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5000</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 20:41:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>