<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008622</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/09/2023 01:21:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/09/2023 01:21:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/09/2023 01:06:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/09/2023 01:06:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was passed out behind the wheel and later arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 01:21:49</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0104</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 12:35:40</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>CRAIN HWY N / MILLERSVILLE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>686762</AddressId>
      <City>MDC258</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 01:21:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/09/2023 04:13:27</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>686762</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Crain</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <StreetSuffixCode>N</StreetSuffixCode>
         <City>Crofton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.65466</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0575</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>659-662 CRAIN HWY N / 1701-1704 MILLERSVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/09/2023 01:21:46</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/09/2023 01:21:46</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/17/2023 08:08:05</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 01:21:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;J-16 equipped with a mobile recording device and BWC, this stop was recorded.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Chanel Evelyn Carter&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 12/27/1991&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 3/9/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 0121 hours&lt;br /&gt; MD SDX: C-636-115-238-985&lt;br /&gt; DUI #: J-23-040&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; * Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; * Apprehended more than 210 impaired drivers during my career with the Maryland State Police to date.&lt;br /&gt; * Attended the 2016 DUI Conference&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Completed the 2017 DUI Institute at the University of Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Received the Smooth Operator Award&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;* Received the Aggressive Drivers are Public Threats (ADAPT) Award.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Completed the Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Course (ARIDE).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;**SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Narrative:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On March 9, 2023 at approximately 0106 hours, I (Tpr. Jeans #6483) was on routine patrol in the uniform of the day and operating unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle J-16. At that time, I heard another unit, Tpr. Gardner #7503 call out a vehicle stopped in the roadway located at northbound Rt. 3 at Millersville Rd, Crofton/Millersville, Anne Arundel County, Maryland. As I listened to the radio, Tpr. Gardner advised the driver was passed out behind the wheel and that she was breathing. Upon arrival to the scene, I observed a silver Mercedes SUV bearing Maryland Registration 1EP8711 in the right turn lane impeding the flow of traffic. Since there were units behind the Mercedes, I parked my patrol car in the front of the Mercedes. I exited my patrol, which I parked in front of the Mercedes, and observed Tpr. Gardner and S/Tpr. Treleaven attempting to wake the driver up. As I walked up to the driver&amp;rsquo;s side of the vehicle, the driver was waking up and appeared confused and it did not seem like the driver knew where she was or what she was doing. As the driver woke up, she let off of the brake and began moving forward and had to be told to stop. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I then made contact with the operator of the vehicle by making a driver side approach. Once the vehicle was stopped, I had to tell the driver to put the car into park, which she lethargically did and it appeared she had to do it twice. I asked the female driver what was going on tonight and she stated she was on her way home and asked if she could just go home. At that time, I requested her driver&amp;rsquo;s license and asked if her current address was on her license, which she stated it was. I advised the driver everything was being recorded. I then asked the driver where she was coming from and what she was doing and she stated she was with a friend. I asked the driver where she met her friend, however she could not remember. She then advised she met her friend downtown Crofton at a bar. The driver was identified by her Maryland Driver&amp;rsquo;s License as Chanel Evelyn Carter, B/F, DOB: 12/27/1991. As I spoke to CARTER, I detected the extremely strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle and intentionally observed her eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I asked the driver how much alcohol she had to drink and she stated she had not had too much, just wine. When I advised CARTER I could smell the alcohol, she appeared confused and stated &amp;ldquo;You can?&amp;rdquo; I again asked her and she stated she had one drink, which was wine. As CARTER was answering these questions, I noticed she had slurred speech. A routine check through the MVA database revealed CARTER had a valid license and was not wanted. I did notice CARTER was on probation for a previous DUI. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Once I gave the Glen Burnie Barrack all of CARTER&amp;rsquo;s information, I made my second approach and asked CARTER if she would perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, to which she agreed. CARTER exited her vehicle and walked to the front of her vehicle like she was instructed to do. While communicating with CARTER by the front of my vehicle, I again detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person and observed her eyes to be bloodshot and glassy.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The evaluation was performed in the right turn lane to Millersville Road. The weather was clear and approximately 35 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of patrol vehicle headlights, spotlight, street lamps and my flashlight. The roadway was level and free from any debris. My patrol vehicle&amp;rsquo;s forward and rear emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. CARTER appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any major visible injuries when walking from the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked CARTER the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Medical Conditions &amp;ndash; None&lt;br /&gt; Injuries &amp;ndash; None.&lt;br /&gt; Medication &amp;ndash; None&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Had not fallen or hit their head.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;CARTER was not wearing glasses at the time of the stop&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from CARTER&amp;rsquo;S eyes. CARTER was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. CARTER&amp;rsquo;S pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. CARTER was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. CARTER was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; CARTER did show signs of vertical nystagmus which indicates there was likely a high concentration of alcohol in her system.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN (6/8 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The walk and turn test was properly explained and demonstrated per the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. At the conclusion of the demonstration and explanation, CARTER was asked if she understood the test, to which she stated &amp;ldquo;yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) CARTER was unable to keep her right foot in front of her left foot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 1 and 5 through 16.&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Stepped off line on step 1 and 5.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;3.) Took a total of 16 steps.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;4.) Stopped walking on step 16.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Turn: Completed unsatisfactorily. Did not make a turn.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; CARTER did not make a turn and did not complete the second series of nine steps.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;ONE LEG STAND (3 out of 4 clues observed, left foot raised)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The one leg stand test was properly explained and demonstrated per the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. At the conclusion of the demonstration and explanation, CARTER was asked if she understood the test, to which she stated &amp;ldquo;yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Nothing to report.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1) Raised arms by more than 6 inches from her sides for balance on counts 1009 through 1012, 1023.&lt;br /&gt; 2) Swayed to maintain her balance on counts 1011, 1012, 1016 and 1023.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;3.) Placed her foot down on counts 1002, 1012 and 1024.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;A preliminary breath test was offered to CARTER and CARTER refused the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ARREST&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe CARTER was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from vehicle/breath.&lt;br /&gt; * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.&lt;br /&gt; * Admitting to consuming alcoholic beverages.&lt;br /&gt; * Clues during standardized field sobriety testing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Slurred speech&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Passed out behind the wheel.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Due to the number of observations, I concluded CARTER was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0121 hours, I placed CARTER under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. A preliminary search of CARTER was conducted on scene and revealed no foreign materials in her mouth. CARTER was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy. Once CARTER was placed into my patrol vehicle, I shut the door. When I walked around to get into my vehicle, the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage had engulfed my vehicle. That smell was not there prior to me arresting CARTER. CARTER was transported to the Maryland State Police Annapolis Barrack for processing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;20 Minute Observation Period&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A secondary search was conducted upon arrival at the Barrack and revealed that CARTER did not have anything in her mouth prior to being asked to submit to a breath test. The DR-15 Advice of Rights was read to CARTER on 3/9/2023. CARTER was also provided a copy to read over. After the DR-15 Advice of Rights was read, CARTER stated she wanted to make her phone call and she was advised she could not until she made a decision on the intoximeter test. CARTER then stated she wanted to speak to a lawyer and so I asked for the lawyer&amp;rsquo;s name, which she was not able to provide. CARTER stated her lawyer information was in her phone and she needed it. I turned CARTER&amp;rsquo;s phone on and as it did, I attempted to take her picture, which is required for the report. Every time I tried to take a picture, CARTER looked down. CARTER even stated she didn&amp;rsquo;t know where to look, even though I had told her several times to look at the camera. I let her make a call to her &amp;ldquo;lawyer&amp;rdquo;, however CARTER asked the supposed &amp;ldquo;lawyer&amp;rdquo; to come pick her up and did not ask for any legal advice. I also noticed CARTER used the word &amp;ldquo;his&amp;rdquo; while talking about her attorney. When CARTER was on the phone, it was clearly a female by the name Christina in the phone and her voice. When CARTER was giving the address out, she initially gave the wrong address. Based on how the name was written in CARTER&amp;rsquo;s phone and not asking the &amp;ldquo;lawyer&amp;rdquo; any legal questions, I believed this person to be a friend. CARTER gave me her phone so I could make sure the person on the phone had the right address. I continued my paperwork and approximately 20 minutes later, CARTER called her &amp;ldquo;lawyer&amp;rdquo; and I asked where she was and how far she was from the barrack. The &amp;ldquo;lawyer&amp;rdquo; stated she still had 30-45 minutes left. I then asked the person on the phone if she was a lawyer and she stated she was not. This is when CARTER became a little more agitated and when asked if she was going to take the intoximeter test, she just kept trying to argue and delay the process. At 0230 hours, I placed the DR-15 in front of CARTER and advised her to check the yes box if she wanted to take the intoximeter test and no if she did not. Ultimately, at 0230 hours, CARTER refused to submit to the intoximeter test by checking the &amp;quot;No&amp;quot; box on the DR-15. CARTER kept stating she was not passed out behind the wheel of a vehicle and kept asking why she was stopped and arrested. CARTER also stated she had already taken a breath test, however this was not the case being that she refused the breath test on the side of the road. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;INTOXIMETER RESULT:&lt;br /&gt; Refusal&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;CARTER was given copies of all pertinent paperwork and was transported to the Jennifer Road Detention Center.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 04:11:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 10:16:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Erin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6739</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gardner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Hunter</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7503</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Treleaven</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jones</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mujaihid</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1788</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jeans</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6483</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498021</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 04:12:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/09/2023 04:12:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 04:13:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371107</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Carter</LastName>
               <FirstName>Chanel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Evelyn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/27/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.79219195E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>03/09/2023 04:05:55</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C636</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Carter</LastName>
               <FirstName>Chanel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Evelyn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/27/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.79219195E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>C636</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/09/2023 04:05:55</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6810</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Pepper</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Capitol Heights</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20743</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2655</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.888152</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.893376</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>412</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2267</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 04:13:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 04:13:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 04:13:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 10:10:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 10:10:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150685</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 04:15:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/09/2023 04:15:36</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WDCTG4GBXHJ348914</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MERZ</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>GL4</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1EP8711</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>5</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/09/2023 11:30:03</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/09/2023 11:30:03</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/17/2023 08:08:05</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7503</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 11:30:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Incident recorded by In car camera (H-4) and Body Worn Camera (Tpr. Gardner #7503).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On March 9, 2023, at approximately 0106 hours, I, Trooper Gardner #7503, was operating marked MSP patrol vehicle H-4 in the area of Crain Highway and Millersville Road in full MSP uniform. While attempted to make the right turn from Crain Highway onto Millersville Road I observed a Silver Mercedez GL450 bearing Maryland registration 1EP8711 directly in front of my patrol vehicle did not react to the light changing from red to green. The traffic light changed from red to green again and the Silver Mercedez still failed to react to the light. I exited my patrol vehicle to check on the welfare of the driver and observed the driver to be unconscious at the wheel. I began to knock on the windows and yell at the driver, the driver still did not wake up. I requested EMS and additional units to assist as I continued to knock on the windows and yell at the driver to wake up. M/Tpr&amp;nbsp;Treleaven #4001 arrived on scene and also began knocking on the windows to attempt to wake up the driver.TFC Jeans #6483 and TFC Lowe #6739 arrived on scene. The driver woke up and took her foot off the brake beginning to drive slowly north in the right turn lane of Crain Highway towards Millersville Road. The driver came to a stop and shut off the vehicle and was identified as Chanel Evelyn Carter, B/F, DOB: 12/27/1991. CARTER exited the vehicle, I observed CARTER&amp;#39;s eyes to be glassy and bloodshot, and detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle. CARTER slurred her speech while answering questions, and swayed as she walked towards the front of her vehicle. TFC Jeans conducted standardized field sobriety testing, CARTER performed the tests poorly. CARTER was offered a Preliminary Breath test and refused. CARTER was arrested for DUI/DWI and transported to the Annapolis Barrack &amp;quot;J&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7503</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 11:31:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7503</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 02:35:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jones</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mujaihid</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1788</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gardner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Hunter</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7503</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>