<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002539</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/21/2023 02:18:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/21/2023 02:18:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/21/2023 01:54:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/21/2023 01:54:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI 23-020</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/21/2023 02:18:58</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 08:57:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>24 RING FACTORY</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>681268</AddressId>
      <City>MDC107</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/21/2023 02:18:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 01:47:15</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>681268</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>24</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Ring Factory</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.3415471666667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.5101971666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/21/2023 02:18:54</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/21/2023 02:18:54</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/29/2023 09:40:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/21/2023 02:18:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:51</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Defendant: Smith, Kristin Invernizzi&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 01/21/2023&lt;br /&gt; License Number: S-530-478-339-686&lt;br /&gt; DUI Number: 23-020&lt;br /&gt; Case Number: 23-MSP-002539&lt;br /&gt; Recording: D-27 is equipped with BWC/MVR. Interaction was captured.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I am a certified police officer in the State of Maryland with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection at the Maryland State Police Academy. My training has led to numerous arrests for impaired driving. I am trained by the Maryland State police to administer standardized field sobriety tests. I am a certified Preliminary Breath Test operator through the Maryland State Police. I am a graduate of the Advance Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement course (A.R.I.D.E.). I was recognized as a DUI Law Enforcement Awardee by the Maryland Highway Safety Office. I am a certified Advanced Collision Investigator through the Maryland State Police.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On 01/21/2023 at approximately 0154 hours I, TFC S McMachan #6940 of the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barracks was on duty, and operating Maryland State Police marked patrol vehicle D-27. At this time, I observed a white Ford Explorer bearing Maryland registration 4EY7143 stopped at the steady red traffic signal on Baltimore Pike at MD-24. It should be noted the entire Ford was stopped past the solid white stop line. Upon the red traffic signal turning green, the Ford made a left turn and traveled south on MD-24. At that time the posted speed limit was 40 miles per hour. The Ford appeared to accelerate and travel above the posted speed limit of 40 miles per hour. My speedometer displayed a speed reading of 52 miles per hour and the distance between my patrol vehicle and the Ford was increasing. The posted limit changed from 40 miles per hour to 55 miles per hour and the Ford continued to accelerate. My speedometer displayed a speed reading of 65 miles per hour and the distance between my patrol vehicle and the Ford was increasing. Furthermore, while following the Ford, I observed its driver side tires drift from lane two into lane one, then immediately back into lane two on two occasions. I activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the Ford.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the operator, stated the reason for the stop and requested her license and registration card. The operator was identified through her Maryland issued driver&amp;#39;s license as Kristin Invernizzi Smith (DOB;9/03/1971 2/F).&amp;nbsp; I asked Smith where she was heading to, to which she advised home. I asked Smith where she was coming from to which, she stated &amp;quot;Bel Air.&amp;quot; I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the Ford. Smith&amp;#39;s eyes appeared to be bloodshot, watery and glassy. Furthermore, Smith&amp;#39;s speech was slurred. I asked Smith where in Bel Air she was coming from to which, she advised &amp;quot;Magerk&amp;#39;s Pub.&amp;quot; I asked Smith how much she had to drink this evening to which, she stated &amp;quot;not a lot.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based off of my observations above, I requested Smith perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests to which, she agreed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed in front of my patrol vehicle. The surface was dry, level and free from any obvious debris. The forward facing emergency lights of all patrol vehicles on scene were deactivated for the duration of field sobriety.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I, once again, asked Smith how much she had to drink this evening to which, she stated &amp;quot;three drinks total.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Smith stated all three drinks were mixed with water and Vodka. While speaking with Smith I continued to detect the strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Smith the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; Glasses/Contacts: Contacts (clear)&lt;br /&gt; Blind in either eye: No&lt;br /&gt; Injuries/Illnesses: No&lt;br /&gt; Medication: Anxiety medication&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Medical disorders/disabilities: No&lt;br /&gt; Recent Head Trauma: No&lt;br /&gt; Under the care of a Doctor other than routine check-up: No&lt;br /&gt; Under the care of a Dentist other than routine check-up: No&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 CLUES):&lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Smith&amp;#39;s eyes. Smith was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Smith&amp;#39;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I asked Smith if she understood the instructions to which, she stated yes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Vertical Gaze Nystagmus - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN (6/8 CLUES):&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Smith performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Smith was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe, and to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in that position until instructed to begin. Smith was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. She was instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, Smith was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn 180 degrees facing the opposite direction. She was, again, explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Smith was instructed that once she began the test she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her sides, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Smith if she understood the instructions to which, she stated yes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Starts too soon&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Cannot keep balance&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Raises arms&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Misses heel to toe&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Steps off line&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Raises arms&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Steps off line&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Misses heel to toe&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Turn: Completed Incorrectly - Smith appeared to stumble on her last step and just turned around.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; It should be noted immediately after getting in the instructional position, Smith began to take steps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ONE LEG STAND (3/4 CLUES):&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Smith performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice approximately 6 inches off the ground. While her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Smith if she understood the instructions to which, she stated yes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Puts foot down&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Raises arms&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Puts foot down&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Sways&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Raises arms&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Puts foot down&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Sways&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Raises arms&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; It should be noted within the first couple seconds of performing the test, Smith said she was not going to be able to perform the test. I asked Smith if she did or did not want to perform the test to which she advised she would do it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to the observations from above, I determined Smith was unable to operate a vehicle safely and placed her under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at 0215 hours. Smith was secured in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and I transported her to the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barracks for processing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I read Smith the DR-15 Advice of Rights in English. She was also provided a copy to read along. At approximately 0244 hours, Smith signed the DR-15 Advice of Rights, refusing to submit to the evidentiary breath test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Smith was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released on her own recognizance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I request this case be closed by arrest.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 00:21:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6940</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 01:56:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mott</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6918</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McMachan</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6940</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brown</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4758</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McMachan</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6940</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McMachan</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6940</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491922</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/21/2023 01:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 01:48:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6940</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>51</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 01:48:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366933</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Smith</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kristin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Invernizzi</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/03/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14988499E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 01:43:26</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Smith</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kristin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Invernizzi</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/03/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14988499E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 01:43:26</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>42</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Northwood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Timonium</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21093</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4219</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.620807</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.438439</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>599</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7506</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 01:52:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 01:52:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 01:52:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 01:52:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 01:48:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6940</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 01:48:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148968</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 01:52:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6940</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 01:52:57</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>13</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1fmeu738x7ub78758</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2007</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>XPL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4ey7143</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>