<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011730</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/02/2023 04:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/02/2023 04:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/02/2023 03:30:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/02/2023 03:30:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>04/02/2023 07:24:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/02/2023 04:08:16</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0266</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/07/2023 07:53:40</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>BLUE STAR MEMORIAL HWY/ DEL RHODES AVE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>176778</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/02/2023 04:08:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/09/2023 11:25:40</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>176778</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Blue Star Memorial</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Queenstown</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21658</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>AVE</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.152851</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.987547</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB BLUE STAR MEMORIAL HWY / 0-0 DEL RHODES AVE EXIT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 BLUE STAR MEMORIAL HWY / 0-0 DEL RHODES AVE EXIT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 BLUE STAR MEMORIAL HWY / 600-604 DEL RHODES AVE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 BLUE STAR MEMORIAL HWY / 601-605 DEL RHODES AVE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 BLUE STAR MEMORIAL HWY / 607-699 DEL RHODES AVE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/02/2023 04:08:13</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/02/2023 04:08:13</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>80</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/15/2023 20:31:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/02/2023 04:08:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP0490</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 22:55:37</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>THE EVENT WAS AUDIBLY AND VISUALLY RECORDED VIA BODYWORN CAMERA&amp;nbsp; AND IN-CAR CAMERA&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Thompson, Charles,&amp;nbsp;Edward&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 02/20/1986&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 04/02/2023&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 0408 hours&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; DUI#: 23-038&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TRAINING/CERTIFICATES&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; Trained and Certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 04/02/2023 at 0333 hours, I, Tpr. Passwaters #7367 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police Centreville Barrack was operating marked Maryland State Police unit S-6. At that time, I was traveling on northbound U.S. Route 301 north of Del Rhodes Avenue when I observed a vehicle&amp;#39;s headlights off the roadway on the southbound side. The vehicle was approximately 50 yards into the field and appeared to be stuck in a ditch.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As I began walking out to the vehicle I observed it to be a red GMC Yukon bearing temporary Maryland registration &amp;quot;T1265087&amp;quot;. The GMC appeared to be stuck in a drainage ditch alongside a grassy farm lane that extends off of Clay Drive and runs parallel to U.S. Route 301. I approached the GMC and observed it to be occupied two times, one black male in the drivers seat, and another in the passenger seat. The GMC was still running.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked the driver &amp;quot;What happened?&amp;quot; he replied &amp;quot;We were trying to get out of this ditch and trying to turn around.&amp;quot; I asked &amp;quot;Why don&amp;#39;t you try to get out.&amp;quot; the driver replied &amp;quot;We&amp;#39;ve been trying to!&amp;quot; I responded &amp;quot;No, I mean get out of the car.&amp;quot; Both occupants exited the vehicle. I asked the driver and passenger for their driver&amp;#39;s licenses. The driver displayed a District of Columbia driver&amp;#39;s license &amp;quot;4915293&amp;quot; on their cellphone and was identified as Charles Edward Thompson Jr (#1/M DOB:02/20/1986). The passenger handed me his North Carolina ID card &amp;quot;000049944662&amp;quot; and was identified as Antwine Orlando Arnez Johnson Jr (#1/M DOB:08/22/1990).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Thompson &amp;quot;where were you coming from?&amp;quot; he replied &amp;quot;DC, but we&amp;#39;re trying to get back on the main road.&amp;quot; Thompson advised me that he ran out of gas so AAA towed his truck to the Royal Farms. Thompson advised that he was trying to get back onto U.S. Route 301 and thought Clay Drive would get him there. Clay attempted to turn around on the farm lane and got stuck in the drainage ditch.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked them where they were coming from prior to Royal Farms and Johnson stated that they were coming from Delmar and were trying to get back to District of Columbia. I asked them &amp;quot;Have you had anything to drink tonight and they replied &amp;quot;No.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then separated Thompson from Johnson. When asked where he was coming from again, Thompson stated &amp;quot;The other side of town, trying to get back to DC.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Thompson to perform a Standardized Field Sobriety Test to confirm that he was okay to drive and he agreed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRE ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the grassy farm lane running parallel with southbound U.S. 301 north of Del Rhodes Avenue. The surface was wet, level, and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and vehicles spotlight. Thompson was positioned in a manner so that passing traffic would not affect the test results. Thompson appeared to be in good physical condition.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Thompson the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Glasses or contacts - None&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Medical conditions - None&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Physical injuries - None&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Thompson performed the test in white sneakers&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of a pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus. It was held approximately 12-15 inches from Thompson&amp;#39;s eyes, slightly above eye level. Thompson was instructed to follow the tip of the stimulus with only his eyes. Thompson&amp;#39;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I instructed Thompson to put his heels and toes together for the HGN test. Thompson just stared at me and did not move. I repeated my instructions and Thompson complied. I re-explained the test and asked Thompson if he understood to which he replied &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I held the up the stimulus and Thompson was not looking at it. I repeated the instructions and asked &amp;quot;Do you understand?&amp;quot; to which he shrugged and said &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot; While checking for lack of smooth pursuit and equal tracking, Thompson immediately began moving his head left and right to follow the stimulus instead of using only his eyes. I then repeated the instructions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The wind changed direction and was blowing directly towards Thompsons face. I stepped behind Thompson and told him to &amp;quot;Face this way.&amp;quot; so that he would not be facing the wind. Thompson stood still and stared in the opposite direction. I tapped his shoulder and told him to turn around to which he finally complied. While standing directly in front of Thompson, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While attempting to check for distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, Thompson kept moving his head to the left and right in order to follow the stimulus. Once again, I instructed him to keep his head still. Thompson was not able to keep his head still.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; RESTING NYSTAGMUS NOT PRESENT. VERTICAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS NOT PRESENT&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN (6/8 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. Thompson was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Thompson was then instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and remain in that position until told to begin. Thompson was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line, and take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Thompson was instructed to complete the second series of nine (9) steps in the same heel to toe fashion.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Thompson could not properly get into the starting position. Instead of facing towards me while I showed him the starting position, he would turn to his left and face the same direction I was facing. Thompson could not continue with walking stage of the test while facing that direction so I repeatedly had to instruct him to face towards me. Thompson needed to be corrected five times.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Thompson placed his left foot in front of his right foot. Once again, I instructed him to place his right foot in front of his left foot.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cannot Keep Balance - Thompson put his right foot in front of his left foot and immediately moved his right foot to his right in an attempt to stay upright.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to beginning the walking stage, Thompson stated &amp;quot;Can my friend drive?&amp;quot; I replied &amp;quot;No, he doesn&amp;#39;t have a license.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (First Nine Steps):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Misses heel-toe - (Steps 1 through 13) Thompson missed his heel to toe by more than one half inch on every step he took.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Steps off line - (Steps 8 and 9) Thompson stepped more than his foot width off line on step 8 with his left foot and step 9 with his right foot.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Raises arms - Thompsons arms were raised approximately 6 to 10 inches from his sides during the entirety of his walking stage.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Actual number steps - Thompson failed to follow my instructions and took 13 steps before his turn.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Improper Turn: Thompson failed to follow my instructions and performed an improper turn. Thompson stepped out with his right foot and picked up his left foot and turned completely around rather than keeping his lead foot planted.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (Second Nine Steps):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Thompson performed an improper turn, stopped taking the test, and looked at me.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then decided to take Thompson up to the shoulder of southbound U.S. Route 301 to retake the walk and turn test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While on the shoulder, I re-explained the test once again. Thompson cut me off while I was explaining it to him and said &amp;quot;I understand the test, I am a special police officer, corrections in DC. I just wanted to make that known.&amp;quot; I asked Thompson to resume with the test and he said &amp;quot;I already took this test, sir.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After explaining the test I told Thompson to begin when he was ready. Thompson stood there staring at the road. I asked Thompson &amp;quot;Are you not gonna do it?&amp;quot; Thompson said &amp;quot;Of course! I didn&amp;#39;t deny I was gonna do the test.&amp;quot; I asked Thompson if I needed to re-explain the test and he replied &amp;quot;No.&amp;quot; I said &amp;quot;Go ahead.&amp;quot; Thompson then said &amp;quot;What&amp;#39;s the test?&amp;quot; I re-explained the test and Thompson had still had no idea how to do the test so I moved onto the one leg stand test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. Thompson was instructed to stand with his heels together and his hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to count out loud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two, etc.) and to not put his foot down until the end of the test. I asked Thompson if he understood the test and he confirmed. Thompson balanced on his right foot for the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 1-10:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Puts foot down (2 times)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Puts foot down (1 time)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Raises arms - Thompson raised his arms approximately 12 inches from his body in an attempt to balance himself.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While on scene, I informed Thompson of his Preliminary Breath Rights. Thompson was offered a PBT, to which he refused. Thompson stated he just wanted to go home.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the totality of circumstances, I concluded Thompson was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Slurred speech&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Thompson&amp;#39;s breath and person&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Thompson&amp;#39;s inability to obey designated lane directions and traveling off of the roadway into a field&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Thompson&amp;#39;s inability to comprehend simple instructions&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Clues during Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (6/6), WAT (6/8), OLS (2/4).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 04/02/2023, at approximately 0408 hours, I placed Thompson under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack. A search incident to arrest of Thompson&amp;#39;s person was conducted. The search of Thompson&amp;#39;s person was negative.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Thompson was read his DR-15 Advice of Rights in English. At approximately 0445 hours, Thompson agreed to take an alcohol concentration test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The test was conducted by Cpl.Turpin #5117 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Thompson refused to blow an adequate amount of air into the intoximeter and his test was counted as a refusal.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The vehicle was towed by Parks Tire and Auto Center&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At 0606 hours, Thompson was transported to the Queen Anne&amp;#39;s County Commissioners Office and was held without bond.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At 0719 hours, I transported Thompson to the Queen Anne&amp;#39;s County Detention Center.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; He was issued the following citations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Citations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TA 21-902(a)(1)(i) Driving vehicle while under the influence of alcohol&lt;br /&gt; TA 21-902(b)(1)(i) Driving vehicle while impaired by alcohol&lt;br /&gt; TA 21-901.1(b) Negligent driving vehicle in careless and imprudent manner endangering property, life and person&lt;br /&gt; TA 21-901.1(a) Reckless driving vehicle in wanton and willful disregard for safety of persons and property&lt;br /&gt; TA 21-309(d) Driver failure to obey designated lane directions&lt;br /&gt; TA 21-801(b) Failure to control vehicle speed on highway in order to avoid a collision.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The defendant was issued copies of the following documents:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Citations (listed above)&lt;br /&gt; -DR-15 Advice of Rights&lt;br /&gt; -DR-15a Order of Suspension&lt;br /&gt; -MSP 033&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Queen Anne&amp;#39;s County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:42:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7367</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/15/2023 15:07:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Maranto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7116</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Winiarski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Corey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7078</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Passwaters</LastName>
            <FirstName>Chase</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7367</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Curley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0490</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Passwaters</LastName>
            <FirstName>Chase</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7367</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Passwaters</LastName>
            <FirstName>Chase</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7367</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/02/2023 03:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:18:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7367</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/09/2023 11:26:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/02/2023 03:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:18:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7367</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/09/2023 11:27:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/02/2023 03:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:18:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7367</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/09/2023 11:28:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/02/2023 03:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:18:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7367</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/09/2023 11:29:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/02/2023 03:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:18:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7367</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/09/2023 11:30:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/02/2023 03:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:18:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7367</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/09/2023 11:31:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:18:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6778</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/25/2023 10:33:34</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373759</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Thompson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Edward</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/20/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.08705036E8</SSN>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 11:58:19</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T512</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Thompson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Edward</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/20/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.08705036E8</SSN>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>T512</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 11:58:19</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3905</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Davis</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>NW</StreetSuffixCode>
               <City>Washington</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20007</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.077978</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.923769</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>880</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1999</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:39:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:39:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:39:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:39:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:39:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:37:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>81789</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Johnson jr</LastName>
               <FirstName>Antwine</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Orlando A</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/22/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/30/2015 02:22:54</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Johnson jr</LastName>
               <FirstName>Antwine</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Orlando A</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/22/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/30/2015 02:22:54</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1020</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Fairground</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>10</SubNumber>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21801</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.618244</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.365227</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PA</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:37:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:25:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7367</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/09/2023 11:25:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151754</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 11:18:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7367</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/09/2023 11:18:51</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1GKS2CE07BR356736</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2011</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>YUK</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>RED</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>T1265087</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/31/2023 09:35:00</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/31/2023 09:35:00</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>80</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/05/2023 22:55:37</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 09:35:00</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 22:55:42</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>No supplement needed. Issued accidentally.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7367</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/04/2023 22:09:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7367</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/04/2023 22:09:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Curley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0490</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Passwaters</LastName>
            <FirstName>Chase</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7367</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>