<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008415</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>88</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/07/2023 11:07:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/07/2023 11:07:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/07/2023 10:53:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/07/2023 10:53:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>PWID MARIJUANA</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/07/2023 11:07:13</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2338</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 11:39:36</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>686573</AddressId>
      <City>MDC421</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/07/2023 11:07:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:32:51</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>686573</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Telegraph</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Severn</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.69076</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.11916</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>7650-7698</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/07/2023 11:07:09</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/07/2023 11:07:09</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>Y</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>88</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/29/2023 08:27:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/07/2023 11:07:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt; &amp;quot;This report has been prepared based upon the observations of this trooper and/or those of other troopers relative to the offense(s). The facts contained herein are intended solely to give the prosecuting authority a basic understanding of the facts pertaining to this case. The facts contained herein are not intended to be an exhaustive recitation of the facts pertaining to pretrial or trial issues. Instead, this trooper anticipates that during the pretrial proceedings in this case, the prosecutor will take the opportunity to interview this trooper in order to ascertain any and all relevant facts which might be the subject of this troopers&amp;#39; testimony during court proceedings.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&amp;nbsp; The camera systems are both manufactured by Axon. When the emergency lights are activated in the patrol car, the in-car camera will go back in time and start the recording 30 seconds before the emergency lights are activated. This is called a &amp;quot;30 second pre-record&amp;quot;. The camera system does not have a date and time stamp on the video itself. The system records the date and time in the metadata. The time only records the hour and minute when the camera starts the recording. Therefore, the timeline below will start with a time that was recorded from the camera&amp;#39;s metadata and then show the duration of the video. The body camera also has a one-minute pre-record after it is activated. The sound does not function until the 60 seconds mark is reached. This is the default function that cannot be altered, set by Axon and the Maryland State Police.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; The in-car camera and body camera remains the best depiction of the events surrounding the traffic stop. However, in order to obtain an exact time of a specific event, the reader will have to add the length of duration from the start of the video that was recorded in the metadata. Although times are recorded by other means such as the &amp;quot;Delta plus&amp;quot; system that prints a time stamp on the warning; citation or safety equipment repair order this time is only when the traffic stop button is activated by the Trooper. This can sometimes be shortly after making contact with a violator. Other programs such as Caliber RMS incident and CAD reports will show a timestamp, but this time depends on when the Police Communications Officer activates the incident. The two aforementioned examples of the recording of time will almost always be different from the in-car camera system due to all the systems utilizing different internal clocks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I, Senior Trooper Shrout, conducted a traffic stop on a white Ford van on southbound Route 175 prior to Route 100, Glen Burnie, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; During the course of the traffic stop, criminal indicators led me to believe that criminal activity was afoot.&amp;nbsp; This was based upon my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper.&amp;nbsp; I requested a canine scan of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; A positive alert led to the search of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; Contained inside the vehicle, I located 6 boxes of suspected marijuana weighing 123,920 grams, 7 jars of THC wax weighing 2,000 grams, 10 packages of THC vape pens weighing 25,260 grams and 10 boxes of marijuana edibles weighing 59,650 grams.&amp;nbsp; The driver was&amp;nbsp;placed under arrest. &amp;nbsp;Outlined below are the details surrounding that traffic stop and what actions were taken following the arrest of the suspect&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;the seizure of the evidence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; Assignment:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On Tuesday, March 7, 2023, I, Senior Trooper Shrout, of the Maryland State Police, Pro-Active Criminal Enforcement team was assigned to work in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; The Pro-Active Criminal Enforcement team is a team of specially trained Troopers designed to locate criminals through traffic enforcement.&amp;nbsp; The idea is that the Troopers will be aggressive and diligent during their enforcement efforts and conduct the complete traffic stop.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The objective is to reduce the number of motor vehicle collisions and locate criminals.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;The Traffic Violation:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;On 3/7/23 at approximately 1100 hours, I was sitting stationary in the area of Digiulian Blvd. and Dorsey Rd. At that time, my attention was directed towards a white Ford Penske van, which appeared to be traveling at a speed over the posted 50mph limit. I pulled into the flow of traffic directly behind the Ford van and activated my Golden Eagle II radar unit, obtaining a moving speed of 57mph. I soon identified the van by its Indiana registration 3289874. I continued to follow the vehicle, waiting for a safe location to conduct a traffic stop. After the van made a left turn onto Southbound MD RT. 170, I activated my emergency equipment to perform a traffic stop. The vehicle came to a stop at S/B RT. 170 and MD RT. 100. I exited my patrol vehicle and approached the front passenger window. I identified myself and the reason for the stop. The driver was identified to be Thomas Owen Dickerson by his Florida license.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; While speaking to Dickerson, I observed he was abnormally nervous as his voice was shaking and hands trembled as he handed me his license/paperwork. The temperature outside had been cold, and I could see Dickerson was beginning to sweat through his shirt and hooded sweatshirt. Through brief conversation, Dickerson stated he flew in to make a delivery for a company he worked for. I could see that Dickerson only had a small backpack with him, which did not look &amp;quot;stuffed&amp;quot; with clothing or any significant amount of property. I requested Dickerson exit the van in order to meet me to verify his information. I met Dickerson at the back of his van and began to gather information pertaining to the rental of the van, as well as his own driver&amp;#39;s information. Dickerson stated the address on his license was current. Dickerson stated he flew in to make a delivery of goods but, he was unsure of what it was and also could not provide a specific address. Dickerson provided the name of the company, but did not have any paperwork for the shipment. There was no bill of lading of any sort and there was no receipt. The rental had been placed out of California for only one day. I entered my patrol vehicle and requested CPL Yates to my location for purposes of a K-9 scan. CPL Yates arrived within approximately one minute. Based on my observations, CPL Yates performed a free-air exterior narcotic sniff on the vehicle while the normal business needs of the traffic stop were being completed. K-9 Buster would alert to the presence of a narcotic odor and a probable cause search was performed. The search began in the front of the van by myself and CPL Yates. The contents of the backpack were only a few hygiene products, less than a full change of clothes and some electronic cords. After searching the front cab of the van, myself and Cpl. Yates opened the two rear cargo doors of the van. At that time, I observed several large cardboard boxes, stacked onto two wooden pallets. Each group of boxes were wrapped in commercial grade plastic wrap and tape. The two groups of boxes were then held together by two metal bands. Cpl. Yates and I began to cut away the plastic wrap and tape on one pallet of boxes. After doing so, I opened the box and observed numerous sealed bags of suspected marijuana, which I immediately identified based on my training, knowledge and experience as a Maryland State Trooper. I placed Dickerson in handcuffs and performed a search of his person. While doing so, Cpl. Yates opened the second group of boxes, which also contained numerous sealed bags of suspected marijuana. This was also identified based on my training, knowledge and experience as a Maryland State Trooper. Dickerson was placed in my patrol vehicle and CPL Yates obtained digital photographs of the van and the shipment. Dickerson and the van were transported back to the Glen Burnie Barrack for processing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Post Arrest Investigation:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;After Dickerson and the rental van were transported to the Glen Burnie barrack, I completed the appropriate paperwork for Dickerson&amp;#39;s arrest. Members of the Metropolitan Area Drug Task Force made an attempt to interview Dickerson and also assisted with the processing of the van and seized contraband. After doing so, a total of 6 boxes of suspected marijuana weighing 123,920 grams, 7 jars of suspected THC wax weighing 2,000 grams, 10 boxes of suspected marijuana edibles weighing 59,650 grams and 10 packages of suspected THC vape pens weighing 25,260 grams were tallied. A total weight for the items came to be approximately 464.8 pounds. Dickerson&amp;#39;s iPhone and case were seized by the MADTF. Dickerson wished not to speak regarding the case and its findings. The paperwork and chain of custody surrounding the interview of Dickerson and seized items were retained by the MADTF. Photographs CPL Yates and I obtained can be seen attached to this case file. The backpack and its contents were stored at the Glen Burnie barrack. Based on my training, knowledge, experience, amounts, weights, packaging methods and other circumstances of the case, I recognized it to be indicative of purposes for distribution. All of the above events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; CASE CLOSED BY ARREST.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:47:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 10:29:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>88</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shrout</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5567</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>88</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hirsch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4526</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>88</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shrout</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5567</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>88</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shrout</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5567</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497814</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0573</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/07/2023 11:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0573</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:28:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:37:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497814</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0233</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/07/2023 11:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0233</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:28:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:36:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497814</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0881</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/07/2023 11:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0881</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:28:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:35:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:28:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:19</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371049</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dickerson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Owen</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/20/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>3.47865251E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 11:07:40</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D262</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dickerson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Owen</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/20/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>3.47865251E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>D262</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 11:07:40</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>323</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>898</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9745</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:39:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:39:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:32:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:32:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:41:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:41:07</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>6 boxes of suspected marijuana. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244988</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>123920</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:41:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:41:07</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>6 boxes of suspected marijuana. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244988</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>123920</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:41:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:41:08</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>6 boxes of suspected marijuana. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244988</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>123920</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:42:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:42:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>7 jars of suspected THC wax. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244989</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>2000</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:42:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:42:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>7 jars of suspected THC wax. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244989</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>2000</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:42:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:42:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>7 jars of suspected THC wax. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244989</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>2000</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:43:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:43:07</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>10 packages of THC vape pens. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244990</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>25260</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:43:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:43:07</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>10 packages of THC vape pens. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244990</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>25260</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:43:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:43:07</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>10 packages of THC vape pens. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244990</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>25260</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:43:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:43:57</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>10 boxes of marijuana edibles. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244991</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>59650</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:43:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:43:57</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>10 boxes of marijuana edibles. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244991</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>59650</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5567</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 11:43:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5567</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 11:43:57</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>10 boxes of marijuana edibles. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244991</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>59650</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/27/2023 13:28:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/27/2023 13:28:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40P</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/29/2023 08:27:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>TF0309</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 13:28:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On 3/6/23 members of the MADTF received information from two reliable sources in reference to a large shipment of CDS that was coming to a local freight company. On 3/7 23 at approximately 0630 HRS an interdiction operation was initiated. Members of the MADTF conducted surveillance on the local freight company and at approximately 0935 hours the arrestee, who was later identified by his Florida driver&amp;rsquo;s license as Thomas O Dickerson arrived in a white transit van to pick up two palletized freight shipments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Once the freight was loaded into the van Owens left the freight company. MSP PACE stopped the vehicle, observed criminal indicators and conducted a K-9 scan which returned with a positive alert. A&amp;nbsp; search of the freight shipment was done and upon opening a card box a large quantity of marijuana was observed inside. Owens was placed under arrest and transported to the MSP Glen Burnie Barrack. I (Det. DIggs #309)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="border:none windowtext 1.0pt; font-size:12.0pt; padding:0in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;nbsp;was contacted and offered &lt;strong&gt;Dickerson&lt;/strong&gt; the opportunity to speak with me, but he declined. An Apple iPhone &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;(S/N: 350002265801961) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="border:none windowtext 1.0pt; font-size:12.0pt; padding:0in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;was also seized from &lt;strong&gt;Dickerson&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/strong&gt; person for further investigation. I subsequently retrieved the Apple iPhone on &lt;strong&gt;March 7, 2023&lt;/strong&gt; at &lt;strong&gt;1254&lt;/strong&gt; hours from S/T Shrout.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;A closer inspection of the freight shipment at the MSP Barrack revealed that it contained the following items;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;-6 BOXES OF MARIJUANA: 123,920 GRAMS, STREET VALUE $1,239,200&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;-7 JARS THC WAX: 2000 GRAMS, STREET VALUE $20,000&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;-10 PACKAGES OF THC VAPE PENS: 25,260 GRAMS, STREET VALUE $252,600&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;-10 BOXES OF MARIJUANA EDIBLES: 59,650 GRAMS, STREET VALUE $596,500&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All of this combined weighed &lt;strong&gt;464.8 pounds of marijuana and marijuana&lt;/strong&gt; related CDS.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="border:none windowtext 1.0pt; font-size:12.0pt; padding:0in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The Apple iPhone &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;(S/N: 350002265801961) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;was&lt;span style="border:none windowtext 1.0pt; padding:0in"&gt; secured at the MSP property storage on &lt;strong&gt;March 7, 2023&lt;/strong&gt; at &lt;strong&gt;1500&lt;/strong&gt; hours. On March 8, 2023, I authored a search and seizure warrant for the aforementioned Apple iPhone that was subsequently granted by the Honorable Judge G. Powell to further the investigation.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; CASE CLOSED BY ARREST&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ALL EVENTS OCCURRED IN ANNE ARUNDEL COUNTY MARYLAND&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>TF0309</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 13:29:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0309</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 15:40:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40P</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McNeely</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4812</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40P</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>DIGGS</LastName>
            <FirstName>GARWOOD</FirstName>
            <InternalID>TF0309</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>