<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-005168</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/10/2023 01:36:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/10/2023 01:36:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/10/2023 01:23:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/10/2023 01:23:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was stopped for a traffic violation and later arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 01:37:01</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4913</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 11:35:51</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>324 ROWE,ANNAPOLIS</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>558963</AddressId>
      <City>MDC102</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 01:37:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/10/2023 03:05:56</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>558963</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Rowe Blvd @ Melvin Ave.</StreetName>
         <City>Annapolis</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21401</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-76.50559</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.98881</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 ROWE BLVD / 0-0 MELVIN AVE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/10/2023 01:36:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/10/2023 01:36:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/10/2023 04:56:41</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 01:37:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;J-16 is MVR and BWC equipped, this stop was recorded.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Watkins Jr., Barry Lovell&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 1/7/1991&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 2/10/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 0136 hours&lt;br /&gt; MD SDX: W-325-081-550-022&lt;br /&gt; DUI #: J-23-023&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; * Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; * Apprehended more than 210 impaired drivers during my career with the Maryland State Police to date.&lt;br /&gt; * Attended the 2016 DUI Conference&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Completed the 2017 DUI Institute at the University of Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Received the Smooth Operator Award&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;* Received the Aggressive Drivers are Public Threats (ADAPT) Award.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Completed the Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Course (ARIDE).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On February 10, 2023, at approximately 0123 hours, I (TFC Jeans #6483) was conducting stationary RADAR enforcement northbound Rowe Blvd and Herbert Sach&amp;rsquo;s Dr., Annapolis, Anne Arundel County, Maryland. I was in the uniform of the day and operating unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle J-16. At that time, I observed a vehicle coming toward my location and appeared to have been exceeding the maximum posted speed limit of 40 MPH. I activated the front antenna of my Golden Eagle II RADAR unit in the stationary mode and obtained a speed of 62 MPH in a posted 40 MPH zone. No other vehicles were around or in my zone of influence. I am certified to operate LIDAR and RADAR and the RADAR unit was tested before and after my shift and found to be functioning properly. The vehicle was observed to be bearing Maryland Registration plate 6EA0448 and the tag was displayed on a gray Mercedes S class, which was in lane two. I pulled out behind the Mercedes and as I did, I noticed the Mercedes was in lane two and it drifted across the dotted white lines that separate lanes one and two prior to Rowe Blvd. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle, northbound Rowe Blvd at Melvin Ave.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;After coming to a stop, I approached the Mercedes and made contact with the operator, and sole occupant, of the vehicle by a passenger side approach. I stated to the male driver the stop was being audibly and visibly recorded and that he was stopped for his speed, 62 MPH in a posted 40 MPH zone. When asked if there was any reason for the violation, the driver stated it was his dad&amp;rsquo;s car and his car was in the shop. I asked the driver where he was coming from and he stated he was coming from Pasadena that he went to Annapolis to drop off a friend and he was now on his way home to Pasadena. I requested his driver&amp;rsquo;s license and registration card, which the driver was only able to display his license to me. The driver was not able to locate the registration card. When asked if he lived at the current address on his license, the driver stated that he did. The driver was identified as Barry Lovell Watkins Jr., B/M, DOB: 1/7/1991. As WATKINS was searching for his registration card and as I spoke to WATKINS, I observed he had slow and lethargic movements. While speaking with WATKINS, I smelled a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle and intentionally observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I also noticed WATKINS had slurred and mumbled speech. I asked WATKINS how much alcohol he had and he stated &amp;ldquo;none&amp;rdquo;. I asked WATKINS what I was smelling and he did not know. I advised WATKINS to stay in the vehicle and he complied.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A routine check through the MVA database revealed that WATKINS was driving on a valid driver&amp;rsquo;s license and was not wanted. On my second approach, I asked WATKINS if he would exit his vehicle to complete Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, which he agreed to. While communicating with WATKINS by the front of the vehicle, I again smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of northbound Rowe Blvd at Melvin Ave. The weather was clear and approximately 54 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of my patrol vehicle headlights, spotlight, flashlight and street lamps. The shoulder was level and free from any debris. My patrol vehicle&amp;rsquo;s forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. WATKINS appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any major visible injuries when walking from the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked WATKINS the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Medical Conditions &amp;ndash; None&lt;br /&gt; Injuries &amp;ndash; L5 injured 10 years ago playing sports.&lt;br /&gt; Medication &amp;ndash; None&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;WATKINS had not fallen down or spun around in circles recently.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WATKINS was not wearing glasses during the time of the stop. He was wearing contacts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;nbsp;Since WATKINS was taller than me, I asked him to sit down on the hood of his vehicle. As he did, he sat down on the Mercedes emblem on the front of the vehicle, breaking it. WATKINS did not react to this.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from WATKINS&amp;rsquo;S eyes. WATKINS was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. WATKINS&amp;rsquo;S pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. WATKINS was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. WATKINS was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WATKINS did show signs of vertical nystagmus, indicating WATKINS had a high amount of alcohol in his system for him. During the test, WATKINS had to be told to just follow the stimulus with his eyes only and to stop moving his head.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The walk and turn test was properly explained and demonstrated per the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. At the conclusion of the demonstration and explanation, WATKINS was asked if he understood the test, to which he stated &amp;ldquo;yes&amp;rdquo;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Lost balance.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 2 and 5.&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Stopped walking on step 9.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Turn: Did not follow instructions and turned with both feet. Rocked back on his heels before starting the second series of steps and did not take small, choppy steps like instructed to do.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on step 1.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;ONE LEG STAND (4/4 clues, Right foot raised)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The one leg stand test was properly explained and demonstrated per the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. At the conclusion of the demonstration and explanation, WATKINS was asked if he understood the test, to which he stated &amp;ldquo;yes&amp;rdquo;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Nothing to report.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage: WATKINS started over three times. WATKINS never counted over 1010.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Raised his arms by more than 6 inches from his sides to maintain balance on count 1002, 1007 and 1010.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;2.) Placed his foot down on count 1002, 1004, 1007, and 1010.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;3.) Swayed to maintain his balance on counts 1001, 1002, 1004, and 1007.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;4.) Hopped to maintain his balance on count 1008.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Due to how slow WATKINS was counting, he only counted to 1010 in a 30 second time span. At one point, WATKINS was counting while his foot was still on the ground and he had to be told to raise his foot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;While on scene, WATKINS was offered a preliminary breath test and results were .22 BrAC.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ARREST&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe WATKINS was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from vehicle/breath.&lt;br /&gt; * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.&lt;br /&gt; * Mumbled and slurred speech.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Slow and lethargic movements.&lt;br /&gt; * Clues during standardized field sobriety testing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Due to the number of observations, I concluded WATKINS was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0136 hours, I placed WATKINS under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. A preliminary search of WATKINS was conducted on scene and the gum in his mouth was spit out. WATKINS was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy. Once belted in the vehicle, I shut my passenger side door and walked around to the driver&amp;rsquo;s side and got into my vehicle. When I did, I noticed the extremely strong odor of an alcoholic beverage had engulfed my patrol vehicle. That odor was not there prior to WATKINS getting into my vehicle. The vehicle was towed by Marc Bowen Tow Service.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 20 Minute Observation Period&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A secondary search was conducted upon arrival at the Barrack and revealed that WATKINS had nothing in his mouth prior to the time he was asked to submit to the test. The DR-15 Advice of Rights was read to WATKINS on 2/10/2023 at 0218 hours. This is when WATKINS stated he was scared and that his chest was hurting him. I started EMS so they could check out WATKINS. Other than the high blood pressure, they did not find anything else wrong with WATKINS. As EMS checked WATKINS out, he asked them for a note to show he was not able to take the breath test being offered to him. After EMS cleared and he was asked again if he wanted to take the test, WATKINS ultimately refused to submit to an intoximeter test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;INTOXIMETER RESULT:&lt;br /&gt; Refusal&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;WATKINS was given copies of all pertinent paperwork and was released to a sober rider. WATKINS was cooperative throughout the process and released.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 03:15:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/10/2023 04:28:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Erin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6739</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jeans</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6483</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494554</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/10/2023 01:23:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 03:06:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/10/2023 03:06:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 03:08:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:29</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368676</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Barry</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lovell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/07/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.15311706E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>02/10/2023 02:44:55</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W325</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Barry</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lovell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/07/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.15311706E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>W325</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/10/2023 02:44:55</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>61</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Magothy Beach</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Pasadena</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21122</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4462</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.518839</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.116877</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>942</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2124</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 03:08:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 03:08:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 03:08:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 03:06:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/10/2023 03:06:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149676</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 03:09:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/10/2023 03:09:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WDDNG7DB6CA451203</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2012</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MERZ</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>S50</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6EA0448</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>