<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009086</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/12/2023 07:03:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/12/2023 07:03:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/12/2023 06:36:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/12/2023 06:36:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>MSP Westminster DUI 23-041 // Osorio Alegria, Ever Luis</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 07:03:37</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 09:37:00</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>1771</AddressId>
      <City>MDC249</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 07:03:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 01:28:46</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>1771</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1400</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Baltimore</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westminster</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21157</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.945158</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.548752</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>CARROLL COUNTY LANDFILL</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>AREA OF CARROLL COUNTY LANDFILL</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/12/2023 07:03:34</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/12/2023 07:03:34</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/29/2023 00:01:04</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 07:03:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:20:55</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Maryland State Police Westminster DUI #23-041&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; TFC Nield #6851&lt;br /&gt; Case Number: 23-MSP-009086&lt;br /&gt; The incident was recorded. MSP marked unit G-23 equipped with MVR and TFC Nield is equipped with a body-worn camera.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Incident:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; TA 21-902(a)(1) Attempting to Drive Motor Vehicle Under the Influence of Alcohol&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Certifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Over 85 career DUI arrests to date&lt;br /&gt; - Collision Reconstruction Specialist&lt;br /&gt; - Certified Field Training Trooper&lt;br /&gt; - 2018 Ocean City Impaired Driving Conference&lt;br /&gt; - Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) training course&lt;br /&gt; - National Highway Safety Transportation Administration (NHSTA) certified to conduct Standardized Field&amp;nbsp;Sobriety Test (SFST)&lt;br /&gt; - Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;nbsp;Certified police officer in the state of Maryland with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with live donors at the Maryland State Police Academy.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Defendant:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Ever Luis Osorio Alegria&lt;br /&gt; H/M DOB: 07/28/1992&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Attachments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DR-15 Advice of Rights&lt;br /&gt; DR-15A Order of Suspension&lt;br /&gt; METERS Printouts&lt;br /&gt; Copy of Traffic Citations&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Location:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; E/B MD-140 in the area of the Carroll County Landfill (1400 Baltimore Blvd)&lt;br /&gt; Westminster. Maryland&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Date and Time:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 3/12/2023 at approximately 0636 hours&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;NARRATIVE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1):&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On 3/12/2023 at approximately 0636 hours, I, TFC Nield #6851, was on routine patrol of E/B MD-140 in the area of the Sheetz (1023 Baltimore Blvd, Westminster, Maryland). At this time, I observed a black Ford Explorer bearing Maryland registration &amp;quot;8EK6611&amp;quot; traveling ahead of me in lane 2. I observed that the Ford Explorer was drifting between its lane lines, touching the left lane line before drifting towards the right lane line, touching it, and then drifting back towards the left lane line and touching it again. I then conducted a pace on the Ford Explorer by keeping approximately 3 car lengths between the rear bumper of the Ford and the front bumper and observed that the Ford was traveling at approximately 35MPH in a posted 45MPH zone. I then pulled alongside the Ford in lane 1 to see if the driver was using a handheld telephone while the vehicle was in motion, but I observed that the operator did not have anything in his hands.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At this time, I had created distance between my patrol vehicle and the Ford, at which time I was able to observe that the Ford&amp;#39;s passenger side headlight was inoperative. I then began to slow my patrol vehicle and change lanes into the U-turn in front of Tractor Supply Co. (1151 Baltimore Blvd, Westminster, Maryland) and waited for the Ford to pass my location. As the Ford passed, I activated my emergency equipment to conduct a traffic stop on the Ford. The Ford continued to travel in the eastbound lane for approximately 10 seconds before activating their right turn signal. The Ford then continued to drive in lane 2 with its right turn signal activated for approximately 10 more seconds before pulling onto the right shoulder.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I made contact with the operator of the Ford at the driver&amp;#39;s side window. I introduced myself, explained that the traffic stop was being audibly and visually recorded, and explained the reason for the traffic stop. As soon as the driver put the driver&amp;#39;s side window down, I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I observed that the driver&amp;#39;s eyes were bloodshot, watery, and glassy. I then asked the driver for his driver&amp;#39;s license and registration, and then asked the driver how much he had to drink. The front seat passenger then began to answer for the driver, but I again asked the driver how much he had to drink. The front seat passenger then answered that the driver had &amp;quot;Three&amp;quot; as the driver held up three fingers and repeated, &amp;quot;Three sir.&amp;quot; I again asked the driver for his driver&amp;#39;s license, at which time the driver began to search his person and the vehicle for the requested document. While the driver searched, I looked into the back seat and observed two open boxes of alcohol; a box of Corona and a box of Smirnoff Ice. The driver then handed me the Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license of the front seat passenger. I again explained to the driver that I needed his driver&amp;#39;s license, at which time the front seat passenger explained that he was driving because she &amp;quot;had been drinking.&amp;quot; I asked the driver if he had a driver&amp;#39;s license, to which he answered, &amp;quot;No sir.&amp;quot; I then asked the driver for an identification card, and the driver provided me with an El Salvador ID card, and I was able to positively identify the driver as&amp;nbsp;Ever Luis Osorio Alegria (H/M DOB: 07/28/1992). I asked the front seat passenger if they had both been drinking, to which she replied, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot; I then asked&amp;nbsp;Osorio Alegria to step out of the vehicle, to which he complied.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Note: The following conversations were translated through Google Translate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Once outside the vehicle, I continued to detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from&amp;nbsp;Osorio Alegria&amp;#39;s breath once he was outside the vehicle. As Osorio Alegria opened the door to exit the vehicle, I observed an empty bottle of Corona on the driver&amp;#39;s side floorboard. I asked&amp;nbsp;Osorio Alegria how much he had to drink, to which he again answered, &amp;quot;Three, sir.&amp;quot; I asked&amp;nbsp;Osorio Alegria when he had those drinks, to which he replied. &amp;quot;Right now.&amp;quot; I asked&amp;nbsp;Osorio Alegria if he had just drank them right now, to which he replied, &amp;quot;Yeah, yeah.&amp;quot; I then asked&amp;nbsp;Osorio Alegria if I could put him through the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, to which he complied.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Medical Screening:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The evaluation was performed on a flat portion of the shoulder on E/B MD-140.&amp;nbsp;I observed the ground to be dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight, the overhead streetlights, and the headlight of Osorio Alegria&amp;#39;s Ford. I asked Osorio Alegria&amp;nbsp;if he took any medications to which replied he did not.&amp;nbsp;I asked Osorio Alegria if he had any physical ailments that would prevent him from taking the tests, to which he replied that he did not.&amp;nbsp;I asked Osorio Alegria if he wore glasses or contacts, and he stated that he did not. As Osorio Alegria answered, I continued to detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN): 6/6 Clues Observed&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) test. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus and was held approximately 12-15 inches from Osorio Alegria&amp;#39;s eyes. Osorio Alegria was instructed to keep his&amp;nbsp;head still and follow the stimulus with his eyes only. Osorio Alegria&amp;rsquo;s pupils were equal size and tracked equally. I asked Osorio Alegria if he could see the stimulus, to which he replied he could. I observed a lack of smooth pursuit in the left and right eye, Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus in the left and right eye, and Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees in the left and right eye. Additionally, Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was observed in&amp;nbsp; both the left and the right eye.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;WALK AND TURN: 4/8 Clues Observed&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The next test given was the Walk and Turn test. Prior to Osorio Alegria performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Osorio Alegria was instructed to imagine a straight line in front of him or to use the solid white fog line&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;place his&amp;nbsp;left foot on the line and then place his right foot directly in front of his left foot touching heel-to-toe. Osorio Alegria was instructed to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in this position until told to begin. Osorio Alegria was instructed to take nine (9) steps on a straight line and given a demonstration on how to perform heel-to-toe on each step.&amp;nbsp; Osorio Alegria was also instructed to keep his hands flat on his side, to count each step out loud, and to look down at his feet. On the ninth step, Osorio Alegria was instructed and shown a demonstration to keep his lead foot planted and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Osorio Alegria was again instructed and demonstrated how to take the returning nine (9) steps identically to the first nine (9).&amp;nbsp; Osorio Alegria was instructed that once he began the test to not stop walking until the test was completed. (Footwear: black athletic shoes).&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Instructional Phase:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 1. Osorio Alegria began walking before being instructed to do so.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Walking Stage (1&lt;sup&gt;St&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;Nine):&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 1. Osorio Alegria raised his right arm for balance on step 9&lt;br /&gt; 1. Osorio Alegria took 11 steps instead of the instructed 9.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Turn:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 1. Osorio Alegria did not complete the turn as instructed. Osorio Alegria attempted to begin walking backwards along the line.&amp;nbsp;Osorio Alegria&amp;nbsp;then began to walk in a circle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Osorio Alegria&amp;nbsp;was instructed to return to the beginning portion before attempting to complete the second set of 9 steps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;ONE LEG STAND: 0/4 Clues observed&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Prior to Osorio Alegria performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. When he was instructed to begin, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately six inches and keep it pointed straight as to be parallel with the ground. While his leg was raised he was to keep his arms at his sides, keep his&amp;nbsp;leg straight, look directly at his raised foot, and count out loud and to continue the test until instructed to stop. Osorio Alegria was asked if he understood the instructions, which he stated he did. Osorio Alegria chose to lift his left foot.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Balance and Count Stage:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10:&lt;br /&gt; No clues observed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20:&lt;br /&gt; No clues observed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30:&lt;br /&gt; No clues observed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Osorio Alegria was offered a preliminary breath test which resulted in a reading of .15.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Arrest:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the clues observed, Osorio Alegria was placed under arrest for driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol. After being placed into handcuffs. Osorio Alegria requested that I allow him to speak into Google Translate, at which time he made a voluntary utterance stating &amp;quot;I had beers with some friends, but I don&amp;#39;t understand what they gave me at the end because I don&amp;#39;t understand.&amp;quot; Osorio Alegria was placed in the front seat of marked MSP patrol vehicle G-23 by M/T Fair and TFC Hollinger. While&amp;nbsp;Osorio Alegria was being placed in my patrol vehicle,&amp;nbsp;I returned to the Ford to document the open and empty containers of alcohol that I had seen previously. In the passenger side front door, I observed a half-empty bottle of Corona. On the passenger side floorboard, I observed a full bottle of Corona and a full bottle of Smirnoff Ice. On the passenger side rear floorboard, I observed the open boxes of Corona and Smirnoff Ice. Underneath the driver&amp;#39;s seat, I discovered 4 empty bottles of Corona in addition to the one empty one on the driver&amp;#39;s side floorboard.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Osorio Alegria was then transported to the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack. During transport, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage. At approximately 0733 hours, Osorio Alegria was read his DR-15 Advice of Rights utilizing the Spanish Interpretation from the Motor Vehicle Administration website, and was offered a decision to submit to an alcohol concentration test. At the conclusion of the form, Osorio Alegria agreed to submit to the test and signed the DR-15, but was unable to provide a sufficient breath sample. A routine METERS check of&amp;nbsp;Osorio Alegria by the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack Emergency Dispatcher revealed that&amp;nbsp;Osorio Alegria did not have a driver&amp;#39;s license.&amp;nbsp;Osorio Alegria was then released to a sober driver with all the DUI related paperwork, Notice to Appear and Notice of Counsel, and citations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I request this case be closed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 20:59:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6851</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 01:35:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nield</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6851</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498485</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/12/2023 06:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:32:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6851</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 09:32:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>30</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:09:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:43</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371994</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Osorio Alegria</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ever</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Luis</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/28/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 21:08:44</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>O264</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E160</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Osorio Alegria</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ever</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Luis</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/28/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>O264</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E160</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 21:08:44</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:09:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:09:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 21:09:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:32:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6851</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 09:32:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>