<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009127</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/12/2023 16:51:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/12/2023 16:51:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/12/2023 16:28:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/12/2023 16:28:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Two vehicle collision // DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 16:52:01</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0266</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/23/2023 07:50:01</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY/ CENTREVILLE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>233447</AddressId>
      <City>MDC219</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 16:52:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP7387</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/15/2023 22:07:55</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>233447</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Ocean </StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Queenstown</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21658</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Distance>0.5</Distance>
         <DistanceUnits>M</DistanceUnits>
         <Longitude>-76.076017</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.953905</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>PRIOR TO RT 213</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/12/2023 16:51:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/12/2023 16:51:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>80</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/22/2023 04:29:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 16:52:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:11</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>THIS STOP WAS AUDIBLY AND VISUALLY RECORDED ON BWC. S-32. DUI #S-23-025&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; TROOPER A. DAMIANO- ID #7387 MARYLAND STATE POLICE &amp;ndash; CENTREVILLE BARRACK &amp;ldquo;S&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING:&lt;br /&gt; -NHTSA CERTIFIED TO CONDUCT STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFST)&lt;br /&gt; -CERTIFIED PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT) OPERATOR&lt;br /&gt; -NHTSA CERTIFIED TO CONDUCT ADVANCED ROADSIDE IMPAIRED DRIVING ENFORCEMENT (ARIDE)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; DESCRIPTION OF VIOLATION / INCIDENT / TRAFFIC STOP (VEHICLE IN MOTION)-&lt;br /&gt; On March 12th, 2023, at approximately 1628 hours, I was dispatched to a two vehicle collision with injuries in the area of westbound Ocean Gateway at Centreville Road in Queenstown, Queen Anne&amp;rsquo;s County. Upon arrival, I observed a two vehicle collision off the roadway on the shoulder. I observed a silver Toyota Matrix bearing Maryland registration &amp;ldquo;2AD14431&amp;rdquo; on the right shoulder with front end damage.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; INITIAL CONTACT WITH DEFENDANT (PERSONAL CONTACT)-&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the driver and identified him by his Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license as Kevin Alan Groce (1/M, 04/18/1975). I asked Groce to gather his license, registration, and proof of insurance. Groce first provided me with an expired Maryland ID card. I then asked Groce twice what happened. He stated &amp;ldquo;they hit the brakes. I have no excuse.&amp;rdquo; &amp;nbsp;Groce then handed me his driver&amp;rsquo;s license. Groce had noticeable difficulty focusing and comprehending and responding to simple questions. I noted his speech to be slurred and his movements lethargic. &amp;nbsp;I also observed his eyes to be red, glassy, and bulging. I observed Groce get distracted by his phone. I then asked Groce again for his registration and proof of insurance. Groce did not look up and make eye contact with me at any point. Groce also did not verbally acknowledge that he heard or understood my questions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked Groce where he was coming from tonight. Groce said he was coming from his mother&amp;rsquo;s house in Marydel, Maryland. I then asked Groce what he was doing there and he did not respond. I then asked what time he left and he stated 12pm. Groce then stated he was coming from his father&amp;rsquo;s house in Greensboro, Maryland. While speaking with Groce, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath and person. I then asked Groce how many alcoholic beverages he had today. Groce replied &amp;ldquo;one beer.&amp;rdquo; I then asked Groce if he had consumed any illicit substances or medication and stated he had not.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked Groce if he would submit to perform standardized field sobriety tests (SFST) on him, to which he agreed to the tests.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Upon exiting the vehicle, I observed Groce be unsteady on his feet and move slowly. Groce had noticeable trouble concentrating or understanding my instructions. Groce became fixated on the damage to his vehicle and had to be coaxed into following instructions. Groce continued to avoid eye contact with me.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to administering SFST, I advised Groce I was going to explain the instructions to each of the tests.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of Ocean Gateway. The surface was dry and free from any obvious debris. The weather was cloudy. Lighting conditions were clear. My patrol vehicle&amp;rsquo;s forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Groce appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries from the collision.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Groce was asked the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; Glasses or Contacts &amp;ndash; None.&lt;br /&gt; Medical Conditions &amp;ndash; None.&lt;br /&gt; Injuries &amp;ndash; None.&lt;br /&gt; Medication &amp;ndash; Flomax for his prostate, taken once a night.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of a pen was used as the test&amp;rsquo;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches Groce&amp;rsquo;s eyes. Groce was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. I then instructed Groce again to follow the stimulus with his eyes and his eyes only. Groce&amp;rsquo;s pupils were constricted, pin point in size, and bulging and showed equal tracking. While administering this test, Groce moved or tilted his head several times. Groce had to be reminded and coached on how to not to turn or tilt his head for several minutes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN (6/8 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Groce performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Groce was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary line. Groce was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Groce was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step. Groce was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Groce was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to the left to turn completely around. Groce was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Groce was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Groce if he understood the test and he advised he understood.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While giving instructions, Groce had trouble understanding how to put his left foot on the line and his right in front of his left. Groce also broke from the position and did not get back into it after being instructed to do so. Groce then became distracted and began walking around after I informed him he had started too soon.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional stage:&lt;br /&gt; -Started too soon&lt;br /&gt; -Failed to maintain balance&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Stepped offline by more than a shoe width on all steps.&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Missed touching heel to toe by more than &amp;frac12; inch on all steps.&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Stopped walking at step 3 to regain balance.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Turn: &amp;nbsp;Completed Unsatisfactory. Pivoted on left foot clockwise instead of counterclockwise as instructed. Groce also lost balance after attempting the turn.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Stopped walking and did not complete the rest of the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Groce performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Groce was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Groce was asked if he understood the test and the instructions. He advised that he understood.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage:&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) &amp;nbsp;Foot hit the ground.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds: 21-30:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Raised arms approximately 6 inches from his side for balance.&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Hopped on one foot.&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Foot hit the ground.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ARREST&lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Groce was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; * Causing a two vehicle collision&lt;br /&gt; * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his body and breath&lt;br /&gt; * Red, glassy, bulging eyes&lt;br /&gt; * Constricted pupils&lt;br /&gt; * Slurred speech&lt;br /&gt; * My observed signs of impairment as Groce performed field sobriety tests&lt;br /&gt; * Several open containers of alcohol inside Groce&amp;rsquo;s vehicle. 2 empty vodka bottles, 1 empty 25 fl oz can of Busch Ice, and 1 empty bottle of Newamsterdam vodka.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to the above stated observations, I concluded Groce was driving while impaired. Groce was placed under arrest for Driving While Under the Influence of Alcohol. Groce was then read his Miranda rights at 1714 hours.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While speaking with the driver, he displayed several indicators. Groce refused to make eye contact, had wide open and bulging eyes, kept hands behind his back or in his pockets, and refused to answer questions verbally. Then DFC Bradley with Queen Anne&amp;rsquo;s County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office was called to conduct a K9 scan of the vehicle. K9 scan alerted on Groce&amp;rsquo;s vehicle and a search was performed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Groce was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and transported to the Maryland State Police Centreville Barrack. For the 20 minute observation period I did not observe Groce regurgitate or place anything in his mouth.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Groce was read the DR-15 Advice of Rights form in English via MVA audio recording, at which time he refused to take the breath test at 1804 hours.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Groce was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to a valid driver.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Queen Anne&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Case closed due to arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7387</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 18:55:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7387</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/21/2023 05:54:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barbiche</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6649</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bolduc</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4889</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Damiano</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ariona</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7387</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498526</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/12/2023 16:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7387</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 22:15:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7387</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 22:15:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>47</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7387</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 22:19:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:02</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371409</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Groce</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/18/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/12/2023 22:18:36</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Groce</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/18/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/12/2023 22:18:36</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7387</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 22:19:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7387</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 22:19:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7387</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 22:15:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7387</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 22:15:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150811</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7387</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 22:20:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7387</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 22:20:55</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/12/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2T1KU4EE1AC290541</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2012</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MTX</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2AD1443</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>