<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012107</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/05/2023 07:46:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/05/2023 07:46:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/05/2023 05:54:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/05/2023 05:54:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Emergency Petition</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 07:46:05</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 15:06:43</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>EP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>77658</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 07:46:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/05/2023 12:25:37</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>77658</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>10580</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Easton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.061395</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.839651</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/05/2023 07:46:01</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/05/2023 07:46:01</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/24/2023 15:06:43</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 07:46:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 15:06:43</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;INCIDENT WAS RECRODED AND SAVED UNDER ID 23MSP012107 TITLED FLOWERS WARRANT ARREST&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; THIS INCIDENT IS LINKED TO 23-MSP-012133, SUSPECT JOHN FLOWERS WAS CHARGED WITH 2ND DEGREE ESCAPE BY CPL FRANZEN OF MSAT.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ATTACHMENTS:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;-Completed Emergency Petition paper work&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;-Signed copies of all warrants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;SUSPECT:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;John Morgan Flowers, 08/13/1992&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;10580 Ocean Gateway&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Easton, Maryland 21601&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;OTHERS:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cpl Andrew Franzen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Maryland State Apprehension Team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;NARRATIVE:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On April 5&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;, 2023 at approximately 0657 hours, I responded to 10580 Ocean Gateway, Easton, Talbot County, Maryland to assist members of the Maryland State Apprehension Team (MSAT) / US Marshals Capital Area Regional Fugitive Task Force (CARFTF) with a warrant apprehension for John Morgan Flowers (8/13/1992 2/M). I knew John Flowers from previous incidents with John Flowers, including one incident where I arrested Flowers for a possession of a controlled dangerous substance. I also knew John Flowers had an active warrant for violation of probation, in reference to my previous case with John Flowers. Prior to arrival to the residence, I was informed by a member of Parole and Probation, that there was also an active Parole Retake warrant for John Flowers, which was in hand. Upon arrival to the residence, TFC Bekefi and I, along with members of CARFTF established a perimeter around the residence. Additional members of CARFTF began knocking on the front door and providing verbal commands, identifying themselves as members of CARFTF with a warrant for John Flowers, and requesting John Flowers come to the door. After approximately 6 minutes of knocking and announcing, members of CARFTF utilized a battering ram to make forced entry into the residence. After making forced entry, a female was observed inside the residence and was provided verbal commands to exit the residence, which she complied with. The female was identified as Heather Ewing Flowers (05/15/1970 2/F) and was the mother of John Flowers. While Heather Flowers was exiting the residence, she informed members of CARFTF that John Flowers was in the residence, and that he was hiding inside the attic. A United States Marshall&amp;rsquo;s Service K9 team began providing verbal warnings from the exterior of the residence, for John Flowers to surrender, or the K9 would be released inside the residence. After approximately 40 seconds, John Flowers complied with the verbal commands and was taken into custody. I took custody of Flowers and placed him in the front seat of marked Maryland State Police Patrol vehicle I-45. I was provided a copy of the active parole retake warrant and requested the Maryland State Police Emergency Dispatcher (MSPED) send a &amp;lsquo;hit&amp;rsquo; request to confirm additional warrants for John Flowers. MSPED Smith advised Flowers had the following confirmed warrants:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Parole retake warrant (No. W-00470427-3476)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Caroline County Arrest Warrant &amp;ndash; Motor Vehicle Theft (No. D220126885)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Talbot County Bench Warrant &amp;ndash; Driving without License Failure to appear (No. SE02720-2)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Talbot County Bench Warrant &amp;ndash; Violation of Probation CDS: Possess-Not Marijuana (No. D-035-CR-17-000816-2)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I transported John Flowers to the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack to retrieve a copy of the Caroline County and Talbot County warrants. During the transport, I continued to utilize my body worn camera, as Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle I-45 is not equipped with Mobile Video Recording Devices. Upon arriving at the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack, I began debriefing with John Flowers. I asked John Flowers if he had any additional information relating to criminal activity and John Flowers stated he did and he would talk because he did not want to go to jail. Ultimately, Sgt Flamma of the Talbot County Drug Task Force was provided a contact number for Flowers to follow up with the debrief. John Flowers stated multiple times while talking how he did not want to go back to jail. John Flowers then stated &amp;ldquo;What do you think happens when you tell them people you want to kill yourself?&amp;rdquo; I asked John Flowers who he was going to tell. John Flowers stated &amp;ldquo;Fucking jail, y&amp;rsquo;all&amp;rdquo;. Based on John Flowers&amp;rsquo; previous comments about not wanting to go to jail, it seemed John Flowers was only making these comments to avoid going to jail. I informed John Flowers he would be seen by a psychiatric specialist at the hospital, while Troopers remained on scene since he was in our custody, and once he was released, he would still be transported to jail. John Flowers then began mumbling under his breath and after a pause stated &amp;ldquo;I want to die, I want to hang it up, I want to kill myself. Going to do it as soon as I get a chance&amp;rdquo;. I informed John Flowers that I believed he was only making the statement since he did not want to go to jail, and he believed by making the statements he would avoid going to jail. John Flowers then stated &amp;ldquo;Hate my life, life sucks, I am going to kill myself as soon as I can, as soon as they give me a chance, as soon as my hands are free, I am going to kill myself&amp;rdquo;. I asked John Flowers how he planned on killing himself, and John Flowers stated &amp;ldquo;asphyxiation or if I can get a blade, I am going to slice everything I can&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Based off the statements John Flowers made, even though it was believed John Flowers was only making those statements to avoid going to jail, I notified the barrack and requested a second unit respond to provide security while John Flowers was being evaluated. I knew John Flowers had a history of fleeing and eluding and informed the barrack we would be staying to provide security until John Flowers was released, to avoid John Flowers leaving the hospital and attempting to escape. John Flowers was transported to Shore Regional Health, Easton for the completion of an emergency petition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Upon arrival to the hospital, my body worn camera was turned off and placed in sleep mode due to HIPAA regulations and Maryland State Police policy ADM 20.02 9.b., which states:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;ldquo;A trooper will not activate MVR equipment to record hospital/medical examination rooms or medivac transports&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Once inside the hospital, John Flowers was placed in room 18 and provided scrubs to change into per hospital policy for emergency petitions. Once John Flowers had changed, I secured Johns Flower&amp;rsquo;s right hand to the hospital bed, using the vertical rail. The rail was secure, and there was a horizontal rail preventing the handcuff from being removed. I then exited the room and remained outside the room with TFC Valcourt until hospital staff stated they would be moving John Flowers to room 7. The hospital staff asked if I wanted to remove the handcuff or if I wanted them to just move the bed. I requested they move the bed to the room to avoid having to constantly change the handcuffs from securing John Flowers to the bed and securing both his hands. John Flowers was moved to room 7 and Cpl Franzen of MSAT / CARFTF responded to the hospital to relieve TFC Valcourt. Cpl Franzen and I remained outside the room, approximately 10 feet from the door, to the left of the door (when facing the door) to allow John Flowers privacy during his evaluation by the behavioral specialist. Once the behavioral specialist was finished the evaluation, she told me and Cpl Franzen, the John Flowers would be released once she completed her paperwork. Cpl Franzen and I continued standing approximately 10 feet from the door to room 7 observing the door, and a few minutes after the behavioral specialist had left the room, I observed John Flowers exit the room, with his head down attempting to avoid being seen, and turn left out of the room and walk towards a set of double doors, which leads to the hallway taking you to the waiting room of the hospital. I had observed that John Flowers was fully dressed in his shirt, jeans, and shoes, which he had on prior to coming into the hospital. I immediately ran over to John Flowers as he opened the double door and put my right arm over his right shoulder onto his chest and used my left hand to grab John Flowers&amp;rsquo; left wrist to secure John Flowers and prevent him from attempting to continue to flee. As I grabbed John Flowers, John Flowers freely stated &amp;ldquo;okay, you got me, I had to try&amp;rdquo;. I then walked John Flowers to the wall in front of us and placed John Flowers&amp;rsquo; chest on the wall to prevent John Flowers from being able to attempt to break free from my grip and attempt to flee again. By this time Cpl Franzen had grabbed John Flowers&amp;rsquo; right wrist and elbow and I used my right hand to grab the handcuffs, still attached to John Flowers&amp;rsquo; right wrist, and secure John Flower&amp;rsquo;s left wrist in the handcuffs. Cpl Franzen and I then escorted John Flowers back to room 7 where John Flowers again stated he did not want to go back to jail, which is why he attempted to escape. John Flowers also stated that he had been able to move the rivet, securing the vertical rail of the hospital bed to the horizontal cross piece, allowing John Flowers to slide the handcuffs up and off the vertical rail. John Flowers then stated that he was not suicidal, and only made those statements since he did not want to go to jail. Once discharge paperwork was completed, I transported John Flowers to the Talbot County Detention Center central booking, where he was released pending an initial appearance with the Talbot County District Court Commissioner. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6415</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/12/2023 12:35:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6415</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/13/2023 14:46:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Chester</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4973</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4539</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Glover</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6415</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>30</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6415</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 12:29:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:01</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>170990</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>FLOWERS</LastName>
               <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MORGAN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/13/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>0</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>12/02/2017 03:46:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F462</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>FLOWERS</LastName>
               <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MORGAN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/13/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>0</SSN>
               <SLastName>F462</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/02/2017 03:46:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>10580</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Easton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.061395</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.839651</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>822</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5906</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/02/2017 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>239</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0882</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/02/2017 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6415</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 12:29:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6415</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 12:29:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>