<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-004114</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/02/2023 02:19:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/02/2023 02:19:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/02/2023 01:40:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/02/2023 01:40:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Motor vehicle was being operated on the on Interstate 68 traveling the wrong direction in lane #1 with a flat driver's side front tire.  Operator was arrested for driving under the influence of CDS.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/02/2023 02:19:42</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4425</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/27/2023 12:05:41</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>683676</AddressId>
      <City>MDC136</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/02/2023 02:19:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/09/2023 15:32:37</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>683676</AddressId>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-78.732864</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.671044</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/02/2023 02:19:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/02/2023 02:19:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>52</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/27/2023 12:05:43</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/02/2023 02:19:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:52:56</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:22px"&gt;*&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:22px"&gt;Maryland State Police Cumberland Barrack&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:22px"&gt;*&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;This incident was recorded on the in-car/mobile recording device of MSP unmarked patrol vehicle C-15 and my, Senior Trooper E. Wilson&amp;#39;s #6100, body worn camera.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Defendant: &lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Shawn Alan Frye&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Driver&amp;rsquo;s License:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Maryland: MD-10272898920&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Date of Birth:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 07/24/1987&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Date of Incident:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;2/2/2023&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Time of Arrest:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 0158 hours&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;DUI #: &lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;23-014&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; * Trained with a successful completion of Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On Thursday, February 2, 2023 at approximately 0140 hours the Maryland State Police Cumberland Barrack was notified of a motor vehicle traveling the wrong direction, west bound in the east bound lanes, on Interstate 68 near north 220 (Love&amp;rsquo;s Truck Stop). &amp;nbsp;At the time of the dispatched information TFC. McCue #6631, and I ST. E. Wilson #6100 were in the area of the vehicle. &amp;nbsp;Upon reaching the 46 mile-marker of east bound I-68, the headlights of a motor vehicle were observed approaching and traveling west bound in lane #1. &amp;nbsp;The emergency equipment of marked MSP patrol unit C-27 and unmarked MSP patrol unit C-15 were activated to stop the vehicle from traveling further in the wrong direction. &amp;nbsp;As the distance between the MSP patrol units and the vehicle closed the operator of the vehicle began to &amp;ldquo;flash&amp;rdquo; high to low headlight beams. &amp;nbsp;The vehicle was stopped in the grass median shoulder of the roadway and identified as a white Volkswagon Jetta GLI bearing Maryland Registration FRYEGUY. &amp;nbsp;The front driver side tire of the vehicle was flat and the rim had obvious damage. &amp;nbsp;Contact was made with the driver and he was identified as Shawn Alan Frye (DOB: 7/24/1987) by his Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license MD-10272898920. &amp;nbsp;Frye was the sole occupant of the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT / SCENE PROCESSING / NARRATIVE (PHASE 2)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Upon approach TFC. McCue and I contacted Frye at the driver&amp;rsquo;s side window. &amp;nbsp;TFC. McCue and I inquired what occurred to cause the vehicle damage and its operation in the wrong direction. &amp;nbsp;Frye replied that he did not know what happened and appeared confused. &amp;nbsp;Frye claimed that he was unaware he was driving the wrong direction. &amp;nbsp;Frye stated that he hit a snow bank and the tire was damaged. &amp;nbsp;He continued that the &amp;ldquo;whole car started shaking.&amp;rdquo; &amp;nbsp;It should be noted that there was no snow on the ground or piled anywhere near the interstate. &amp;nbsp;Frye stated that he does not drink alcohol and had not taken any medication. &amp;nbsp;He advised that he works as a &amp;ldquo;Door Dash&amp;rdquo; driver and had made a delivery from Taco Bell. &amp;nbsp;There was no odor of an alcoholic beverage detected emanating from the interior of the vehicle or from his breath. &amp;nbsp;Frye&amp;rsquo;s speech was slurred. &amp;nbsp;Frye&amp;rsquo;s body movements were consistent with signs of impairment. &amp;nbsp;Frye fumbled with the cards as he attempted to locate his license and again appeared confused while attempting to locate the keys to the vehicle. &amp;nbsp;An orange prescription pill bottle was in plain view located in the driver&amp;rsquo;s cup holder compartment. &amp;nbsp;Frye advised it was his prescribed Xanax (alprazolam) and stated that he had not taken it in days. &amp;nbsp;Frye was asked to the exit the vehicle and was offered to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Testing to which he consented. &amp;nbsp;As Frye exited the vehicle I noticed his head and body movements to be slow and sluggish. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The testing was conducted at the rear of his front of his vehicle. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the paved shoulder of the roadway. The surface was dry, slightly graded, and free from any obvious debris. &amp;nbsp;The weather was clear and approximately 29 degrees. &amp;nbsp;Lighting conditions consisted of patrol vehicle headlights, streetlights, and my flashlight. Frye appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Frye the following questions:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Injuries &amp;ndash; None visible. Claimed to have &amp;ldquo;busted&amp;rdquo; his face falling off porch 2 weeks prior. Contacts: no&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Glasses &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;No&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; Contacts &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;No&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; Medication &amp;ndash; Initially stated none (Xanax)&lt;br /&gt; Medical Conditions &amp;ndash; None&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pointer finger and pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Frye&amp;#39;s eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. &amp;nbsp;Frye&amp;#39;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. He was positioned in a manner to ensure the passing traffic would not interfere with the test results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; *During the HGN test, I observed Frye to be consistently swaying his body in a circle while attempting to stand with his feet together and arms down by his side. (Blue Eyes)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash; Present&lt;br /&gt; *Frye repetitively moved his head while the test was administered. &amp;nbsp;Frye had to be continuously reminded to follow the stimulus with only his eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Vertical Nystagmus - Present&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WALK AND TURN (7/8 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to Frye performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Frye was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Frye was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Frye was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Frye was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Frye was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Frye was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Frye was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. Frye was asked if he had any questions regarding the test, and he stated &amp;ldquo;no.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;1.) Lost balance - Feet broke apart. (Stood in a normal stance and had to be reminded to remain in instructional position.)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;1.) Raised arms greater than 6 inches for balance.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;2.) Stepped off the line.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;3.) Missed heel-to-toe.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;4.) Stopped walking.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;5.) Took 10 steps.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;1.) Raised arms greater than 6 inches for balance.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;2.) Stepped off the line.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;3.) Missed heel-to-toe.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;4.) Stopped walking.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;5.) Took 10 steps.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Turn:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;1.) Improper - multiple steps using both feet.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to Frye performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Frye was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Frye was asked if he had any questions regarding the test, and he stated &amp;ldquo;no.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;1.) Swayed body in a circle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Right foot was raised.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;1.) Swayed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;2.) Raised arms more than 6 inches.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;3.) Placed foot down on the ground.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;1.) Swayed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;2.) Raised arms more than 6 inches.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;3.) Placed foot down on the ground.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Did not complete.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The test was ended on the count of 9 after 17 seconds.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PBT: S/N: 1403162 (MSP No: 70017252)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Frye submitted to a preliminary breath test and a digital read of .00 was obtained. &amp;nbsp;Frye stated he had no issue taking the &amp;ldquo;PBT&amp;rdquo; because he does not drink alcohol.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARIDE TESTING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Additional testing was not conducted for preliminary evaluation of the presence of an additional impairing substance.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Frye was driving a motor vehicle while impaired and under the influence of a substance:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Slow and lethargic head and body movements.&lt;br /&gt; * Difficulty with diverted attention.&lt;br /&gt; * Lack of depth perception.&lt;br /&gt; * Difficulty with coordination.&lt;br /&gt; * Swaying while standing still/Loss of balance.&lt;br /&gt; * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests.&lt;br /&gt; * PBT read of .00.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I arrested Frye for driving under the influence of a controlled substance at approximately 0158 hours and he was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. &amp;nbsp;Frye was transported to the Cumberland Barrack for processing. At the Barrack, I played the English audio version of the DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Frye via the Maryland Motor Vehicle Administration&amp;rsquo;s official website. While at the Barrack and at the conclusion of the DR-15 audio, I verbally repeated and reviewed the possible suspensions and sanctions that can be imposed by the MVA per the DR-15 form. &amp;nbsp;Frye agree to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the DR-15 indicating the same at approximately 0242 hours.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;INTOXIMETER RESULT&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ***.00***&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The Maryland State Police Headquarters was contacted for the response of a Drug Recognition Expert due to no available DRE on-duty within Allegany County, Maryland. &amp;nbsp;On his own admission, Frye stated that he had not consumed any illegal substance and only what he was prescribed. &amp;nbsp;Frye stated that he was willing to submit a blood sample for drug or controlled dangerous substance (CDS) and indicated as well on the DR-15. &amp;nbsp;No available DRE&amp;rsquo;s were within a viable responding distance and MSP TFC. Bunger #6459 (DRE ID# 28902) was contacted by phone. &amp;nbsp;Based upon the above listed facts a voluntary Blood Kit (C-212) was completed. &amp;nbsp;Frye was transported to UPMC Western Maryland and blood was drawn at 0425 hours by Erica Bittinger. &amp;nbsp;Frye was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and was transported to his residence. &amp;nbsp;It should be noted that Frye was extremely polite and cooperative during the entire interaction.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All the above events occurred in Allegany County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLOSED BY ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 11:04:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 11:16:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McCue</LastName>
            <FirstName>Hunter</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6631</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wilson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ersel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6100</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Forrester</LastName>
            <FirstName>Douglas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1174</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wilson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ersel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6100</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wilson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ersel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6100</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/02/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/09/2023 15:00:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/09/2023 15:17:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/02/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/09/2023 15:00:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/09/2023 15:19:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/02/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/09/2023 15:00:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/09/2023 15:21:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/02/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/09/2023 15:00:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/09/2023 15:12:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/02/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/09/2023 15:00:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/09/2023 15:15:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/02/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/09/2023 15:00:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/09/2023 15:09:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19745</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/02/2023 01:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19745</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/09/2023 15:00:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/09/2023 15:05:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/07/2023 12:11:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:25</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>280089</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>FRYE</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shawn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/24/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/17/2020 23:12:04</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>FRYE</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shawn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/24/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/17/2020 23:12:04</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>409</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Springdale</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Cumberland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21502</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4548</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-78.7648956</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.634637</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>697</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3964</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/17/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6100</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 11:40:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:48</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6100</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 11:40:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:48</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 11:02:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 11:02:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/08/2023 19:22:15</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/08/2023 19:22:15</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/27/2023 12:05:43</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 19:22:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:52:56</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>TRAINING/CERTIFICATES&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Apprehended over 200 DUI/DWI Arrests to date.&lt;br /&gt; IACP National Training Conference on Drugs, Alcohol, and Impaired Driving 2019, 2020, 2021, 2022.&lt;br /&gt; DRE Instructor, November 2022.&lt;br /&gt; Distinguished graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute 2019.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Maryland Department of Transportation Medically Impaired Driver Detection December 2018.&lt;br /&gt; Collision Reconstruction, March 2018.&lt;br /&gt; SFST Instructor, February 2018.&lt;br /&gt; Drug Recognition Expert, July 2017.&lt;br /&gt; Maryland Department of Transportation DUI Enforcement Award, 2016, 2017, 2018.&lt;br /&gt; Maryland Department of Transportation Impaired Driving Conference, October 2016.&lt;br /&gt; Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.), September 2016.&lt;br /&gt; Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, August 2016.&lt;br /&gt; National Traffic Incident Management Responder Training, March 2016.&lt;br /&gt; Advanced Collision Investigation, March 2016.&lt;br /&gt; Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, October 2014.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 02/02/2023 at approximately 0345 hours, I, TFC Bunger # 6459 DRE # 28902, was contacted by the Maryland State Police Headquarters Duty Officer regarding a request for a DRE in Allegany County. I called the Cumberland Barrack and made contact with the arresting officer, S/T E. Wilson # 6100, who briefed me on the DUI arrest. S/T Wilson advised that he located a vehicle driving the wrong way on I-68. The vehicle had fresh collision damage and a flat tire. When he made contact with the driver, Shawn Alan FRYE, S/T Wilson immediately detected signs of impairment. FRYE performed poorly on SFST and was arrest for DUI at 0219 hours. He admitted to taking multiple Xanax and an empty Xanax /&amp;nbsp;Alprazolam prescription bottle assigned to FRYE was located in the vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; FRYE submitted to Intoximeter testing which produced a result of .00 BrAC at approximately 0300 hours. He consented to DRE evaluation. S/T Wilson requested two state-wide pages from headquarters, which produced negative results, and contacted surrounding barracks and allied agencies, also with negative results. Due to a two-hour response time from the Golden Ring Barrack to the Cumberland Barrack, I was unable to perform the DRE evaluation. I requested that FRYE take a blood test for controlled dangerous substances. FRYE consented to blood testing with results pending.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As a certified DRE, I request that the blood sample be tested for controlled dangerous substances and drugs.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 10:44:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6459</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/20/2023 22:19:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Divelbiss</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4425</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bunger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gregory</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6459</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>