<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008177</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/05/2023 04:30:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/05/2023 04:30:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/05/2023 04:06:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/05/2023 04:06:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/Single Vehicle Collision</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 04:30:44</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/05/2023 18:37:37</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>686545</AddressId>
      <City>MDC132</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/07/2023 05:40:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 05:40:39</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>686545</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Capital Beltway</StreetName>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>N</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <Longitude>-76.942492</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.022862</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/05/2023 04:30:40</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/05/2023 04:30:40</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/21/2023 20:27:58</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 04:30:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Q-25 IS EQUIPPED WITH AN IN CAR CAMERA&lt;br /&gt; THE EVENT WAS AUDIBLY AND VISUALLY RECORDED&lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Noune, Michel Kevin&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 01/18/1993&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 0429 hours&lt;br /&gt; DUI#: 23-052&lt;br /&gt; TRAINING/CERTIFICATES&lt;br /&gt; Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;br /&gt; On March 5th, 2023, at approximately 0406 hours, I, Trooper Fleming #7439 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, was on routine uniform patrol in the area of the outer loop of 495 at the I-95 split. I was in full uniform operating a marked patrol vehicle Q-25. The incident was audibly and visually recorded on my body worn camera and Q-25&amp;rsquo;s in-car camera.&lt;br /&gt; I observed a wrecked black SUV and a police unit stationary in lanes one and two. I activated my emergency lights. Upon my arrival, I identified a Black GMC Terrain bearing the Maryland registration &amp;ldquo;2EM6174&amp;rdquo; with heavy damage all around damage the vehicle. The front of the vehicle was facing the left shoulder and was blocking lanes one and two. There was a Cheverly police unit on scene. The Cheverly police officer was talking with a man seated on the left shoulder&amp;rsquo;s guardrail. The officer&amp;rsquo;s hand was on the man&amp;rsquo;s chest trying to keep the man seated on the guardrail. I exited my patrol vehicle to make contact with the driver involved in the motor vehicle collision and the officer already on scene.&lt;br /&gt; PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; I approached the man and the Cheverly police officer. The man was sitting on the guardrail on his phone. The man then stood up, grabbed the Cheverly police officer&amp;rsquo;s hand, and attempted to push past the Cheverly police officer towards the black GMC Terrain. The driver slurred &amp;ldquo;Let me check something, I want to check something.&amp;rdquo; The Cheverly police officer and myself had the driver sit back down on the guardrail.&lt;br /&gt; I observed that the driver&amp;rsquo;s eyes were bloodshot and glassy. The driver&amp;rsquo;s movement was slow and lethargic. There was a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath and person. The driver&amp;rsquo;s pants fly was left unzipped. When the Cheverly police officer asked for the driver&amp;rsquo;s identification, the driver continued to use his smartphone and mumbled something unintelligible.&lt;br /&gt; When I asked for his identification, he handed me a credit card and Driver&amp;rsquo;s License from his left coat pocket. The driver did not notice that he dropped an additional card on the ground as he removed the two cards from his left pocket. I then identified the driver as Noune, Michel Kevin (1/M, 01/18/1993) via his Maryland Driver&amp;rsquo;s license.&lt;br /&gt; Noune then began asking the Cheverly police officer if he could go to his car despite Noune already being told to stay where he was. At this time, Noune again stood up in an attempt to push past the Cheverly police officer and myself. Noune was made to sit back down on the guardrail. I asked Noune if he needed to go to the hospital or needed an ambulance; to which Noune said &amp;ldquo;No, no, no, no.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; I asked Noune where he was coming from. Noune slurred &amp;ldquo;Silver Spring&amp;rdquo; and pointed in the direction his vehicle would have been headed. I asked Noune where he was going to. Noune ignored my question and looked down at his phone. I asked again where Noune was going to. Noune slurred &amp;ldquo;Silver Spring&amp;rdquo;. I again asked Noune where he was driving to; Noune again confirmed &amp;ldquo;Silver Spring&amp;rdquo;. I confirmed with Noune that he had been driving from Silver Spring and was driving to Silver Spring. Noune said that he was coming from &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo;. This did not make sense as to why Noune was on outer loop of 495 at the I-95 split in Prince Georges County when Silver Spring is located approximately seven miles away in Montgomery County.&lt;br /&gt; When asked if he had anything to drink, Noune said &amp;ldquo;Two beers.&amp;rdquo; I asked what he had to drink, Noune said &amp;ldquo;Uhh&amp;hellip; Heineken?&amp;rdquo; I then asked how much he had to drink; Noune said &amp;ldquo;two.&amp;rdquo; When asked what happened, Noune pointed and slurred something unintelligible. Noune then shrugged and said &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what happened.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; Trooper Peris #7511 and Trooper Stallings #7589 arrived on scene. I asked Noune to perform standard field sobriety in order to determine if alcohol was a contributing factor to the collision. Noune grabbed my arm for support as he stood up from the guardrail. Noune then attempted to answer a phone call; I asked Noune to put his phone away. Noune swayed in place as he stood upright.&lt;br /&gt; PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on of the outer loop of 495 at the I-95 split in lane one and the left shoulder area. The area level and dry. The area was clear of any debris. Noune appeared to be in good physical condition. Noune had an abrasion between his eyebrows and bruising on his left eyelid and left cheek. When asked if he required medical attention, Noune refused.&lt;br /&gt; I asked Noune the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; Medication &amp;ndash; Noune informed me that he does not take any kind of medication.&lt;br /&gt; Physical Injuries &amp;ndash; Noune informed me that he had no physical injuries.&lt;br /&gt; Glasses or Contacts &amp;ndash; Noune informed me that he does not wear glasses or contacts.&lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (Unable to Perform)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained. The tip of a pen was used as the test&amp;rsquo;s stimulus. The stimulus was held approximately 12-15 inches from Noune&amp;rsquo;s eye, slightly above eye level. &amp;nbsp;Noune was instructed to look straight ahead, keep his head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. Noune&amp;rsquo;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Before beginning the test, I asked Noune if he understood my instructions, to which he confirmed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Additional Observations &amp;ndash; Noune was unable to keep his head still and follow the stimulus with just his eyes. Noune was unable to perform HGN despite the test being both explained and demonstrated multiple times. Noune insisted that he was not turning his head. Lack of smooth pursuit (nystagmus) was observed. Noune then said &amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t have nothing, I just had one beer. That&amp;rsquo;s it.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN TEST (8/8 Clues Observed)&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. Noune was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Noune was then instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and remain in that position until told to begin. Noune was advised to take nine steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line, and take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Noune was instructed to complete the second series of nine steps in the same heel to toe fashion. &amp;nbsp;Noune was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, to count every step out loud, and once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Noune if he understood, and he confirmed that he did.&lt;br /&gt; Instructional Phase &amp;ndash;&lt;br /&gt; Cannot Keep Balance &amp;ndash; Noune could not remain balanced with his right foot directly in front of his left foot touching heel to toe while I was demonstrating and giving instructions for the walking stage of the test. Noune broke this form on at least four occasions. Noune&amp;rsquo;s starting spot shifted from the middle of lane one to the left solid yellow line of lane one due to him continuously breaking his starting form.&lt;br /&gt; Starts Too Soon &amp;ndash; Noune began the walking stage of the test before I could finish explaining the rest of the instructions and tell him to begin on one occasion.&lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (First Nine Steps) &amp;ndash;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Misses Heel-Toe &amp;ndash; On all twelve of his first nine steps, Noune missed his heel to toe by more than one half inch.&lt;br /&gt; Steps Off Line &amp;ndash; On all twelve of his first nine steps, Noune stepped off line by more than one half inch.&lt;br /&gt; Raises Arms &amp;ndash; On all twelve of his first nine steps, Noune raises his arms greater than six inches from his body.&lt;br /&gt; Stops Walking &amp;ndash; Noune stopped walking on his twelfth step. I had to remind Noune to turn around and take nine more steps.&lt;br /&gt; Actual Number of Steps &amp;ndash; Noune stepped twelve times. Noune counted to &amp;ldquo;two&amp;rdquo;, said &amp;ldquo;Let me start over&amp;rdquo;, then stepped three times without counting out loud. Noune then counted his steps out loud &amp;ldquo;four&amp;rdquo; though &amp;ldquo;ten.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; Improper Turn - Noune turned clockwise when his left foot was in front of his right foot which resulted in an unnatural turn.&lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (Second Nine Steps)&lt;br /&gt; Misses Heel-Toe &amp;ndash; On all four of his second nine steps, Noune missed heel to toe by more than one half inch.&lt;br /&gt; Steps Off Line &amp;ndash; On all four of his second nine steps, Noune stepped off line by more than one half inch.&lt;br /&gt; Raises Arms &amp;ndash; On step three of his second nine steps, Noune raises his arms greater than six inches from his body.&lt;br /&gt; Actual Number of Steps &amp;ndash; Noune stepped four times and counted his steps out loud as &amp;ldquo;seven&amp;rdquo; through &amp;ldquo;ten&amp;rdquo;.&lt;br /&gt; ONE-LEG STAND TEST (3/4 Clues Observed)&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. &amp;nbsp;Noune was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch the raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two, etc.), and not put his foot down until the end of the test. I asked Noune if he understood the test, and he confirmed.&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 1-10&lt;br /&gt; Hopping &amp;ndash; Noune hopped on one foot to maintain his balance during this period.&lt;br /&gt; Puts foot down &amp;ndash; Noune lowered his foot to the ground, touching the ground with his entire foot twice during this period.&lt;br /&gt; Sways &amp;ndash; Noune&amp;rsquo;s body would sway from the left and right greater than two inches.&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20&lt;br /&gt; Puts foot down &amp;ndash; Noune lowered his foot to the ground, touching the ground with his entire foot once during this period.&lt;br /&gt; Sways &amp;ndash; Noune&amp;rsquo;s body would sway from the left and right greater than two inches.&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30&lt;br /&gt; Raises Arms &amp;ndash; Noune would keep his left arms raised greater than six inches from her body throughout the second ten seconds.&lt;br /&gt; Puts foot down &amp;ndash; Noune lowered his foot to the ground, touching the ground with his entire foot twice during this period.&lt;br /&gt; Sways &amp;ndash; Noune&amp;rsquo;s body would sway from the left and right greater than two inches.&lt;br /&gt; Additional Observations &amp;ndash; Noune started the test before I told him to begin on two occasions. Noune did not count out loud. Noune answered a phone call in the middle of the test.&lt;br /&gt; ARREST&lt;br /&gt; Based on the totality of circumstances, I concluded Noune was driving a motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol.&lt;br /&gt; Noune&amp;rsquo;s involvement as the driver in a single motor vehicle collision.&lt;br /&gt; Noune said that he was driving from Silver Spring to Silver Spring. The scene of the collision was approximately seven miles east of Silver Spring.&lt;br /&gt; Noune&amp;rsquo;s eyes were bloodshot and glassy.&lt;br /&gt; Noune&amp;rsquo;s speech was mumbled and slurred.&lt;br /&gt; Noune&amp;rsquo;s movement was slow and lethargic.&lt;br /&gt; Noune&amp;rsquo;s swaying while standing upright and in place.&lt;br /&gt; Noune&amp;rsquo;s pants fly was left unzipped.&lt;br /&gt; Noune handed me a credit card with his Maryland Driver&amp;rsquo;s License.&lt;br /&gt; The odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Noune&amp;rsquo;s breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; Admission to consuming an alcoholic beverage.&lt;br /&gt; Clues during Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (Unable to Perform), WAT (8/8), OLS (3/4)&lt;br /&gt; On March 5th, 2023, at approximately 0429 hours, I placed Noune under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack. A search incident to arrest of Noune&amp;rsquo;s person was conducted. The search of Noune&amp;rsquo;s person was negative. I transported Noune to the College Park Barrack.&lt;br /&gt; PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST&lt;br /&gt; After being transported to the barrack, Noune was informed of his Preliminary Breath Rights. Noune was offered a PBT, to which he agreed (PBT Results: .19).&lt;br /&gt; Noune was played the DR-15 Advice of Rights English recording provided by MVA. &amp;nbsp;Noune was provided with a copy of the DR-15 to read along as well. Noune requested a French interpreter. The DR-15 Advice of Rights was read out loud to Noune in French. At approximately 0654 hours, Noune agreed to take an alcohol concentration test.&lt;br /&gt; 20 MINUTE OBSERVATION&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Noune beginning with his arrest. A preliminary search of Noune was conducted on scene and it was revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. I observed Noune from the time of arrest until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by Tpr. Peris #7511 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Noune failed to provide a sufficient breath and sample to the intoximeter.&lt;br /&gt; Noune&amp;rsquo;s vehicle was towed by Hannan Towing.&lt;br /&gt; I processed Noune and released him to Enom Moussinga, Loic Romuald (1/M, DOB: 08/08/1999).&lt;br /&gt; Noune was issued the following citations.&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-902(a1i) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-902(b1i) DRIVING VEH. WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-901.1(a) RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OF PERSONS AND PROPERTY&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-901.1(b) NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON&lt;br /&gt; TA - 13-401 (h) DRIVING VEHICLE ON HIGHWAY WITH SUSPENDED REGISTRATION&lt;br /&gt; TA - 17-107 (a1) KNOWINGLY DRIVING UNINSURED VEHICLE&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-201 (a1) DRIVER FAILURE TO OBEY PROPERLY PLACED CONTROL DEVICE INSTRUCTIONS&lt;br /&gt; TA - 17-104 OWNER FAILURE TO MAINTAIN REQUIRED SECURITY FOR VEHICLE DURING REGISTRATION PERIOD&lt;br /&gt; The defendant was issued copies of the following documents:&lt;br /&gt; -Citations (listed above)&lt;br /&gt; -DR-15 Advice of Rights&lt;br /&gt; -DR-15a Order of Suspension&lt;br /&gt; All documents were forwarded to the Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County, State Attorney Office.&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/07/2023 05:50:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 06:49:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>PERIS</LastName>
            <FirstName>BRYAN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7511</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stallings</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7589</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Aaron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fleming</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sierra</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7439</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497576</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/05/2023 04:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/07/2023 05:34:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 05:34:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>30</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/07/2023 05:36:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370778</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Noune</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kevin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/13/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 06:09:05</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Noune</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kevin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/13/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>N500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 06:09:05</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3638</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Bel Pre</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <City>Silver Spring</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20906</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.07229</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.092883</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/07/2023 06:21:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/07/2023 06:21:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/07/2023 06:21:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/07/2023 06:21:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/07/2023 05:34:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 05:34:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150540</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/07/2023 05:37:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 05:37:58</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2GKALMEKXF6361396</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>TRN</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2EM6174</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>