<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009016</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/11/2023 20:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/11/2023 20:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/11/2023 20:20:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/11/2023 20:20:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop resulting in the arrest of the driver for DUI (Drugs). DRE notified.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 20:54:41</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2864</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/21/2023 01:13:34</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>SOMERSET AVE/ CHESTNUT CIR</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>615138</AddressId>
      <City>MDC217</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 20:54:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 13:33:10</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>615138</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Somerset</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Princess Anne</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>CIR</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.69334</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.224122</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12499-12635 SOMERSET AVE / 12407-12508 CHESTNUT CIR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12408-12496 SOMERSET AVE / 12407-12508 CHESTNUT CIR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12384-12406 SOMERSET AVE / 12407-12508 CHESTNUT CIR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/11/2023 20:54:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/11/2023 20:54:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/21/2023 01:12:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 20:54:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:42</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Maryland State Police&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Princess Anne Barrack &amp;ldquo;X&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tpr. J. D. Revel III, IBM 7146&lt;br /&gt; Field Operation Bureau&lt;br /&gt; March 11&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;, 2023&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;X-11 is a maroon unmarked 2021 Ford Explorer equipped with MVR system.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Type of Report:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;DUI//DWI (Drugs)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;DUI Case Number:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;23-95-019&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Driver/Suspect:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;William Tarpeh&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Date of Birth:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;7/11/1992&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Subsequent Offender:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;No&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Accident Involved:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;No&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;MVR Recordings:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Serial:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/device/device-profile/cffc1559dd7547259dc001e40d534b3d" style="color:#0563c1; text-decoration:underline"&gt;X60A61415&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Model: Axon Body 3&lt;br /&gt; Link:&amp;nbsp; https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=39c8875d44694ff086c559dc20d5c9ed&amp;amp;partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Troopers Training/Experience:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Trained and certified to operate Radar and LiDAR through the Maryland State Police.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * NHTSA certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Attended numerous&amp;nbsp;NHTSA certified cannabis impairment detection workshops.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Federal Motor Carrier Safety Administration (FMCSA) certified commercial vehicle weights officer.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * FMCSA certified North American Standard (NAS) Level III Commercial Vehicle Inspector.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Attended the 2021 Middle Atlantic-Great Lakes Organized Crime Law Enforcement Network (MAGLOCLEN) Conference.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Certified At-Scene (Level I) Crash Reconstructionist through the Baltimore County Police Department and Maryland Crash Reconstruction Committee (MCRC).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Certified in Advanced (Level II) Crash Investigation through the Montgomery County Police Department and Maryland Crash Reconstruction Committee (MCRC).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Attended the 2022 Maryland Impaired Driving Conference hosted by the Maryland Department of Transportation and Zero Deaths Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Trained in Human Trafficking investigation and recovery through the Federal Bureau of Investigation and the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Certified Standardized Field Sobriety Instructor through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Narrative:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This report has been prepared based upon the observations of this trooper and/or those of other troopers relative to the offense(s). The facts contained herein are intended solely to give the prosecuting authority a basic understanding of the facts pertaining to this case. The facts contained herein are not intended to be an exhaustive recitation of the facts pertaining to pretrial or trial issues. Instead, this trooper anticipates that during the pretrial proceedings in this case, the prosecutor will take the opportunity to interview this trooper in order to ascertain any and all relevant facts which might be the subject of this troopers&amp;#39; testimony during court proceedings.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Phase #1 - Vehicle in Motion:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On the evening of March 11&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;, 2023, I was on proactive patrol along MD Route 822 in Princess Anne, Somerset County, Maryland. At approximately 2020 hours, I was traveling westbound on MD Route 822 when I observed a black Acura Sedan following me closer than reasonable. The Acura less than a half of a car length behind me, close enough that I could not see the headlights on the vehicle. As soon as I left the roundabout and started heading north on Somerset Avenue, the Acura continued to follow me at an unreasonable distance. As we approached MD Route 529, I pull off to let the Acura pass. As soon as it did, I performed a traffic stop on the vehicle. I was able to identify the license plate as 1EF4856, through the State of Maryland. The final location of the traffic stop was Somerset Avenue at MD Route 529. I never lost sight of this vehicle during the observation process.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Phase #2 - Personal Contact:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I exited my patrol vehicle and approached the drivers&amp;#39; door where I contacted&amp;nbsp;the operator, later identified as William Tarpeh (DOB: 7/11/1992) via his Maryland Driver&amp;#39;s License. I introduced myself, stated the reason for the traffic stop, and advised him that he was being audibly and visually recorded.&amp;nbsp;I immediately detected a moderate but distinct odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the driver&amp;#39;s compartment of the vehicle. I observed Tarpeh&amp;rsquo;s eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. See the attached image IMG_0000 for a depiction of Tarpeh&amp;rsquo;s eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Tarpeh for his license and registration. As he was grabbing his information, I asked him where he was coming from. Tarpeh replied &amp;ldquo;UMES&amp;rdquo; before handing me his Driver&amp;#39;s License. I asked Tarpeh how much he had to drink that night. He stated &amp;ldquo;I ain&amp;rsquo;t really had too much to drink.&amp;rdquo; Tarpeh also advised he was coming from a sorority reunion.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Phase #3 - Pre-Arrest Screening:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I asked Tarpeh to exit the vehicle, and he did as I asked. As he exited the driver&amp;#39;s seat, I observed him to be wearing black dress shoes, gray dress pants, and a white collared shirt with a striped tie. His movements exiting the vehicle were very slow and lethargic. I asked Tarpeh to stand at the front of his vehicle while I asked him a few questions. While he walked to the front of the car, Tarpeh could barely walk straight. As I spoke with Tarpeh outside the vehicle, I continued to detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on Tarpeh&amp;rsquo;s driving that I observed and his admission to drinking paired with the odor of alcohol, he was offered field sobriety testing as a means to determine his level of impairment. He agreed to participate in the field sobriety testing. I began the testing with the Alphabet F to T test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Alphabet F to T&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Tarpeh if he knew the English Alphabet, and he advised that he did. I asked Tarpeh to recite the English Alphabet from the letter F to T without singing it. Tarpeh said: &amp;quot;F, G, H, I, A, B, C, D, E hold on.&amp;quot; Then he paused. He resumed at &amp;quot;F, G, H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, P, R, S, T.&amp;quot; Tarpeh did the following:&lt;br /&gt; - Skipped the letter &amp;ldquo;Q&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Count From 59 to 31&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Tarpeh to count backwards starting at 59 and ending at 31. Tarpeh did the following:&lt;br /&gt; - Skipped number 50&lt;br /&gt; - Skipped number 33&lt;br /&gt; - Stopped at number 30&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Starting off the introduction to the standardized tests, I asked Tarpeh if he wore glasses or contacts or was prescribed to be wearing them, and he stated &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo; I also asked Tarpeh if he had taken or is prescribed any medication. He advised &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo; I asked Tarpeh if he had suffered any traumatic head injuries recently, and he advised that he had not.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I explained the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test to Tarpeh. I instructed him to stand still with his feet together, hands down by his side, and to follow the stimulus (my pen) with his eyes and eyes only, keeping his head straight.&amp;nbsp;He advised&amp;nbsp;that he understood and could see the stimulus clearly, so I began the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Resting Nystagmus: No&lt;br /&gt; Equal Tracking: Yes&lt;br /&gt; Equal Pupil Size: Yes&lt;br /&gt; Eye Color: Brown&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; - Lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; - Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; - Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Note: Failed to track with his eyes multiple times, following with head and sometimes just staring straight at me.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Total Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Clues&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;6&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;6&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Walk and Turn&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Weather:&lt;/u&gt;&amp;nbsp;Clear&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Surface:&lt;/u&gt;&amp;nbsp;Flat paved surface free of any debris/used imaginary straight line&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I explained and demonstrated the Walk and Turn test to Tarpeh. He was instructed to assume the starting position by placing his left foot on the imaginary&amp;nbsp;line and his right foot directly in front, heel touching toe, and to maintain this position while I explained the test. He was also instructed not to start or stop the test until instructed to do so.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; He was advised to&amp;nbsp;take nine heel-to-toe steps along the imaginary&amp;nbsp;line while looking down at his feet and counting each step out loud. Once he reached nine steps, he was instructed to leave his lead foot planted and take a series of small steps to turn himself around, then take nine more heel-to-toe steps back along that&amp;nbsp;line.&amp;nbsp;During the test, he was also instructed to keep his hands down by his side. I asked Tarpeh if he had questions, and he stated he did not.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Tarpeh if he was comfortable performing this test in the shoes he was wearing now, and he stated &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While explaining and demonstrating, I observed Tarpeh to lose his balance, break the heel-to-toe position immediately, and stand normally, contrary to my instruction.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Instruction Stage&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Cannot keep balance in starting position&lt;br /&gt; - Starts too soon&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Walking Stage 1st 9 Steps&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Stops walking on 9&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; step&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; - Stopped test for an entire minute trying to remember how to turn around&lt;br /&gt; - Took&amp;nbsp;9&amp;nbsp;steps total&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Turn&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Lost balance while turning and pivoted once on lead foot.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Walking Stage 2nd 9 Steps&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Misses heel to toe on 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;step&lt;br /&gt; - Stepped off the line by approximately 3 inches on 1&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt; step&lt;br /&gt; - Took 9 steps total&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Total Walk and Turn Clues&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;6&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;8&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;One Leg Stand&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Weather:&lt;/u&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Same as Above&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Surface:&lt;/u&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Same as Above&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I explained and demonstrated the One Leg Stand test to Tarpeh. He was instructed to lift one foot of his choice about six inches off of the ground, look down at his raised&amp;nbsp;foot, and count out loud by the method given -&amp;nbsp;one-thousand one, one-thousand two, one-thousand-three, etc. He was also advised to keep his hands down to his side and to not stop counting nor stop the test until he is instructed&amp;nbsp;to do so. I asked Tarpeh if he understood the test, and he advised me that he did.&amp;nbsp;Tarpeh then began the test by lifting his&amp;nbsp;&lt;u&gt;left&lt;/u&gt;&amp;nbsp;foot from the ground.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Seconds 0-10&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Sways from side to side approximately 4 inches&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Seconds 11-20&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Sways from side to side approximately 4 inches&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Seconds 21-30&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Sways from side to side approximately 4 inches&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Ended test at 30 seconds&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Total One Leg Stand Clues&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;1&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;4&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Preliminary Breath Test&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I explained the reasons for using a&amp;nbsp;preliminary&amp;nbsp;breath test and Tarpeh was&amp;nbsp;offered the opportunity to submit a&amp;nbsp;breath sample.&amp;nbsp;Tarpeh agreed and submitted a breath sample of .027 BrAC. Due to level of alcohol showing inconsistent to the impairment I observed, I notified the barrack to call a DRE.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Arrest and Transport&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At 2045 hours, I placed Tarpeh under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of alcohol and/or drugs. Tarpeh was placed into the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. Back at the barrack, I performed a secondary search and checked Tarpeh &amp;#39;s mouth for foreign objects. I did not locate any foreign objects. I then pulled up a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, sat it in front of Tarpeh, and asked if he could see the form. Tarpeh advised that he could, and I played the DR-15 audio directly from the MVA website, having Tarpeh follow along. After the reading was complete, Tarpeh stated that he would like to submit a breath sample.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Breath Test&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. White, a certified Intoximeter operator, arrived and contacted Tarpeh. At 2130 hours, Sgt. White administered the Intoximeter Test with a result of .000 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;DRE Evaluation &amp;amp; Blood Sample&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At 2206 hours, Tpr. Romeo, a certified Drug Recognition Expert, responded to the Princess Anne barrack to conduct an evaluation on Tarpeh. MSP HQ advised that nobody was available and the barrack struggled to obtain a local DRE after the original officer called out became busy. Tpr. Romeo concluded that everything appeared normal at the time, but due to the fact that she conducted the assessment over two hours from my initial contact, Tarpeh had already out measured the half-life of most drugs.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Charging&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Tarpeh was charged with the following:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL/DRUGS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE SO FAR IMPAIRED BY DRUGS/ALCOHOL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;FOLLOWING TOO CLOSELY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OF PERSONS AND PROPERTY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Tarpeh was given all appropriate documentation and released to a sober friend, Tyere Louis Ferguson (DOB: 5/17/1989) at 0015 hours without incident.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events did occur in Somerset County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 14:46:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 21:30:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bynum</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7345</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brown</LastName>
            <FirstName>Clinton</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7569</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Revel</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7146</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498415</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 20:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 13:35:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 13:35:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498415</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 20:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 13:35:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 13:35:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>30</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 14:47:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:24</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>83797</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Tarpeh</LastName>
               <FirstName>William</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>D</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/11/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/18/2015 22:00:07</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T610</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W450</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Tarpeh</LastName>
               <FirstName>William</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>D</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/11/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T610</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W450</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/18/2015 22:00:07</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9914</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Forest View</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Gaithersburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20886</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.203835</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.189758</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>300</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9592</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/18/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 21:32:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 21:32:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 13:35:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 13:35:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/23/2023 17:14:14</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/23/2023 17:14:14</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/21/2023 01:12:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7126</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 17:14:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:42</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On March 11, 2023, I, TFC Romeo, conducted a 12-step Evaluation on William Tarpeh at the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack. Please see attached report for my evaluation.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7126</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 17:17:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7126</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 15:52:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mareck</LastName>
            <FirstName>Keven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3258</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Romeo</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ashley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7126</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>