<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000374</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/04/2023 00:00:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/04/2023 00:00:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/03/2023 23:42:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/03/2023 23:42:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI arrest of Kehinde Olatunde Lawal.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 00:00:30</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4792</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/20/2023 12:55:30</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN HWY/ PEGGY NECK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>585136</AddressId>
      <City>MDC217</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 00:00:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/11/2023 17:36:54</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>585136</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Princess Anne</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.66655</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.260908</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB 13 / JUST NORTH OF PEGGY NECK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13848-14120 OCEAN HWY / 31259-31279 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13647-13844 OCEAN HWY / 31298-31853 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13647-13844 OCEAN HWY / 31280-31297 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13656-13847 OCEAN HWY / 31259-31279 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13845-14111 OCEAN HWY / 31280-31297 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/04/2023 00:00:26</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/04/2023 00:00:26</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/13/2023 03:14:05</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/04/2023 00:00:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/13/2023 03:14:05</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kehinde Olatunde Lawal&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Maryland SOUNDEX: L-400-465-660-184&lt;br /&gt; Breath Test Result: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#f1c40f"&gt;0.10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DUI Citation #: 4JV0J79&lt;br /&gt; DUI MVR/Body Cam #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-000374 (Axon View XL Software).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;* Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the&lt;br /&gt; Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; * Certified SFST Instructor.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Chemical Breath Test Operator.&lt;br /&gt; * Graduate of the University of Maryland&amp;#39;s DUI Institute.&lt;br /&gt; * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland&lt;br /&gt; State Police.&lt;br /&gt; * Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.).&lt;br /&gt; * Trained in Cannabis Impairment Detection (Maryland State Police).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;NARRATIVE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;-PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION-&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 01-03-2023 at approximately 2342 hours, I (Corporal J. Ruiz #6312), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating unmarked MSP vehicle X-17 in the area of U.S. Route 13 southbound just north of Eden Allen Road (Eden). I was stationary on the right shoulder area, monitoring all southbound traffic. At that time, I observed a white sedan traveling southbound in Lane 2 pass my location. I made the following observations on the same vehicle:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;NORTH OF EDEN ALLEN ROAD&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. As the vehicle continued traveling southbound, the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s right tires were &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;directly on top&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;of the solid white shoulder line on &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;three (3) occasions&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. The vehicle drifted back into Lane 2 each time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;I safely entered the roadway and closed in on the same vehicle just south of Eden Allen Road.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;BETWEEN EDEN ALLEN ROAD AND PEGGY NECK ROAD&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. The vehicle&amp;rsquo;s right tires &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;crossed&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (1 tire width) the solid white line into the right shoulder area on &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;three (3) occasions&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. The vehicle drifted back into Lane 2 each time. On one of the occasions, the vehicle &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;straddled&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; the white shoulder line for approximately 30 feet.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. The vehicle&amp;rsquo;s right tires were &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;directly on top&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;of the solid white shoulder line on &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;seven (7) occasions&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. The vehicle drifted back into Lane 2 each time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ADDITIONAL OBSERVATIONS&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 4. The vehicle failed to maintain proper lane position due to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;pronounced and excessive weaving&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (alternately moving toward one side of the lane and then the other) during the entire duration of my observations.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 5. Total distance traveled was approximately 1.59 miles.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;TRAFFIC STOP&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I activated the emergency lights to my patrol vehicle, initiating a traffic stop on U.S. Route 13 southbound near Peggy Neck Road. The vehicle was a white 2015 Nisan Altima bearing Maryland Registration 7EZ3390.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;-PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT-&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the driver via the driver side door, and I immediately smelled the faint odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop and requested the driver&amp;rsquo;s license and the registration card to the vehicle. The driver was identified as Kehinde Olatunde Lawal by his Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license. I asked Lawal where he was traveling from, and he responded: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;I went to see a friend&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. I asked Lawal where he was traveling to, and he replied: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Going home, sir&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. I asked Lawal how much he had to drink earlier in the evening, and he stated: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Just, uh, 1 sip of, what&amp;rsquo;s it called, uh, Natural Light&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. When asked how long ago he had consumed the alcoholic beverage, Lawal responded: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Uh, probably like, um, 2 hours&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As Lawal spoke, I made the following observations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. I intentionally observed his eyes to be &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;glassy and bloodshot&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Lawal.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I later returned to the Nissan and requested Lawal exit the vehicle and walk to the front of it, to which he complied. While at the front of the vehicle, I continued to speak with Lawal. I asked Lawal again where he was traveling from, and he stated: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;I went to see a friend. Somewhere in Salisbury&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. I asked Lawal how many total alcoholic beverages he had consumed prior to driving, and he advised: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;I just had 1 kind of, um, Natural Light&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. When asked if he had consumed that drink at his friend&amp;rsquo;s residence, Lawal replied: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;No, not my friend&amp;rsquo;s house. I took it when I was, when I was leaving the house&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. As Lawal spoke, I smelled the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I informed Lawal that I wanted him to perform field sobriety tests which he agreed to submit to.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;-PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING-&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder area of U.S. Route 13 southbound. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and vehicle headlamps. Weather was clear and approximately 51 degrees. I asked Lawal if he had any significant medical issues with his eyes, arms, or legs which would prevent him from performing the field sobriety tests or if he had taken any medication prior to driving. Lawal responded: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;No&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Yes, blood pressure&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Lawal appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries, limps, or any limb ailments.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Lawal was wearing a tan pattern Lacoste brand polo shirt, black jeans, black socks, and black Nike slides.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Lawal displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. Lawal displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. Lawal displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**WALK AND TURN: 4 of 8 clues**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Lawal could not maintain his balance during the Instruction Phase. Lawal&amp;rsquo;s feet broke from the start position on four (4) occasions, and he stumbled to his right each time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. Lawal missed heel-to-toe on step 2 during the first series. Lawal missed heel-to-toe on steps 1, 2, and 8 during the second series. All misses were of more than half an inch.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. Lawal did not complete the turn in a satisfactory manner, simultaneously pivoting his feet to the left which was contrary to my instructions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 4. Lawal was unable to maintain a straight line and stepped off the line on all steps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**ONE LEG STAND: 2 of 4 clues**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Lawal&amp;rsquo;s body swayed to the left and right during counts 5, 7, 9, 10, and 15.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. Lawal put his right foot down on counts 5 and 16.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ADDITIONAL ANNOTATIONS REFERENCE FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN)&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Lawal verbally stated &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;left, right&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; out loud as I moved the stimulus during this test. This was contrary to my instructions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Walk And Turn (WAT)&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Lawal removed his slides for this test.&lt;br /&gt; B.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Lawal did not start the test when instructed to initially.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;One Leg Stand (OLS)&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Lawal&amp;rsquo;s slides remained off for this test.&lt;br /&gt; B.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Lawal&amp;rsquo;s right leg remained bent throughout the test, which was contrary to my instructions. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Lawal the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Lawal submitted to a PBT with a reading of &lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#f1c40f"&gt;0.102&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt; BrAC.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ARREST&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Lawal was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;* Driving vehicle in a negligent manner which caused it to commit 13 designated lane direction violations in addition to excessive weaving &amp;ndash; &lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#f1c40f"&gt;DRIVING SKILLS IMPAIRED&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; * Faint odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Admission to consuming at least one (1) alcoholic beverage prior to operating a motor vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * PBT result of 0.102 BrAC.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I determined that Lawal was impaired by the presence of an alcoholic beverage in his system that adversely affected his ability to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests properly can also adversely affect the person&amp;rsquo;s ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. I placed Lawal under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 2359 hours on 01-03-2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Lawal&amp;rsquo;s mouth to check for foreign objects and none were found. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lawal was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Lawal was given his Advice of Rights via the audio version of the DR-15 Form (played through the patrol vehicle&amp;rsquo;s Bluetooth speakers). At the conclusion of the audio version, I verbally re-explained the driver&amp;rsquo;s license sanctions and penalties (section printed in red) to Lawal. Lawal stated that he understood his Advice of Rights and agreed to submit to a breath test at approximately 0026 hours on 01-04-2023.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;TRANSPORT&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lawal was subsequently transported to the Princess Anne Barrack for processing. During transport, the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Lawal continued to be moderate. At this time, I asked Lawal what his country of origin was. Lawal advised that he was from Nigeria and has been living in the United States for approximately one (1) year and six (6) months. Throughout my interaction with Lawal, he displayed a good command of the English language.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;**INTOXIMETER RESULT**:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to the breath test, I observed Sergeant M. White #3325 visually check the inside of Lawal&amp;rsquo;s mouth for any foreign objects. None were found. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The breath test was administered by SGT White at approximately 0054 hours on 01-04-2023, and two (2) sufficient samples of Lawal&amp;rsquo;s breath were obtained. The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#f1c40f"&gt;0.10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;RELEASE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lawal was provided and explained all forms and citations prior to his release. Lawal was released to a sober driver at approximately 0136 hours on 01-04-2023.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CHARGES&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lawal was charged with the following citations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (4JV0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 2. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol Per Se (4JW0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 3. Driving While Impaired By Alcohol (4JX0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 4. Failure To Obey Designated Lane Directions (4JY0J79)&lt;br /&gt; 5. Negligent Driving (4JZ0J79)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Somerset County, MD.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 17:47:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/11/2023 18:54:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lloyd</LastName>
            <FirstName>Harry</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5845</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489751</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/11/2023 17:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 17:36:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/11/2023 17:38:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489751</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/11/2023 17:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 17:36:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/11/2023 17:38:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489751</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/11/2023 17:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 17:36:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/11/2023 17:37:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489751</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/11/2023 17:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 17:36:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/11/2023 17:37:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489751</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/11/2023 17:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 17:36:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/11/2023 17:37:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 17:36:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:07</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365304</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lawal</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kehinde</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Olatunde</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/10/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 18:24:17</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K530</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lawal</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kehinde</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Olatunde</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/10/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K530</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 18:24:17</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1762</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Buck Harbor</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Pocomoke City</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21851</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2816</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.528632</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.059902</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>703</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>665</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8129</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 17:39:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 17:36:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/11/2023 17:36:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148268</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 17:40:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/11/2023 17:40:30</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1N4AL3AP4FN397741</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ALT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7EZ3390</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>5</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>