<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000506</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/05/2023 02:49:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/05/2023 02:49:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/05/2023 02:15:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/05/2023 02:15:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was stopped for a moving violation and was found to be driving under the influence of alcohol.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 02:49:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4425</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/19/2023 15:03:48</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>679391</AddressId>
      <City>MDC153</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 02:49:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 03:38:42</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>679391</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>90</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Main</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Frostburg</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-78.931397</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.660287</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/05/2023 02:49:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/05/2023 02:49:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>52</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/15/2023 11:45:09</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 02:49:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;ATTACHMENTS:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DR-15&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; DR-15A&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; MSP-33&lt;br /&gt; TRAFFIC CITATIONS&lt;br /&gt; DRIVING RECORD/METERS&lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE REGISTRATION/METERS&lt;br /&gt; PHOTOCOPY OF DRIVERS LICENSE&lt;br /&gt; FRONT PHOTO OF SUBJECT ON MORNING OF ARREST&lt;br /&gt; DETENTION LOG&lt;br /&gt; INTOXIMETER WORKSHEET&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The DUI Number for the following incident is 23MSP000506/23-004.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;C-19 is equipped with an in-car camera and was operational at the time of the incident.&lt;br /&gt; TFC T. Michael is issued a body camera (00017189) and was operational at the time of the incident.&lt;br /&gt; C-19 is equipped with an in-car radar system, which was functioning and calibrated per MSP policies and standards.&lt;br /&gt; C-19 is a marked police unit.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;VIOLATION:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On Thursday, January 5, 2023 at approximately 0215 hours, I was on routine patrol working stationary (rear) radar monitoring traffic traveling eastbound on US-40 ALT.&amp;nbsp; I was located on the eastbound, right shoulder of US-40 ALT west of Tisdale Street NW.&amp;nbsp; While conducting speed enforcement in the area, I observed a gray 2015 Ford F-150, bearing Maryland registration FI0046 turn onto eastbound US-40 ALT from the parking lot Charlie&amp;rsquo;s Motel.&amp;nbsp; I audibly heard the sound of high engine revolutions per minute and squealing, I identified as tires spinning.&amp;nbsp; I observed the rear of the vehicle sway while traveling eastbound up the incline of that portion of the roadway. &amp;nbsp;I visually observed the Ford F-150 accelerate in a manner unnecessary for the weather and traffic conditions at the time while traveling eastbound of US-40 ALT.&amp;nbsp; Note that there was no oncoming traffic at that time; however, due to a concentrated area of residences, businesses sidewalks and crosswalks, the speed limit in that area is limited to 25 mph.&amp;nbsp; During that time, the roads were damp; however, it was not raining at that time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on my observations, I left my stationary position and caught up to the Ford F-150 in the area west of Chestnut Street.&amp;nbsp; I activated my emergency equipment and made contact with the driver, identified by his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license as Stephen Lee Frost, W/M, DOB 12/28/1979 by his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license.&amp;nbsp; Upon initial approach, I observed the driver had a freshly lit cigarette and I politely asked him to extinguish and the driver complied with my request. &amp;nbsp;I identified myself; I was audibly and visually recording and my identification number. I advised him for the reason of the traffic stop.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;While speaking to the driver, I detected the strong odor of alcohol emanating from his breath and person. &amp;nbsp;I observed his eyes were bloodshot and glassy.&amp;nbsp; Note that during our conversation, I noticed that his voice was stuttered and slurred.&amp;nbsp; I asked Frost if he had anything to drink and he advised &amp;ldquo;a couple&amp;rdquo;.&amp;nbsp; Upon asking him to clarify, Frost stated &amp;ldquo;5&amp;rdquo;. &amp;nbsp;I proceeded to ask him when he had his last drink and he first advised one hour prior to the traffic stop, then apologized stating that his last drink was just prior to leaving the Hurry Back Tavern.&amp;nbsp; Frost advised that he consumed Bud Lite beer.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I returned to my patrol vehicle to advise the Maryland State Police &amp;ndash; Cumberland Barrack of the traffic stop and that I would need an additional police unit for standardized field sobriety testing.&amp;nbsp; A Frostburg City Police Officer assisted during the remainder of the traffic stop.&amp;nbsp; I deactivated my forward facing flashing light and lowered my spotlight to illuminate the testing area.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I approached the vehicle and asked Frost to exit the vehicle in order to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Testing and he complied.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I am trained and certified to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. &amp;nbsp;The tests were performed on the right shoulder of E Main Street west of Chestnut Street.&amp;nbsp; The roadway was blacktop, wet and free from debris. It is noted that the area was illuminated and on a slight decline.&amp;nbsp; My front emergency equipment was deactivated and I lowered the spotlight to illuminate the ground only for the test.&amp;nbsp; Prior to testing, I asked if Frost had anything inside his mouth and he advised he had gum and I asked him to remove that and he complied.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Defendants Attire:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Frost was wearing a jeans, sweater and jacket. &amp;nbsp;Frost was wearing high top boots at the time of the stop, which Frost advised he was comfortable wearing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Physical injuries:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Frost advised that he had a prior injury of a tear of the left Achilles tendon.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Medication:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Frost advised that he was currently taking Adderall and it was last consumed at approximately 1400 hours on 1/4/2023.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eyesight:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Frost advised that he did require corrective lenses in order to drive.&amp;nbsp; Frost&amp;nbsp;was wearing contact lenses at the time of testing.&amp;nbsp; James eye color is green.&amp;nbsp; Post arrest at the barrack Frost mentioned an astigmatism.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **Prior to SFST, Frost advised that he did not know he spun his wheels, however advised that his passenger told him he did in fact spin them.&amp;nbsp; I advised him I understood and continued with the roadside investigation. **&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #1 Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Frost stated that he could see the stimulus.&amp;nbsp; I advised Frost that I needed to follow the stimulus with his eyes and eyes only.&amp;nbsp; I advised Frost that his head was to remain stationary. &amp;nbsp;The stimulus was held 12-15 inches from Frost and just above eye level. &amp;nbsp;Frost was able to track the stimulus with his eyes only. &amp;nbsp;Frost had equal pupil size and tracking ability. Frost displayed lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;6 out of 6&lt;br /&gt; Stimulus: Tip of a ball point pen&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #2: Walk and Turn&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Frost was placed in the instructional stage, which was demonstrated to Frost as standing with his right foot in front of the left foot, touching heel-to-toe and arms placed at his sides. Frost was advised not to deviate from the instructional position, and was advised not to begin the test until told do so.&amp;nbsp; I then proceeded to demonstrate the test by taking three heel to toe steps on line, turn around keeping one foot on line, and return three heel to toe steps.&amp;nbsp; I explained to Frost that he would have to take nine heel to toe steps and return taking another nine heel to toe steps. I explained that the three steps I took were for demonstration purposes only.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On the first series of nine steps, the following clues were observed.&amp;nbsp; On step two, Frost placed his foot offline and missed heel to toe.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On the second series of nine steps, the following clues were observed.&amp;nbsp; On step two, Frost missed heel to toe and stepped offline.&amp;nbsp; On step three Frost again missed heel to toe.&amp;nbsp; On steps five thru nine, Frost&amp;rsquo;s hands were more than 6 inches away from his sides.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;3 out of 8&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #3 One Leg Stand&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Frost was told to stand with his heels together and arms placed at his sides and instructed not to begin the test until told to do so. The test was explained and demonstrated to Frost by explaining that I wanted him to raise one leg, whichever he felt most comfortable with, approximately six inches off the ground, foot pointed out.&amp;nbsp; Frost was also instructed to keep both legs straight and to keep his eyes on the elevated foot. While holding that position, count aloud, one thousand and one, one thousand and two, one thousand and three, and so forth until told to stop. &amp;nbsp;Frost stated that he understood the instructions and agreed to perform the test. Frost raised his left leg and began to count aloud.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Frost began to sway beginning on count six.&amp;nbsp; Frost placed his foot down for the first time on count eight.&amp;nbsp; Frost began to sway again on count thirteen and continued until the conclusion of the test.&amp;nbsp; Frost&amp;rsquo;s hands were more than six inches from his sides for the entirety of the test.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;3 out of 4&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At the end of demonstrating each standardized field sobriety test, I asked Frost if he understood the test and needed another demonstration.&amp;nbsp; Frost advised that he understood all the tests prior to him performing them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Frost if he wished to consent to taking the preliminary breath test.&amp;nbsp; I advised Frost in detail that the PBT was a voluntary test and would not be used against him in the court of law; however, it is an additional instrument I use during the course of my duties.&amp;nbsp; I advised Frost that he could refuse the test and I would not use his refusal against him.&amp;nbsp; I advised Frost that the PBT is used in addition to the results of the SFST&amp;rsquo;s.&amp;nbsp; Frost consented to taking the PBT.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PBT results:&amp;nbsp; .21 BAC&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;ACTION TAKEN:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Frost was placed under arrest on January 5, 2023 at approximately 0236 hours.&amp;nbsp; Frost was transported to the Maryland State Police &amp;quot;C&amp;quot; Barrack, his DR-15 rights were advised, and he agreed the intoximeter test at 0303 hours.&amp;nbsp; At approximately 0321 hours, Frost&amp;rsquo;s alcohol concentration resulted in .14.&amp;nbsp; Frost&amp;rsquo;s license was seized. A DR-15, DR-15A, MSP 33, citations, and MSP 225 were issued.&amp;nbsp; Frost was released to the custody of his mother from the Maryland State Police &amp;ndash; Cumberland Barrack.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Based on the above stated facts, I respectfully request this case be closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Allegany County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 03:31:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 03:31:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Barry</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Barry</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489883</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/05/2023 02:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 03:48:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 03:49:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489883</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/05/2023 02:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 03:48:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 03:49:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489883</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/05/2023 02:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 03:48:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 03:50:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>43</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 03:48:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>265809</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Frost</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/28/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/22/2020 04:53:46</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F623</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Frost</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/28/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F623</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/22/2020 04:53:46</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1076</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Finzel</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Frostburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21532</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-78.9573659</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.6939114</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>920</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9910</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/22/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 03:55:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 03:55:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 03:55:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 03:55:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 03:48:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 03:48:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148428</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 03:48:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 03:48:29</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FTEX1EP4FFD05360</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>F15</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>FI0046</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>10</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>