<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-033042</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/20/2023 15:00:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/20/2023 15:00:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/18/2023 09:40:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/18/2023 09:40:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect became prohibited from possessing firearms and previously possessed and HQL and seven registered firearms in MAFSS.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/20/2023 15:00:45</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0965</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 06:34:28</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>Suspect's Residence</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>709034</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/20/2023 15:00:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 11:55:15</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>709034</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>5448</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Gallant Green</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Waldorf</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20601</Zip5>
         <Zip4>4333</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.795424</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.561502</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/20/2023 15:00:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/20/2023 15:00:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40R</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/19/2023 16:27:44</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/20/2023 15:00:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSPQ031</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 11:32:03</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;This incident was not captured on MSP issued body worn camera.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On September 18, 2023, ST Barnas #6328 of MSP Licensing Division &amp;ndash; HQL Unit completed an HQL revocation for David Warren Henson Jr (W/M, DOB: 09/25/1969) due to becoming disqualified from possessing firearms from a guilty conviction Sex Abuse Minor: Family/Household (Felony) on 08/25/2023 in the Circuit Court for Charles County (Case # C08CR000187).&amp;nbsp; He was additionally found to be the responded in a final protective order active until 03/14/2024 (#D042FM23000132).&amp;nbsp; A check of MAFSS revealed Henson has eight firearms registered in MAFSS.&amp;nbsp; This information was forwarded to the Maryland Gun Center where the prohibited status was confirmed.&amp;nbsp; Further investigation revealed that three firearms had been traced by Charles County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office.&amp;nbsp; This case was forwarded to ST S. DiToto for further action.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; ST S. DiToto began conducting searches for the registered firearms which were identified as follows:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Glock 30 .45 SN: BKMF539 (2019)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. S&amp;amp;W MP9 Shield 9mm SN: LFF7269 (2018)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Taurus PT111 9mm SN: TLM99358 (2018)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. Glock 21 .45 SN: SHD023 (2012)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;5. Glock 22 .40 SN: KVZ214 (2007)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;6. S&amp;amp;W 10 .38 SN: AUB1200 (1998)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;7. Other 22 .40 SN: CCP000US (1997)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;8. S&amp;amp;W 686 .357 SN: BJB8627 (1992)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Through investigative efforts, ST S. DiToto located Charles County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office report #2302039 from the service of the above-mentioned protective order on March 15, 2023.&amp;nbsp; CCSO seized a Taurus (SN: TLM99358), Glock (SN: BKMF539), S&amp;amp;W (SN: LFF7269), and a Topper shotgun (not registered).&amp;nbsp; ST additionally located a pawn record from 2014 for the Glock (SN: SHD023).&amp;nbsp; Further checks of social media and law enforcement resources revealed no further leads regarding the remaining four (4) firearms.&amp;nbsp; ST S. DiToto found David Henson Jr is currently in custody at Jessup Correctional Institution, but his estranged wife Kristine Henson, who&amp;rsquo;s daughter is the victim and protected person in the above referenced cases, still resides at 5448 Gallant Green Road, Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland. Kristine Henson was found to not be prohibited from possessing firearms.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On September 26, 2023 at approximately 1450, ST S. DiToto contacted Kristine Henson and interviewed her regarding the status of the firearms.&amp;nbsp; Kristine Henson advised she directed the Charles County Deputy to all known locations of firearms belonging to Henson.&amp;nbsp; She stated there were no other handguns remaining in the home belonging to David Henson.&amp;nbsp; She advised she was unsure of any additional locations he would store or have access to firearms.&amp;nbsp; She stated if she found further information regarding any firearms she would forward it to ST S. DiToto as she does not trust David Henson to be in possession of any firearms.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On October 3, 2023 at approximately 1150 hours, ST S. DiToto responded Jessup Correctional Institution where an interview was conducted with David Henson.&amp;nbsp; Henson verified he understood he was now prohibited from possessing firearms. ST S. DiToto reviewed the MAFSS list with Henson and pointed out the previously seized/located firearms.&amp;nbsp; Henson confirmed he sold/pawned one handgun in 2014 at All Pawn and Guns in White Plains, Maryland. He stated he was uncertain about the location of the Glock 22 and presumed it to be with his other firearms at the Gallant Green Road address.&amp;nbsp; He stated the S&amp;amp;W .38 was last known to be in possession of his ex-wife, Connie Henson, who resides in White Plains, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; Henson said the S&amp;amp;W .357 he has not seen in years and was not sure where it may be if not located at either residence.&amp;nbsp; He stated the other unknown make .40 caliber handgun registered in 1997 was also unknown.&amp;nbsp; When asked to identify any location firearms may be located within the residence at Gallant Green Road, Henson stated firearms were possibly located in a lower drawer of an otherwise empty gun cabinet in his garage, in his bedroom dresser, above a book shelf in the dining room, in the bedroom closet and in a case behind the living room couch.&amp;nbsp; Henson stated the firearms seized were located in on the book shelf and in the bedroom closet.&amp;nbsp; He stated the firearm behind the couch was an unknown non-regulated AR15 he purchased from Gun Monkey in La Plata, Maryland approximately two (2) years prior.&amp;nbsp; He stated he was concerned Kristine Henson may have sold the firearm if she knew its location and if it had not been seized.&amp;nbsp; David Henson understood the civil issues associated with marital property.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On October 3, 2023 at 1438 hours, ST S. DiToto #5416 contacted Kristine Henson via telephone as she was not home.&amp;nbsp; While attempting to arrange a meeting with Kristine Henson at the residence, she stated she was uncomfortable with meeting as she felt David Henson was only stating firearms may be in the home to cause her undue stress or interruption in life.&amp;nbsp; Kristine advised she had previously cleaned the gun cabinet and moved it into the house and found it to only contain a BB gun.&amp;nbsp; She stated she was certain it was a BB gun based on the observations she made and her familiarity with firearms.&amp;nbsp; Kristine advised she had also cleaned the dresser of all of David Henson&amp;rsquo;s belongings to remove them from the house.&amp;nbsp; She stated she located miscellaneous items, but no firearms.&amp;nbsp; She further advised when she was originally contacted by law enforcement she was cooperative and directed them to the specific locations of the firearms on the book shelf and in the bedroom closed.&amp;nbsp; Kristine Henson stated she had previously located the AR15 rifle behind the living room couch and since sold the item to a third party who she wished not to identify due to retaliation concerns from David Henson.&amp;nbsp; Kristine Henson insisted there were not further firearms belonging to David Henson in the residence, but if she were to find any, she would contact ST S. DiToto immediately.&amp;nbsp; Kristine Henson did not consent to a search of her residence at the time of contact.&amp;nbsp; At this time no further, corroborating information has been located to verify statements from either David Henson or Kristine Henson.&amp;nbsp; Additional contact with Kristine Henson will be addressed base on development of further information as the investigation progresses.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; ST S. DiToto was able to identify David Henson&amp;rsquo;s ex-wife as Connie Jean Henson (W/F, DOB: 01/02/1968) of 10437 Sextant Place, White Plains, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; Connie Henson was found to not be prohibited from possessing firearms.&amp;nbsp; ST S. DiToto attempted to contact Connie Henson via telephone to verify the information, however, contact has not been successfully established and messages have not yet been returned.&amp;nbsp; A knock and talk will be completed at the residence in an attempt to contact Connie Henson.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; This case remains open pending further investigation.&amp;nbsp; Due to his incarceration status, David Henson does not currently possess or have access to any firearms.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Above events occurred in Charles County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 12:03:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 12:30:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sawa</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2916</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ditoto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5416</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522496</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1106</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/18/2023 09:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1106</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 11:56:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 11:56:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>53</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 12:02:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 12:02:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389613</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Henson</LastName>
               <FirstName>David</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Warren</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/25/1969 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>10/05/2023 12:02:04</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Henson</LastName>
               <FirstName>David</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Warren</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/25/1969 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>H525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/05/2023 12:02:04</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5448</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Gallant Green</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Waldorf</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20601</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4333</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.795424</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.561502</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 12:02:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 11:56:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 11:56:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/29/2023 13:41:40</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/29/2023 13:41:40</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40R</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/30/2023 06:33:10</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 13:41:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSPQ031</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 11:32:03</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Following previous investigative efforts, ST S. DiToto #5416 made multiple attempts at knock and talks as well as be telephone contact with Connie Henson through October and November.&amp;nbsp; On November 12, 2023 after one knock and talk attempt, ST S. DiToto received a phone call from Henson much later.&amp;nbsp; A brief interview was conducted via telephone and ST S. DiToto schedule to speak with Henson again the following week.&amp;nbsp; At that time Henson indicated she had no firearms registered to David Henson in her residence and anything David Henson had was gone long ago.&amp;nbsp; Following that contact, was a period of time without contact via phone on in person via knock and talk.&amp;nbsp; There was no new information developed to provide probable cause that firearms were located in either residence identified.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On November 28, 2023 ST S. DiToto was again able to establish contact with Henson, who reviewed the list of firearms investigators were trying to locate.&amp;nbsp; Henson provided a description of the smith and Wesson revolvers accurate based on model information and her recollection.&amp;nbsp; She stated she recalled one being located in her vehicle and placed in a plastic bag inside the residence because she did not want it in either location.&amp;nbsp; She stated that firearm may have subsequently been placed in the trash and thrown away.&amp;nbsp; Henson advised there were no lost or stolen reports for any of the firearms, but advised she had not seen any firearm belonging to David Henson in several years.&amp;nbsp; Although she stated she was unfamiliar with any firearms being in her residence, she advised if for any reason she located one that she would contact investigators to surrender it. The only other information Henson had was she believed David may have sold or traded a firearm with a subject she knew as &amp;ldquo;Kevin Kans&amp;rdquo; from Maryland, but she had no further details.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; ST S. DiToto identified Kevin Robert Kans (08/12/1960) of LaPlata, Maryland through use of MVA and other law enforcement resources.&amp;nbsp; Further investigation revealed Kans is not prohibited from possessing firearms in Maryland.&amp;nbsp; Contact was established with Kans who advised he had purchased a Glock 22 handgun from David Henson, who he knew through his Church at least ten or more years prior.&amp;nbsp; Kans stated when he completed the purchase he did not recall completing any registration paperwork.&amp;nbsp; Kans was able to verify the serial number of the firearm, which was found to indeed have been one of the handguns registered to David Henson.&amp;nbsp; Kans was instructed to complete the appropriate registration paperwork to properly register the firearm and complete the transfer, although it was several years ago. &amp;nbsp;A short time later Kans contacted to advise the firearm registration forms were submitted to MSP Licensing Division via Licensing Portal and he was awaiting further instruction.&amp;nbsp; Kans stated he did not receive any other firearms from Henson and he had felt Henson&amp;rsquo;s character was questionable prior to his criminal conviction prompting this investigation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; At this point in the investigation three of eight firearms have not been located through use of various investigative methods.&amp;nbsp; Contact with the owner/prohibited person, David Henson, has been successful and he is aware of the prohibited status.&amp;nbsp; In addition, persons or residences he&amp;rsquo;s associated with following his potential release from Jessup Correctional Institution have been check for any firearm association.&amp;nbsp; The outstanding firearms have not been located, but there is no evidence available to suspect they are at the known locations.&amp;nbsp; There is no evidence to believe Henson would have access to said firearms.&amp;nbsp; In addition due to the information located through this investigation, there has been no evidence developed to indicate Henson possessed firearms following his prohibiting conviction in 2023.&amp;nbsp; If further information or evidence becomes available at a later time, this investigation will be re-opened.&amp;nbsp; Case closed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Above events occurred in Charles County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 13:42:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 13:42:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dulski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Steve</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0965</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ditoto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5416</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522496</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>09</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1106</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 13:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1106</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 13:41:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 13:42:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>