<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-034546</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/02/2023 08:15:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/02/2023 08:15:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/02/2023 07:36:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/02/2023 07:36:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 08:15:14</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/23/2023 15:52:55</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>29 MM I95 SB, BELTSVILLE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>708687</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 08:15:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/15/2023 02:55:02</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>708687</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>29</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I95 Sb Beltsville</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.93252</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0462123333333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/02/2023 08:15:09</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/02/2023 08:15:09</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/18/2023 02:14:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 08:15:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MARTINEZ MENDOZA, OSCAR EDUARDO // 23-MSP-034546 // 0MG0Y2X&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Martinez Mendoza, Oscar Eduardo&lt;br /&gt; Incident Number: 23-MSP-034546&lt;br /&gt; DUI Folder: 23-230&lt;br /&gt; Date of Offense: 10/02/2023&lt;br /&gt; Arresting Officer: Tpr. Fleming #7439&lt;br /&gt; Breath Technician: N/A&lt;br /&gt; Subsequent Offender: No&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TRAINING/CERTIFICATES&lt;br /&gt; Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;br /&gt; On October 2nd, 2023, at approximately 0815 hours, I, Trooper Fleming #7439 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, was on uniformed patrol of the area of northbound I-95 at 212.&lt;br /&gt; I observed a parked car on the left shoulder of northbound I-95 at 212 with its hazard lights on. It appeared as though the driver was reclined back in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat. I identified the parked car as a tan Subaru Forester bearing the Maryland registration &amp;ldquo;1FL7304&amp;rdquo;. I notified the barrack of my location and the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s information. I exited my patrol vehicle to check the welfare of the driver.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; I approached the driver&amp;rsquo;s side of the vehicle in order to make contact with the operator. Upon my approach, I observed a 12 pack of Michelob Ultra bottles that had been ripped open sitting on the rear seats. There were multiple crushed empty cans of Michelbob Ultra laying on the rear seats.&lt;br /&gt; I also observed a man asleep reclined back in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat. The driver&amp;rsquo;s eyes were closed and there was a strand of drool coming from the corner of his mouth. The man did not open his eyes or acknowledge me as I approached and stood next to the front driver&amp;rsquo;s side door. I requested another unit for field sobriety.&lt;br /&gt; I knocked on the front driver&amp;rsquo;s side window. The driver did not wake up. I opened the driver&amp;rsquo;s side door. There was an open can of Michelbob Ultra in the driver&amp;rsquo;s side door an additional bottle of Michelbob Ultra in the passenger&amp;rsquo;s side door. The driver slowly began to wake up.&lt;br /&gt; I asked the driver for his license. The driver pulled out his wallet and showed me his license without taking it outside of his wallet. I identified the driver as Martinez Mendoza, Oscar Eduardo (5/M, DOB: 05/15/1987) via his Maryland Driver&amp;rsquo;s License.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; The driver&amp;rsquo;s speech was slurred and mumbled. His movements were slow and lethargic. His eyes were bloodshot and glassy as well. There was a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from within the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; I asked Martinez Mendoza about the multiple cans and bottles of beer in his vehicle. Martinez Mendoza stated he drank three beers approximately 12 hours ago. I asked Berrios Ochoa where he was traveling to; Berrios Ochoa stated he was driving to his home in Laurel. I asked Berrios Ochoa if he had any alcohol to drink before leaving; Berrios Ochoa claimed that he did not have any.&lt;br /&gt; PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;br /&gt; An additional unit arrived on scene. I asked Martinez Mendoza to perform the field sobriety test to confirm that he was okay to drive, to which he agreed. Upon separating Martinez Mendoza from the vehicle, I identified that there was a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; I asked Martinez Mendoza the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; Medical Condition &amp;ndash; Martinez Mendoza stated that he did not take any kind of medication.&lt;br /&gt; Physical Condition &amp;ndash; Martinez Mendoza stated that he did not have any physical injuries.&lt;br /&gt; Glasses or Contacts &amp;ndash; Martinez Mendoza stated he did not wear glasses or contacts.&lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the left shoulder of northbound I-95 at 212. The shoulder was level and dry. Martinez Mendoza appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 Clues Observed)&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained. The tip of a pen was used as the test&amp;rsquo;s stimulus. The stimulus was held approximately 12-15 inches from Martinez Mendoza&amp;rsquo;s eye, slightly above eye level. &amp;nbsp;Martinez Mendoza was instructed to look straight ahead, keep his head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. &amp;nbsp;Martinez Mendoza&amp;rsquo;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Before beginning the test, I asked Martinez Mendoza if he understood my instructions, to which he confirmed.&lt;br /&gt; Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Additional Observations &amp;ndash; Resting gaze nystagmus was not present. Vertical gaze nystagmus was not present.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN TEST (4/8 Clues Observed)&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. Martinez Mendoza was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Martinez Mendoza was then instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and remain in that position until told to begin. Martinez Mendoza was advised to take nine steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line, and take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Martinez Mendoza was instructed to complete the second series of nine steps in the same heel to toe fashion. Martinez Mendoza was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, to count every step out loud, and once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Martinez Mendoza if he understood, and he confirmed that he did.&lt;br /&gt; Instructional Phase &amp;ndash;&lt;br /&gt; Cannot Keep Balance &amp;ndash; Martinez Mendoza could not remain balanced with his right foot directly in front of his left foot touching heel to toe while I was demonstrating and giving instructions for the walking stage of the test. Martinez Mendoza broke this form on at least two occasions. Martinez Mendoza then gave up standing in the starting position and stood with his feet side by side for the remainder of the instructions.&lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (First Nine Steps) &amp;ndash;&lt;br /&gt; Raises Arms &amp;ndash; On all nine of his first nine steps, Martinez Mendoza raises his arms greater than six inches from his body.&lt;br /&gt; Improper Turn &amp;ndash; Martinez Mendoza took one large step using his rear foot to pivot around his front foot. Martinez Mendoza ended the turn with his feet side by side.&lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (Second Nine Steps)&lt;br /&gt; Raises Arms &amp;ndash; On all nine of his second nine steps, Martinez Mendoza raises his arms greater than six inches from his body.&lt;br /&gt; Actual Number of Steps &amp;ndash; Martinez Mendoza stepped ten times.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ONE-LEG STAND TEST (2/4 Clues Observed)&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. &amp;nbsp;Martinez Mendoza was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch the raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two, etc.), and not put his foot down until the end of the test. I asked Martinez Mendoza if he understood the test, and he confirmed.&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 1-10&lt;br /&gt; Raises Arms &amp;ndash; Martinez Mendoza would keep his arms raised greater than six inches from his body on one occasion during the first ten seconds.&lt;br /&gt; Puts foot down &amp;ndash; Martinez Mendoza lowered his foot to the ground, touching the ground with his entire foot once during this period.&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20&lt;br /&gt; Raises Arms &amp;ndash; Martinez Mendoza would keep his arms raised greater than six inches from his body on one occasion during the first ten seconds.&lt;br /&gt; Puts foot down &amp;ndash; Martinez Mendoza lowered his foot to the ground, touching the ground with his entire foot once during this period.&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST&lt;br /&gt; While on scene, I informed Martinez Mendoza of his Preliminary Breath Rights. Martinez Mendoza was offered a PBT, to which he agreed.&lt;br /&gt; Preliminary Breath Test Results: .127&lt;br /&gt; ARREST&lt;br /&gt; Based on the totality of circumstances, I concluded Martinez Mendoza was driving a motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol.&lt;br /&gt; The vehicle was running while Martinez Mendoza was asleep at the wheel.&lt;br /&gt; Martinez Mendoza&amp;rsquo;s speech was slurred and mumbled&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Martinez Mendoza&amp;rsquo;s eyes were bloodshot and glassy.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Martinez Mendoza&amp;rsquo;s slow movement.&lt;br /&gt; The odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Martinez Mendoza&amp;rsquo;s breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; Multiple open containers of alcohol within reach of the driver.&lt;br /&gt; Clues during Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (6/6), WAT (4/8), OLS (2/4)&lt;br /&gt; On October 2nd, 2023, at approximately 0822 hours, I placed Martinez Mendoza under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack. A search incident to arrest of Martinez Mendoza&amp;rsquo;s person was conducted. The search of Martinez Mendoza&amp;rsquo;s person was negative. I transported Martinez Mendoza to the College Park Barrack.&lt;br /&gt; Martinez Mendoza was played the DR-15 Advice of Rights Spanish recording provided by MVA. &amp;nbsp;Martinez Mendoza was provided with a copy of the DR-15 to read along as well. At approximately 0839 hours Martinez Mendoza agreed to take an alcohol concentration test.&lt;br /&gt; 20 MINUTE OBSERVATION&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Martinez Mendoza beginning with his arrest. A preliminary search of Martinez Mendoza was conducted on scene and it was revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. I observed Martinez Mendoza from the time of arrest until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by Cpl. Williams #6099 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Martinez Mendoza had a result of .13 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath on October 2nd, 2023 at 0858 hours.&lt;br /&gt; Intoximeter Result: .13 BrAC, Martinez Mendoza agreed to take an alcohol concentration test.&lt;br /&gt; Martinez Mendoza&amp;rsquo;s vehicle was towed by N&amp;amp;S Towing.&lt;br /&gt; I processed Martinez Mendoza and released him to Mohammad, Nur (5/M, DOB: 06/17/1990).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Martinez Mendoza was issued the following citations.&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-902(a1i) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-902(b1i) DRIVING VEH. WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-902(a1ii) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL PER SE&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-901.1(a) RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OFPERSONS AND PROPERTY&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-901.1(b) NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The defendant was issued copies of the following documents:&lt;br /&gt; -Citations (listed above)&lt;br /&gt; -DR-15 Advice of Rights&lt;br /&gt; -DR-15a Order of Suspension&lt;br /&gt; -MSP 33 Notification to Defendant of Result of Test for Alcohol Concentration&lt;br /&gt; All documents were forwarded to the Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County, State Attorney Office.&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/17/2023 05:53:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/17/2023 05:53:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Richards</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jerrell</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7514</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Aaron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fleming</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sierra</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7439</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524004</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/02/2023 07:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/15/2023 02:56:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/15/2023 02:56:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>36</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/15/2023 02:58:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/15/2023 03:04:38</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389313</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Martinez Mendoza</LastName>
               <FirstName>Oscar</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Eduardo</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/15/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 10:23:18</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M635</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>O260</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Martinez Mendoza</LastName>
               <FirstName>Oscar</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Eduardo</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/15/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M635</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>O260</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 10:23:18</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>323</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Gorman</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Laurel</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20707</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4707</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.851325</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.099414</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>960</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0379</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/15/2023 02:58:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/15/2023 02:58:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/15/2023 02:58:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/15/2023 02:58:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/15/2023 02:56:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/15/2023 02:56:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157656</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/15/2023 03:00:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/15/2023 03:00:14</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JF2SH64689H736221</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2009</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>SUBA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FOR</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GLD</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1FL7304</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>6</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>