<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-007295</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/26/2023 03:14:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/26/2023 03:14:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/26/2023 02:58:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/26/2023 02:58:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI TS</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/26/2023 03:14:24</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/06/2023 09:56:05</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I695 WB,HALETHORPE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>685542</AddressId>
      <City>MDC429</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/26/2023 03:14:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 09:30:12</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>685542</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I695 Wb Halethorpe</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.6679011666667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.237983</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE6FF607MD102729+17261907+</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/26/2023 03:14:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/26/2023 03:14:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/05/2023 13:25:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/26/2023 03:14:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:25</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*This stop was captured on in-car and body worn camera*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUI #: P-23-019&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CASE #: 23-MSP-007295&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUSPECT: Akinkuade, Stephen (BM DOB: 04/15/1995)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VICTIM: Society&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NARRATIVE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;On February 26, 2023 at approximately 0258 hours, I was on duty and in uniform operating unmarked MSP vehicle P-11. I was on routine patrol in the area of N/B I-97 in the area of Dorsey Road, Anne Arundel County, Maryland, when I first observed the suspect vehicle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 1 &amp;ndash; VEHICLE IN MOTION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;As I was traveling in lane 1, I observed the suspect vehicle ahead of me in lane 2. While approaching the rear of the vehicle, I observed it randomly, abruptly, and aggressively swerve into lane 3 by approximately half the vehicle width, straddle the lane line for approximately 1-2 seconds, and then drift slowly back into lane 2. As we began to pass Dorsey Road, the vehicle continued in lane 2 and drifted slowly to the left causing both driver side tires to cross into lane 1 and then immediately back across lane 2, causing both passenger side tires to cross into lane 3, and again across lane 2 causing both driver side tires to cross into lane 1. After correcting back into lane 2, the vehicle began to randomly accelerate at speeds greater than 88 MPH in a posted 65 MPH zone and passing another vehicle. After passing Rt. 648, the vehicle began to slow its speed and I was unable to obtain an accurate pace at that time. As we negotiated the slight curve in the road, the vehicle slowly drifted to the right again causing more than half the vehicle to cross into lane 3 and straddle the lane line for several seconds before finally moving completely in lane 3. After the vehicle did move into lane 3, it crossed completely across the lane causing both passenger side tires to touch the solid shoulder line. After corrected in lane 3, the vehicle again began to accelerate as we approached the ramp to W/B I-695. As the vehicle was accelerating, it continued to rock back and forth in its lane and I was again unable to obtain a pace due to the vehicle slowing down as it approached the ramp. When the vehicle slowed its speed, it once again slowly drifted to the left causing both driver side tires to cross into lane 2.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; While navigating the ramp to WB I-695, the vehicle continued to show difficulty maintaining its lane and crossed the lane line on three more occasions. After merging fully on I-695, the vehicle again began to accelerate while now traveling in lane 2 as I was traveling in lane 1. As I began to attempt a pace prior to Rt. 295, the vehicle briefly drifted left causing the driver side tires to cross into lane 1 before corrected across the lane and causing more than half the vehicle to cross into lane 3, straddling the lane line for several seconds. The vehicle then corrected and briefly slowed its speed as we passed another vehicle in lane 3, and then accelerated again. At that time, I positioned myself behind the suspect vehicle to attempt a pace but the vehicle than changed lanes into lane 1. I again positioned behind the vehicle and was able to obtain a pace of 88 MPH in a posted 55 MPH zone in the area of Nursery Road.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; After obtaining a pace of the vehicle, I activated my emergency equipment to conduct a lawful traffic stop on the suspect vehicle. I activated my emergency equipment at the Anne Arundel County border of Baltimore County, but the vehicle continued to drive at a high rate without immediately slowing its speed. After activating my emergency equipment, the vehicle changed lanes into lane 2 and then slowly began to reduce its speed. As the vehicle began to slow down, the vehicle slowly drifted to the right causing both passenger side tires to cross into lane 3 as if it was moving towards the right shoulder, but then corrected back into lane 2, activated its turn signal, and then moved towards the right shoulder. The vehicle stopped on the right shoulder of W/B I-695 at Hollins Ferry Road, Baltimore County, Maryland. The vehicle was a black Hyundai Sonata bearing Maryland registration 6FF6907.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 2 &amp;ndash; PERSONAL CONTACT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;I made a driver side approach to the vehicle and made contact with the driver and two passengers. When I approached the vehicle, I immediately detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the passenger compartment of the vehicle, and observed the driver was drowsy with a disheveled appearance as he had an apparent red wine stain on his shirt and his shirt was untucked and partially unbuttoned. After making my initial contact with the driver, he stated that he was unaware that he was speeding or swerving and then began to stare blankly at me. When I asked the driver for his license and registration, he continued to stare at me while stating, &amp;ldquo;yeah,&amp;rdquo; causing me to ask a second time. The driver stated that he was on his way home from Bowie at the time of the stop. The driver also stated that he was recently engaged to his new fianc&amp;eacute;, who was the front seat passenger, and stated that they were out celebrating.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The driver was identified by his Maryland issued driver&amp;rsquo;s license as Stephen Akinkuade (B/M DOB: 04/15/1995). As I was speaking with Akinkuade, I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person, his eyes were glossy and bloodshot, and his speech was slightly slow and slurred. Akinkuade also appeared drowsy with droopy eyelids. When I asked Akinkuade if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages that evening, he stated, &amp;ldquo;not much.&amp;rdquo; When I asked Akinkuade to clarify, he stated that he had consumed &amp;ldquo;one shot&amp;rdquo; approximately 1 &amp;ndash; 2 hours prior to the traffic stop.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 3 &amp;ndash; PRE-ARREST SCREENING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Based on my observations and conversations with Akinkuade, I asked him to exit the vehicle and perform standardized field sobriety tests to confirm he could safely operate a motor vehicle. Akinkuade agreed to exit the vehicle and perform the tests. When Akinkuade exited the vehicle, he had to put his shoes on as he was driving without them. Akinkuade walked slowly to the front of his vehicle and stayed within close vicinity to the vehicle. The tests were performed on the right shoulder in front of Akinkuade&amp;rsquo;s vehicle. The ground at the time was level and free from debris. The weather at the time was clear and approximately 36 degrees Fahrenheit. Akinkuade was wearing dress pants, a dress shirt, suit jacket, and dress shoes. Akinkuade stated that he did not wear contacts or glasses and did not take any medications. Akinkuade also stated that he did not have any injuries or impairments that affected his balance or ability to walk. Akinkuade was also chewing gum at the time and was asked to spit it out. While standing outside the vehicle, and especially after he removed the gum from his mouth, I continued to detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting form his breath as he spoke and was breathing through his mouth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instructions: The subject is told to stand with their feet together and their arms down at their side. A stimulus (ink pen) is held approximately twelve to fifteen inches from the subjects&amp;rsquo; face, and they are asked to follow the stimulus with their eyes only and not to move their head. Prior to beginning the test, I ask the subject if they understand the instructions. I initially check for equal pupil size, resting nystagmus, and equal tracking. I next check for lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees. Finally, I check for vertical nystagmus. Both eyes are checked twice for each clue.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Results: &lt;strong&gt;6/6&lt;/strong&gt;. Akinkuade had brown eyes that were glossy and bloodshot. Akinkuade appeared drowsy with droopy eyelids. Both pupils appeared normal and equal in size. Both eyes were tracking equally and resting nystagmus was not present. All clues were present. Akinkuade attempted to move his head with the stimulus and had to be corrected, but otherwise performed the test correctly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;WALK AND TURN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instructions: The subject is told to stand with their right foot in front of their left foot in a heel to toe manner. They are told to stay in that position and keep their arms at their side until being told to begin the test. I ask to make sure they understand and then begin explaining and demonstrating the test. The subject is instructed to take nine heel-to-toe steps on a straight, imaginary line. On the ninth step, they are instructed to leave their lead foot planted and take a series of small steps to turn 180 degrees. They are then told to take an additional nine heel-to-toe steps back down the same imaginary line. They are told to watch their feet, count their steps out loud, keep their hands at their side, touch heel-to-toe on every step, and to not stop walking until the test is completed.&amp;nbsp; I then ask if they understand the instructions before having them begin the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Results:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Starts Too Soon: &lt;/strong&gt;Akinkuade immediately began walking before I had a chance to give him all of the instructions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steps Off Line:&lt;/strong&gt; Akinkuade wobbled and began to lose his balance when he first began the test, causing his first step to step off line.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raises Arms:&lt;/strong&gt; On Akinkuade first two steps as he lost and attempted to regain his balance, he began to sway his arms and body, raising his arms greater than 6 inches. Akinkuade continued to keep his arms raised from his side for the entire test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improper Number of Steps:&lt;/strong&gt; Akinkuade counted his right foot in the starting position as his first step, resulting in only taking 8 steps. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stops Walking:&lt;/strong&gt; Akinkuade stopped walking at the turn and broke his cadence for me to remind him what to do. Akinkuade was instructed to finish the test as instructed and then he continued. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Turn:&lt;/strong&gt; Performed satisfactorily, but in the opposite direction due to the incorrect number of steps. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other:&lt;/strong&gt; While I was explaining the test, Akinkuade stated that he worked in corrections at the Baltimore City DOC. Akinkuade continued to mention it several times throughout my interaction with him. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total Clues: 6/8&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ONE LEG STAND&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instructions: The subject is instructed to stand with their feet together with their hands at the side while I explain the instructions and demonstrate the test. They are told to raise either foot of their choice approximately six inches off the ground. They are told to begin to count, one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-three&amp;hellip;etc. They are told to continue counting until I tell them to stop. They are told to watch their feet, to count out loud, to keep their arms at their side, and to not put their foot down. I then ask if the subject understands the instructions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Results:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sway:&lt;/strong&gt; Akinkuade began swaying initially at the beginning of the test before correcting for the remainder of the test. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other:&lt;/strong&gt; Akinkuade began the test by standing on his right foot and raising his left foot. Not looking at his foot as instructed. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total Clues: 4/4&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;While on scene, Akinkuade was asked if he would submit to a preliminary breath test. I am certified by the Maryland State Police and the State of Maryland Office of the Chief Medical Examiner to conduct preliminary breath tests with the use of the Alco Sensor. This is the approved preliminary breath test for the State of Maryland. Akinkuade agreed to submit to the test. While attempting to perform the test, Akinkuade was obviously attempting to advert the test by not following my instructions. I was unable to get an accurate reading.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Based on my observations and training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper and Drug Recognition Expert, I placed Akinkuade under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0315 hours. Akinkuade was polite and cooperative during my entire interaction with him. Akinkuade continued to make comments about where he worked as if I was supposed to give him leniency. Akinkuade was secured in my vehicle to be transported to the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack for further processing. After securing Akinkuade in my vehicle, I spoke to the front seat passenger and explained the process to her. The front seat passenger was provided a preliminary breath test which showed there was no alcohol present. The front seat passenger was identified by her Maryland issued driver&amp;rsquo;s license as Ruth Olumaranti Samson (B/F DOB: 05/07/1995). Samson was allowed to take possession of the vehicle after it was confirmed she had a valid license to drive. Akinkuade was mostly quiet on the way to the Barrack, appearing to be sleeping most of the way. When we first left the scene, Akinkuade asked again what the remainder of the process would be like, even though I had already explained it to him two other times prior. We arrived at the Barrack at approximately 0329 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; After arriving at the Barrack, Akinkuade was escorted to the Barrack DUI processing room. Akinkuade was provided a copy of his DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along as I read the form in its entirety. While I was reading the form, Akinkuade was holding the form in both hands and looking down at it, appearing to be following along. After reading the form, Akinkuade stated that he understood the form. When I asked Akinkuade if he understood the form, he stated, &amp;ldquo;not really.&amp;rdquo; When I asked Akinkuade what I could clarify for him, he wanted to know about what would happen to his license. After explaining that section of the form again, Akinkuade stated that he did not have any further questions. Akinkuade agreed to submit to the test. Sgt. Natale #5419, a certified intoximeter operator, performed the test. When performing the test, Akinkuade had two insufficient breaths and had to provide a total of four breath samples because of that. Akinkuade had two insufficient breaths due to similar behaviors he displayed while attempting the preliminary breath test. The result of the test was .07.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DISPOSITION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;After completing the initial paperwork, Akinkuade was secured in a temporary holding cell while I completed the remaining paperwork. After finishing the appropriate paperwork, Akinkuade was released from the Barrack to a sober driver after being charged accordingly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All events occurred in Anne Arundel and Baltimore County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 11:16:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 13:08:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Keller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brady</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7360</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Young</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6101</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496692</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/26/2023 02:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 09:29:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 09:34:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 09:29:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:41</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370786</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Akinkuade</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/15/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 09:21:59</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Akinkuade</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/15/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>A252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 09:21:59</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1008</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Rosecroft</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>York</City>
               <StateCode>PA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>17403</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.743061</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.939225</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>467</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0357</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 09:35:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 09:35:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 09:30:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 09:30:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>