<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-028576</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/13/2023 02:50:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/13/2023 02:50:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/13/2023 01:36:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/13/2023 01:36:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Subject intoxicated and suffering from mental issues.  Subject became disorderly while at Super 8 Motel and began destroying property.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 02:50:45</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4816</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/28/2023 13:29:45</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>EP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>MDOP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PIX</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>Super 8 Motel room #117</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>32115</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>522</SubBeat>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 02:50:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 03:19:28</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>32115</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1301</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>NATIONAL</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>CUMBERLAND</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>522</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-78.84625588232446</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.637053568259134</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>DOG IN A HOTEL ROOM @ SUPER 8 MOTEL</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SUPER 8 MOTEL</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SUPER 8</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SUPER 8 , ROOM #120</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/13/2023 02:50:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/13/2023 02:50:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>52</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/28/2023 13:28:15</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 02:50:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:02:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>- Incident captured on both Sgt. Divelbiss&amp;#39; and TFC Cosgrove&amp;#39;s Axon body cameras&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Narrative:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 8/12/2023 at approximately 2300 hours, I (Sgt. Divelbiss #4425) arrived at the MSP Cumberland Barrack in uniform to assume shift commander responsibilities for my assigned shift 2300 to 0700 hours.&amp;nbsp; I was advised from the previous shift commander, Cpl. D. Diehl of a female outside the front entrance of the Cumberland Barrack, later identified as Rashida Raquel Bridgeman (B/F DOB: 10/28/1984). I was informed by Cpl. Diehl that TFC S. Williams from his group handled a call for service with Bridgeman at the Super 8 Motel located at 1301 National Hwy, LaVale, MD.&amp;nbsp; Bridgeman told TFC. Williams she was in fear for her safety and believed someone was trying to track her down and rob her.&amp;nbsp; TFC. WIlliams relocated Bridgeman to the Cumberland Barrack lobby to wait for a friend to pick Bridgeman up, however, the friend had extended travel from New York.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I made contact with Bridgeman outside the front of the barrack.&amp;nbsp; It was clear Bridgeman suffers from mental issues.&amp;nbsp; She was delusional and had parodynia of being robbed from unknown people as well as talking to be people who were not present.&amp;nbsp; When asked why she felt she was going to be robbed she explained her boyfriend was arrested earlier today in Cumberland City for drug related charges.&amp;nbsp; Bridgeman said since her boyfriend has been in jail several people claiming to be friends with her boyfriend showed up at this house on Spring Street, Cumberland.&amp;nbsp; She felt these people were going to rob her thinking she was holding his drugs and or money.&amp;nbsp; She described how she drove around Cumberland with these people, however, she could not provide a physical description.&amp;nbsp; She recalled going to the marijuana dispensary in Cumberland, where she purchased marijuana for all of them.&amp;nbsp; Bridgeman explained she also purchased food at Chick-Fil-A in Cumberland for them as well.&amp;nbsp; Afterwards they all went to the Super 8 motel, and she rented a room for the day.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Bridgeman struggled to describe one of the two people and the vehicle they rode in.&amp;nbsp; She recalled on of them was named &amp;quot;Jamie&amp;quot; and only could say she was &amp;quot;white&amp;quot; and a female.&amp;nbsp; She could not or would not provide any description of the other person who I only gathered was a male.&amp;nbsp; At the conclusion of my conversion with Bridgeman I determined there was not anyone coming to get her from New York.&amp;nbsp; I offered to call someone for her or take her to the Union Rescue Mission (homeless shelter).&amp;nbsp; Bridgeman felt she could now go back to the Super 8 Motel seeing she had already purchased the room for the night.&amp;nbsp; I transported her to the motel in my assigned maroon unmarked patrol vehicle C-24.&amp;nbsp; I walked her into the motel and spoke to the night shift employee, Marla Hudgins.&amp;nbsp; Hudgins was not familiar with Bridgeman however, had heard about her from the previous shift motel employee.&amp;nbsp; Hudgins confirmed Bridgeman had paid for a night stay and was assigned to room #117 located just down the hall from motel&amp;#39;s main desk.&amp;nbsp; I explained to Hudgins the concerns Bridgeman had of someone trying to rob her.&amp;nbsp; Hudgins explained the motel had numerous cameras in and outside the motel to include the hallway of room 117.&amp;nbsp; Hudgins said she would notify the barrack if she observed anyone in the area of room 117.&amp;nbsp; I walked Bridgeman to her room and made a check of the room to make sure nobody was in there.&amp;nbsp; During my check of the room, I did not observe anyone and noticed the room was clean, organized, and untouched from Housekeepings last cleaning.&amp;nbsp; Bridgeman was left in the room.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Within 30 minutes of leaving Bridgeman, she began calling 911.&amp;nbsp; She claimed people were at her door and outside in the parking lot trying to get her.&amp;nbsp; I called the motel and spoke with Hudgins.&amp;nbsp; Hudgins stated she was actively looking at the cameras and there was nobody outside room #117 or outside in the parking lot.&amp;nbsp; Bridgeman was ensured that nobody was there and to try to get some sleep.&amp;nbsp; Bridgeman repeatedly continued to call 911 staying she was in danger and needed law enforcement.&amp;nbsp; She claimed people were waiting for her in a white vehicle outside her window.&amp;nbsp; She stated one of the people had a gun.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Bridgeman called 911, nine (9) times in just a short amount of time.&amp;nbsp; TFC. Cosgrove and I responded to motel in attempted to contact Bridgeman.&amp;nbsp; Bridgeman refused to answer the door, but screamed from inside the room she did not believe we were police and that she had barricaded the door.&amp;nbsp; Due to Bridgeman&amp;#39;s room being on the first floor, I walked to the parking lot and was able to see inside Bridgeman&amp;#39;s room.&amp;nbsp; Bridgeman noticed me outside and opened the window.&amp;nbsp; I immediately noticed from the window, the room was in complete disarray.&amp;nbsp; I observed the room dresser, tv, and mini refrigerator stacked up against door.&amp;nbsp; One of the two mattress and box springs were stacked against the wall facing the parking lot.&amp;nbsp; I noticed an empty pint of vodka liquor on a night stand.&amp;nbsp; I attempted for several minutes to get Bridgemen to unlock the door and allow TFC Cosgrove and I to come in to talk with her.&amp;nbsp; Bridgeman refused stating she did not trust us.&amp;nbsp; Bridgeman began screaming a yelling at a white unoccupied SUV vehicle parked in the parking lot.&amp;nbsp; I walked over to this vehicle and showed Bridgeman that nobody was in the vehicle. She continued screaming very loud and at one point punched out the motel window screen damaging the metal frame.&amp;nbsp; I attempted to calm Bridgeman down for several minutes, however, she stated I was conspiring with the people who wanted her dead.&amp;nbsp; I was able to talk her into allowing me to climb into the window and enter the room with her.&amp;nbsp; I entered the room and moved the furniture from behind the door.&amp;nbsp; I located another pint of vodka liquor in the bathroom that was nearly empty.&amp;nbsp; I could now smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on her breath as she spoke.&amp;nbsp; I explained to Bridgeman she needed to be transported to the hospital to talk with doctors about the way she was feeling.&amp;nbsp; She ultimately agreed and was secured in handcuffs and transported by TFC. Cosgrove.&amp;nbsp; Bridgeman had two large purses with her belongs inside them.&amp;nbsp; Bridgeman was in view of her bags during our entire encounter with her.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Bridgeman was released to the staff at Western MD UPMC.&amp;nbsp; An emergency petition form was completed and filed with the hospital.&amp;nbsp; A check with the MD Gun Center was completed and did not reveal Bridgeman had any firearms registered to her.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Hudgins the motel employee was shown the damage to room 117.&amp;nbsp; Hudgins advised she did not believe the motel would pursue charges, but said she would let me know if they decided to.&amp;nbsp; Hudgins stated numerous motel guests had called the front desk in fear over Bridgeman screaming and yelling.&amp;nbsp; The guest were disturbed by Bridgeman&amp;#39;s conduct.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I later received a call from UPMC staff saying Bridgeman claimed troopers stole $4,000 from her.&amp;nbsp; It should be noted Bridgeman several times made statements captured on body camera she did not have any cash.&amp;nbsp; The UPMC staff was advised to tell Bridgeman to contact the barrack if she would like to file a complaint against TFC. Cosgrove or I.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Case Status: Open pending charges if requested by Super 8</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 01:20:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 09:44:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Divelbiss</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4425</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stern</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4816</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Divelbiss</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4425</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cosgrove</LastName>
            <FirstName>Laurence</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6630</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518021</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>04</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>NOCHG</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>14</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/13/2023 01:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>NOCHG</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 03:22:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 03:22:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518021</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>CO193</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>14</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/13/2023 01:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>CO193</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 03:28:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 03:28:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518021</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1662</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>14</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/13/2023 01:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1662</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 03:28:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 03:28:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518021</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0050</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>14</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/13/2023 01:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 0050</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 03:30:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 03:30:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 04:02:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 04:02:50</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>385014</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bridgeman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Rashida</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Raquel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/28/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/13/2023 04:02:19</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B632</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R230</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bridgeman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Rashida</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Raquel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/28/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B632</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R230</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/13/2023 04:02:19</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2719</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Winchester</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21216</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4329</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.662346</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.301275</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>501</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8451</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4425</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 04:02:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>54</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 04:12:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 04:12:55</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>385015</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hudgins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Marla</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Raye</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/27/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/13/2023 04:12:37</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H325</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M640</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hudgins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Marla</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Raye</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/27/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H325</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M640</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/13/2023 04:12:37</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1301</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>National</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Cumberland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21502</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-78.846028</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.637393</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>338</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6704</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4425</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 04:12:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 03:28:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 03:28:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240016522</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>Super 8 Motel</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 03:23:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 03:34:52</UpdatorDate>
         <BusinessAddress>
            <AddressId>199177</AddressId>
            <StreetNumber>1301</StreetNumber>
            <StreetName>National</StreetName>
            <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
            <SubTypeCode>RM</SubTypeCode>
            <SubNumber>318</SubNumber>
            <City>Lavale</City>
            <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
            <Zip5>21502</Zip5>
            <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            <Longitude>-78.846028</Longitude>
            <Latitude>39.637393</Latitude>
            <BusinessPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>BUS</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>338</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6703</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/28/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </BusinessPhone>
         </BusinessAddress>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 03:34:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 03:34:18</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Motel window screen </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>834</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>200</PropertyValue>
         <Value>200</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>252863</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>