<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-021851</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/18/2023 02:53:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/18/2023 02:53:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/18/2023 02:30:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/18/2023 02:30:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>06/18/2023 03:52:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>Kyle Timothy Hammond was arrested for DUI/ DWI. DUI Folder #23-96-171</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/18/2023 02:53:04</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 17:56:55</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN EXPY/ RACETRACK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/18/2023 02:53:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 21:53:52</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>EXPY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.170578</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.38053</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 E/O 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB/ 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 PRIOR 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MERGING OFF OF 90 INTO OCEAN PINES</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB BETWEEN BRIDGE AND OCEAN PINES EXIT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB PAST 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11083-11086 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1296-1352 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/18/2023 02:53:01</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/18/2023 02:53:01</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/18/2023 17:11:13</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/18/2023 02:53:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUI Folder # 23-96-174&lt;br /&gt; SUSPECT: Kyle Timothy Hammond&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;LICENSE #&amp;nbsp;DE/ 1889474&lt;br /&gt; DUI CITATION #&lt;br /&gt; SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER: No&lt;br /&gt; ACCIDENT INVOLVED: No&lt;br /&gt; VIDEO: Maryland State Police; Axon Evidence Video ID #: 23MSP021851. BWC Utilized.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;ul style="list-style-type:square"&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I am trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of 2021.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of 2020.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I have apprehended more than 80 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phase #1 - Vehicle in Motion:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;On June 18, 2023 at approximately 0230 hours, I, Tfc. Pinto #7212 was on duty, operating unmarked patrol vehicle V-9, patrolling in the area of westbound Ocean City Expressway at mile marker 8, Berlin, Worcester County, Maryland. At this time, I observed a black Chevrolet bearing Delaware registration, &amp;ldquo;491793&amp;rdquo; traveling directly in front of my patrol vehicle, cross the solid white line into the right shoulder by approximately one (1) tires width, and drift back into the westbound lane. The black Chevrolet continued westbound on Ocean City Expressway east of Ocean Parkway, and I observed the vehicle cross the solid white line into the right shoulder by approximately half the vehicles width, remain in the shoulder for approximately 100 feet, and drift back into the westbound lane. I remained behind the black Chevrolet at westbound Ocean City Expressway at Ocean Parkway and I observed the vehicle cross the solid white line into the right shoulder by approximately one (1) tires width, and drift back into the westbound lane. The black Chevrolet continued westbound on Ocean City Expressway east of Racetrack Road and I observed the black Chevrolet cross the solid white line into the right shoulder by approximately one (1) tires width, and drift back into the westbound lane.&amp;nbsp; I continued behind the black Chevrolet at westbound Ocean City Expressway east of Racetrack Road when I observed the vehicle cross the solid, into the right shoulder, by half the width of the vehicle for approximately 200 feet before drifting back into the westbound lane. The black Chevrolet continued westbound on Ocean City Expressway at Racetrack Road and I observed the vehicle cross the solid white line, into the right shoulder by approximately one-half (1/2) tires width and drift back into the westbound lane. While behind the black Chevrolet at westbound Ocean City Expressway at Racetrack Road, I activated my emergency equipment to conduct a traffic stop on the vehicle. The black Chevrolet came to a stop into the right shoulder on the Ocean City Expressway exit ramp onto Racetrack Road. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phase #2- Personal Contact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;I exited my patrol vehicle and made contact with the driver on the driver&amp;rsquo;s side open front window. While making contact with the driver and two passengers, I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the passenger compartment of the vehicle. I locked in on the odor of an alcoholic beverage due to my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I made contact with the driver at the open driver&amp;rsquo;s side window and immediately detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage and observed the driver&amp;rsquo;s eyes were glassy. I explained to the driver that I stopped him for crossing into the shoulder area of the roadway multiple times and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yea I&amp;rsquo;m alright, I was, I&amp;rsquo;m not from here, I&amp;rsquo;m from Delaware, I was trying, trying to make my way home. I asked the driver for his license and registration. While the driver retrieved his license and registration, I asked the driver where they were traveling from and he stated, &amp;ldquo;um coming from uh Ocean City.&amp;rdquo; I asked the driver where in Ocean City he was coming from and he stated, &amp;ldquo;um down at the beach.&amp;rdquo; The driver asked, &amp;ldquo;you said my license and registration,&amp;rdquo; and that I did need his license and registration. &amp;nbsp;The driver provided his Delaware driver&amp;rsquo;s license and I identified him as Kyle Timothy Hammond (W/M 11/12/1998).&amp;nbsp; I then observed Hammond look at his Insurance card and hand me a copy of his insurance. I advised Hammond that the document was his insurance card and again requested his Delaware registration card and the Hammond complied. I asked Hammond if he still lived at his Harrington, Delaware address and he advised he did. I asked Hammond if that is where he was traveling to and he stated it was. I asked Hammond if he owned the vehicle and he advised he did. I asked Hammond how many alcoholic beverages he had this evening before driving and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I had one.&amp;rdquo; I advised Hammond that I was detecting the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the passenger department of the vehicle. The backseat passenger advised that the odor was coming from her.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;I returned to my patrol vehicle, conducted license and wanted check on the driver, and requested back-up for Standardized Field Sobriety.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Once back-up arrived, I exited my patrol vehicle and made contacted with Hammond on the driver&amp;rsquo;s side open window, requested him to step out of his vehicle, and he complied. I asked Hammond to step to the front of my patrol vehicle and he complied.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Phase #3- Pre-Arrest Screening&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;While in front of my patrol vehicle, I advised Hammond I wanted to make sure he can make it home safely and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I understand, yes sir, thank you.&amp;rdquo; &amp;nbsp;I observed Hammond to be wearing a white ball back, black t-shirt, blue jeans, and white tennis shoes. I advised Hammond I was going to ask him some questions and asked him to stand with his feet together and hands by his side while I asked the questions and he complied. I asked Hammond how many alcoholic beverages had before operating the vehicle and he stated, &amp;ldquo;One.&amp;rdquo; I asked Hammond where he consumed the alcoholic beverages and he stated, &amp;ldquo;That was down at the beach.&amp;rdquo; I asked Hammond where at the beach he consumed the alcoholic beverage and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Um I believe it was secrets, I had a Miller Lite was the beer.&amp;rdquo; &amp;nbsp;I asked Hammond if he beer was a bottle and he advised it was. I asked Hammond if it was a twenty-ounce Miller Lite and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Whatever the glass bottles are, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what that is, but whatever that is.&amp;rdquo; I asked Hammond around what time he consumed the alcoholic beverage, advised him it that it was currently 0241 hours, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Probably about an hour ago, so maybe one-forty-one one-thirty.&amp;rdquo; I asked Hammond if he had any physical disabilities and he stated, &amp;ldquo;No sir.&amp;rdquo; I asked Hammond if he has any medical disabilities and he stated, &amp;ldquo;No sir.&amp;rdquo; I asked Hammond if he had any recent injuries that prevent him from walking in a straight line or standing on one leg and he stated, &amp;ldquo;No sir.&amp;rdquo; I asked Hammond if he is currently on any medications and he stated, &amp;ldquo;No sir.&amp;rdquo; I asked Hammond if he wears glasses or contacts and he stated, &amp;ldquo;No sir.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. I asked Hammond to lean on the front bumper of my vehicle due to him being much taller than me and asked him to keep his hands by his side and he complied. A pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from eyes, slightly above eye level. Hammond was instructed to look straight ahead at my pen, instructed to follow the pen with his eyes and eyes only, and keep his head and shoulders still. When asked if he understood the instructions, Hammond stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes sir.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lack of smooth pursuit: Present in both eyes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation: Present in both eyes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees: Present in both eyes&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Vertical Nystagmus: not present.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;For information purposes, while conducting the test I continued to detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from Hammond&amp;rsquo;s breath and person. I also observed Hammond&amp;rsquo;s eyes to be glassy. Also, Hammond had to be reminded multiple times to keep his head still and to follow the stimulus with his eyes when it was moved. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Walk and Turn&amp;nbsp;(4/8 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Weather: Clear&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Surface: Flat, free from debris, and dry.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Hammond was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot, touching heel to toe. Hammond was instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. I then asked Hammond to get into the starting position and he complied. I asked Hammond if he understood to remain in the starting position and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes sir.&amp;rdquo; Hammond was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step. Hammond was told to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Hammond was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Hammond was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. I advised Hammond I was taking three (3) steps for instructional purposes, but he was to take nine (9) steps. Hammond began walking while he was being instructed once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keeping his hands down by his sides, looking down at his feet, and to count every step out loud. Hammond was asked to get back into the starting position.&amp;nbsp; Hammond was advised he could begin the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Keep Balance. Hammond stepped out of starting position by moving right foot next to his left foot.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Started Test to Soon. Hammond began the test while he was still being instructed how to conduct the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Missed Heel to Toe: Steps 1, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Stepped Off Line: Step 2&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Turn: Unsatisfactory. Hammond turned left by turning his left foot to the right, pivoting both feet to the right, and then placed his feet side by side.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Walking Stage (2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;Nine):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Missed Heel to Toe: Step 4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stepped Off Line: Steps 3, 7&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;One Leg Stand&amp;nbsp;(1/4 Clues Observed)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Weather: Same as Above&lt;br /&gt; Surface: Same as Above&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Hammond performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Hammond was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his foot, keep his toe pointed forward, keep his hands at his sides, to count out loud by thousands (one-one thousand, two- one thousand), and to continue the test until told to stop. When asked if he understood the instructions, Hammond stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes sir.&amp;rdquo; When told to begin, Hammond lifted his left leg.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Swayed: 0-10 seconds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Put Food Down: 0-10 seconds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raised Arms for Balance: 0-10 seconds, 11-20 seconds, 21-30 seconds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Alphabet Test (F to T):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;I asked Hammond if he was familiar with the English alphabet and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; I asked Hammond if he graduated high school and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yea.&amp;rdquo; I asked Hammond to say the Alphabet starting at F and end at T.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Hammond stated, &amp;ldquo;FGHIJKLMNOPQRST.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Count Backwards (59 to 36):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Hammond was asked to count backwards starting at 59 and end at 36.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Hammond counted, &amp;ldquo;58, 57, 56, 55, 54, 53, 52, 51, 50, 49, 48, 47, 46, 45, 44, 43, 42, ,41, 40, 39, 38, 37, 36.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Preliminary Breath Test&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I explained the reasons for using a preliminary breath test and asked Hammond if he wanted to submit a breath sample. Hammond refused to the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Arrest&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Based on the following totality of circumstances, I had reason to believe Hammond was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hammond&amp;rsquo;s failure to obey a properly placed traffic control device.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Hammond&amp;rsquo;s breath and person.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hammond&amp;rsquo;s&amp;nbsp;eyes were glassy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hammond completed Standardized Field Sobriety Test unsatisfactory.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; At 0252 hours, I placed Hammond under arrest.&amp;nbsp;I then placed Hammond into the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. I then entered my patrol vehicle and detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage that was not present prior to placing Hammond inside.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;DR-15 Advice of Rights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;While in the front seat of my patrol vehicle,&amp;nbsp;I placed a paper copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights in front of Hammond. I played the MVA Audio version of the DR-15 from the MVA website and asked Hammond to follow along.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;After the DR-15 was completed, Hammond advised at 0307 hours he refused to submit to take an intoximeter test.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Hammond was processed and advised not to drive for 12 hours. Hammond was given his paperwork and citations&amp;nbsp;released to a sober driver from the scene of the traffic stop.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Charge&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driving Vehicle While Under the Influence of Alcohol (3LJ0VPH)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driving Vehicle While Impaired by Alcohol (3LK0VPH)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Negligent Driving (3LL0VPH)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reckless Driving (3LM0VPH)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Failure to Obey a Properly Placed Traffic Control Device (3LM0VPH)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Case Closed by Arrest.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;All above events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 21:57:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/29/2023 13:23:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511287</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/18/2023 02:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 21:51:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 21:54:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 21:51:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:52</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>381075</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hammond</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Timothy</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/12/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.22904582E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>06/27/2023 21:38:43</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H553</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hammond</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Timothy</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/12/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.22904582E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>H553</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/27/2023 21:38:43</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>216</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Friendship</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>VLG</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Harrington</City>
               <StateCode>DE</StateCode>
               <Zip5>19952</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3271</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.587135</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.93099</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>302</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>424</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2031</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 21:55:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 21:55:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 21:53:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 21:53:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154601</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/27/2023 21:56:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 21:56:30</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2G1FB1ED0B9201100</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2011</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CAM</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>DE</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>491793</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>