<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-026779</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/28/2023 16:52:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/28/2023 16:52:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/28/2023 14:49:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/28/2023 14:49:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Theft of concert tickets</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 16:52:59</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2637</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 15:09:49</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>THT</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>702293</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 16:53:00</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 00:16:09</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>702293</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>29</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Gammy</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Elkton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.924414</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.538422</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/28/2023 16:52:55</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/28/2023 16:52:55</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>Y</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/09/2023 06:22:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 16:52:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;strong&gt;Scene Processing&lt;/strong&gt;: None.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Neighborhood Check&lt;/strong&gt;: None.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Attachments&lt;/strong&gt;: None.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Narrative&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; On 07/28/2023 at approximately 1449 hours, I, Trooper Jones #7445 of the Maryland Police - North East Barrack was on duty and dispatched to 29 Gammy Dr, Elkton, MD 21921 in reference to a report of credit card fraud / theft.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; I made contact with the victim who I was able to identify as Alec Anthony Swartz (DOB: 11/07/1999). Swartz advised me he was at work at approximately 1400 hours, and received confirmation emails from Ticketmaster confirming a purchase of 4 concert tickets to a Luke Combs concert in Philiadelphia, PA. Swartz stated when he first saw the email, he thought it was just spam. 10 minutes later, Swartz advised he received another email confirming a purchase of 4 concert tickets to a Tyler Childers concert in New York City. Swartz advised he knew something was going on at this point because he had not purchased any tickets to concerts and immediately went to check his bank account. Upon checking his account, Swartz advised he saw both transactions on his bank statements and then left work early to go into the PNC Bank branch located at 1 S. Main St. North East, MD 21901 to report the fraud and to get a new bank card. Swartz stated he also made an appointment to come back the following morning to dispute the fraudulent charges. I asked Swartz if he could provide me with any documentation showing the alleged purchase of the concert tickets. He stated he had screenshots of everything to include the possible suspect information that he could provide me. I then provided Swartz with my agency email and requested he forward them to me. When asked how much money had been spent on the tickets, Swartz advised between to the two concerts and 8 tickets total that were purchased, the total amount was $2,732.00.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; Once Swartz emailed me the information, I asked if he could explain more about why he believes he has the name of the possible suspect. Swartz advised that when he got the email confirmations, he also got a notification from Apple asking if he&amp;#39;d like to merge another contact name into his account since the suspect used his card information associated with his Apple Pay. Swartz explained that Apple assumed the tickets were purchased by the suspect with his permission, and they have a feature that would allow him to add the suspect name to his account to make future purchases easier. When Apple notified Swartz that he could add the person&amp;#39;s name to his account, he realized the name that Apple was notifying him about was the name attached to the concert tickets purchased with his bank card. I asked Swartz what the name listed with the purchase was and if he knew the person, and he advised it was a female named Laura Denardo, and he did not know her. He also provided me with two different phone numbers which were (410) 558-1493 and (410) 375-5852. It is noted, after speaking with Swartz and, I attempted to call the phone numbers provided to try and make contact with the Denardo subject.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;After a few attempts, I was able to make contact with a woman who stated her name is Laura Denardo. I explained to Denardo who I was, the reason for the call and if she could explain why her name was listed on concert tickets purchased with Swartz&amp;#39;s bank card. Denardo advised she was in Pittsburgh, PA at a family reunion and had not purchased tickets nor planned to attend any concerts. She stated she did not know how her name was attached to this purchase and asked if she could contact me at a later time that evening to speak more about it. Denardo did not contact me back nor answer her phone when I attempted to call her again later that evening. I will be attempting to gather more information on Denardo and reach out to her again.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; I then asked Swartz if he had gone anywhere and used his bank card recently that could have allowed someone to gain access to his banking information. Swartz stated he and his girlfriend had gone to Little Italy in Baltimore on 07/22/2023 for the day. Swarts advised he only used his bank card to try and pay for parking and to purchase gas, but added his card was not working for some reason when attempting to pay for parking. Swartz stated when his card failed to work, his girlfriend attempted to pay and her card did work. Swartz acknowledged that he is always aware of &amp;quot;skimmers&amp;quot; at ATM&amp;#39;s, gas pumps, and even at the parking garages he sometimes uses. He stated he pulled on the machine at the parking garage while in Baltimore and did not think at the time that the machine could have possibly had a &amp;quot;skimmer&amp;quot; installed. Swartz continued by explaining that at the moment while trying to pay for parking, he did not think to question if his card had been compromised until he received the email confirmations.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; Upon gathering all the information related to this incident, I advised Swartz I would be submitting a report and provided him with the case number. I requested he contacted me if he was to come across any additional information pertaining to this case.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case Status: Open.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 11:13:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/06/2023 22:16:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Siemek</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6684</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jones</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7445</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516224</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1136_AOL</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/28/2023 14:49:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1136_AOL</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 11:08:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 11:08:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>23</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 11:12:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:12</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383912</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Swartz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alec</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anthony</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/07/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/31/2023 11:11:35</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S632</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A420</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Swartz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alec</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anthony</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/07/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S632</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A420</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/31/2023 11:11:35</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>29</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Gammy</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Elkton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.924414</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.538422</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>406</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5205</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 11:12:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 11:12:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>7</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/06/2023 22:27:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/06/2023 22:27:38</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>7</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>C</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>CSH</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>2732</PropertyValue>
         <Value>2732</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>252695</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>0</Quantity>
         <Amount>2732</Amount>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>