<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-014828</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/26/2023 22:37:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/26/2023 22:37:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/26/2023 22:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/26/2023 22:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Two Vehicle Collision / DUI, DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/26/2023 22:37:09</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/08/2023 13:17:08</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>TANEYTOWN PIKE/ RICHARDSON RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>570313</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/26/2023 22:37:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 22:06:38</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>570313</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Taneytown</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PIKE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westminster</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-77.077191</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.612318</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2300-2401 TANEYTOWN PIKE / 1340-1347 RICHARDSON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1900-1990 TANEYTOWN PKE / 1340-1347 RICHARDSON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1900-1991 TANEYTOWN PIKE / 1418-1597 RICHARDSON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/26/2023 22:37:06</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/26/2023 22:37:06</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/04/2023 12:00:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/26/2023 22:37:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:28</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THIS INCIDENT WAS AUDIBLY AND VISUALLY RECORDED ON AXON BODY WORN AND VEHICLE CAMERAS&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defendant:&lt;/strong&gt; Edward Joseph Dietz Jr.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date of Birth:&lt;/strong&gt; 01/28/1976&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date of Arrest:&lt;/strong&gt; 04/26/2023&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time of Arrest:&lt;/strong&gt; 2234 hours&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MD License #:&lt;/strong&gt; MD10272233662&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Westminster DUI #:&lt;/strong&gt; 23-063&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRAINING/CERTIFICATES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, July 2019.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Trained to investigate collisions through the Maryland State Police, July 2019.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement through the Baltimore County Police Department, February 2021&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute, August 2021.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Drug Recognition Expert, December 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;On April 26, 2023, at approximately 2200 hours, I, Trooper First Class Mills #6784, currently assigned to the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack, responded to eastbound Maryland Route 140 at Richardson Road for a two-vehicle collision while operating marked Maryland State Police vehicle G-9.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Upon my arrival at the scene, I observed Fireboard and Emergency Medical Service (EMS) units were on scene and had both directions of Maryland 140 shut down to secure the scene since vehicles and debris were still in the roadway. Due to the lane closure, I positioned my patrol vehicle directly behind a Honda CRV that was parked on the right shoulder of eastbound Maryland Route 140 at Richardson Road.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;I made contact with the female driver of the Honda, who was identified by her Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license as Kelly Lynn Brady (DOB 06/10/2000 W/F). Brady stated that she witnessed the collision occur. Brady stated that she was driving and saw a white vehicle (which she positively identified to be the crashed vehicle approximately one hundred (100) feet in front of her location) pass her vehicle and another vehicle on the right shoulder and strike the guardrail. Brady added that the white vehicle then struck another vehicle traveling eastbound on Maryland Route 140 after striking the guardrail. Brady stated that she observed the Hyundai travel at a high rate of speed around her on the shoulder. After the crash occurred, Brady checked on the welfare of all involved drivers. Brady stated that when she made contact with the driver of the white vehicle, he stated, &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;#39;t see straight.&amp;rdquo; Deputy First Class Remmes #0677 of the Carroll County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Office requested that she complete a written statement, which she voluntarily completed (See attached written statement.)&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;EMS personnel made contact with the sole male occupant of the vehicle, and he refused any medical treatment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;I made contact with a deputy from the Carroll County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Office who was on scene prior to my arrival. The deputy handed me a Maryland Driver&amp;rsquo;s license and vehicle insurance card for the driver and the Hyundai. The deputy further explained the driver of the Hyundai was argumentative and had not given him the vehicle registration despite his efforts in asking for the registration card several times. The deputy advised the driver of the Hyundai claimed that he gave him the registration card. I asked the deputy where the driver said he was coming from, and the deputy advised the driver stated he was coming from the Reisterstown, Glen Burnie area and going toward Westminster. The deputy also advised he could detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage while interacting with the driver. The deputy also advised had asked the driver to exit the vehicle, and the driver refused. I advised the deputy I was going to give the vehicle and driver information to the barrack, and the deputy advised he would stay with the driver.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;I then made contact with the driver of the Ford Bronco and asked for her driver&amp;rsquo;s license, vehicle registration, and insurance information. The driver was identified by her Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license as Stacy Marie Little (DOB 09/05/1973 W/F). Little advised that she saw the Hyundai traveling on the right shoulder, adjacent to her vehicle and shortly after, the Hyundai struck the guardrail. Little added that as a result of the Hyundai colliding with the guardrail, the vehicle spun into her path of travel and struck her Ford Bronco on the passenger side. Due to the airbags deploying in the Ford as result of the impact, Little could not make any further observations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;After a closer examination of the Hyundai, I noted that a combination of airbags had deployed inside the vehicle. I also noted that the keys were still in the vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;After investigating the collision, I determined that the driver of the white Hyundai made an unsafe lane change on the shoulder, passed two vehicles while offroad, failed to control the Hyundai, struck the guardrail end, and struck the passenger side of the Ford Bronco as a result of the impact of the collision.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;The driver was identified by his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license as Edward Joseph Dietz Jr. (01/28/1976 W/M.)&amp;nbsp; While speaking with Dietz Jr., I observed glassy and bloodshot eyes. Dietz Jr. was seated in the driver&amp;#39;s seat of the Hyundai, smoking a freshly lit cigar. Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody, they hit me. Look at me in the road, I&amp;rsquo;m in the road. I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody, they hit me. I&amp;rsquo;m in the road. Nonononono, I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. I did not say that he did, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m in the road I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody, they hit me. Nononononah, they hit me.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. that I had asthma and did not want to cough on him, and asked that he extinguish his cigarette. Dietz Jr. complied with my request. I asked Dietz Jr. if the EMS personnel had evaluated him yet, to make sure he was okay, and Dietz Jr. did not respond. Dietz Jr. looked straight ahead and did not speak. As I continued to attempt to speak with Dietz Jr., he stated, &amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody, they hit me.&amp;rdquo; I continued to explain to Dietz Jr. I wanted to make sure he was okay and have EMS evaluate him to ensure he was not seriously injured, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t move cause he hit me.&amp;rdquo; I advised Dietz Jr. that he might have internal injuries, and I wanted EMS to, at a minimum, evaluate him on scene, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;If I was internally hurt, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be able to move. They hit me, I am not able to move. I got airbags, airbags, I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody. In the intersection, I didn&amp;rsquo;t fucking hit nobody.&amp;rdquo; As I was advising TFC Parrell of the information I had gathered, Dietz Jr. lifted the driver-side curtain airbag that had deployed and stated, &amp;ldquo;Answer me, answer me the question, you ask me a question, I&amp;rsquo;ll answer you.&amp;rdquo; I attempted to speak with Dietz Jr. again, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. where he was coming from and where he was going, to which he did not respond. I asked Dietz Jr. if he needed me to repeat the questions. I asked Dietz Jr. where he was coming from if he was coming from Westminster or headed to Westminster, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m in Westminster, where was I coming from?&amp;rdquo; I confirmed with Dietz Jr. that I asked where he was coming from, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Westminster. It&amp;#39;s fucked up cause they driving erratically. Nah, he was driving erratically, and I was driving fifty-five (55) miles an hour.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. what kind of vehicle it was that he was describing as driving erratically, Dietz Jr. hesitated, stating, &amp;ldquo;That was a Impala, nineteen ninety-eight (1998).&amp;rdquo; I confirmed with Dietz Jr. the year he stated, and he further stated, &amp;ldquo;Got it. And he driving two (2) lanes, stopped somebody, and you fucking with me, (Dietz Jr. became visibly agitated and began shouting) and you fucking with me, you have two (2) stops away, you know it, you know it!&amp;rdquo; I advised Dietz Jr. I did not know the information he just gave me until he mentioned it, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Oh, you ain&amp;rsquo;t know it, there&amp;rsquo;s two (2), there two (2) cop, there&amp;rsquo;s two (2) stops away. There&amp;rsquo;s a cop and his car, a cop driving, and he&amp;rsquo;s dirty. Oh, you don&amp;rsquo;t know that, oh you know that, there&amp;rsquo;s a cop right there. Oh, you didn&amp;rsquo;t know that.&amp;rdquo; I advised Dietz Jr. I did not know the information until he told me, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Oh, you ain&amp;rsquo;t know that. But I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody, he hit me. But I&amp;rsquo;m in the right lane, I&amp;rsquo;m in the right lane (Dietz Jr. pointed, with his left hand, out of the driver&amp;#39;s side window to the eastbound travel lane), and nobody hit me, I hit them, they hit me.&amp;rdquo; I attempted to confirm with Dietz Jr. that he was coming from Westminster, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;No, no, no, no, no, I&amp;rsquo;m in the right lane, and they hit me.&amp;rdquo; I confirmed with Dietz Jr. he was in the right lane, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Where am I at?&amp;rdquo; I advised Dietz Jr. he was in Westminster, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;And I&amp;rsquo;m in the lef&amp;hellip;, right lane, I&amp;rsquo;m in the right lane. So, you, you, you, fucking with me, and he wrapped two (2) cars ahead of you, that fucked up. You&amp;rsquo;re fucking wit me.&amp;rdquo; I attempted to speak with Dietz Jr. further; however, he interrupted me, stating, &amp;ldquo;Nah, I not answering any questions no more, you fucking go at me.&amp;rdquo; I advised Dietz Jr. I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage and asked how many alcoholic beverages he consumed, and Dietz Jr. did not respond. I asked Dietz Jr. to tell the truth, and he did not respond. I requested Dietz Jr. step out of his vehicle, to which he complied. Prior to exiting the vehicle, Dietz Jr. relit the cigarette he previously had. Once outside the vehicle, Dietz Jr. was asked to extinguish the cigarette but refused. TFC Perrell then assisted Dietz Jr. extinguish the cigarette.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;A check through the Maryland Department of Motor Vehicles revealed that Dietz Jr.&amp;rsquo;s license was valid. He did not have any open warrants.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;As I continued to communicate with Dietz Jr. outside of the vehicle, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Due to Dietz Jr.&amp;rsquo;s aggressive and argumentative behavior, Standardized Field Sobriety Testing was not administered.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Due to Dietz Jr.&amp;rsquo;s aggressive and argumentative behavior, the Preliminary Breath Test was not offered.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Based on the totality of circumstances, I concluded that Dietz Jr. was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;At fault in a two motor vehicle collision (vehicle passed two vehicles on the shoulder, struck guardrail end, and struck another vehicle as a result of striking the guardrail)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Dietz Jr.&amp;rsquo;s own statements&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Dietz Jr.s argumentative and aggressive behavior&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Refusing to exit the vehicle so that he could be evaluated by EMS personnel&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;A strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Dietz Jr.&amp;rsquo;s breath and person.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Unable to operate a vehicle safely&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;At approximately 2234 hours, I placed Dietz Jr. under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. TFC Perrell notified the barrack Dietz Jr. was placed under arrest. I informed Dietz Jr. he was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I explained to Dietz Jr. that because of his argumentative demeanor and my observations of him stumbling while exiting his vehicle, standardized field sobriety was not conducted. I asked Dietz Jr. if he had a cell phone he wanted to bring with him because he would have the opportunity to make a phone call later, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;In the car.&amp;rdquo; I advised Dietz Jr. I needed his cooperation for the rest of the process, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes, sir.&amp;rdquo; I continued to explain to Dietz Jr. that he would need to cooperate with me throughout the rest of the process, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, sir.&amp;rdquo; Prior to walking Dietz Jr. back to my patrol vehicle, Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Officer, officer, I&amp;rsquo;m, I&amp;rsquo;m, I&amp;rsquo;m para, I&amp;rsquo;m paranoid, and I&amp;rsquo;m about to flip out., can you take me, and just, whatever you gotta do.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. if he would feel comfortable in my patrol vehicle, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes, sir.&amp;rdquo; While walking Dietz Jr. to my patrol vehicle, he stated, &amp;ldquo;They hit me, sir, I didn&amp;rsquo;t do anything, you see that, you see the accident, I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody. It hurt me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody. Officer, I never would hurt somebody, that&amp;rsquo;s my job. They hit me. I&amp;rsquo;m being honest. It was nothin&amp;rsquo; I did, he hit me &amp;#39;cause they was trying to go fast. I did nothing, motherfuckers hit me.&amp;rdquo; Once at the front of my patrol vehicle, I explained to Dietz Jr. he was going to be searched, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody, they hit me. I have no guns, I have nothing. Camera, I&amp;rsquo;m telling the truth.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz the front camera in my patrol vehicle was activated, following departmental policy, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;You can do it all you want, I&amp;rsquo;m telling the motherfuckers hit me, I ain&amp;rsquo;t going nowhere, I was just going around a loop.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Dietz Jr. was searched his person for weapons and contraband, both with negative results. While conducting the search incident to arrest of Dietz Jr., I removed his baseball hat, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Keep my hat on, I&amp;rsquo;m cold.&amp;rdquo; I assured Dietz Jr. he would have his hat back, and I continued the search. Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t give a fuck if it&amp;rsquo;s New York, I&amp;rsquo;m cold.&amp;rdquo; I informed Dietz Jr. it would not be long, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;No. Put my hat on I&amp;rsquo;m cold. I didn&amp;rsquo;t do shit, man, I didn&amp;rsquo;t do nothing.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. if he remembered what was explained to him when he exited his vehicle, and he continued to have an aggressive and argumentative demeanor, stating, &amp;ldquo;I got out the car, I don&amp;hellip;, fuck that, fuck that.&amp;rdquo; I informed Dietz Jr. he would be taken to jail, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t care neither motherfucker. Fuck you.&amp;rdquo; TFC Perrell instructed Dietz Jr. to look away from me, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll look away from him, fucking hurt me. That don&amp;rsquo;t hurt me bitch, that don&amp;rsquo;t hurt me. I ain&amp;#39;t do nothing, I didn&amp;rsquo;t do nothing.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. to start over in an effort to de-escalate his behavior, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;You can start over all you want, I ain&amp;rsquo;t do nothing. I ain&amp;rsquo;t got nothin on me. Take my handcuffs off, take the handcuffs off me.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. I was not going to remove the handcuffs, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;You with God right bitch, I ain&amp;rsquo;t got nothing on me, take my pants down if you want.&amp;rdquo; I informed Dietz Jr. I would not be doing that, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Work, &amp;#39;cause I don&amp;rsquo;t like my ass out. This motherfucker, come on, man.&amp;rdquo; There were two (2) dollar bills in Dietz Jr.&amp;rsquo;s pants pocket, I began counting the money in front of Dietz Jr., and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Two (2) dollars, two (2) dollars. Where am I going, nowhere. You holding me, there&amp;rsquo;s no reason for you holding me. You got the camera on record, alright, then keep it rolling. I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody, I&amp;rsquo;m in my fucking lane.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. to take a step back, off the front bumper of my patrol vehicle, and he stated, There you go. I&amp;rsquo;m a fucking thug, right? No reason to fucking search me, you don&amp;rsquo;t even have a protocol to search me.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. that because he was under arrest, he was being searched, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m under arrest, no reason to search me, cause I never hit nobody, they hit me. It&amp;rsquo;s called a search, and it&amp;rsquo;s wrong. Imma let you know that right off my bat. Are your cameras recording?&amp;rdquo; I assured Dietz Jr. the cameras were recording, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I hate nobody. Nononono, Imma search you, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna search you. Officer, I didn&amp;rsquo;t do nothing. I didn&amp;rsquo;t do nothing. I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody, hit me.&amp;rdquo; While conducting the search incident to arrest, I observed the groin area of Dietz Jr.&amp;rsquo;s pants to be wet to the touch from urine.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRANSPORT TO BARRACK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Dietz Jr. was escorted to the passenger side of my patrol vehicle, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Imma go in, you don&amp;rsquo;t got to push me.&amp;rdquo; It was explained to Dietz Jr. he was not being pushed. Once seated in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle, Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes, sir. Can you loosen this up a little bit? This hurts me.&amp;rdquo; While attempting to instruct Dietz Jr. on how to sit in the front seat of my patrol vehicle, he stated, &amp;ldquo;Dude, I&amp;rsquo;m not hurtin&amp;rsquo; nobody, I ain&amp;rsquo;t do nothing. Officer, officer, can I see your name, please?&amp;rdquo; I informed Dietz Jr. my name was Mills, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Mills, I ain&amp;#39;t hurt nobody Mills.&amp;rdquo; I instructed Dietz Jr. to sit forward in the seat in an effort to have him seated comfortably, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Dude, I&amp;rsquo;m in my lane. Even in my lane I was in my lane.&amp;rdquo; I instructed Dietz Jr. to scoot forward in the seat again, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Officer, can you please I would never hurt nobody officer.&amp;rdquo; I instructed Dietz Jr. on how to sit in the seat, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t, officer, it hurts, officer I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t hurt nobody.&amp;rdquo; I put the seatbelt on Dietz Jr., and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Officer, that hurts.&amp;rdquo; I explained I wanted him to be safe, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Officer, Officer, a little link in this handcuffs.&amp;rdquo; I explained I could not adjust the handcuffs, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Officer, I can&amp;rsquo;t even move. Imma asking you, officer, one link.&amp;rdquo; I explained I could not adjust the handcuffs, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Dude, I not going nowhere, not going nowhere. Put it in front of me.&amp;rdquo; I stepped to the front of my patrol vehicle to retrieve Dietz Jr.&amp;rsquo;s personal belongings, and he began to state, &amp;ldquo;Officer, can I take a picture? Can I take a picture because this is wrong?&amp;rdquo; I informed Dietz Jr. what of his personal belongings I had and where I was putting them, Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Can you, can you loosen these up, please?&amp;rdquo; I explained I could not adjust the handcuffs again. Dietz Jr. then stated, &amp;ldquo;Well look, look, I didn&amp;rsquo;t create no accident they hit me. I was in my lane. So obviously, you are incarcerating me for no reason. I was in my lane.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. he would have an opportunity in court to make that argument, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Court for is the reality.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;As I began to transport Dietz Jr. to the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack for processing, he stated, &amp;ldquo;I ain&amp;rsquo;t gon let this go, I&amp;rsquo;m a tell you this shit right now, I hit nobody, they hit me. They don&amp;rsquo;t know how to drive. I&amp;rsquo;m a professional driver I drive forty-five (45) miles an hour in a fifty-five (55). I don&amp;rsquo;t give a fuck how fast they drive! And I never hit nobody, you have any camera, you have any proof to prove me wrong, no, I hit nobody. If they wanna go fast in a forty-five (45), that&amp;rsquo;s their problem. I hit ain&amp;rsquo;t nobody, tell me I hit somebody. they hit me. I&amp;rsquo;m in my right lane. I see my car. Can I take a picture of my car? Stop for a second, officer! Take a picture of my car.&amp;rdquo; I attempted to explain pictures of the vehicles would be taken, but Dietz Jr. shouted over me, stating, &amp;ldquo;No nnnnnoooo, stop for a second officer, take a picture of my car.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. he was not in charge of the situation, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna be charged cuz I ain&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody, they hit me. I was in behind they hit me. Officer, can I get a picture of this accident, please? Just, I don&amp;rsquo;t have any money, officer. I&amp;rsquo;m fucking fucked up, my wife wants to leave me I don&amp;rsquo;t have any more money, officer. If you think I did anything wrong, I didn&amp;rsquo;t do anything wrong (Dietz Jr. began crying). I explained to Dietz Jr. that he just made a statement about being wrong, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;That doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody they hit me. If they&amp;rsquo;re driving sixty-five (65) miles an hour in a fucking fifty-five (55), it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matta.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr., as I had done before, that we are both humans trying to get through the situation, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;What are you gonna, you&amp;rsquo;ll, you&amp;rsquo;ll figure it out, a person driving 65 on a fifty-five (55), you&amp;rsquo;re gonna, they&amp;rsquo;re gonna to hurt you. I have no reason to drive fast. I&amp;rsquo;m going home. I live twenty (20) miles away, there&amp;rsquo;s no reason for me to drive fast.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. if we could talk like men, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Do you want to talk like men? A man is this, I hit nobody. That&amp;rsquo;s my man. How are you gonna hit me and tell me I&amp;rsquo;m wrong? &amp;lsquo;Cause I&amp;rsquo;m driving forty-five (45). And they think it&amp;rsquo;s okay, that&amp;rsquo;s not right. I was driving forty-five (45) miles an hour. And you want to hit me &amp;#39;cause you think I&amp;rsquo;m not driving fast. I don&amp;rsquo;t drive fast, I&amp;rsquo;m going home. Why you drive fast when you go home, no reason.&amp;rdquo; I explained there was a cause of what happened and that I was just trying to understand what that cause was, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;You tell me the underlying cause, officer, obviously, the person hit me because I was driving forty-five (45) miles an hour. Officer, I don&amp;rsquo;t drive faster than that. I&amp;rsquo;m going home. Why the fuck would I drive faster than fifty-five (55) on fifty-five (55) when I&amp;rsquo;m going home, twenty (20) miles. Makes no sense they want to get by me, they want to hit me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody. You can see my car, And you going to see the, the scription on it when it prints out. I hit nobody, they hit me. I don&amp;rsquo;t deal with traffic like that, they want to race around it, they race around it, that&amp;rsquo;s not who I am. Just not, I ain&amp;rsquo;t trying to hurt nobody, I don&amp;rsquo;t hurt nobody, it&amp;rsquo;s not who I am, I just drive. Fuckers wanna hit me to hit me, you gon see it, you gon see impact on the ticket. You gon see the impact, I hit nobody. Remember what I&amp;rsquo;m saying to you &amp;lsquo;cause you gon see the impact, cause I hit nobody. And I want that documentioned, documentioned, docker, what the fuck am I, dockermentioned, cause I hit nobody. Forty-five (45) in a fifty-five (55) is not illegal ten (10) miles below the spear limit means that, no, look, I don&amp;rsquo;t drive fast, I can&amp;rsquo;t see, that&amp;rsquo;s all it means. I fucking drivin&amp;rsquo; safe in a fuckin&amp;rsquo; dark zone, that&amp;rsquo;s fucked up. Guardless of what the fuck had happened, I didn&amp;rsquo;t drive fast, and I don&amp;rsquo;t drive fast because I don&amp;rsquo;t like to drive fast, it&amp;rsquo;s not my character. They wanna hit me, so I&amp;rsquo;m fucking to blame. You wanna, you better check their stats on that camera, on that car that hit me in the back, I swear to God, Imma keep promotin&amp;rsquo; this,&amp;nbsp; I never did nothing I was driving straight, and he hit me in the back. Never drive fast. Nowhere to go, I&amp;rsquo;m going home. Fucked up, man. I&amp;rsquo;m sitting in handcuffs, I did something, and the mother fucker hit me. And you know he hit me, you know he hit me, right? Tell me! (Dietz Jr. shouted) Officer, did he hit me or not? you have to answer this question, did he hit me or not?&amp;rdquo; I attempted to explain to Dietz Jr. the answer to his question, but he began talking over me, stating, &amp;ldquo;Officer, did he hit me or not?&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. that I was not going to answer his question because he continued to talk over me, and he shouted, &amp;ldquo;You have to answer! It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter, the law says you have to answer. Did he hit me or not? He hit me. I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit him, he hit me.&amp;rdquo; I attempted to explain to Dietz Jr. that if he stopped yelling, I would talk to him, but he again interrupted me and stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not yelling at you, officer, I&amp;rsquo;m being direct. Officer, I would never yell at you I respect your position, I respect what you do. Officer, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trained in the military, I went to war, just not, it&amp;rsquo;s not labeled. I went to war.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. how many years he was in the military, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Two years, officer, I killed many people, I&amp;rsquo;m not legit, they don&amp;rsquo;t label me, I do what I do.&amp;rdquo; I expressed my appreciation for his service to Dietz Jr. and explained we are on the same team, Dietz Jr. then stated, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t have a team, I&amp;rsquo;m a soldier, there&amp;rsquo;s no team. Somebody hits me you need to respect that, I ain&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. what branch of the military he was in, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;One ninty-two (192).&amp;rdquo; I explained I did not have military experience and asked what branch of the military he meant, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Air Force.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. what his MOU was, and he mumbled incoherently and then stated, &amp;ldquo; Sir, I train people to kill, you know that, sir? I ain&amp;rsquo;t never hit nobody, he hit me in the back. I train people to kill, sir.&amp;rdquo; I again asked Dietz Jr. what his MOU was, and he stated, &amp;ldquo; MOU is not labeled, I&amp;rsquo;m a trainer, I train soldiers to kill. It&amp;rsquo;s not labeled, sir. You&amp;rsquo;re gonna get a call, you&amp;rsquo;re gonna get a call from the FBI, you&amp;rsquo;ll get a call. I&amp;rsquo;m not labeled.&amp;rdquo; I asked who I should expect a call from, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Mr. McGuire.&amp;rdquo; I asked if that was his supervisor, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;No. He&amp;rsquo;s the police comm., police commissioner of New York State. I did nothing, I had nobody. I got hit, and I&amp;rsquo;m being charged for no reason. You telling me what I&amp;rsquo;m charged for?&amp;rdquo; I explained I told him what he was arrested for when I put the handcuffs on him, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Nononono, no, what did you tell me I was charged for?&amp;rdquo; I explained he was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol. Dietz Jr. then stated, &amp;ldquo;DUI? I hit nobody.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. he was still placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;It don&amp;rsquo;t matter, but I hit nobody. Tell me what I&amp;rsquo;m charged for, tell me all the charges.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. about the Bronco and the guardrail he hit, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t have a Bronco, I have a fucking hyndai elantra.&amp;rdquo; I again asked about the Bronco that he hit, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I hit no, bronco, he hit me cause I was doing forty-five (45) miles an hour, in the back. Look at my, look at my car, he hit me in the back. Look at it, on the right side, on the rear bumper, on the right side. Fuck his Bronco. I hit nobody I drive forty-five (45) miles an hour going home. it&amp;rsquo;s wrong. do you want to drive sixty-five (65), seventy (70) miles an hour, he was wrong, check his, check his car, you have the stats in his car. That&amp;rsquo;s easy. so easy. he was driving seventy (70) miles an hour, officer, on a fifty-five (55), and clip me, and wanna blame me for this shit. That&amp;rsquo;s wrong, it&amp;rsquo;s OK though, officer, I got, I got, I got people. I&amp;rsquo;m pissed off, though, I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody, I&amp;rsquo;m driving straight, and I am, you saw my car though I&amp;rsquo;m in my lane, I&amp;rsquo;m in my lane. I&amp;rsquo;m in my fucking lane, and these mother, this fuc, fuckers hit me in the right side. It&amp;rsquo;s a merge area, and he hits me in the right side. I&amp;rsquo;m doing forty-five (45) miles an hour, he can&amp;rsquo;t accept I&amp;rsquo;m doing forty-five (45). Fuck him. You gon see his, you gon see it, because his car has an impact camera, it has impact camera, it tells the speed, it gone tell you I was driving forty-five (45). I did everything I was supposed to, my wife trains, you officers. I did everything I was supposed to do, officer. My wife trains you guys every day, trains are you CIT officers? I did nothing wrong. I just want you, I just want you give me the benefit of the doubt. I don&amp;rsquo;t care if I&amp;rsquo;m going to jail, I did nothing wrong, officer.&amp;rdquo; I explained I was trying to help him and that I did not want him to go to jail, Dietz Jr. then stated, &amp;ldquo;Honestly, though, officer, I&amp;rsquo;m suicidal, I don&amp;rsquo;t give a fuck about this life. But I would never hurt nobody, that&amp;rsquo;s who I am. I&amp;rsquo;m willing to die for somebody else, But I would never hurt somebody, never! They hit me. That&amp;rsquo;s the honest truth I would never hurt somebody. I&amp;rsquo;ve safe so many people, put my life on the line, you don&amp;rsquo;t even know, bro. Think that this is a job, I&amp;rsquo;ve been shot at, they try to stab me, they try to kill me, and yet I still protected them mother fuckers that didn&amp;rsquo;t have nothing. But yet I&amp;rsquo;m a white mother fucker, they dont care about me. Du, where you going, dog the fucking barracks is right here on one forty (140), where you going? I want all my stats on all the car, I&amp;rsquo;ma tell you that right now. I did nothing wrong. Somebody hit me from the back automatically, it&amp;rsquo;s that person that hit me in the back&amp;#39;s fault, you hear me? You got the camera running? Officer, do you have a camera running?&amp;rdquo; I explained that is what the red light was, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Ain&amp;rsquo;t no red light on, on that officer.&amp;rdquo; I pointed out the red light, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s on the top. That&amp;rsquo;s a speed camera, that&amp;rsquo;s not a red light on a camera.&amp;rdquo; I explained it was a camera, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t tell me the truth, don&amp;rsquo;t tell me a lie. You&amp;rsquo;re lying to me.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. that if he looked to the right, he would see a camera, Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I look to my right, I see a fucking car on the right.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. to look up, not out the window, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;You still arresting me for doing nothing wrong, officer are you still arresting me for doing nothing wrong officer, I hit nobody. You illegally arrested me, bro, you know that, right?&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. that is what court is for, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Nonononono, no, that&amp;rsquo;s not for court. You illegally arrested me for no reason. Put me in handcuffs for no reason. I got me in this car talking to you shit, so you can get me say something that I ain&amp;rsquo;t do. For somebody hit me, I&amp;rsquo;m driving forty-five (45) miles an hour. When you see the camera, and you see their footage, and you see the speed limit they were going, then you understand I do a fucking thing. Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m pissed off, I don&amp;rsquo;t give a fuck you got me in handcuffs for no reason, you shoulda took the motherfucker in front of me. Take the motherfucker that was in front of me, that was there, who hit me. Take &amp;lsquo;em! You won&amp;#39;t take him right, he hit me, but you won&amp;rsquo;t take him.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Once at the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack, I escorted Dietz Jr. inside the building. As I escorted him into the barracks, he stated, &amp;ldquo;You see the reports, I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody. I&amp;rsquo;m in the back they hit me.&amp;rdquo; As the door was opened for Dietz Jr. to walk through, stopped and stated, &amp;ldquo;I know the law hold up, officer officer what&amp;rsquo;s your name, Officer Mills? Did you get the camera footage? Officer Mills. Officer Mills, did you get the camera footage?&amp;rdquo; Dietz Jr. was taken to the DUI procession room, and a secondary search of his person was conducted by Sgt. Smith #2927, per Maryland State Police Policy and Procedures. While Sgt. Smith was explaining the procedures to Dietz Jr., Dietz Jr. became argumentative and stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing this since I was fucking fourteen (14), I&amp;rsquo;ve been shot at, they stab me. You wanna see my stab wounds? They hit me in the back, I did nothing.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained that it did not matter because he was arrested for driving under the influence, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;It don&amp;rsquo;t matter. No, it don&amp;rsquo;t, no, it don&amp;rsquo;t. I break no law by drinking. I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody they hit me in the back.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained he was not going to argue with him, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;You can argue all you want. I&amp;rsquo;ma tell you the truth.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained he appreciated being told the truth. Dietz Jr. then stated, &amp;ldquo;They hit me in the back, you gonna pull up the footage?&amp;rdquo; Sgt Smith further explained that once the processing was completed, he would be released from the Barrack, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;No, I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna get out of here because they hit me in the back. I want, I want, I want a lawsuit because he hit me in the back.&amp;rdquo; Sgt Smith explained if he wanted a lawsuit, that was fine, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I want a lawsuit. He hit me in the back&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith continued to attempt to explain the process, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;#39;m not going to refuse, but what I&amp;rsquo;m saying is he hit me in the back, officer. I had no, I hit nobody in the front. My car is not merged in the front. He hit me in the back. Officer, I just want this, no disrespect to you or your fellow officer, what I want, can you put this on paper? I hit nobody he hit me in the back, on the right side, and you&amp;rsquo;ll see where he sideswiped me, that&amp;rsquo;s it. I didn&amp;rsquo;t drive fast, I was driving forty-five (45).&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith attempted to explain further, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Honestly, officer, how many times you&amp;rsquo;ve been drinking and been intoxicated, don&amp;rsquo;t fuck with me. Both of all been drunk and driving.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith attempted to talk to Dietz Jr., and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t care, I didn&amp;rsquo;t drive drunk he hit me in the back.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained he was not concerned about the collision, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;The accident, he hit me in the back because he was driving fast. And you can see, you gonna pull it up?&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith again explained he was not concerned about the collision, that he was concerned about the DUI process, Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll sit down, I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, sir. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, sir.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained the process would go faster if he did not argue, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m just mad because he hit me in the back, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t do anything. I&amp;rsquo;m sorr&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t want to get out of here I want revenge. I want vindication, he hit me in the back.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Sgt. Smith explained that I would be going over paperwork with him, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I hit nobody. If he hit me in the back, then I&amp;rsquo;m right. I don&amp;rsquo;t care it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if I was drunk if he hit me in the back, I was right. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter.&amp;rdquo; As Sgt. Smith left the room, Dietz Jr. continued to state, &amp;ldquo;He hit me in the back, I&amp;rsquo;m a keep I&amp;rsquo;m a keep saying that. He hit me in the back, on my right side, and you&amp;rsquo;ll see the damage. It was a 4 x 4, and he hit me in the back because he was driving fast.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;I explained we were going to move on with the processing in an effort to get him home, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not going home. I want revenge, he hit me in the back because he was a asshole, I want revenge. Can you do that for me, officer? At least if I&amp;rsquo;m A E, look, I am drunk, I don&amp;rsquo;t give a fuck, but he hit me in the back. I don&amp;rsquo;t drive fast, he hit me in the back, he was mad because I didn&amp;rsquo;t drive fast. It was a 4 x 4, it is brown-black, I saw it on the side of the road.&amp;rdquo; I explained I was concentrating on completing paperwork, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I am, I am, I&amp;rsquo;m, I&amp;rsquo;m not trying to disrespect you, officer, but Mr. Mills, he hit me in the back, sir. I was in my lane, you saw my car, in my lane, he hit me in the back, sideswiped me on the right.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. how long he and his wife had been married, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Do you really care, or are you just asking questions to see if I&amp;rsquo;m coherent?&amp;rdquo; I explained that I actually cared, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Twelve (12) years.&amp;rdquo; I asked where they met, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;New York.&amp;rdquo; I asked if she was a New York Yankees fan as well, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I guess so.&amp;rdquo; I asked if she was a Boston fan, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Fuck the Bostons (Dietz Jr. laughed).&amp;rdquo; I told Dietz Jr. I am an Orioles fan and that the Yankees have Aaron Judge, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Judge is just a judge, he&amp;#39;s just a man. The team don&amp;rsquo;t wanna pay for the man. That&amp;rsquo;s why the, that&amp;rsquo;s why the Baltimore not good, they don&amp;rsquo;t wanna pay for the mound. They got rid of aa, what&amp;rsquo;s his name, machinnee, they got rid of uh, uh, so many other cats that were uh, uh, really good on the O&amp;rsquo;s.&amp;rdquo; I explained I lost interest when the team lost Machato, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Machato, there ya go, because they can&amp;rsquo;t pay him, why? So, they go out, get all these good stars for a year, and can&amp;rsquo;t pay &amp;lsquo;em. That was just like the Yankees, they had a good third baseman, but if you can&amp;rsquo;t get home runs, but in all reality, they can get rid of you. That&amp;rsquo;s every good job, if you ain&amp;rsquo;t, if you ain&amp;rsquo;t getting tickets and ain&amp;rsquo;t putting that clamoring and you ain&amp;rsquo;t putting that every month, what do you need to get in, you gon lose your job. It is what it is. It&amp;rsquo;s just like me, if I&amp;rsquo;m not making more, I&amp;rsquo;m a lose my house.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. what he did for work, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Nah, I don&amp;rsquo;t drive, I&amp;rsquo;mma, uh, I drive in a parking lot I do a, um, parking lots I don&amp;rsquo;t drive in the streets, I don&amp;rsquo;t like to.&amp;rdquo; I asked what company he worked for, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I work for my friend who owns a company and park his trucks in the yard. I haven&amp;rsquo;t had an accident all my life. I never hit nobody. I want you to know that. they hit me in the back I never hit nobody, never had an accident in my whole life. Somebody wanna sideswiped me, that&amp;rsquo;s not my fault, officer. You better, I swear to God, I want the car that was in front of me, you know what car that was. It was a Toyota. That&amp;rsquo;s why I wanted my phone so I could take pictures of this shit, but you didn&amp;rsquo;t take pictures of the car in front of me. Did you?&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. that there were multiple investigators on the scene and that we all work together, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;But you&amp;rsquo;re charging me for no reason, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody they hit me. So because I was the only car that was stopped, and the other car was on the left side of the hand, on the shoulder, I&amp;rsquo;m the one that&amp;rsquo;s going to be blamed for this?&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. that in the State of Maryland, you can not drive intoxicated, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if I was intoxicated, somebody hit me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;I explained to Dietz Jr. that I had some questions for him to fill out the necessary paperwork, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t want to answer your questions until I have a lawyer here right now, because of the fact you&amp;rsquo;re trying to charge me some for something I didn&amp;rsquo;t do. Because somebody hit me in the back, so I&amp;rsquo;m in the right, I want a lawyer. Do you understand that?&amp;rdquo; I asked how old he was, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Forty-seven (47).&amp;rdquo; I began to ask Dietz Jr. another question, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Did you get my wallet, so I can have my, my lawyer on hand?&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. where in his wallet his lawyer&amp;rsquo;s information was, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;In the middle place.&amp;rdquo; I confirmed what Dietz Jr. said by repeating it back to him, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes, there somewhere in the middle.&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. what his lawyer&amp;rsquo;s name was, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know his name, dog, (Dietz Jr. mumbled incoherently) You pay him a certain amount of money a month and they stand up for you. That&amp;rsquo;s OK, I&amp;rsquo;ll get them. I got a phone call, right? Officer.&amp;rdquo; I explained he would be able to make a phone call when we were done going through the paperwork, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Nah, I want a lawsuit officer. He hit me in the back officer.&amp;rdquo; I explained he could handle the lawsuit at a later time, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Nah, Nahnahnah, nah, I want a file a official report, officer, he hit me in the back.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr.&amp;nbsp; I was completing a report, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re not doing a report, you&amp;rsquo;re playing games.&amp;rdquo; I explained I was not playing games, I was completing a report, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Mr. Mills, I&amp;rsquo;m looking at you, you&amp;rsquo;re lying to me, Mr. Mills.&amp;rdquo; I pointed to the paper I was filling out and indicated to Dietz Jr. the case number for the report, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;So where is the fact that he hit me in the back, Mr. Mills.&amp;rdquo; I explained there was a process that we had to go through, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I was in my lane, Mr. Mills. So get the cameras on the scene that show me I was in my lane, Mr. Mills.&amp;rdquo; I advised Dietz Jr. he mentioned earlier that he was drunk, and I asked him where he consumed the alcohol he had that night, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t say I was drunk, never said I was drunk, what the fuck you talking about?&amp;rdquo; I asked Dietz Jr. where he consumed the alcohol he had that night, and he did not respond, I noted that he was refusing to say, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Refused to say, no, I want a lawyer. Tell me that, tell me what I said, I want a lawyer. Not I refuse to say I want a lawyer. You hear me?&amp;rdquo; I ensured Dietz Jr. that what he said was documented, and he shouted, &amp;ldquo;I want a lawyer. Imma scream it loud, dog.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. that I could hear him, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re wrong for denying me. Your camera on, put your camera on.&amp;rdquo; I ensured him my body camera was on and pointed to it, Dietz Jr. looked at the camera and stated, &amp;ldquo;He&amp;rsquo;s denying me a lawyer, he&amp;rsquo;s breaking my rights. I asked you for a lawyer. Did you get my lawyer?&amp;rdquo; I attempted to explain what I was doing, and Dietz Jr. interrupted, stating, &amp;ldquo;Did I, I asked you for a lawyer, did you get my lawyer? You&amp;rsquo;re breaking my rights.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;I placed a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights on the table next to Dietz Jr. and explained that I would be reading the form, in its entirety, to him. Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;You can read it to me all you want, if I don&amp;rsquo;t have a lawyer, it&amp;rsquo;s def., it&amp;rsquo;s in invalid. Gimme a lawyer. That that document doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean nothing to me cause I ain&amp;rsquo;t signing it. Gimme a lawyer. I know my rights. Back up off me.&amp;rdquo; I explained to Dietz Jr. I was going to begin reading the form, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;And you can read it to me all you want, I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna listen. Don&amp;rsquo;t read it to me, (Dietz Jr.mumbled incoherently) wait.&amp;rdquo; I explained that I was not going to wait, that I was going to read the form, and he started, &amp;ldquo;All right, so I&amp;rsquo;m gonna conflict you on this whole thing you said to me.&amp;rdquo; As I began reading the DR-15 Advice of Rights to Dietz Jr., he stated, &amp;ldquo;No, no, no, no, they hit me in the back. You&amp;rsquo;re lying. No. I want a lawyer. You didn&amp;rsquo;t give me a lawyer, you violated my rights. You&amp;rsquo;re violating my rights. You ain&amp;rsquo;t give me a lawyer. I asked for a lawyer, and you didn&amp;rsquo;t give me a lawyer.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;At this point, Sgt. Smith re-entered the room and attempted to explain the process to Dietz Jr., but Dietz Jr. interrupted him, shouting, &amp;ldquo;Gimme a lawyer. I asked for a lawyer.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained we are not required to give him a lawyer at this point, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes, you do, I know my rights! You can hit me all you want I know my rights.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained he was not hitting him and asked him to stop being uncooperative, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna stop being anything. I know my rights. Do you understand me I&amp;rsquo;m forty-seven (47) years old, I am not your son.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith asked Dietz Jr. to stop being uncooperative, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Stop being a prick, somebody hit me in the back.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained he understood the situation and that I was trying to process him, and Dietz Jr. interrupted him, stating, &amp;ldquo;You know, you know, you know, Mr. Mills, you know he hit me in the back, Mr. Mills, you know. Do you know?&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith advised he knew, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Mr. Smith, he hit me in the back.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained it did not matter, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m doing forty-five (45) he&amp;rsquo;s doing sixty (60), seventy-five (75), and hit me in the back.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained I was trying to read the paperwork to him, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I want to check his car.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith advised him he was not going to check his car, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Whatchu mean you&amp;rsquo;re not gonna check his car I&amp;rsquo;ma get a lawyer. And I&amp;rsquo;m gonna fucking sue you, and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna sue him. You ain&amp;rsquo;t do, you didn&amp;rsquo;t do your, you didn&amp;rsquo;t do your dill diligence.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained to Dietz Jr. that he was being recorded on both my camera and his, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes, sir, I know it.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith further explained there was a third camera, the one in the DUI Processing room, and Dietz Jr. looked up at the camera in the corner of the room and stated, &amp;ldquo; A ya, a, listen, I want a lawyer. I have no more questions to answer. If I don&amp;rsquo;t get a lawyer, they&amp;rsquo;re violating my rights.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained I was going to continue to read the paperwork, and in the end, he could refuse the test or not, and he would be asked to sign the paperwork, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna sign nothing. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna say this right now. He hit me in the back. I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna listen to you.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith attempted to explain I was going to continue reading the paperwork, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t care. I don&amp;rsquo;t care I&amp;rsquo;m handcuffed. It don&amp;rsquo;t even matter.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;I resumed reading the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I want a lawyer, I want a lawyer, I want a lawyer, I want a lawyer, I want a lawyer, I want a lawyer! You cannot ask me no questions if I ask a lawyer. Do you answer that? (Dietz Jr. turned his head and started talking to Sgt. Smith) He knows that, he&amp;rsquo;s violating my privileges. I want a lawyer.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith indicated to Dietz Jr. he needed to pay attention to the form I was reading, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;If I refusal a test because somebody hit me in the back and I ask for a lawyer, and nobody&amp;rsquo;s answering my questions. Officer, can I get a lawyer? You violated, you violated my privileges. I&amp;rsquo;m not a black man. I know my rights. (Dietz Jr. began shouting) I&amp;rsquo;m not a black man. I know my fucking rights.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained to Dietz Jr. it did not matter what color he was, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Yeah, it does, it does, it does, Mr. Smith, it does, you fucking hillbilly, fuck you. I hit nobody, they hit me. I did nothing wrong. I hit nobody they hit me. I wanna lawyer. Give me a lawyer. I have no questions to answer. I want a lawyer. you are violating my rights. I&amp;rsquo;m asked for a lawyer 5 to 6 times, if you don&amp;rsquo;t give me a lawyer, everything you&amp;rsquo;re doing right now is violating, do you understand that right now? All right, but I hit nobody they hit me, so what now? If I hit nobody and they hit me, tell me, tell me what the law is when they hit me. Tell me what the law is when they hit me. Officer, you tell me a bunch of bullshit, you reading some bullshit. Tell me what happens when the motherfucker hits me. Fuck outta here with your bullshit, you can keep reading that shit, I never hurt anything cause I want a lawyer, so I hurt nothing cause I want a lawyer. I want a lawyer. Lawyer, lawyer, lawyer, I know my rights, you&amp;rsquo;re violating them. You are violating my rights. You are violating my rights. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter about a test you didn&amp;rsquo;t stop nobody else on that accident scene, the motherfucker who hit me, you didn&amp;rsquo;t even fucking brought him in, you took me, but you didn&amp;rsquo;t brought him in. I want a lawyer, I got hit in the back in my car. I want to lawyer, you&amp;rsquo;re violating my privileges. You can you can keep reading that shit. You are a trainee learning the system, which you&amp;rsquo;re violating my rights, you should know better, dog. Mr. Mills, you should know better, Mr. Smith is telling you wrong cause he knows better. He knows that if I say I need a lawyer, you&amp;rsquo;ve got to stop.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith indicated to Dietz Jr. he needed to pay attention to the form I was reading, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Am I wrong?&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained he was wrong and that he needed to pay attention to the form I was reading, Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;ve got to read me my rights, you&amp;rsquo;ve got to read me my Miranda.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained we did not, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Oh, you don&amp;rsquo;t, oh you don&amp;rsquo;t know.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith indicated the form I was reading was his rights and that he should pay attention to what I was reading, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Really? You&amp;rsquo;re lying. I&amp;rsquo;m not fucking stupid, you&amp;rsquo;re lying. You&amp;rsquo;re a liar. Look at my eyes and tell me you&amp;rsquo;re a liar.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained he was not lying, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re lying, you&amp;#39;re a fucking liar. I&amp;rsquo;m looking in eyes, you tell me you fucking lying or not, you&amp;rsquo;re a liar. Oh man, you can&amp;rsquo;t even look at me straight because you lying. What the fuck you reading a hundred-fifty money order for? Just tell me, dude, I have the right to remain silent, I have the right to an attorney, I have the right to make my case before the judge, not before you and him. Motherfuckers piss me off. I&amp;rsquo;ma sit back because I will fuck both you up, I&amp;rsquo;ma sit back. I&amp;rsquo;ma sit back you&amp;rsquo;re violating my rights I&amp;rsquo;ma keep saying this shit. I want a lawyer, and you have denying me of my lawyer. I asked you three times, officer, for a lawyer and you violating my rights. Three times and you keep reading that shit, you should&amp;rsquo;ve stopped, you should&amp;rsquo;ve stopped when I asked you for a lawyer. You fucked up, you fucked up. And Mr. Smith has taught you wrong you fucked up, you both fucked up, you know that, right? (Dietz Jr. mumbled incoherently) was in the system, they fucked up, that&amp;rsquo;s really fucked up, cause I don&amp;rsquo;t hurt nobody. I go to work every day, I help people, I give them food, I do what I do. You fucked up, you really fucked up, you violated my rights, you really fucked up. I want a lawyer you can stop reading this shit. If I ask for a lawyer, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to read no more. Do you hear me? Officer Mills, I asked for a lawyer, you stop, I asked for a lawyer, you keep reading Officer Mills, you&amp;rsquo;re a fucking rookie.&amp;rdquo; I finished reading the form and asked Dietz Jr. if he wished to take the test, Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t res&amp;hellip;, I didn&amp;rsquo;t refuse to no test, I want a lawyer, that&amp;rsquo;s it.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Sgt. Smith explained he was the Duty Officer, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t care, I want a lawyer, no, no, shut up. Shut up I want a lawyer. Shut up. I want a lawyer. I know my rights.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith asked Dietz Jr. if he had an attorney he wanted to call, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes, sir, it&amp;rsquo;s in my wallet!&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith asked Dietz Jr. for the name of his attorney, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;If I look at my wallet, I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained to Dietz Jr. he was under arrest and could not have his wallet, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;OK, I&amp;rsquo;m not under arrest, I did nothing wrong. I did nothing wrong. I&amp;#39;m not under arrest.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith asked for permission to go into Dietz Jr.&amp;#39;s wallet to retrieve his attorney&amp;rsquo;s information, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I did nothing wrong, tell me what I did wrong. I hit nobody they hit me.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained to Dietz Jr. he had been read the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and Dietz Jr. interrupted him and stated, &amp;ldquo;I have been arrested for what, for what? For hitting somebody, no, they hit me in the back.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained he was arrested for driving while intoxicated, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter, they hit me in the back.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained he was in the room to conduct the test if he wanted to take it, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I want a lawyer, I&amp;rsquo;m not taking a test, I want a lawyer.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained the test would be marked as a refusal, and Dietz Jr. continued to state, &amp;ldquo;It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter, I want a lawyer.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith again asked for permission to go into his wallet for the attorney&amp;rsquo;s information, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I want a lawyer.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained the state does not appoint a lawyer until the case is in court, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;What? You&amp;rsquo;re lying to me. What the fuck you talking about the state afford a lawyer (incoherent mumbling) the fuck you lying about. What the fuck I don&amp;rsquo;t know my rights? Nah, what the fuck you talking about. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have a lawyer, the state would fucking approve it to you. Why the fuck you lying to me. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what world you&amp;rsquo;re living in if you don&amp;rsquo;t have an attorney, the state woulda provided for you. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have an attorney, the state woulda provided for you.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;INTOXIMETER TEST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At approximately 2335 hours, Dietz Jr. refused to take a breath alcohol concentration test. Sgt. Smith explained the test will be marked as a refusal, Sgt. Smith also tried to ask Dietz Jr. if his attorney&amp;rsquo;s information was on a business card in his wallet, Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll figure it out, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to talk to you no more. I asked for a lawyer, and you&amp;rsquo;re violating my rights. I want to call my wife. I have a right to a phone call, and I have a right to an attorney. I have not been charged with anything, so I have a right to an attorney, and I have a right to a phone call.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained he could not find an attorney&amp;rsquo;s business card in his wallet and asked if he knew where the information was, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I have a right to a phone call it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter who I call, doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. I have a right to an attorney, and I have a right to a phone call, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. I have a right to attorney and write to a phone call, if somebody hits me from behind, I&amp;rsquo;m not at fault.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith advised he may not be at fault, but he is intoxicated, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if somebody hits me from behind, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith advised he was not going to argue, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;You can argue all you want, but if somebody hits me from behind, it&amp;rsquo;s null. The, even the insurance claim, it&amp;rsquo;s null because he hit me from behind. So what you saying, we can go to court over this.&amp;quot; Sgt Smith advised he would be in court, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;You come to court, I&amp;rsquo;m going. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna get the best lawyer, I want you there. I want to see you, Mr. Smith. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna smile in your face when they fucking tell you the motherfucker hit me from behind, and I&amp;rsquo;m good to go. Fuck I don&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody fuck, I don&amp;rsquo;t need to hit nobody for. The fuck I drive Forty-five (45) miles an hour on a fifty-five (55), I&amp;rsquo;m not violating anybody&amp;rsquo;s rights, I&amp;rsquo;m allowed to drive ten (10) under.&amp;rdquo; Sgt Smith explained he could drive ten (10) under, but he could not drive drunk, that was the issue, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Yeah all right, that you don&amp;rsquo;t drive drunk motherfucker, fuck you both, bunch of fucking hypocrites, fucking hypocrites. Like if I was driving drunk, like motherfucker, like du, I was driving the speed limit, what the fuck. If you don&amp;rsquo;t get me, my lawyer, all the shit that you&amp;rsquo;re doing right now is null. I&amp;rsquo;m a tell you that right now, so do it, right? If you don&amp;rsquo;t get my lawyer, you&amp;rsquo;re violating my privileges. I hit nobody they hit me, you need to go get the person that hit me, the fuck is wrong with y&amp;rsquo;all. Investigating a, a accident when somebody hits me, my airbags go off, why the fuck my airbags go off, they hit me. I had nobody in the front. you&amp;rsquo;ll see that in my lane. Hey, if I&amp;rsquo;m not arrested, and I&amp;rsquo;m not being charged, these (Dietz Jr. began turning in the chair, wanting the handcuff taken off).&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained to Dietz Jr. that he was arrested, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;No, no, no, no, if I&amp;rsquo;m not being charged, these handcuffs need to come off. (Dietz Jr. began shouting) Officer, if I&amp;rsquo;m not being charged handcuffs, need to come off, take them off!&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained that he was under arrest, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not being charged. Under arrest for what?&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained he was under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;DUI, I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody they hit me, it does matter it does matter. Officer, it does matter, if somebody hit me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit them, it does matter. I didn&amp;rsquo;t turn twice I turned. You can hit me all you want, I&amp;rsquo;m suicidal, hit me, I&amp;rsquo;m suicidal, hit me, hurt me hurt me, hurt me, officer, but I ain&amp;rsquo;t never hurt nobody, they can hurt me all they want that&amp;rsquo;s what they did my whole life. Fuck you fuck you.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;I attempted to explain a form to Dietz Jr., and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Shut the fuck up. I want a lawyer you fucking violated my rights. I want a lawyer, I want a lawyer, I never refused anything. I want a lawyer, they&amp;rsquo;re violating my rights, I have a right to an attorney. I have a right to a phone call. I have a right to remain silent I have the right. I don&amp;rsquo;t give a fuck where I&amp;rsquo;m at, but I have a right. What&amp;rsquo;s the crime I&amp;rsquo;m being charged with?&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith advised Dietz Jr. that would be explained to him, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;No, no, no, no, you have to give it to me right now. Yes, you do, yes you do. I know my rights, yes, you do. Because if I&amp;rsquo;m in handcuffs, you have to give me a charge. Or you have to take these fucking handcuffs off, I know my rights, I&amp;rsquo;m not stupid, I was going to be a cop until you motherfuckers beat me when I was a kid, so fuck you. Fuck all you cops.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;As I walked down the hallway to exit the building to print out paperwork, I could hear Dietz Jr. continue to shout at Sgt. Smith.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;When I returned to the DUI Processing room Dietz Jr. was stating, &amp;ldquo;Nobody was in front of me I was hit.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained once the DUI paperwork was done, Dietz Jr. was to be transported to the hospital for an emergency petition, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Nah, I want my lawyer, can&amp;rsquo;t do anything, you can&amp;rsquo;t do anything until I get a lawyer.&amp;rdquo; Sgt Smith explained he asked for the attorney&amp;rsquo;s information, but he did not give any information, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes, I did, yes I did, fuck that where&amp;rsquo;s my lawyer.&amp;rdquo; I retrieved other necessary paperwork, and when I returned to the DUI Processing room, Dietz stated, &amp;ldquo;You playing, I&amp;rsquo;m telling you come, my uncle is charge of the FBI, y&amp;rsquo;all, y&amp;rsquo;all motherfuckers are fucking with me. I did nothing. Randall Maguire, who is the councilman of New York City, and Bob Maguire, who is a state prosecutor of New York City, that&amp;rsquo;s my uncle, I did nothing wrong. You don&amp;rsquo;t care, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to care, because you did something wrong, you violated my rights, so I&amp;rsquo;m a sue you too. Mr. Smith and Mr. Mills, your careers are ended, you&amp;rsquo;re not recording, you&amp;rsquo;re not recording the footage.&amp;rdquo; I assured Dietz Jr. that my camera was recording, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;No, you&amp;rsquo;re not. I just saw him record. I ask for a lawyer, and nobody give me a lawyer where is my lawyer? Where&amp;rsquo;s my phone call? It&amp;rsquo;s been an hour. I was supposed to get a phone call in that first half an hour, go ahead and go on, Mr. Mills, I asked for a phone call. You&amp;rsquo;re violating my rights, Mr. Mills, should just stay here all night. I&amp;rsquo;m a tell you you&amp;rsquo;re violating my rights, Mr. Mills. If somebody hit me in the back, Mr. Mills is is, my fault. Regardless if I&amp;rsquo;m drunk or not, Mr. Mills. If somebody hit me in the back doing seventy-five (75) and I&amp;rsquo;m doing forty-five (45) in a fifty-five (55), on the right lane, not the left lane, who&amp;rsquo;s fault is it, Mr. Mills? Look at his fucking, look at the car, seventy-five (75) in a forty-five (45).&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith instructed Dietz Jr. to lift his leg up to him as Sgt. Smith was putting ankle restraints on Dietz Jr., and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Ah come on man, Mr. Smith, do you want to hurt me like this? This whole thing Mr. Smit, Mr. Smith. It&amp;rsquo;s ok, it&amp;rsquo;s ok, Mr. Smith, go ahead do your thing. I&amp;rsquo;m good now, Mr. Smith I like it I like you. I like that. You want to hurt me, go ahead, Mr. Smith.&amp;rdquo; Sgt Smith explained he did not want to hurt him, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;You can hurt me, Mr. Smith, I&amp;rsquo;m good with that. I&amp;rsquo;ve been hurt a lot in my life. I&amp;rsquo;ve been shot at three times, I&amp;#39;ve been stabbed.&amp;rdquo; Sgt Smith explained he had been shot and it is what it is, Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Yeah, but you a cop, I had to survive as a kid in the hood by myself, a white man, and a black hood, fuck all y&amp;rsquo;all, can never understand me, fuck you, fuck off, fuck everybody. Violating my rights, though. I know my rights I ask for a lawyer you never gave it to me, write that down.&amp;rdquo; Sgt Smith explained everything was recorded, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;No, it&amp;rsquo;s not your camera is off, I&amp;rsquo;m not stupid. No, it&amp;rsquo;s not. No, it&amp;rsquo;s not. I&amp;rsquo;m not stupid. And my wife, don&amp;rsquo;t tell me the shit that y&amp;rsquo;all do. Fuck out of here. She trained you motherfuckers think I don&amp;rsquo;t know. I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk to your pinnacle today, though I never hurt nobody, I know you&amp;rsquo;re care for me. You should&amp;rsquo;ve grabbed the person in front of me. (incoherent) You violated my rights. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if I&amp;rsquo;m drunk or not, if somebody hit me, they&amp;rsquo;re at fault, right? You know law, you know law, so if somebody hits me.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained he was not going to argue, and Dietz Jr. interrupted and stated, &amp;ldquo;But you violated my rights. How are we gonna go through this all night? We&amp;rsquo;re gonna tell this to the lawyer, I&amp;#39;m not gonna let up, he violated my rights, he didn&amp;rsquo;t take the other guy that hit me was driving seventy-five (75), and you could take, you could detect it on his cam, on his car. Why didn&amp;rsquo;t pull the car over? He was the one that hit me. Mr. Mills, I filed a report, Mr. Mills. You&amp;rsquo;re not filing a report, Mr. Mills? I&amp;rsquo;m filing a report, Mr. Smith, the car that was in front of me hit me, but you&amp;rsquo;re not filing it out.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained an ACRS report will be done for the crash but that we also have this report to take care of, Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter, he hit me, paperwork is all good, but if he hit me, he violated my rights I ask for an attorney, never gave me an attorney, I ask for a report, you didn&amp;rsquo;t even show me a report, you didn&amp;rsquo;t even take in my statement. Nothing, you&amp;rsquo;re violating my rights. Who took my statement? Him no. No, nobody asked me questions. You know why you done arguing with me because I&amp;rsquo;m too fucking smart for you. You fucking idiot. I&amp;rsquo;m fucking rich right now. I want you to hit me. I want you to hit me. I won&amp;rsquo;t let you lose your job. I ain&amp;rsquo;t do nothing, though. Somebody hits me, I admit, admit I made a mistake. Wait, you pay taxes for alcohol, it&amp;rsquo;s illegal, it&amp;rsquo;s legal. First of all, I didn&amp;rsquo;t hit nobody, and you never took my statement, I&amp;rsquo;m a keep saying this, I&amp;rsquo;m a keep saying this. Violated my rights. If I hit nobody and I did nothing wrong. Yeah, well, you didn&amp;rsquo;t stop me on a speed infraction. You stop me at an accident, and somebody else hit me, and you never even investigated the accident, so you&amp;rsquo;re wrong. You violated my rights. You didn&amp;rsquo;t know there&amp;rsquo;s a loophole in this shit. You fucked up, both of you, you violated my rights, you didn&amp;rsquo;t take the car in front of me, you just violated my rights. That&amp;rsquo;s fucked up. You didn&amp;rsquo;t even investigate the whole accident scene somebody hit me. And you didn&amp;rsquo;t even investigate it that&amp;rsquo;s fucked up, nobody was hurt I was the only car, my airbags went off, and nobody else was hurt, the only car, but you didn&amp;rsquo;t investigate the scene. Write that down. The scene was not investigated, no questions were asked, nobody asked any questions. Don&amp;rsquo;t write it down. Because if you&amp;rsquo;re real, if your cameras are really on, they would hear it, but I know their cameras are not on, I&amp;rsquo;m not stupid.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained that when Dietz Jr.&amp;rsquo;s attorney makes a request for the camera footage, he could view all three (3), and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;But there&amp;rsquo;s two of you ain&amp;rsquo;t stupid, I don&amp;rsquo;t have a camera, where is the camera?&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained it was the camera in the room, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t believe you, I&amp;rsquo;m not stupid, I&amp;rsquo;ve, I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in places before with the FBI. I know how to turn a camera off. I&amp;rsquo;m not stupid. Believe me, I&amp;rsquo;m not stupid, I know, I know the process. You really think I don&amp;rsquo;t? I didn&amp;rsquo;t do shit, ain&amp;rsquo;t nobody that hit me. And if you think I don&amp;rsquo;t know somebody that knows the FBI, you fucked up. I don&amp;rsquo;t really give a fuck about the FBI, but I&amp;rsquo;m talking about my rights. You violated my rights. Can you put ankle cuffs on me for no reason, just ta fuck with me, yes, you did, Mr. Smith?&amp;rdquo; Sgt Smith attempted to explain why the ankle cuffs were put on, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Just a fuck with me, Mr. Smith, just a fuck with me, Mr. Smith. I love you, though. Just to fuck with me, you put ankle cuffs on my ankles. You are a fucking asshole, I love you, though. I fuck with, I fuck with you, though. I would like to, I would love to brawl with you on a regular occasion. But I, I fuck with you, though. I&amp;rsquo;m just fucking with you, Mr. Smith. Ain&amp;rsquo;t no personal. I&amp;rsquo;m angry because somebody hit me, and I did nothing wrong, Mr. Smith.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith explained he understood, but that did not change the course of the following procedures. Dietz Jr. replied, &amp;ldquo;You can&amp;rsquo;t change the course, but it actually wasn&amp;rsquo;t my fault there it goes. Where can I prove this right now I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. I&amp;rsquo;m not signing nothing. I&amp;#39;m not happy. I got handcuffs on ankle cuffs on. Where can I sign it, brother? I didn&amp;rsquo;t say not sign. Nothing, you got handcuffs on me. I want a lawyer before I sign anything so I can pre-approve anything and proofread it. I want a lawyer stating that. Do you understand me? It&amp;rsquo;s not that I refuse to sign anything, I want a lawyer before I sign anything. I don&amp;rsquo;t believe you, I don&amp;rsquo;t trust cops. I&amp;#39;ve been hurt plenty of times before cops I was a poor man growing up in Harlem, cops didn&amp;rsquo;t like me because I was hanging out with black people. Fuck you. Fuck the cops. That&amp;rsquo;s why I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to be a cop, Mr. Smith. My dream was to be a cop, you know that, but you beat me up, you stole my dream, Mr. Smith, Mr. Mills, because you don&amp;rsquo;t know how to act, you stole my dreams because you abuse people, you abuse your power. I&amp;#39;m not lying, I&amp;rsquo;m telling you the truth, I want to be a cop. I would&amp;rsquo;ve been a good cop. And I love people. I have no respect for y&amp;rsquo;all. You need to get a better job, man, what the fuck y&amp;rsquo;all don&amp;rsquo;t even make thirty-eight thousand (38,000) a year, sheriff&amp;#39;s department and troopers only making forty-five (45) what the fuck you doing. I make ninety (90,000) a year driving a truck. No job, not even hard. What the fuck are y&amp;rsquo;all doing? Driving a fucking cop car. Yeah, your overtime is still under a hundred (100). I&amp;rsquo;ll make one-fifty (150). Stupid shit. Easy job, though. I ain&amp;rsquo;t gonna lie easy job. You in the wrong business, Mr. Smith, Mr. Mills I see your, I see your self-righteousness. You&amp;rsquo;re a Mormon, I&amp;rsquo;m watching you, you&amp;#39;re Mormon. You&amp;rsquo;re in the wrong business bro. Your love for God ain&amp;rsquo;t gon do you right here.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Sgt Smith instructed Dietz Jr. to stand up, and we were going to walk him down the hall, back out to my patrol vehicle, Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re going to move me because I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna move with these cuffs on. It hurt, it hurt.&amp;rdquo; Sgt. Smith advised he would walk alongside him to ensure he did not fall. Once in my patrol vehicle, Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re doing it on purpose, fucking bastard. I love you. Fuck you, Mr. Smith. Fuck you. Fuck you, Mr. Smith. You&amp;rsquo;re doing it on purpose. Fuck you, Mr. Smith. I love you. Do it on purpose fucking bastard.&amp;rdquo; I explained to him I was putting the paperwork in his wallet, so it would not get lost, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;It is, I&amp;rsquo;m being violated, my rights are being violated. Who&amp;#39;s in the back?&amp;rdquo; Sgt Smith explained it was him and that I would be driving; Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m gonna tell you like I told the other officer, my rights are being violated, you are Mr. Smith, no you&amp;rsquo;re not. Mr. Smith, I like your voice. I&amp;#39;m too easy, I know your voice. I know you&amp;rsquo;re not Mr. Smith. What&amp;rsquo;s your name? I like to know names. What&amp;#39;s your name? Trooper Iman? All right, Trooper Iman, in why they put me in the car so tight, and I can&amp;rsquo;t move, I&amp;#39;m uncomfortable. No, I&amp;#39;m hurting, you violating my rights and hurting me. You&amp;rsquo;re hurting me right now. I did nothing wrong. I hit nobody. I broke my law. I did nothing wrong, and you&amp;rsquo;re violating my rights. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to know what&amp;rsquo;s going on. I&amp;rsquo;m telling you, they&amp;rsquo;re violating my rights. They never investigated the scene. Yeah, we can go through the shit I ask for a lawyer, nobody got me a lawyer we&amp;rsquo;re gonna go through this shit. Take me along the road and just shoot me in the fucking head, get it over with, I&amp;rsquo;m good with that, just dump me on the side of the road motherfuckers. Trust you motherfuckers, I don&amp;rsquo;t like cops. All you did was hurt me, look what you&amp;rsquo;re doing to me. I&amp;rsquo;m in a fucking car in the front seat, the seatbelt on the tightest shit because the cop did it on purpose with with fucking ankle cuffs on me for no reason, I broke no laws somebody hit me. What the fuck? Put me in a cell by myself. Cause I&amp;rsquo;ll fuck somebody up. Don&amp;rsquo;t put me in a cell with somebody else. I don&amp;rsquo;t fuck with people I don&amp;rsquo;t like people don&amp;rsquo;t put me in a cell with somebody I&amp;rsquo;m a tell you that right now I don&amp;rsquo;t fuck with people, they say something to me I&amp;rsquo;m a fuck them up. Put me in a cell with somebody, bro, I&amp;#39;m asking you for leniency. Do you think I can review because it&amp;rsquo;s a spiritual thing, Mr&amp;hellip;, what&amp;rsquo;s your name, Mr. Mills, because you&amp;rsquo;re a Mormon, it&amp;rsquo;s not a spiritual thing I just see you, I don&amp;rsquo;t give a fuck what you believe truth be told, believe in God, believe in whatever you want but if you ain&amp;rsquo;t doing the right thing, fuck you. I didn&amp;rsquo;t hurt nobody. I&amp;rsquo;m a keep it real. They hit me in the back, but you never investigated the scene. Y&amp;rsquo;all done did wrong didn&amp;rsquo;t investigate the scene, try asking for a lawyer never got a lawyer, try to lawyer the first fifteen (15) minutes, you know that you&amp;rsquo;re violating my rights, in the first half an hour I was supposed to have a lawyer. All right, Mr. Mills, you can beat my ass if you want, if you don&amp;rsquo;t like that, hit me, go ahead, do you wanna, right? We ain&amp;rsquo;t going to the Sheriff&amp;#39;s Department. Where we going Mr. Mills?&amp;rdquo; I explained we were going to Carroll Hospital Center, and Dietz Jr. stated, &amp;ldquo;Okay, I&amp;rsquo;m just asking questions. I just wanted to know. I know this area, so I&amp;rsquo;m asking. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I&amp;rsquo;m about to be killed, you understand me? At least I know it&amp;rsquo;s about to happen, makes me feel good. Ready all my fucking. What does it feel to kill somebody because you had no choice, you don&amp;rsquo;t know Mr. Mills, you don&amp;rsquo;t know. How does it hurt, when somebody hurt you and you don&amp;rsquo;t wanna hurt them, how do you feel Mr. Mills? How do you live with that? I didn&amp;rsquo;t wanna hurt nobody but they hurt me. How do you live with that Mr. Mills, happen all the time, officer in the back, how do you move on? I&amp;#39;m a soldier officer, how do you move on? How do you move on, officer? I killed many people, how do you move on? Can you feel it, it hurts. Going on. Do you like this or not? Clean driving, how about your parents? I could tell I was a profiler for the FBI, they paid me, I&amp;#39;m really good at this shit. I watch y&amp;rsquo;all, and I just pick you apart just to fuck with you. Too easy, I learned this shit when I was a kid, never had a mom or dad, fuck &amp;lsquo;em. Mom and dad too busy, fuck &amp;lsquo;em. Do you know what is missing, Mr. Mills, no love. It hurts, it hurts really bad. I&amp;rsquo;ve protected so many people in my life, gave my life one time, tried to kill me, do you know what he did? Got a knife and tried to stab me, I looked in his eyes, turn the fuck around, little bitch. What does that say? Tried to fuck with a man, and you stabbing me.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Once at Carroll Hospital Center, I went to assist Dietz Jr. out of the vehicle, and he mumbled incoherently, then stated, &amp;ldquo;If I see Mr. Smith, I want to fuck his ass up, just on purpose, just because, put these handcuffs on tight. I&amp;rsquo;m going to fuck Mr. Smith up, tell him. Fuck Mr. Smith up. Mr. Smith, on the fuck you up bitch put these handcuffs on me tight, and I ask for a lawyer, fuck you.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;While at the Carroll Hospital Center, I deactivated my body-worn camera in accordance with Maryland State Police Administration Directive 20.02(C)(9)(b). Dietz Jr. was screened for mental health illness by Dr. Loper. Dr. Loper refused to admit Dietz Jr. to the hospital for the suicidal statements he made due to the statements being a result of inebriation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Dietz Jr. was issued the following citations:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CITATIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;TA 21-304(c) Driving Motor Vehicle Off Roadway While Passing Vehicle&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;TA 21-309(b) Driver Changing Lanes When Unsafe&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;TA 21-801(b) Failure To Control Speed On Highway To Avoid Collision&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;TA 21-901.1(a) Reckless Driving Vehicle In Wanton And Willful Disregard For Safety of Persons And Property&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;TA 21-901.1(b) Negligent Driving Vehicle In Careless And Imprudent Manner Endangering Property, Life, And Person&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;TA 21-902(a)(1)(i) Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;TA 21-902(b)(1)(i) Driving Vehicle While Impaired By Alcohol&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;The defendant was issued copies of the following documents:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Citations (listed above)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;DR-15 Advice of Rights&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;DR-15A Officer&amp;rsquo;s Certification and Order of Suspension&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;All documents were forwarded to the Carroll County State&amp;#39;s Attorney&amp;rsquo;s Office.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Both involved vehicles in the collision were towed by Rockdale Towing.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CASE CLOSED BY ARREST.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 19:30:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/30/2023 20:38:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Perrell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Curtis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7140</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dale</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2927</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mills</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryder</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6784</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504247</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/26/2023 22:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 22:07:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 22:07:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504247</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/26/2023 22:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 22:10:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 22:10:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504247</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/26/2023 22:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 22:10:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 22:10:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504247</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/26/2023 22:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 22:10:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 22:10:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504247</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/26/2023 22:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 22:10:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 22:10:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504247</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17510</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/26/2023 22:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 22:24:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/28/2023 22:24:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>47</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 22:17:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:15</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375500</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>DIETZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>EDWARD</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>JOSEPH</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/28/1976 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>04/27/2023 22:16:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E363</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>DIETZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>EDWARD</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>JOSEPH</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/28/1976 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>D320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E363</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/27/2023 22:16:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>291</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Pleasant Valley</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Westminster</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21158</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3047</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.008539</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.619696</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 22:17:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 22:17:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 22:17:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 22:17:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 22:17:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>49</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 19:45:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:55</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375754</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>LITTLE</LastName>
               <FirstName>STACY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MARIE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/05/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/30/2023 19:44:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L340</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S320</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>LITTLE</LastName>
               <FirstName>STACY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MARIE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/05/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L340</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S320</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/30/2023 19:44:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>15817</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Old Frederick</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Emmitsburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21727</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.337158</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.667554</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>674</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9576</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 19:52:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 19:52:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 19:52:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 19:52:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 19:52:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 19:52:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375757</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>BRADY</LastName>
               <FirstName>KELLY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LYNN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/10/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/30/2023 19:51:47</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>BRADY</LastName>
               <FirstName>KELLY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LYNN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/10/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/30/2023 19:51:47</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>153</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Westview</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Taneytown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21787</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2038</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.179587</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.663972</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>605</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9160</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 19:52:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 19:52:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 19:52:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 19:52:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 22:07:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 22:07:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152425</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/27/2023 22:32:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/27/2023 22:32:07</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>KMHD35LE9DU104803</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HYUN</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ELN</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4CW9888</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>4</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>