<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-016915</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/12/2023 13:13:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/12/2023 13:13:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/12/2023 13:13:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/12/2023 13:13:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Sex Assault</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 13:13:51</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 08:14:49</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SAS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>89830</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 13:13:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/15/2023 09:48:54</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>89830</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1380</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>MARSHALL</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>HAGERSTOWN</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.73242506316372</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.66214709962193</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>POTOMAC CENTER</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/12/2023 13:13:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/12/2023 13:13:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/14/2023 08:14:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 13:13:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 08:14:14</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Attachments:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;MSP Form 67 - Chain of Custody Logs&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Seven digital photographs&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;MSP Form 180 - Advice of Miranda Rights&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Supplement reports from Officer Miller&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;SAFE Exam report&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;DNA Search Warrant&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Narrative:&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 05/12/2023, I was advised by D/Sgt. Martin of a possible sexual assault that took place at the Potomac Center which is located at 1380 Marshall St, Hagerstown MD 21740.&amp;nbsp; The Potomac Center is described as a secure facility that provides quality person-centered supports to adults with intellectual disabilities.&amp;nbsp; After speaking to D/Sgt. Martin, I made contact with Officer Tammy Miller who was the Officer at the Potomac Center handling the initial report.&amp;nbsp; Officer Miller advised it was reported that the victim, Arianna Santos (B/F, D.O.B. 10/31/2004) had consensual sex with suspect, Ezra Shon Thomas (B/M, D.O.B. 08/13/2001).&amp;nbsp; Arianna is currently court ordered to be at the facility and her admission date was 03/02/2023.&amp;nbsp; Thomas is currently employed by the Potomac Center and holds the position of Residential Aide.&amp;nbsp; Officer Miller described Thomas&amp;rsquo; daily job duties as assisting residents with daily activities, unlocking doors/bathrooms, and assisting them with lunch.&amp;nbsp; Through Officer Miller&amp;rsquo;s investigation she was able to determine the sexual contact happened on 05/08/2023.&amp;nbsp; I requested that Officer Miller have Santos transported to Meritus Medical Center, so a Sexual Assault Evidence Collection Kit (SAFE) could be completed.&amp;nbsp; Portions of Officer Miller&amp;rsquo;s report are captioned below.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;On Thursday evening, 05/11/2023 I was the on call officer for the Maryland Department of Health/Secured Transport &amp;amp; Investigation Unit for the Potomac Center/SETT (1380 Marshall Street, Hagerstown, Washington County, MD).&amp;nbsp; At 6:15 PM I received a call from Melissa Harper, a supervisor for SETT (Secured Evaluation and Therapeutic Treatment), concerning an allegation of sexual contact between a female resident and a male staff.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Miss Harper provided the following information.&amp;nbsp; She said resident Arianna Santos reported to female staff Alexis Tillman that she had sex with a male staff, who she identified as Ezra Thomas.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Arianna was asked when and where it happened and she said in her room on Blue Hall (Cottage # 3).&amp;nbsp; Arianna couldn&amp;#39;t provide the date when it happened, but said it was the day Mr. Thomas was wearing grey Nike shorts.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Arianna went on to report she was experiencing a vaginal discharge and was concerned.&amp;nbsp; Arianna also said she didn&amp;#39;t want Mr. Thomas to &amp;quot;get in trouble&amp;quot;, because she liked him and felt they were in a relationship.&amp;nbsp; Staff told Arianna they would notify nursing and make the appropriate notifications concerning the allegation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;I was aware that Mr. Thomas was already on administrative leave for an allegation that was being investigated by Officer Wolfensberger (Report # 2023-0282).&amp;nbsp; The details of that allegation were a female resident alleged Mr. Thomas made inappropriate sexual comments to her and showed her a video on his cell phone of him masturbating and having sexual intercourse with a female.&amp;nbsp; She also alleged that Mr. Thomas offered to bring her marijuana in exchange for having sexual intercourse with him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Mr. Thomas was subsequently put on administrative leave in reference to that allegation and was not on campus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;I contacted my supervisor, Lt. Richard Smith about this allegation, to determine if it was part of the allegation Officer Wolfensberger was currently investigating and he said it was not.&amp;nbsp; It was decided that I didn&amp;#39;t need to respond at that time to begin an investigation of this new allegation and would make contact with Arianna in the morning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;It should be noted that based on the initial allegation that was made against Mr. Thomas, a review of the campus CCTV was done.&amp;nbsp; A copy of the schedule Mr. Thomas worked was provided and I knew he worked on Cottage # 3 on Saturday, 05/06/2023 from 11:30 AM until 3:30 PM, Sunday, 05/07/2023 from 10:30 AM until 3:30 PM and on Monday, 05/08/2023 from 11:30 AM until 3:30 PM.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Based on what was observed on the CCTV, I knew that on Saturday, 05/06/2023 Mr. Thomas reported to work wearing a white shirt and khaki colored joggers with a drawstring.&amp;nbsp; On Sunday, 05/07/2023 Mr. Thomas reported to work wearing a burgundy T-shirt and black joggers and on Monday, 05/08/2023 he reported to work wearing a white T-shirt and grey Nike shorts.&amp;nbsp; Mr. Thomas worked from 11:30 AM until 3:30 PM on Cottage # 3.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Based on what Arianna reported in the allegation, that Mr. Thomas was wearing grey Nike shorts on the day they had sexual intercourse, I reviewed the CCTV for Monday, 05/08/2023 prior to interviewing her.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;In reviewing the CCTV for that date, I observed Mr. Thomas entering Arianna&amp;#39;s room on two occasions and was out of view of the CCTV.&amp;nbsp; It is campus policy that staff are instructed not to enter a resident&amp;rsquo;s room without having another staff with them, as there are no cameras in the resident&amp;rsquo;s rooms.&amp;nbsp; Staff are supposed to stand in the door way of the residents&amp;rsquo; rooms so they are visible on the CCTV that are mounted on both ends of the halls.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;On Monday, 05/08/2023 at 12:50:46 PM, I observe Mr. Thomas in the lobby of Cottage # 3 with other residents and staff.&amp;nbsp; Arianna is observed walking into the lobby, asking for and being given paper towels by a female staff to dry her hands.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;After Arianna dries her hands, she approaches Mr. Thomas and tries to put the paper towels between his left arm and body.&amp;nbsp; Mr. Thomas moves away from Arianna, then grabs her right wrist with his left hand and appears to poke her in the stomach with his right index finger.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Arianna pulls her right wrist away from Mr. Thomas and slaps/punches at his right hip/thigh area.&amp;nbsp; Arianna begins to walk away, but turns and walks back toward Mr. Thomas.&amp;nbsp; They stand in the lobby for about a minute before Arianna turns and walks away.&amp;nbsp; Mr. Thomas begins following her and Arianna quickens her pace and then jogs into her room.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Mr. Thomas follows behind Arianna, enters her room and is not in view of the camera.&amp;nbsp; Mr. Thomas enters the room at 12:51:32 PM and exits at 12:51:40 PM.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;It should be noted that as Arianna enters her room, she is seen smiling and does not appear to be in distress.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The next incident begins at 1:37:41 PM.&amp;nbsp; Mr. Thomas is seen walking toward Arianna&amp;#39;s room on Blue Hall.&amp;nbsp; Her door is closed and he&amp;#39;s seen opening the door and stands in the door way.&amp;nbsp; Presumably Mr. Thomas is having a conversation with Arianna and at 1:38:28 PM is seen walking into her room and out of view of the camera (the door remains open).&amp;nbsp; Mr. Thomas is then seen exiting her room at 1:39:39 PM and remains standing in her doorway.&amp;nbsp; Mr. Thomas is observed with his hands in his short pockets.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Mr. Thomas remained standing at the doorway to Arianna&amp;#39;s room until he walks toward the lobby at 1:42:14 PM.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;It should be noted there were no other residents or staff on Blue Hall, however there was a staff sitting in the lobby.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;On Friday, 05/12/2023 James Cromwell (Quality Assurance Lead Investigator) and I responded to Cottage # 3 to interview Arianna.&amp;nbsp; We interviewed Arianna in a private office at 9:45 AM.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Arianna provided the following information.&amp;nbsp; I reminded Arianna who James and I were, and that we were there to talk to her about the allegation she made the previous day about Ezra (Mr. Thomas).&amp;nbsp; Arianna said she knew what I was talking about.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;I asked Arianna to tell me about what happened between her and Ezra the day he was wearing the grey Nike shorts.&amp;nbsp; Arianna said they had sex that day in her room.&amp;nbsp; I asked Arianna if it was after breakfast and before lunch or after lunch and before dinner in order to narrow down a time frame.&amp;nbsp; Arianna said it was after breakfast and before lunch, but then later said it happened before her phone time.&amp;nbsp; (I confirmed via the CCTV that her phone time was at 2:15:23 PM until 2:34:43 PM).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;I asked if she remembered what day it happened on.&amp;nbsp; Arianna said it was after a visit she had with her mother.&amp;nbsp; I asked her when she had her visit and she said Sunday.&amp;nbsp; (I was able to confirm with RAS Shaye Knowlton that Arianna had a visit with her mother on Sunday, 05/07/2023 at 2:00 PM).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Arianna said it was the day after her visit, which would be 05/08/2023.&amp;nbsp; It should be noted that what she said corroborated what I had already viewed on the CCTV and was able to confirm that Mr. Thomas was wearing grey Nike shorts that day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Arianna said Ezra came into her room and asked her if she wanted to have sex.&amp;nbsp; Arianna said she told him &amp;quot;it didn&amp;#39;t matter&amp;quot; and she pulled down her pants and underwear.&amp;nbsp; She demonstrated to us how she leaned on her bed and he stood behind her.&amp;nbsp; Arianna showed us that she bent forward over her bed and supported herself by placing her hands on the bed.&amp;nbsp; Arianna said Ezra pulled his shorts aside to expose his penis and penetrated her from behind.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;I asked Arianna if she remembered how long Ezra was behind her and she said not long, maybe about a minute or two.&amp;nbsp; She specifically said she counted &amp;quot;about ten strokes&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp; I asked her if Ezra ejaculated.&amp;nbsp; Arianna said she didn&amp;#39;t know what that word meant.&amp;nbsp; I then asked if Ezra &amp;quot;came&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp; She told me he didn&amp;#39;t.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;I asked if she remembered if there were any other staff or residents in the hallway.&amp;nbsp; Arianna said Ezra told her that &amp;quot;Sean&amp;quot; (staff identified as Sean Wilson) was in the bathroom and they &amp;quot;did it&amp;quot; while he was in the bathroom.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;I asked Arianna if she felt pressured or threatened by Ezra to allow him to have sexual intercourse with her and she said no, but said she was nervous.&amp;nbsp; I asked her to explain about her being nervous and she said she was worried about a resident or staff walking by her room and seeing them.&amp;nbsp; I asked Arianna if her door was open or closed and she confirmed that it was open.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Arianna told me the day this happened, she remembered that Ezra had asked RAS Knowlton if his shorts were &amp;quot;too short&amp;quot;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;I asked Arianna if this was the same day she gave him a &amp;quot;blow job&amp;quot; (fellatio) and she said no, she believed that was possibly the week before and before the visit with her mother.&amp;nbsp; I asked Arianna how Ezra mentioned it to her and she said they had talked about it for a couple of days.&amp;nbsp; She said Ezra brought it up and said, &amp;quot;When are you going to stop playing and suck my dick?&amp;quot;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Arianna confirmed this incident happened in her room also.&amp;nbsp; I asked her if Ezra &amp;quot;came&amp;quot; and she said no.&amp;nbsp; I asked her how long the &amp;quot;blowjob&amp;quot; lasted and she said less than a minute.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;I asked Arianna if she had already washed the underwear she had been wearing on Monday, 05/08/2023 and she indicated she did.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;I asked Arianna if she was being truthful about what happened or was just trying to get Ezra in trouble?&amp;nbsp; Arianna said she didn&amp;#39;t want to get Ezra in trouble because she likes him, but told me she was being truthful.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Arianna said she told her mother about what happened during their call on Thursday, 05/12/2023 and said her mother was going to hire an attorney.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Arianna was unable to provide any more specific details about either incident and the interview was concluded.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Mr. Cromwell and I then talked with RAS Knowlton.&amp;nbsp; I asked RAS Knowlton if she recalled having a conversation with Mr. Thomas in which he asked her about the length of his shorts.&amp;nbsp; RAS Knowlton said she remembered Mr. Thomas asking her that and believed it was either Sunday, 05/07/2023 or Monday, 05/08/2023.&amp;nbsp; It should be noted that Mr. Thomas did work overtime both of those days on Cottage # 3 until 3:30 PM, however in reviewing the CCTV it was determined the only day he was wearing grey shorts was Monday, 05/08/2023.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Based on what I observed on the CCTV for Monday, 05/08/2023, Mr. Thomas entered Arianna&amp;#39;s room twice and was not in view of the camera.&amp;nbsp; The second time he entered her room he was out of view for one minute and 11 seconds.&amp;nbsp; There were no other residents or staff on Blue Hall during the time he was inside her room.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;During the interview with Arianna, she said Mr. Thomas told her that staff &amp;quot;Sean&amp;quot; was in the bathroom when he came into her room.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;In watching the CCTV for Monday, 05/08/2023, I saw staff Sean Wilson enter the staff bathroom at 1:37:08 PM as Mr. Thomas unlocks and enters the office door.&amp;nbsp; Mr. Thomas exits the office at 1:37:21 PM and walks directly to Arianna&amp;#39;s room and then enters her room at 1:38:28 PM.&amp;nbsp; Mr. Wilson exits the bathroom at 1:39:31 PM, after Mr. Thomas had already entered and exited Arianna&amp;#39;s room.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;It should be noted that Arianna was in her room with the door closed and would not have known that Mr. Wilson was in the bathroom but for the fact that Mr. Thomas told her.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; End of Officer Miller&amp;rsquo;s report.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 05/15/2023, I responded to Meritus Medical Center and picked up the SAFE exam kit.&amp;nbsp; The SAFE kit was captured on MSP Form 67 (Chain of Custody Log) and stored at the Hagerstown Barrack per Maryland State Police policies and procedures.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 05/17/2023, a search warrant was authored by this investigator to obtain DNA from Ezra Thomas.&amp;nbsp; The search warrant was signed by the Honorable Judge Victoria Lobley, Judge of the District Court, Washington County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 05/18/2023, I responded to the Potomac Center and met with Officer Miller to review the video surveillance of the incident.&amp;nbsp; After reviewing the video with Officer Miller, she provided me a copy of the videos on two separate DVDs.&amp;nbsp; Those DVDs were captured on MSP Form 67 (Chain of Custody Log) and stored at the Hagerstown Barrack per Maryland State Police policies and procedures.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Contact was made with Ezra Thomas via telephone, and I advised him of my investigation.&amp;nbsp; Thomas agreed to come to the Hagerstown barrack on 05/22/23, so that an interview could be conducted.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 05/22/2023, Thomas arrived at the Hagerstown Barrack.&amp;nbsp; He was advised of his rights via MSP Form 180 (Advice of Miranda Rights) and Thomas agreed to waive his rights and he agreed to a recorded interview.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The below is a summation of the facts and information collected during the interview.&amp;nbsp; It is not considered to be an absolute verbatim account of the interview; for that please refer to the compact-disc&amp;nbsp;recording made of the interview which is stored at the Hagerstown Barrack.&amp;nbsp; This summation is only intended to provide a brief record for general understanding of the interview content.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I advised Thomas that I wanted to speak to him about his relationship with Arianna Santos and told him that she reported that they had consensual sex in her bedroom at the Potomac Center, and she had also stated that she performed fellatio on him on one occasion.&amp;nbsp; Thomas said he was not aware of those allegations and heard he was suspended because there are allegations that he and Sierra Lewis (another resident) were supposed to have made an agreement that if she performed fellatio on him that he would bring her marijuana.&amp;nbsp; Thomas said as far as his relationship with all the residents, he does not play favoritism, and he tries to be friendly to everyone.&amp;nbsp; Thomas said he just found out Arianna was leaving, and he was talking to her about her plans about when she was getting out.&amp;nbsp; Thomas said he was confused as to how he is being accused of having sex with the residents.&amp;nbsp; Thomas said his relationship with the residents has always been on a friend level and some residents consider him to be like a brother.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I asked Thomas about Arianna again, and he said she had just found out that she would be getting discharged soon, and she was inside her room, and he was standing in her doorway.&amp;nbsp; They were talking about what she was going to do when she got discharged and how she was going to avoid the friends she hung around prior to coming to the Potomac Center.&amp;nbsp; I asked Thomas if he knew what day this was, and he said it was either Sunday, or Monday.&amp;nbsp; I asked Thomas why those days stuck out to him, and he said those were the only days he worked in that cottage because he was off Tuesday, and they suspended him Wednesday.&amp;nbsp; I asked Thomas if he ever went in Arianna&amp;#39;s room and he explained that Arianna was trying to pull the curtain that divides her room and it was stuck.&amp;nbsp; Thomas said he asked Arianna to stand by the door if she needed help and she said she did so she stood by the side of the door and Thomas went in the room and pulled the curtain across.&amp;nbsp; Thomas said the curtain was stuck and it took approximately one minute for him to pull it across.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I told Thomas that I watched the video surveillance at the Potomac Center and noticed that he shows Arianna a lot of attention and they seem very playful with each other.&amp;nbsp; Thomas explained again that he believes he treats all the residents at the Potomac Center the same and he does not show any favoritism.&amp;nbsp; I brought up the incident where Arianna was in her room and Thomas was standing in the doorway throwing cards at her.&amp;nbsp; Thomas explained that was them just joking around, Arianna was supposed to be cleaning up her room and they were messing around with the cards.&amp;nbsp; I asked Thomas if he ever offered to bring marijuana in to any of the residents and he said no, and stated that he does not even smoke or do drugs.&amp;nbsp; I asked Thomas if he ever showed anyone any videos on his phone and he said no.&amp;nbsp; Thomas believes these rumors come from a prior incident that involved a former staff member that was fired, and they were spreading rumors about him.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I showed Thomas the video surveillance documenting the incident on 05/08/2023.&amp;nbsp; I walked Thomas through the video showing him there was no one in the doorway as he stated.&amp;nbsp; Thomas stated again that he did not do anything, and he was in the room pulling the curtain across.&amp;nbsp; The next video I showed Thomas was from 05/04/2023.&amp;nbsp; That was the day Thomas stood in the doorway and threw cards at Arianna.&amp;nbsp; Thomas explained that Arianna was cleaning her room and he walked into her room to grab the deck of cards off her dresser.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;After watching both videos Thomas said he understood how it looked.&amp;nbsp; I asked Thomas if anything happened in the room when he was in the room for one minute and 11 seconds and he stated &amp;quot;honestly nothing can really hap&amp;hellip; I mean I guess a lot could happen in a minute and however many seconds but I didn&amp;#39;t do anything.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I watched the first video again with Thomas and went through it step by step.&amp;nbsp; When we got to the part where Thomas opened Arianna&amp;#39;s door I told him that is when Arianna said that he asked her if she wanted to have sex.&amp;nbsp; There was a brief pause, and Thomas stated &amp;quot;oh shit it&amp;#39;s bad.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Thomas said Arianna asked him who was in the hall, and he told her Shawn who is a coworker of his.&amp;nbsp; I asked Thomas if he knew what him and Arianna were talking about and he said if it was the day she found out she was getting discharged they would have been talking about her leaving.&amp;nbsp; I zoomed into the doorway again and showed Thomas that no one enters the doorway until Shawn exits the bathroom and the video lines up with what Arianna says. I asked Thomas again if he did anything in the room with Arianna, and he said he was positive that he did not do anything with her.&amp;nbsp; Thomas said they have never said anything sexual to each other or Sierra Lewis.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Thomas said they would grab his underarm and tell him that he was getting thick, meaning he was getting chubby, but that is as far as their statements would ever go.&amp;nbsp; Thomas said there were also times that Sierra Lewis would rub his arm up and down, Thomas said it&amp;#39;s never a straight forward sexual comment.&amp;nbsp; Thomas said again that he believes this came from prior staff that were fired that were talking &amp;quot;shit&amp;quot; about him in front of other staff and residents.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I presented Thomas with a search warrant for this DNA.&amp;nbsp; After explaining the search warrant to Thomas.&amp;nbsp; He had questions about the process and about the charge associated with the incident.&amp;nbsp; Thomas asked if we would have to go to court and I told him if his DNA was found in the SAFE kit, but that was a long way away and Thomas stated, &amp;quot;can&amp;#39;t rule anything out.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked Thomas if he thought there was a possibility that his DNA could be there, and he said &amp;quot;I hope not, no I didn&amp;#39;t do nothing but at the same time there&amp;#39;s been, I don&amp;#39;t do drugs, yet weed was brought into the scenario&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp; I told Thomas this was DNA and asked Thomas if his semen could be in Arianna&amp;#39;s vagina, and he stated &amp;quot;no, no, my semen should not be in her vagina.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I collected Thomas&amp;#39; DNA using two (2) DNA buccal swabs.&amp;nbsp; Those swabs were captured on MSP Form 67 (Chain of Custody Log) and stored at the Hagerstown Barrack per Maryland State Police policies and procedures.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;After the Interview, I followed up with Arianna&amp;#39;s Social Worker Jessica Lopez.&amp;nbsp; Jessica described Arianna as a very impressionable 18-year-old who likes to hang out with the older crowd.&amp;nbsp; Jessica explained that Arianna is diagnosed with a moderate intellectual disability, and she has an IQ of 64.&amp;nbsp; I told Jessica that Thomas said that Arianna was being discharged soon, and Jessica said that was not true.&amp;nbsp; Jessica explained that part of her job as Arianna&amp;#39;s Social Worker is being in charge of her discharge.&amp;nbsp; Jessica explained that Arianna&amp;#39;s next court hearing is not until August.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Contact was made with Officer Miller and I advised her of my interview.&amp;nbsp; I explained to Officer Miller that Thomas said he was in Arianna&amp;#39;s room fixing a curtain and asked if she could check Arianna&amp;#39;s room and see what type of curtain is in her room and if she could take photographs of the room for me.&amp;nbsp; I also asked Officer Miller if she could see if the bathroom door could be heard from Arianna&amp;#39;s bedroom.&amp;nbsp; I explained to Officer Miller that Thomas had mentioned Supervisor Anand had told Arianna that she was going to be discharged soon and asked for his contact information, so I could speak to him.&amp;nbsp; Officer Miller explained that Anand was a nickname for Cottage Manager Sahadat Ramnarain, and she provided me with his contact information.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On the morning of 05/23/2023, I received an email from Officer Miller.&amp;nbsp; She sent me a total of seven photographs of Arianna&amp;#39;s bedroom that will be added as attachments to the case file.&amp;nbsp; She also noted that Arianna&amp;#39;s does have a curtain that divides her bedroom, but she does not have a roommate she uses the other bed to put her clothes on and sleeps in the bed closest to the door.&amp;nbsp; Officer Miller also had the HR director stand in the doorway to the room across from Arianna&amp;#39;s and opened/locked/unlocked the staff bathroom door, and she could hear it.&amp;nbsp; The locking mechanism when turned has a loud clicking noise.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Officer Miller also asked Arianna if she ever asked any staff to help with her curtain because it was &amp;quot;stuck,&amp;quot; and Arianna immediately thought she was talking about the blankets she has over her windows.&amp;nbsp; Arianna said she asked a female staff for a chair to stand on, so she could wedge the blankets in a small opening between the wall and ceiling.&amp;nbsp; Officer Miller asked Arianna about the privacy curtain in her room and asked if she ever needed any help pulling it closed because it was stuck and Arianna said no.&amp;nbsp; Officer Miller then asked her on the day Thomas came in her room when he was wearing the grey shorts if she asked him to help where with the privacy curtain, and she said, no she never asked him to help with the curtain, he just came in.&amp;nbsp; Officer Miller did a supplement report documenting her efforts, and it was added as an attachment to the case file.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 05/24/2023, the SAFE kit and DNA buccal swabs were transported to the Maryland State Police Forensic Science Division by this investigator.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 05/26/2023, I was able to make contact with Cottage Manager Sahadat Ramnarain via telephone.&amp;nbsp; I asked Ramnarain if he recalled having a conversation with Arianna about being discharged soon.&amp;nbsp; Ramnarain said he did recall having a conversation with Arianna on either Thursday, May 4th or, Friday, May 5th about getting discharged.&amp;nbsp; Ramnarain said when he had the discussion with Arianna he told her that did not mean she would be leaving the next day, they would have to find a group home that would accept her, and it could take some time.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I request this case remain open, pending the analysis from MSP Forensic Science Division&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All the above events occurred in Washington County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 11:20:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/26/2023 10:57:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Angermeier</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5544</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burleson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Darren</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5743</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506340</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 1130</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/12/2023 13:13:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/18/2023 10:33:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/18/2023 10:33:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/18/2023 10:42:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:14</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377356</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Thomas</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ezra</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shon</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/13/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/18/2023 10:40:58</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E260</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Thomas</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ezra</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shon</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/13/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E260</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/18/2023 10:40:58</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>200</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Morningside</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Martinsburg</City>
               <StateCode>WV</StateCode>
               <Zip5>25401</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/18/2023 10:42:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 10:13:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:55</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377987</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Santos</LastName>
               <FirstName>Arianna</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/31/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/25/2023 10:13:22</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Santos</LastName>
               <FirstName>Arianna</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/31/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/25/2023 10:13:22</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1388</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Marshall</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hagerstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21740</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 10:13:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/12/2023 09:30:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/12/2023 09:30:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/14/2023 08:14:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/12/2023 09:30:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 08:14:14</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Narrative:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;As of 07/12/2023, I am still waiting for analysis of the SAFE kit and DNA buccal swabs from MSP Forensic Science Division.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case remains open.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/12/2023 09:30:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/12/2023 09:35:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burleson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Darren</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5743</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/22/2023 09:57:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/22/2023 09:57:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/14/2023 08:14:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/22/2023 09:57:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 08:14:14</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Narrative:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;As of 08/22/2023, I am still waiting for analysis of the SAFE kit and DNA buccal swabs from MSP Forensic Science Division.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case remains open.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/22/2023 09:57:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 09:58:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burleson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Darren</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5743</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/12/2023 10:31:55</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/12/2023 10:31:55</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/14/2023 08:14:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/12/2023 10:31:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 08:14:14</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Narrative:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;As of 10/12/2023, I am still waiting for analysis of the SAFE kit and DNA buccal swabs from MSP Forensic Science Division.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case remains open.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/12/2023 10:33:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 10:33:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Angermeier</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5544</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burleson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Darren</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5743</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/13/2023 13:10:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/13/2023 13:10:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/14/2023 08:14:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 13:10:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 08:14:14</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #4 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Attachments:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Copy of MSP Forensic Sciences Division Laboratory Report&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Narrative:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 12/13/2023, I received the laboratory report from the Maryland State Police Forensic Sciences Division.&amp;nbsp; The report indicated there was insufficient male DNA detected in the evidence to proceed with DNA analysis.&amp;nbsp; Exhibit 2 (vaginal/cervical swabs), and 3Q1 (taken from inside crotch area) were not processed further due to insufficient quantities of male DNA detected.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A copy of that report will be added as an attachment to the case file.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Contact was made with Assistant State&amp;#39;s Attorney Beverly Plutnick and the case was discussed with her.&amp;nbsp; Due to the fact that DNA results were inconclusive, this case will be closed, lack of prosecution.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 13:11:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 13:45:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burleson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Darren</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5743</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506340</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>20</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 1130</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>4</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/13/2023 13:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5743</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 13:43:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5743</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 13:43:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>