<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-021992</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/19/2023 12:58:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/19/2023 12:58:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/19/2023 12:37:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/19/2023 12:37:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI / DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 12:58:09</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 09:11:52</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>698279</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 12:58:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 13:27:27</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>698279</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Old Washington</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westminster</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.004513</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.46211</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4027-4114</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/19/2023 12:58:06</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/19/2023 12:58:06</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 21:44:11</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 12:58:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>R-24 equipped with in-car camera and body-worn camera. Contact Sgt. Twardowski (joseph.twardowski@maryland.gov) for camera footage.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case# 23-MSP-021992&lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Victor Weinberg JR&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 06/26/1985&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 06/19/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 1253hours&lt;br /&gt; DUI #: 23-103&lt;br /&gt; Citation #: 4TS0XD0&lt;br /&gt; Breath Result: .00&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Certificates and Training&lt;br /&gt; *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) Certified&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Certified Emergency Medical Technician by the Maryland Institute of Emergency Medical Services Systems&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Certified RADAR/LIDAR operator by the Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Certified License Plate Reader (LPR) operator by the Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Apprehended over 125 impaired driver&amp;rsquo;s while working as a Maryland State Trooper&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *2023 Distinguished graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Vehicle In Motion (Phase 1)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On June 19th, 2023 at approximately 1237 hours I, Trooper Sigman #7376, currently assigned to the Golden Ring Barrack, was on routine patrol in Carroll County in the area of Old Washington Road prior to Nicodemus Road when I observed a black Ford F-150 bearing Maryland registration of 4FJ4953 traveling in lane 1. I observed that the F-150 was following within one car length of the vehicle in front of it. I observed that the F-150 would gradually get closer to the other vehicle then suddenly brake to create distance then slowly get closer again. I then observed the F-150 fail to maintain a single lane of travel and drift off of the roadway right and proceed to drive half in lane 1 and half on the right shoulder with both passenger tires across the solid white line. The F-150 continued to drive half off of the roadway. I then ran the registration through METERS/MVA. MVA showed the registration to be expired from 06/01/2023. I then activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the black Ford F-150 bearing Maryland registration of 4FJ4953. The F-150 did not react to my lights and sirens and continued to drive as if I was not behind him. The F-150 then approached the stop sign at Nicodemus Road. The F-150 then noticed my presence, made a right turn onto Nicodemus, then stopped in the middle of lane 1. I then got on my PA speaker and requested the driver to pull forward as I was stuck in the middle of the intersection behind him. The F-150 did not react.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Personal Contact (Phase 2)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then made a driver&amp;rsquo;s side approach of the black Ford F-150 bearing Maryland registration of 4FJ4953. I then identified myself, the reason for the stop, and requested the driver&amp;rsquo;s license. The driver displayed pinpoint pupils and slow uncoordinated movements. The driver then advised me that he had been arrested for a drug DUI several days earlier and had his license confiscated. The driver then handed me a DR15A which identified him as Victor Weinberg Jr. (06/26/1985). Weinberg&amp;rsquo;s identity was confirmed by his MVA photograph. Weinberg advised that he was driving from his house to a job site in Gaithersburg. I then asked Weinberg when he had last used a controlled dangerous substance. Weinberg stated that he had used &amp;ldquo;heroin or fentanyl&amp;rdquo; at approximately 0730 today. Weinberg stated that he takes heroin twice a day intravenously. Weinberg stated that this was what he was arrested for with his previous DUI. I then asked Weinberg to exit and walk to the front of his vehicle. Upon stepping out I observed that Weinberg displayed gait ataxia and swayed heavily from side to side. Weinberg then asked if he could switch shoes and wear his tennis shoes as he was more stable while wearing them. Weinberg was then provided with his tennis shoes. While changing shoes Weinberg almost fell over. I observed numerous track marks on both arms. Weinberg states he &amp;ldquo;shoots up&amp;rdquo; wherever he can find a vein. I then asked Weinberg if he would submit to standardized field sobriety testing. Weinberg agreed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed in front of Weinberg&amp;rsquo;s vehicle. &amp;nbsp;The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 80 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of normal daylight. My vehicles front facing emergency lights were deactivated for the duration of the field sobriety tests. Weinberg appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries and or defects.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Weinberg the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Injuries- previous leg and back issues&lt;br /&gt; Medical conditions- none&lt;br /&gt; Medications- none&lt;br /&gt; Glasses or contacts- none&lt;br /&gt; Alcoholic beverages- &amp;nbsp;denied&lt;br /&gt; Controlled dangerous substance- heroin/fentanyl at approximately 0730&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (0/6)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The test was explained. I then began the test. I did not observe any resting nystagmus. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lack of Smooth Pursuit - not present&lt;br /&gt; Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - not present&lt;br /&gt; Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - not present&lt;br /&gt; *Vertical Gaze Nystagmus - not present&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I observed that Weinberg&amp;rsquo;s eyes were pinpoint.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walk and Turn (6/8 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to Weinberg performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. I asked Weinberg if he had any questions. Weinberg stated that he understood the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; Steps out of starting position to prevent falling over twice&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Steps off line&lt;br /&gt; Misses heel to toe&lt;br /&gt; Raises arms for balance&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Steps off line&lt;br /&gt; Misses heel to toe&lt;br /&gt; Raises arms for balance&lt;br /&gt; Takes 10 steps&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Turn:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Incorrect, moves counterclockwise in one large jerky movement almost falling over&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; One Leg Stand (4/4)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to Weinberg performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Weinberg advised that he understood the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; Sways from side to side&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10:&lt;br /&gt; Sways from side to side&lt;br /&gt; Puts foot down&lt;br /&gt; Hops&lt;br /&gt; Raises arms for balance&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20:&lt;br /&gt; Sways from side to side&lt;br /&gt; Puts foot down&lt;br /&gt; Hops&lt;br /&gt; Raises arms for balance&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30:&lt;br /&gt; Sways from side to side&lt;br /&gt; Puts foot down&lt;br /&gt; Hops&lt;br /&gt; Raises arms for balance&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Modified Romberg Balance Test&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I instructed Weinberg to stand with his feet together and arms by his side. Weinberg was instructed to close his eyes and estimate the passage of thirty seconds. Weinberg was instructed to open his eyes and say &amp;ldquo;done&amp;rdquo; when thirty seconds had passed. Weinberg stated that he understood the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Weinberg estimated thirty seconds had passed in 40 seconds&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I instructed Weinberg to stand with his feet together and arms by his side. I instructed Weinberg to extend the index finger of both hands while down at his side. I advised that when I say &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; he was to lift his right index finger, touch the tip of his nose, then put it back down at his side. Weinberg was instructed to do the same with his left index finger when I said &amp;ldquo;Left.&amp;rdquo;. Weinberg stated that he understood the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Left- misses nose&lt;br /&gt; Right-&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Left-&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Right-&lt;br /&gt; Right- misses nose&lt;br /&gt; Left-&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Arrest&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had probable cause to believe Weinberg was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of a controlled dangerous substance:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Unable to maintain a single lane of travel&lt;br /&gt; *Following other vehicle within one car length&lt;br /&gt; *Slow to react to emergency light and sirens&lt;br /&gt; *Pinpoint Pupils&lt;br /&gt; *Slow uncoordinated motor movements&lt;br /&gt; *Gait ataxia&lt;br /&gt; *Admission to taking Heroin prior to driving&lt;br /&gt; *Poor SFST&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At this time Weinberg was placed under arrest for DUI. Weinberg was then handcuffed, searched, and placed in the front seat of R-24 and seat belted inside. Weinberg was then mirandized. Weinberg was then transported to the Westminster Barrack. Weinberg&amp;rsquo;s vehicle was towed by Priority Towing&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Once at the Westminster &amp;nbsp;Barrack Weinberg was walked inside and placed in the intoximeter room. A physical copy of the DR15 was placed in front of him &amp;nbsp;and the audio version was played aloud. At the conclusion of the audio Weinberg stated that he wished to take the intoximeter test. The time was 1335 hours.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 20-Minute Observation Period:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Nothing observed during the observation period.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Intoximeter Result:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; .00 at 1350 hours CPL Eyles 5445 was the intoximeter operator.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked if Weinberg would submit to a DRE evaluation. Weinberg refused. I then contact DRE Eckhardt #6469. Eckhardt then asked Weinberg if he would take a blood test. Weinberg refused. The time was 1411 hours.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Weinberg &amp;nbsp;was then issued the appropriate citations as well as a DR15A. Weinberg was then released to his mother in the front lobby lot of the Westminster Barrack.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All above events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 15:06:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/16/2023 16:25:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Morrison</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6069</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Twardowski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sigman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7376</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511428</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/19/2023 12:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 13:28:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 13:28:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511428</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/19/2023 12:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 13:28:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 13:28:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511428</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/19/2023 12:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 13:28:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 13:28:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511428</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/19/2023 12:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 13:28:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 13:28:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 13:29:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:24</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>36029</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Weinberg</LastName>
               <FirstName>Victor</FirstName>
               <DOB>06/26/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.19088288E8</SSN>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>09/30/2014 13:56:58</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W516</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>V236</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Weinberg</LastName>
               <FirstName>Victor</FirstName>
               <DOB>06/26/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.19088288E8</SSN>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>W516</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>V236</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/30/2014 13:56:58</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2004</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Herbert</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Westminster</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21157</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.00089</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.518346</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>984</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3769</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/30/2014 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>984</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5457</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/30/2014 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 13:29:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:16</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 13:29:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:16</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 13:29:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:16</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 13:29:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:16</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 13:29:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:16</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/21/2023 17:03:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/21/2023 17:03:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154326</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 13:33:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 13:33:51</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FTPW14595FB35183</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2005</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>F15</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4FJ4953</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/19/2023 21:13:35</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/19/2023 21:13:35</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 21:44:11</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6469</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 21:13:35</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Date and time of evaluation: 06/19/2023 1402 Hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;MSP Case number: 23-MSP-021992&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Other Agency Case number: N/A&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rolling log number: 23-006-0090&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Location of evaluation: Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Suspect: Weinberg Jr., Victor&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Date of birth: 06/26/1985&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Breath Alcohol Test&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The suspect submitted to a breath alcohol test with the arresting officer which resulted a 0.00 BrAC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Interview of Arresting Officer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On June 19, 2023, I (TFC Eckhardt #6469), was contacted by Tpr. Sigman #7376 of the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack. He stated that he had a subject at the Westminster Barrack who had submitted to the breath test and had a result inconsistent with his observations of impairment. I was in an off duty status and could have responded to the Barrack; however, Tpr. Sigman advised that he asked his subject if they would be willing to submit to a DRE evaluation and they refused.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I spoke with Tpr. Signman and asked what took place. He explained that his arrestee, Victor Weinberg, was driving his vehicle, a Ford F150, in front of him in Carroll County. He observed the Ford following the vehicle in front of it too closely. He observed the Ford get closer to the vehicle in front of it and then suddenly brake. He also observed the Ford failing to maintain its lane. A MVA check also revealed that the Fords registration was expired. He conducted a stop on the vehicle and identified the driver as Weinberg. While speaking with Weinberg he observed his pupils to be pinpoint and his speech to be slow and lethargic. He also observed Weinberg&amp;rsquo;s motor skills to be slow and uncoordinated. After asking Weinberg out of the vehicle, he observed his balance to be poor. Weinberg did admit to narcotic use earlier in the day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Based on his observations, Tpr. Sigman placed Weinberg through SFST&amp;rsquo;s. He observed HGN 0/6 clues, WAT 6/8 clues, and OLS 4/4 clues. Based on his observations, Tpr. Sigman placed Weinberg under arrest for driving impaired. While back at the Westminster Barrack, Weinberg agreed to the breath test, which had a result of 0.00 BrAC, a result inconsistent with the level of impairment observed by Tpr. Sigman.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Preliminary Evaluation &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Due to Weinberg refusing to even speak with a DRE, I elected to not respond to the Barrack. Based on the detailed observations that Tpr. Sigman provided me, I developed enough reasonable suspicion to believe that Weinberg was under the influence of a controlled dangerous substance and to request a blood kit.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. Examination of the eyes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Not completed. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;5. Divided Attention Tests&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Not completed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;6. Vital Signs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Not completed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;7. Dark Room Examination &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Not completed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;8. Muscle Tone Examination&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Not completed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;9. Injection Site Examination&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Not completed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;10. Observations and Subject Statements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Not completed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;11. Opinion of Evaluator &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In my opinion as a certified Drug Recognition Expert, I have enough reasonable suspicion to believe that Victor Weinberg Jr., is under the influence of a controlled dangerous substance, impaired, and cannot operate a motor vehicle safely.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;My opinion is based on the observations made by Tpr. Sigman&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;12. Toxicology Exam&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Tpr. Sigman advised Weinberg of my request for a blood kit and the MVA sanctions that would be imposed if he agreed or refused the test. Ultimately, Weinberg refused the blood test. I issued a DR23 to Tpr. Sigman for the DR-15A.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;13. Miscellaneous&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;N/A&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6469</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 21:13:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6469</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 21:22:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Snedeker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5367</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckhardt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derek</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6469</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>