<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-028568</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40L</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/13/2023 01:46:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/13/2023 01:46:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/13/2023 01:41:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/13/2023 01:41:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Assist Other Agency</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:46:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1897</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 09:20:55</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>Homicide occurred in Ohio, suspect was stopped by MSP patrol in Frederick Co, Md.</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>703746</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:46:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/17/2023 09:08:15</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>703746</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Marcies Choice</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Frederick</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.415929183</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.3656630719</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MARCIES CHOICE LN / RT85</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/13/2023 01:46:00</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/13/2023 01:46:00</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40L</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/14/2023 09:20:23</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:46:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP1897</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 09:20:37</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 8/12/23, at approximately 1830 hours, I was notified by D/Sgt Knight of the Homicide Unit that MSP patrol Troopers had detained a homicide suspect from Ohio. D/Sgt Knight then sent me a report detailing that Wauseon Police Department Officers from Fulton County, Ohio responded to the scene of a homicide located at 407 E Park Street in Wauseon, Ohio 43567, at approximately 0800 hours on 8/12/23. The reports advised that police responded to the above residence, and discovered a deceased male, Edwin Ramos-Aguilera, with an open wound to the throat, on the front porch of the residence. According to the report, at the time officers responded, Ramos-Aguilera&amp;rsquo;s wife, Candelaria Cespedes De Aguilera was banging on a neighbor&amp;rsquo;s door. She responded back to where Ramos-Aguilera was, and informed police that their son, Jose Daniel Aguilera Cespedes, had sliced Ramos-Aguilera&amp;rsquo;s throat. In the report, De Aguilera advised that Cespedes had a fight with his father. In the report, police noted that Cespedes de Aguilera was also injured and covered in blood. Cespedes de Aguilera stated that her son, Cespedes, suffers from mental illness.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Ohio law enforcement reported to MSP that Cespedes&amp;nbsp;fled the scene prior to police arriving. Detectives from Ohio &amp;quot;pinged&amp;quot; Cespedes&amp;#39; cell phone, and contacted MSP Hagerstown Barrack when they observed the cell phone traveling along on I-70 in Maryland. Hagerstown Barrack Troopers located the suspect vehicle, a 2015 Black Honda Accord with Ohio registration JAD7450. The vehicle then traveled into Frederick County, Maryland, where Troopers attempted to conduct a traffic stop on I-70 E/B at the 48 mm. The suspect vehicle fled the traffic stop. The suspect vehicle later encountered heavy traffic, and Troopers were able to take the driver, identified as Jose Daniel Aguilera Cespedes, into custody, in Frederick County, Md at the 51mm.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; D/Sgt. Knight requested that MSP Homicide investigators respond to the Frederick County Adult Detention Center, located at 7300 Marcies Choice Lane, Frederick, MD 21704, in order to seize clothing from Cespedes, and attempt to interview him.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 8/12/23, I completed a search warrant to seize Cespedes&amp;#39; clothing, and responded to the Frederick County Detention Center, where Cespedes was being held on an arrest warrant from Ohio. Sgt. Jonathan Martin of the MSP Homicide unit responded to the detention facility with me, as well.&amp;nbsp; Together we spoke with Cespedes after he waived Miranda Rights.&amp;nbsp; The interview was audibly recorded.&amp;nbsp; Please refer to the actual audio recording for exact details.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes was read Miranda Rights at 2333 hours.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes signed the MSP Miranda Form, and agreed to waive his Miranda Rights.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes explained that he went to Maryland because he bought tickets for a Ravens game, and they were playing against the Eagles.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he wanted to be honest with us.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that when he was in 8th grade, he saw a video, and he was a perfectly normal kid until then. Cespedes advised that the video woke him up, and it explained that there were some really bad people out there who did things to innocent people.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes explained that the video impacted him, but he stayed quiet about it.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he knows he isn&amp;#39;t crazy, and he knows the things he has seen and heard.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised, referring to Ohio, that there are factories, and the workers keep children and babies, and innocent people there.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes elaborated that there were 5 year olds and 10 year olds there, and they are deep, deep underground, so you can&amp;#39;t hear anything.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that they will work their shifts, then they&amp;#39;ll go underground and do these things, to the children that they keep.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes added that they will just clean up, have showers, put their clothes back on, and just go home.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes began to name factories where he said that this occurred at.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that his father worked at one of the factories, also.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes advised that he knows his father is a really powerful guy.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he is the guy who is supposed to help his father.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes then went on to explain that he is not from Santa Cruz, Bolivia, but is instead from Egypt.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes advised that his parents have brainwashed him since he was a baby, and they don&amp;#39;t want his mind to work.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he moved here when he was 4 years old.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes explained that he had a difficult childhood because he didn&amp;#39;t know any English.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he was made fun of because of that, and was awkward and shy.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes then inferred that he is not great at speaking Spanish now.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that his dad, who was bald, would often tell Cespedes in Spanish that he was going to die without hair.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he later learned the Spanish word that his dad was using, actually meant that he would die a crazy death.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that his parents were just mocking him.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespdes advised that his parents sacrifice each other and kids, and stuff.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes went on to describe that his parents need to sacrifice people that they have a connection with, in order to get more kids.&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes if he believed his parents were part of that.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that they were, 100%, and stated that both his mom and his dad were.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that his parents make sick jokes all the time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes advised that he is Daniel.&amp;nbsp; Cespdes stated that he is a son of God, not &amp;quot;the&amp;quot; son of God.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes clarified that he is really just here to help God out, and explain his world.&amp;nbsp; Cespdes advised that he is a regular human being, and God helped him.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes informed us that he knows he has made a lot of progress, and all eyes are on him.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised he is just trying to help people.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I stated to Cespedes that I heard him mention his mom.&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes what happened with his mom today.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that they knew he was going to Baltimore, and they didn&amp;#39;t want him to go to Baltimore.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes explained that when he goes out, or becomes really happy, or gets love from people, it gives him energy.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he can think a lot more clearly.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes described that if he went to Baltimore and maybe met some players, or just watched the team, it would give him something.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes explained that his parents didn&amp;#39;t want him to do small stuff like that.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that &amp;quot;they&amp;quot; just didn&amp;#39;t want him to go.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if he saw this as them preventing Cespedes from being happy and getting energy.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised yes, and that he thought he made a lot of progress explaining about God, and who he is, and the whole network.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that we needed the whole story of how everyone got here, from Native Americans to the angels, to how we got here today.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes advised that there is a whole website about him (Cespedes), and he doesn&amp;#39;t know what it is.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if he knew what the website was.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;They know the website.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he isn&amp;#39;t allowed to see the website, and he has never known about it.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that his parents have the website and millions, and millions of other people.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes guessed it is the most looked at website in the country right now.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that &amp;quot;they&amp;quot; know his thoughts, and &amp;quot;they&amp;quot; put a chip in him when he was 8.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes added that &amp;quot;they&amp;quot; know what he thinks, what he&amp;#39;s looking at, everything he&amp;#39;s doing, and how he feels.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that his whole life is on this website.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes how long he has known about this website.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he knew about the website 2 years ago, when he was big enough.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes explained that he didn&amp;#39;t understand how everyone knew so much about it.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes added, &amp;quot;It&amp;#39;s like my thoughts.&amp;nbsp; It has to be the website.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes continued by adding that he knows a lot of people on it, and that one time Trump talked about the website and said it was the most viewed website in the country.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he realized all eyes were on him, and he would do what he could to help people.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes what was different about today.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin explained that he assumed in the past his parents have told him not to do something he wanted to do.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin explained that even in his twenties, his parents told him no before.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes to explain what was different about today compared to other times.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he didn&amp;#39;t think it was just today.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that it was building up, and today was just the straw that broke the camel&amp;#39;s back.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes added that he feels empathy for people, and he&amp;#39;s not a monster.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;So, I know what I did today.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; There was a pause, and Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;I know I&amp;#39;m just listening to my father.&amp;nbsp; He really wanted me to do it.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes what he meant by &amp;quot;do it.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked if we could just clear that up.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes did not answer.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin informed Cespedes that if he wasn&amp;#39;t ready, it was okay, but &amp;quot;it&amp;quot; has a lot of meanings.&amp;nbsp; I emphasized to Cespedes that we weren&amp;#39;t here to judge him.&amp;nbsp; I informed Cespedes that we talk to people, every day, from all walks of life, and everyone uses different language and different words when they talk.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes then stated, &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t think this is going to help me.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if he was more comfortable talking about the prior conflict, and the website and the chip.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he was more comfortable talking about that.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that everyone already knows about those things.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin advised that he was just trying to figure out what changed today, and what happened.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes advised, &amp;quot;I get a lot of confidence from him. I just trust him.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes explained that he has taken a lot of risks in his life because of what &amp;quot;he&amp;quot; has told him (Cespedes).&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised, &amp;quot;He&amp;#39;s just so beautiful,&amp;quot; and then added, &amp;quot;How could you not trust him?&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he (Cespedes) isn&amp;#39;t perfect, and he (Cespedes) fucks up a lot.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes informed us that even when he (Cespedes) fucks up, &amp;quot;he&amp;quot; is always going to love him (Cespedes).&amp;nbsp; Cespedes asked us, &amp;quot;Why would I not trust someone like that?&amp;quot; Cespedes added, &amp;quot;He&amp;#39;s told me like everything I needed to do and say.&amp;quot; Cespedes began naming off numbers, that he related to who he was referring to.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes correlated the numbers &amp;quot;555&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m gonna talk to you&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;666&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;It&amp;#39;s gonna take some courage to let go.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes continued to name off numbers that referred to who he was talking to.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes conveyed that he spoke to the person he was referring to, by utilizing these numbers.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that every step of the way, &amp;quot;he&amp;quot; has been with Cespedes.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes informed us that even when times get hard and he (Cespedes) wants to give up, &amp;quot;he&amp;quot; is still right.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I referred Cespedes back to when he said that &amp;quot;he&amp;quot; told Cespedes to do it.&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes if he was talking about God.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes said yes.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;He&amp;#39;s telling me that if I get in trouble, I can just call him.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that today, he was talking to God a lot, and God told Cespedes to trust him.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes advised that he was sent down here, with a message.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he gave his message, the statue is gone and toppled, and Michelle is gone.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes then began talking about the war in heaven, which included lawyers arguing and someone named Michelle.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes went into detail about Michelle not being on the same side as God.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he is from the 2nd earth, so he did not fall for what Michelle was saying.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes then spoke about what heaven was like.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that heaven is awesome, beautiful, and you have free will.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes compared being in heaven to being in a relationship, in that everyone there chooses to serve God and follow his laws.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that everyone there has to pass two tests.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that when you pass the first test, you grow by 7 years.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes added that the other test is a test of beauty.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes compared the tests to being a girl, and being cheated on by a guy that you like.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes continued to talk about relationships.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I made an attempt to redirect Cespedes away from this conversation.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes requested that he finish.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes began talking about the test in heaven again.&amp;nbsp; During this, Cespedes&amp;#39; voice was loud, clear and confident.&amp;nbsp; I then interrupted Cespedes and asked him why God would want his father to die or be killed.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes informed me that he was getting to that.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes went back to talking about the test that is given in heaven.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that God has a ring attached to his finger, and he places his hand over a flame or a blue cube, and that&amp;#39;s how he makes everything.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that two Arab brothers in heaven got control of the blue cube, in order to make themselves God.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that the Arab brothers failed, so God made a new earth.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes then spoke about fallen Angels and alliances that the Arab brothers were attempting to make.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes advised that he was God&amp;#39;s son, and he was helping God save this earth.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that God also sent his daughter, named Molly, who is a queen.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes explained that Molly went down and completely fucked up everything on earth, and exposed the Arab brothers.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that Molly is just a vessel, and it&amp;#39;s actually God.&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes if that happens with him, and he stated that is correct.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes informed us that everyone in heaven who stayed, and didn&amp;#39;t go with the Arab brothers, passed the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes stated that the previous earth was a lot harder for girls than it was for guys.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that this earth is a lot harder for guys than it is for girls.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that this earth is about power and no emotion.&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes to explain what God told him to do today, if he is a vessel for God.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he is working through that story, and he is practically done with it.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes continued by saying that Michelle is fucking everything up right now, and God is letting her do it.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that the Arab brothers wanted the blue cube, but Michelle wants the flame.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that God is letting Michelle fuck everything up so that everyone can see that it would be bad if Michelle ever got the flame.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Cespedes if his parents were of God, or were children of God.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;Uh, no, I think they&amp;#39;re really bad people.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes if God pointed out to him that they were not his children.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;A lot of people,&amp;quot; and went on to add the people who work in the factories.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he thinks a lot of people know he is God&amp;#39;s son. I asked Cespedes what God said to him today because he said that God wanted him to &amp;quot;do that.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that God told him to have some courage because it was going to be a big risk.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes added that God told him he was going to have to have some faith.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that God told him, &amp;quot;We gotta get these guys outta here.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that God told him he might get in trouble.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that the whole week was, &amp;quot;Orange and green, orange and green, orange and green.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes what that meant, and he said that orange is courage is green is faith.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that &amp;quot;777&amp;quot; is faith and is green.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that &amp;quot;666&amp;quot; is courage and it&amp;#39;s orange.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he trusts him, referring to God, and he knows that God has his back.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes added that he tried to call God multiple times today from different numbers.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that God wants Cespedes to call him, but Cespedes doesn&amp;#39;t know the number.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he thinks he called God, and &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m almost sure that he&amp;#39;s got my back.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Martin informed Cespedes he had been building up orange and green all week.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if he had been thinking about killing his parents all week.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised, &amp;quot;No, not about killing them.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes added that his parents are a bunch of pedophiles.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked if that was a mistake today.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that if we just go to all of the factories, they&amp;#39;re there.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if his mom was involved in that, too.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes confirmed that his mom and dad both worked in factories that did this.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if it was his job to kill all of them.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he is here to help expose them.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes stated that when he was alive in his previous life he was really, really powerful.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes explained that he protected the Rocky Mountains from being destroyed.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he made the Mississippi River and every river attached to it.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if his parents tried to stop him from this goal.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked, &amp;quot;What caused you to kill them today?&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;Well, they&amp;#39;re pedophiles.&amp;nbsp; They beat and rape children.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes went back to saying that when the Vikings were around, he was pretty powerful back then.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin attempted to get Cespedes to explain why he killed his parents.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that his parents didn&amp;#39;t want him to know all of this.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes clarified that his parents didn&amp;#39;t want him to know the colors, numbers and shapes.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he isn&amp;#39;t supposed to know he&amp;#39;s Daniel, and he isn&amp;#39;t supposed to be telling people about this.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes described that today God told him that he had Cespedes&amp;#39; back.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if ultimately, today was his decision then.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;No, I think it was God&amp;#39;s decision.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes informed us that he thinks God is going to come down here as &amp;quot;George&amp;quot; with khaki pants, boots, a belt, a vest, a long sleeve white t-shirt, and a hat.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that when God walks, he has a baseball cap, and you can&amp;#39;t see his face.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes described that when God walks, he walks where the sun hits him at an angle so that there is a shadow over his face, and you can&amp;#39;t see his face.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Martin stated to Cespedes that God didn&amp;#39;t tell him to kill his parents today.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that God told him to.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that all week God had been building him up, and he didn&amp;#39;t tell anyone else about it.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked what happened after he did it.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised he went to watch the Baltimore Ravens game.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes advised that there are a lot of things he needs to tell people.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he used to play Safety.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes informed us that flowers make you bigger, faster, and stronger.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes began talking about trees then.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes then began talking about white people with different colored hair, and the traits that they have.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then interrupted Cespedes and told him that I had a question.&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes if God told him how he was supposed to kill his parents, or if God talked him through it.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;I think I was just supposed to do it.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin again asked Cespedes why this didn&amp;#39;t happen at another time.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that it was building up.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin informed Cespedes that he was worried there would be skeptics who would say Cespedes killed his parents because they told him no about going to Baltimore.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that it wasn&amp;#39;t because he got angry when they told him no.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes added it was because of who they are, and all of this shit they have done.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that they are monsters, and they&amp;#39;re bad.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes informed us that the world is so dark, and you can&amp;#39;t have monsters here.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if he was upset about what he did to them.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes asked, &amp;quot;Me?&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin explained that at first, he (Cespedes) wouldn&amp;#39;t tell us about them, and he (Cespedes) didn&amp;#39;t seem to want to tell us that he killed them, and how he did it.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;Yeah, I totally agree.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin questioned why that was.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he didn&amp;#39;t know if we were trustworthy or not.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes added that he didn&amp;#39;t think it mattered at this point.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Martin pointed out to Cespedes that he spent so much time explaining everything to us, that he didn&amp;#39;t see why trust would matter.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes questioned, &amp;quot;Why I shouldn&amp;#39;t trust God?&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin clarified that it shouldn&amp;#39;t matter whether or not he (Cespedes) trusts us.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he thought this might be a waste of his time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if he thought his mom was dead, too.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t know.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he doesn&amp;#39;t know what happened to his real mom.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes informed us that he was Arab.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin and I explained to Cespedes that we were talking about his mom on earth, today.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes explained that what happened with Jesus, and the Virgin Mary, is the same thing that happened with his mom.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes clarified that his parents today are not his real parents.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked if the mom from today should be dead, too.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes stated that he was kidnapped from his mom.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes referred back to the factory and the people there abusing people.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin and I asked Cespedes if his parents abused him.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that they did not.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes then told a story about an uncle who would touch his butt, and made him feel uncomfortable.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that his uncle died maybe a year ago.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes what the movie was that he said he watched in 8th grade.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;I, Pet Goat II.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; When Sgt. Martin and I asked for clarification, Cespedes stated that he didn&amp;#39;t know if it mattered.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that the prophecy is that if fucks up, up it&amp;#39;s not his (Cespedes&amp;#39;) fault, it&amp;#39;s God&amp;#39;s fault.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes explained that it&amp;#39;s God&amp;#39;s fault because God should have never trusted him and sent him down here.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he didn&amp;#39;t fuck up, and God was right to trust him.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that today was following through with trust.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes how he gets past the part in the Bible that says, &amp;quot;Thou shalt not kill.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he doesn&amp;#39;t believe in the Bible, even thought he thinks some parts are beautiful.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if he believed that the Bible was God&amp;#39;s inspired Scripture.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he doesn&amp;#39;t think it&amp;#39;s from God, but believes it&amp;#39;s from Michelle, instead.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that there are things that are accurate in the Bible, and God is in the Bible.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that there is a one, true God.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that God does speak directly to him, and helps him out a lot.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he loves God, and he loves everyone else, too.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Cespedes if he had an expectation about what would happen, after leaving his parents.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he was going to watch the game.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that because God has his back, he thinks it&amp;#39;ll be alright.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes commented that he was calm right now because he has been in so many situations that God has gotten him out of.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes commented that it doesn&amp;#39;t matter how bad the cards are stacked against him.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if the cards were against him because he committed murder.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes paused and then stated that he thinks a lot of Native Americans committed murder because people were trying to kill them.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked if he intended to turn himself in after the game.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he did not.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes what he was going to do after the game.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;Walk around free.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes if he was going to go back home.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;No.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if he would never return to Ohio.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he would probably return to Ohio.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if he learned that his parents were still alive, would that be a failure to him.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that they were monsters.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that people will find those kids, and eventually they&amp;#39;ll be released.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked Cespedes if he would go back and kill them if he learned they were still alive.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he didn&amp;#39;t want any monsters here on earth.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he doesn&amp;#39;t know how many monsters are here, but he doesn&amp;#39;t want them here.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes added that they can&amp;#39;t be doing the things they do, and just enjoy all the shit in front of them like it&amp;#39;s okay.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes referred to God watching over the whole earth, and asked if we thought God was watching them do what they were doing, like they had some kind of power over him (God).&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that God fucked up a whole earth, and he doesn&amp;#39;t give a shit.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes advised that God is letting Michelle do this.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin pointed out to Cespedes that if God wanted Michelle to run rampant, that would mean that he should not have killed his parents.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;No, I&amp;#39;m his vessel, so...&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that God sits on his throne, and only comes out in rare occasions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Cespedes what he thinks about himself, sitting here, in another state.&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes if that was part of the plan.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that God has his back.&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes if God told him to kill his parents.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;He told me to expose everyone.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes, &amp;quot;So he didn&amp;#39;t tell you to kill your parents?&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes didn&amp;#39;t answer.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked, &amp;quot;You were supposed to expose this?&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;Well, they are exposed right now.&amp;nbsp; A lot of people see why.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised, &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t know.&amp;nbsp; I just know God is God.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes went back to talking about Molly and how she was a vessel.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he isn&amp;#39;t going to fight God because he&amp;#39;s 10 feet tall.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Cespedes if it was easy today, and if God gave him the power to do that.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t think it matters.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Both Sgt. Martin and I explained to Cespedes that it does matter.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin advised that these people raised him for a number of years, and he had feelings for them.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that they are monsters.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes reminded us that his dad told him he would have a crazy death.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Cespedes if his dad fought back today or if it was easy.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes was silent, and stared down at his hands.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes then stated, &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t think this matters.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin pointed out to Cespedes that he was staring down at his hands because he felt guilt and remorse.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;No I don&amp;#39;t.&amp;nbsp; Trust me.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes why he wouldn&amp;#39;t tell us then.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised, &amp;quot;I just don&amp;#39;t think it matters.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes eventually conceded that God did not make him strong in order to do this.&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes if his dad fought back.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes again stated that it didn&amp;#39;t matter.&amp;nbsp; I explained to Cespedes that I&amp;#39;m wondering if God gave him all the power to do this.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;And I said no to that.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I stated to Cespedes that it was just human body killing another human body.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;Uh yeah, I didn&amp;#39;t have any super powers then.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin stated, &amp;quot;So just you had to be stronger than him and able to kill him.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated yes.&amp;nbsp; Sgt. Martin asked if it would have been easier with super powers.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes confirmed that it would be.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Cespedes if it was the same thing with his mom.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated he thinks it&amp;#39;s going to be alright.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Martin asked where he went afterwards.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he stopped to get gas.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes denied talking to anyone, and advised he was just in his car.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Cespedes where his parents were when he left.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised both of his parents were outside on the porch when he left.&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes if either of them asked for help when he was leaving.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that he doesn&amp;#39;t know why this matters.&amp;nbsp; I explained that I wanted to talk to him about what happened today.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes informed us that he is supposed to be getting married and having a family.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes went back to talking about the tests in heaven.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes began referring to the colors again.&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes if he believed he was the prophet Daniel.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes didn&amp;#39;t answer.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that the Golden Age is almost here, and God is going to flood the whole earth.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that in the Golden Age, you get your spouse.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated that sex is frowned upon in heaven.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I interrupted Cespedes again and asked if he thought that he was the prophet Daniel.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes advised that he was not, but he is the son of God.&amp;nbsp; I summarized for Cespedes that he is the son of God, his parents are on the porch, bleeding, injured, and he left.&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes if he offered them assistance, or if they asked for help.&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes to tell me what that looked like.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated, &amp;quot;Uh, I just left.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked Cespedes if he knew they were going to die.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes informed us, &amp;quot;They&amp;#39;re dead.&amp;nbsp; Why does it matter if I was like...how I did it?&amp;nbsp; They&amp;#39;re dead.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cespedes stated that he thinks God is going to come down.&amp;nbsp; We asked Cespedes if there was anything else he wanted to tell us, or if there was anything else he needed to talk about.&amp;nbsp; Cespedes stated no.&amp;nbsp; This concluded our interview with Cespedes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Following the interview, investigators seized Cespedes&amp;#39; pants, shirt, and shoes, pursuant to the search warrant.&amp;nbsp; After removing Cespedes&amp;#39; shoes, investigators observed suspected blood on Cespedes&amp;#39; socks, however, socks were not listed as items to be seized in the search warrant.&amp;nbsp; Detention Center personnel seized the socks from Cespedes, and placed them in a bag, after investigators explained that they would write an additional search warrant to seize the socks, and would return the following day with the search warrant.&amp;nbsp; Additionally, Detention Center personnel advised that when Cespedes was brought into the detention center, he also had a knit hat and wallet on his person.&amp;nbsp; Investigators advised that they would add those items to the search warrant that would be completed the following day.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 8/13/23, I, Cpl Ward, responded back to the Detention Center, and seized the socks, knit hat, and wallet belonging to Cespedes.&amp;nbsp; The search warrants were presented to both the Detention Center, and then to Cespedes, who signed for the release of his items.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All of the above events occurred in Frederick County, Maryland and Fulton County, Ohio.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/17/2023 09:12:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 13:55:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40L</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Knight</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1897</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40L</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ward</LastName>
            <FirstName>Amanda</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5570</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>25</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/17/2023 09:11:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/17/2023 09:11:05</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>384993</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cespedes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jose</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Aguilera</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/01/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>8.42747986E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>08/12/2023 19:50:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C213</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cespedes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jose</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Aguilera</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/01/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>8.42747986E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>C213</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/12/2023 19:50:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>407</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Park</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Wauseon</City>
               <StateCode>OH</StateCode>
               <Zip5>43567</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-84.139453</Longitude>
               <Latitude>41.543979</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>419</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>388</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9793</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/12/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/17/2023 09:11:05</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/03/2023 14:20:27</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/03/2023 14:20:27</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40L</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/14/2023 09:20:37</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP4841</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 14:20:27</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP1897</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 09:20:37</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On Saturday, August 12th, 2023, I assisted Cpl. Ward with an interview of the above listed suspect.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I also assisted with a search warrant completed at the Frederick County Detention Center afterward.&amp;nbsp; This supplement is issued to facilitate the uploading of my attached notes.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;See. Cpl. Ward&amp;#39;s report / interview recording for details of the interview.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Report Closed.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4841</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 14:21:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4841</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 14:23:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40L</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Knight</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1897</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40L</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jonathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4841</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>