<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-004503</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/05/2023 03:10:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/05/2023 03:10:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/05/2023 02:52:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/05/2023 02:52:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/05/2023 03:10:28</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/07/2023 08:16:36</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MD-295 / RIDGE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>544381</AddressId>
      <City>MDC430</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/05/2023 03:10:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/05/2023 04:16:18</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>544381</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Md-295</StreetName>
         <City>Hanover</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.70267</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.1981</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10391-11389 MD-295 / 6974-6996 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11401-11559 MD-295 / 6957-6969 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10394-11400 MD-295 / 6956-6968 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10393-11399 MD-295 / 6957-6969 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10394-11400 MD-295 / 6957-6969 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11392-11510 MD-295 / 6971-6973 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11391-11509 MD-295 / 6971-6973 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MD-295 / 915</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10391-11389 MD-295 / 6971-6973 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 MD-295 / 0-0 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 MD-295 / 6948-6980 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/05/2023 03:10:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/05/2023 03:10:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/06/2023 05:45:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/05/2023 03:10:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 05:45:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>ELENA SUZETTE VERGARA&lt;br /&gt; DOB: 04/23/2001&lt;br /&gt; TN SOUNDEX: 150827&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;027&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:18px"&gt;This traffic stop and arrest was audibly and visually recorded via body worn camera. My marked patrol vehicle, MV-26, is NOT fitted with recording equipment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE IN MOTION:&lt;br /&gt; On Sunday, February 5th, 2023, at approximately 0250 hours, I was traveling southbound on MD 295 in the area of I-195 in Anne Arundel County, Maryland. I was traveling in the far right lane, lane 2. I was traveling directly behind a black Toyota Corolla bearing expired Maryland temporary registration T1119706. I observed the vehicle slowly swerving to the right and left within their lane. I then observed the vehicle drift to the left crossing over partially into lane 1. The vehicle quickly jerked back to the right. I observed the vehicle drift one again to the left, crossing partially into lane 1 another time. The vehicle then slowly drifted back to the right into lane 2. I observed the vehicle drift to the right, crossing over the solid white line onto the shoulder and rolling over the rumble strips for a short period of time. The vehicle quickly jerked back into the roadway. I activated my emergency lights to initiate a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle slowed down and stopped on the right shoulder.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PERSONAL CONTACT:&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the driver via a passenger side approach to the vehicle. I observed a female driver seated in the driver&amp;#39;s seat and a male passenger in the right front passenger seat. I stood at the front passenger window for a long period of time before the window was rolled down. When the front passenger window was rolled down, I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from inside the vehicle. I introduced myself and explained the reason for the traffic stop. The driver stated &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m just really tired&amp;quot;. I asked the driver for her license and vehicle registration, to which she provided her license and could not locate the registration. I identified the driver as Elena Suzette Vergara W/F DOB 4/23/01 by her Tennessee driver&amp;#39;s license. I asked&amp;nbsp;Vergara how much she had to drink. She pointed over the passenger, later identified as her husband, stating he had been drinking. I noticed&amp;nbsp;Vergara&amp;#39;s eyes were bloodshot and glassy and her speech was slurred. I returned to my patrol vehicle for a few moments. I made my second approach to&amp;nbsp;Vergara&amp;#39;s vehicle via a driver&amp;#39;s side approach. I asked&amp;nbsp;Vergara to exit her vehicle.&amp;nbsp;Vergara shook her head and stated &amp;quot;no, absolutely not.&amp;quot; I explained to&amp;nbsp;Vergara I could smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from the vehicle and wanted to make sure she was safe to drive. I advised&amp;nbsp;Vergara that if she refused standardized field sobriety testing, she would be placed under arrest.&amp;nbsp;Vergara stated she was unfamiliar with Maryland laws.&amp;nbsp;Vergara eventually exited her vehicle and submitted to standardized field sobriety testing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Standardized field sobriety testing was conducted on a flat surface clear of any debris.&amp;nbsp;Vergara had not taken any drugs or medications.&amp;nbsp;Vergara stated her last alcoholic drink was approximately 2 hours ago.&amp;nbsp;Vergara stated they were coming from Baltimore Sound Stage.&amp;nbsp;Vergara did not have any injuries and stated she may have low blood sugar.&amp;nbsp;Vergara stated she is not under the care of a doctor for low blood sugar. While outside of the vehicle standing directly in front of me, I could smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from&amp;nbsp;Vergara&amp;#39;s breath and person.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS:&lt;br /&gt; The tip of my pen was utilized as the stimulus for the duration of this test.&amp;nbsp;Vergara had red colored contact lenses in both eyes that were for cosmetic purposes only.&amp;nbsp;Vergara stated she has glasses but did not have them on.&amp;nbsp;Vergara stated she could see the stimulus. I observed both of&amp;nbsp;Vergara&amp;#39;s pupils were equal in size and displayed equal tracking. Both eyes displayed lack of smooth pursuit. Both eyes displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation. I observed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes. Vertical gaze nystagmus was present in both eyes. I observed a total of 6 out of 6 clues.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN:&lt;br /&gt; Vergara was wearing slide sandals that she stated she was comfortable wearing for this test. I explained and demonstrated the walk and turn test to&amp;nbsp;Vergara. I explained and demonstrated to&amp;nbsp;Vergara to place her right foot in front of her left, touching her heel to her toe in a straight line with her arms to her sides. I instructed her to remain in this position while I demonstrated the test to her. I explained and demonstrated to take 9 heel to toe steps forward, complete a turn how I demonstrated, then take another 9 heel to toe steps on that same line.&amp;nbsp;Vergara stated she understood the testing instructions.&amp;nbsp;Vergara was swaying and leaning to the right, causing her to lose her balance in the instructional phase before beginning the test.&amp;nbsp;Vergara missed touching her heel to her toe with every step in both sets.&amp;nbsp;Vergara completed an improper turn after the first set of steps.&amp;nbsp;Vergara stopped to regain her balance half way through her second set.&amp;nbsp;Vergara stepped off line with the majority of her steps.&amp;nbsp;Vergara raised both arms from her sides more than 6 inches. I observed a total of 6 out of 8 clues.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ONE LEG STAND:&lt;br /&gt; I explained and demonstrated the one leg stand test to&amp;nbsp;Vergara. I explained and demonstrated to choose whichever leg she felt more comfortable with and raise one foot in the air 6 inches. I advised to keep both legs straight and both arms to her sides, keeping her raised foot parallel to the ground counting out loud as she balanced.&amp;nbsp;Vergara stated she understood the testing instructions.&amp;nbsp;Vergara balanced on her right foot, raising her left.&amp;nbsp;Vergara was swaying from side to side. I observed 1 clue.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A preliminary breath test (PBT) was offered to&amp;nbsp;Vergara, to which she agreed. The PBT displayed the result of 0.10.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ARREST:&lt;br /&gt; Based on my observations of&amp;nbsp;Vergara&amp;#39;s driving and standardized field sobriety testing, I placed her under arrest for DUI at 0310 hours. I transported&amp;nbsp;Vergara to the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack for further processing. TFC Smith transported her husband to the barrack as well. The vehicle was secured on the right shoulder. The audio version of the DR-15 Advice of Rights was played for&amp;nbsp;Vergara inside my patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp;Vergara refused to submit to a breath test at 0325 hours.&amp;nbsp;Vergara was provided with copies of the DR-15, DR-15A, and traffic citations.&amp;nbsp;Vergara stated she was in the US Coast Guard and was able to contact a co-worker to pick her and her husband up from the barrack.&amp;nbsp;Vergara was released from the barrack to a sober ride at 0432 hours.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/05/2023 04:18:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6589</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/05/2023 05:36:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kelvin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6317</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5006</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wahl</LastName>
            <FirstName>Corey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6589</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493886</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/05/2023 02:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/05/2023 04:16:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6589</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/05/2023 04:16:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/05/2023 04:17:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:19</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368172</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>VERGARA</LastName>
               <FirstName>ELENA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>SUZETTE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/23/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/05/2023 04:11:20</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>V626</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E450</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>VERGARA</LastName>
               <FirstName>ELENA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>SUZETTE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/23/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>V626</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E450</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/05/2023 04:11:20</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetName>MAPES</StreetName>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.73602</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.10386</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6589</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/05/2023 04:17:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:43</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6589</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/05/2023 04:17:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:43</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6589</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/05/2023 04:16:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6589</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/05/2023 04:16:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>