<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-024910</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/12/2023 12:00:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/12/2023 12:00:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/12/2023 10:41:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/12/2023 10:41:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>alleged assault; landlord-tenant dispute</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/12/2023 12:00:48</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/20/2023 11:04:18</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DIS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>.6 miles down single lane paved road and then across a creek</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>344693</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/12/2023 12:00:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/12/2023 12:48:26</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>344693</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2929</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Hampstead Mexico</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Hampstead</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21074</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.889678</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.606986</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/12/2023 12:00:44</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/12/2023 12:00:44</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/13/2023 02:16:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/12/2023 12:00:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:49</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;strong&gt;Attached documents&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DILLON, Laura METERS 27&lt;br /&gt; POFF, Carolyn METERS 27&lt;br /&gt; POFF, Ronald METERS 27&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Report number&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 23-MSP-024910&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Originating MSP Trooper&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; TPR Bukoski #7570&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Service Type&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 911 Call&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dispatch number&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 2023-00282448&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Victim&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DILLON, Laura Lee&lt;br /&gt; 2/F DOB 03/31/1959&lt;br /&gt; Hgt: 5&amp;rsquo;02&amp;rdquo; Wgt: 120lbs&lt;br /&gt; Hair: Gray, rib-cage length, straight Eyes: dark prescription glasses: yes&lt;br /&gt; Geometric black-and-white patterned dress, dark blue flipflops&lt;br /&gt; 2929 Hampstead Mexico Road, Hampstead, MD, 2174-1512&lt;br /&gt; (443) 293 - 2175&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Victim Statement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DILLON alleges that there is a worsening relationship between herself and her landlord. DILLON states that 3 days prior, the landlord&amp;rsquo;s mother died and passed the landlord contract onto her adult son, POFF, Ronald. DILLON states that POFF, R (RONALD). and POFF, Carolyn (CAROLYN)/(POFF, R&amp;rsquo;s wife) entered into her rented apartment to empty a dehumidifier. DILLON states that she feels it is too hot to have it running so unplugs it. This morning, DILLON alleges that CAROLYN. struck DILLON in the stomach with a closed, clenched fist during an argument over the landlord&amp;rsquo;s right to run a dehumidifier in her apartment against her wishes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Suspects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; POFF, Ronald &amp;ldquo;Ronnie&amp;rdquo; Clay&lt;br /&gt; 2/M DOB 11/19/1951&lt;br /&gt; 5&amp;rsquo;05&amp;rdquo; 120lbs eyes: light colored hair: gray poor dentition&lt;br /&gt; Gray sunhat, gray cotton t-shirt, light workpants, boots&lt;br /&gt; 2929 Hampstead Mexico Road, Hampstead, MD, 2174-1512&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;POFF, R&amp;rsquo;s statement:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; RONALD states DILLON has rented a home on his property for 3-4 years now. The original rental agreement contract was between DILLON and RONALD&amp;rsquo;s recently deceased mother. RONALD states that he is meeting with an estate lawyer within the week to have the contract redrawn. RONALD and CAROLYN will always go into DILLON&amp;rsquo;s apartment together to have witnesses to her actions and statements. RONALD stated that while he and CAROLYN were in the rented area to empty the dehumidifier DILLON approached CAROLYN aggressively, citing prior times CAROLYN had turned on the dehumidifier as the aggravating factor. CAROLYN attempted to get away from DILLON who refused to remove from her immediate bodyspace and so CAROLYN elbowed DILLON defensively in the stomach to get space. After this interaction, CAROLYN and RONALD both left DILLON&amp;rsquo;s rented area and started daily chores around the property.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; RONALD states that the reason he and CAROLYN want the dehumidifier running is because the three story home DILLON rents had an upstairs basement&amp;rsquo;s toilet overflow. The resulting damage required a plumber and a contractor to repair damage to the house. The plumber and contractor both stated that RONALD needed to run a dehumidifier at all times to ensure mold would not grow in the building as part of the restoration process. RONALD stated he is attempting to protect his property, follow the advice of renovation professionals, and to preserve the health of his tenant by running the dehumidifier.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; RONALD stated that originally DILLON was agreeable to the dehumidifier and, over time, has become more and more resistant to its presence. RONALD stated that he comes over to her rental area twice a day to empty the dehumidifier as DILLON refuses to do so on his request.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; RONALD states that DILLON has exhibited odd behavior over the past few months. RONALD states that she had plugged an unsafe amount of appliances into a powerstrip without any circuitbreaker and melted it. RONALD stated he removed the powerstrip from apartment but DILLON requested local fire department for &amp;ldquo;fire in my walls&amp;rdquo;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; RONALD also reported DILLON and him have had prior disagreements with DILLON moving her vehicle to enable him to cut his grass; DILLON refusing to park where RONALD requested her to; DILLON agreeing to mow the lawn and then never mowing it; DILLON complaining that a walnut tree&amp;rsquo;s dropping walnuts was intolerable and insisted RONALD cut down the tree; and DILLON has made remarks in the past alluding to suing him if she is injured on his property while walking around under the walnut tree with a helmet on.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;POFF, Carolyn Ann&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 2/F DOB 07/07/1952&lt;br /&gt; Hgt: 5&amp;rsquo;02&amp;rdquo; Wgt: 180lbs Eye: Brown Hair: Gray&lt;br /&gt; Glasses: yes; Gray sun-visor blue sleeveless cotton shirt blue jeans&lt;br /&gt; MD OLN P100108067539&lt;br /&gt; 2929 Hampstead Mexico Road, Hampstead, MD, 2174-1512&lt;br /&gt; (443) 974 - 1210&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Poff, C&amp;rsquo;s statement:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; CAROLYN is in agreement with RONALD&amp;rsquo;s statement.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Other Subjects Interviewed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; MICHAEL, Lauren (DILLON&amp;rsquo;s daughter)&lt;br /&gt; 2/F DOB 03/25/1984&lt;br /&gt; 76 Winchester Lane, Westminster, MD, 21157&lt;br /&gt; (443) 613 - 4005&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;OS&amp;rsquo;s Statement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; MICHAEL states that two weeks prior she was visiting DILLON&amp;rsquo;s rented space and witnessed DILLON and the POFFs get into a shouting argument. MICHAEL states she feels the POFFs are &amp;ldquo;mean&amp;rdquo;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Scene Processing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I arrived on scene and observed the following: the property was on a large acreage. There was rolling farmland cresting on a hill and the road curved around the hill before going down.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As the road went down south-westward, there was a cluster of eight buildings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On the right-hand side, there was a two story structure made of white clapboard and it had green awning trim and green rain gutters. The northern side of this building was 52 feet and the east-west width was 44 feet (per google map measurements). The roof was a dark green metal roofing material. There was a small window with four panes on the upper story. The roof also had a gabled vent. It had the appearance of a mixed use building.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; There was a car port on the northern up-hill side. There was an exit to a ground floor on the lower-side of the building. A single vehicle sat under a steel-poled shelter.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Immediately across the street was another building of the same construction and color patterning. This building was for agricultural purposes and appeared to be constructed as a cattle barn. This building&amp;rsquo;s width was 50 feet on its north-south axis and 120 feet on its east-west axis. The southern side of the building was open to a feed yard with a wooden split-rail fencing that measured north-south 60 feet by east-west 120 feet. A 10ft x 100ft chicken coop ran down the center of this yard and a storage silo was on the far eastern end.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; South of the cattle barn was a fenced-in grazing area that measured roughly 400ft by 200ft. A small stream meandered through the field at the base of the hill. Multiple cattle were in the yard grazing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I parked behind the car-port structure and observed a secondary agricultural building that appeared to be a dairy milking barn. It was 25-feet along its north-south axis and 75 feet along its east-west axis. There were bales of hay stacked and open to air along the southern-face.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The road continued beyond over the creek and went up a hill. A residential-looking structure was on the hill and I walked over to this. As I walked towards it, another shed-type structure appeared from behind some trees. This was a dark gray-green with wooden construction. A red 4-door sedan was parked outside with its nose towards the shed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The main residential building was a two-storied home with a basement on the down-hill side. It was constructed of the same material: white, wooden painted sides with green trim. The central roof was angled and stopped on the second story. There was an addition on the western side of the home with an angled roof and on the eastern side of the home was an open-aired porch.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; The railings and porch posts were painted a brick-red color. An external staircase sloped northwards onto the front lawn and met with a pathway.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The area under the porch was enclosed totally by white-painted latticed wood and the basement floor had an exit door onto the secondary lower porch. The lower porch&amp;rsquo;s construction was brick. It was surrounded by raised flowerbeds with wooden rail retaining walls and a pathway met the porch door.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; These two pavement pathways curved around a raised flower bed, merged, and headed down to the driveway together.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Location&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 2929 Hampstead Mexico Road, Hampstead, MD, 21074-1512&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Narrative&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On 07/12/2023 I, Trooper Bukoski assigned to the Westminster Barrack of the Maryland State Police was dispatched for a call for service of a landlord-tenant dispute.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I arrived on scene to contact the complainant.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; See above statement.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then approached and interviewed the alleged suspect&amp;rsquo;s husband and the suspect.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; See above statement.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then interviewed by phone the complainant&amp;#39;s daughter at the complainant&amp;rsquo;s request.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; See above statement.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; There was no evidence to support a criminal matter as a result. Both parties were provided a victims rights pamphlet, case number, and referred to the District Court Commissioner&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All above events occurred in Carroll County Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/12/2023 13:25:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/20/2023 15:07:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>FAIR</LastName>
            <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5334</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eyler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0670</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bukoski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Conrad</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7570</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514352</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>09</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/12/2023 10:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>no evidence to support criminal matter, advised subjects</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 15:26:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/20/2023 15:04:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>71</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/12/2023 13:07:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:09</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382336</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Poff</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Clay</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/19/1951 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/12/2023 13:07:19</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R543</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Poff</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Clay</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/19/1951 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R543</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/12/2023 13:07:19</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2929</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hampstead Mexico</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hampstead</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21074</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.889678</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.606986</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CD</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 16:04:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:12</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 16:04:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:12</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 16:04:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:12</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>71</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/12/2023 13:19:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:07</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382338</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Poff</LastName>
               <FirstName>Carolyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/07/1952 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/12/2023 13:19:40</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C645</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Poff</LastName>
               <FirstName>Carolyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/07/1952 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C645</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/12/2023 13:19:40</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2929</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hampstead Mexico</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hampstead</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21074</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.889678</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.606986</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CD</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 16:05:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:06</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 16:05:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:06</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 16:05:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:06</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>64</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/12/2023 13:23:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 02:15:11</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382340</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dillon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Laura</FirstName>
               <DOB>03/31/1959 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/12/2023 13:23:01</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D450</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dillon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Laura</FirstName>
               <DOB>03/31/1959 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D450</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/12/2023 13:23:01</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2929</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hampstead Mexico</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hampstead</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21074</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.889678</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.606986</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 15:27:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>R</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 15:27:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 15:27:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/03/2023 15:19:16</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/03/2023 15:19:16</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/13/2023 02:16:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 15:19:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:49</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>INCIDENT&lt;br /&gt; Alleged second degree assault&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; DATE/TIME OF INCIDENT&lt;br /&gt; 07/12/2023 1041 hours&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; LOCATION&lt;br /&gt; 2929 Hampstead Mexico Road, Hampstead, MD 21074&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; VICTIM&lt;br /&gt; DILLON, Laura RMS ID 382394&lt;br /&gt; DOB 03/31/1959&lt;br /&gt; 2929 hampstead mexico road, hampstead, md 21074&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; SUSPECT&lt;br /&gt; POFF, Ronald Clay&lt;br /&gt; DOB 11/19/1951, RMS ID 382390&lt;br /&gt; 2929 Hampstead Mexico Road, hampstead, MD, 21074&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; POFF, Caroline Anne&lt;br /&gt; 07/07/1952 RMS ID 382392&lt;br /&gt; 2929 Hampstead Mexico Road, hampstead, MD, 21074&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; There was no evidence to support a criminal matter as a result. Both parties were provided a victims rights pamphlet, case number, and referred to the District Court Commissioner.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I request that this case be closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/03/2023 15:20:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/03/2023 15:25:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bukoski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Conrad</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7570</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/22/2023 06:48:34</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/22/2023 06:48:34</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/13/2023 02:16:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/22/2023 06:48:34</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:49</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>INCIDENT&lt;br /&gt; Domestic/Civil Dispute/Alleged 2nd Degree Assault&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; DATE/TIME of incident&lt;br /&gt; 07/12/2023 at 10:41&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; LOCATION&lt;br /&gt; 2929 Hampstead Mexico Road, Hampstead, MD, 21074-1512&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to death of the complainant, DILLON, Laura Lee (DOB 03/31/1959), and the victims&amp;#39; refusal to apply for charges, I request that this case be closed. See MSP&amp;nbsp;23-MSP-028792.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; CLOSED</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/22/2023 07:39:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 01:15:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eyler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0670</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bukoski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Conrad</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7570</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/13/2023 02:11:03</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/13/2023 02:11:03</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/13/2023 02:16:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 02:11:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:49</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Open to correct coding issues.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 02:14:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 02:14:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bukoski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Conrad</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7570</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514352</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>04</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>3</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/13/2023 02:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>no evidence to support criminal matter, advised subjects</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 02:11:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 02:13:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>