<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-015128</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/28/2023 21:40:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/28/2023 21:40:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/28/2023 20:27:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/28/2023 20:27:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Verbal Domestic</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 21:40:06</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4794</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/30/2023 18:34:56</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>687559</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 21:40:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/28/2023 23:17:34</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>687559</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>12517</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Salisbury</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.118372</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.351556</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/28/2023 21:40:03</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/28/2023 21:40:03</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>04/30/2023 18:34:56</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 21:40:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4794</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/30/2023 18:34:56</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On 04/28/23 at approximately 2030 hours, I, TFC. Brittingham #6722, responded to 12517 Salisbury Road, Ocean City, Maryland 21842 for the report of a verbal domestic dispute. Upon my arrival, I made contact with the complainant, Karen Lauren Bell, and her husband Charles Michael C Bell, who were both identified by their Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license. Upon entry to the residence, both parties were calm and collected. Mr. Bell was seated on the couch in the living room and Mrs. Bell proceeded to walk into the kitchen area after greeting my shift partners and I at the front door. TFC. C. Shubert #7062&amp;nbsp;proceeded to speak with Mrs. Bell in the kitchen area, while myself and TFC. S. Shubert #6944 began to gather Mr. Bell&amp;#39;s recollection of the dispute which occurred prior to our arrival.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Mr. Bell proceeded to advise he arrived home after hanging out with a friend by the name of &amp;quot;Colby.&amp;quot; He began to talk to Mrs. Bell about the stipulations of their divorce and separation agreement, and began &amp;quot;challenging&amp;quot; her about things revolving around their divorce. Mr. Bell advised he is moving out of the residence on Monday, 05/01/23, to move into a condo in Ocean City. He felt it was necessary to talk things out about the upcoming situation. Mr. Bell stated this conversation quickly turn sour and he and Mrs. Bell began to have a disagreement and essential began bickering about the situation with one another. Mr. Bell advised the situation never escalated beyond that and that no raised voices, yelling or screaming occurred. Mr. Bell stated this particular time is just very tense due to the fact he is moving out and leaving on Monday. Mr. Bell did advise they had been drinking alcohol this evening and that alcohol causes them to become more argumentative with one another.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I then spoke with Mrs. Bell to obtain her side of the incident. Mrs. Bell advised she was home with their two daughters. Their five-year-old daughter Ava was asleep on the couch and their three-year-old daughter Eliana was cuddled on Mrs. Bell&amp;#39;s lap.&amp;nbsp; Mrs. Bell stated Mr. Bell arrived home around roughly, 2000 hours. After coming inside, Mr. Bell said hello and then immediately started &amp;quot;going on&amp;quot; about their current marital situation. Mrs. Bell advised emotions are high, tensions are high, and it&amp;#39;s a tough time for their family given it is a &amp;quot;big&amp;quot; weekend due to Mr. Bell moving out on Monday. Mrs. Bell advised Mr. Bell proceeded to call her and her lawyer &amp;quot;dummies&amp;quot; and that she &amp;quot;stupid.&amp;quot; Mrs. Bell was clearly emotional, and I was able to sense a level of exhaustion from this situation weighing on her family. She basically felt that &amp;quot;enough is enough,&amp;quot; and she is tired of being called names in front of her children. Mrs. Bell stated Mr. Bell had a doctor&amp;#39;s appointment at 1600 hours and did not return home until 2000 hours. She felt Mr. Bell was most likely at a bar somewhere in town drinking and then proceeded to come home to start things with her because he was under the influence of alcohol. Mrs. Bell advised Mr. Bell did not make any threatening statements to her.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Mrs. Bell advised she wanted Mr. Bell to leave the residence. She stated she knew he would continue to &amp;quot;pick&amp;quot; at her. Mrs. Bell advised she has family nearby in Salisbury, Maryland and Lewes, Delaware. She stated that Mr. Bell does not have family in the nearby area. She advised she preferred him to leave and stay with a friend or get a hotel, etc. I asked Mrs. Bell if she would be willing to leave if Mr. Bell would not agree to leave, and she advised she could possibly stay with her father or have her father come to stay at their home which he had done in the past. Mrs. Bell did however advise that in the past when she has felt the need to have law enforcement intervene, Mr. Bell had gone into his bedroom and stayed in there for the remained of the evening. Mrs. Bell advised her husband sleeps in their master bedroom and that she has been sleeping in the same bedroom as her daughters.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Mr. Bell was unwilling to leave the residence and adamant about staying in his bedroom in the home. He wanted to remove himself from the situation and go to his bedroom for the night which he does not share with his wife. He stated he needed to wake up early to work the next day and did not want to leave because he had been drinking alcohol.&amp;nbsp; Mrs. Bell was advised of this and proceeded to make contact with her father. She ultimately decided to have her father stay the night at her residence to feel more comfortable and safe.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; At this time, my shift partner and I proceeded to standby and await the arrival of Mrs. Bell&amp;#39;s father, James &amp;quot;Jim&amp;quot; Atkinson to ensure no other confrontation ensued. During this time, Mrs. Bell removed herself to her daughter&amp;#39;s room. Mr. Bell proceeded to converse with my shift partner and I in the kitchen of the residence. A few moments later, Mrs. Bell entered the kitchen and her attitude/demeanor had completely changed from our previous interaction with her. Mrs. Bell proceeded to advise she received a phone call from her stepmother advising her that her father &amp;quot;Jim&amp;quot; was highly upset due to this incident. Mrs. Bell began demanding Mr. Bell to leave or be removed from the residence. She was advised that we cannot force her husband out of his residence and that he has a right to be there. She was not receptive to this advisement and continued to become emotional and raise her voice. Mr. Bell removed himself from the kitchen and stayed in his bedroom for the remainder of the time. Mrs. Bell was adamant about Mr. Bell needing to leave the home and stating she did not feel safe with him staying there. She did not want to upset her father and felt it was ridiculous that she felt unsafe and needed her father to stay at her residence to protect her and her daughters. Mrs. Bell was advised she could also leave herself and stay with her father if she felt that unsafe. She refused to remove herself from the residence and would only accept Mr. Bell leaving. Mrs. Bell was reminded multiple times that we would not force Mr. Bell out of his home. She then advised us to leave her residence if we were not going to help her. She then walked over to the front door to open it, and we were asked to leave.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6722</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 15:47:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6722</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/30/2023 17:03:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7062</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jonischek</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4794</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brittingham</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6722</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>47</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6722</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 23:22:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375591</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael C</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/26/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>04/28/2023 23:22:34</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael C</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/26/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/28/2023 23:22:34</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12517</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Salisbury</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Ocean City</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.118372</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.351556</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>838</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5532</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6722</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 23:22:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6722</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 23:22:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6722</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 23:22:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6722</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 23:25:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:07</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375593</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Karen</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>A</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/17/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/28/2023 23:25:39</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Karen</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>A</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/17/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/28/2023 23:25:39</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12517</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Salisbury</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Ocean City</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.118372</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.351556</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>783</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0446</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6722</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 23:25:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6722</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 23:25:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6722</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 23:25:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>