<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-034079</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/28/2023 20:00:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/28/2023 20:00:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/28/2023 18:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/28/2023 18:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop resulting in a K9 scan and search of the vehicle, which yielded CDS not Cannabis.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 18:10:42</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5829</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 07:17:25</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>314166</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 18:10:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 19:07:12</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>314166</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>150</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>N</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Solomons Island</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Prince Frederick</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20678</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.591492</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.540838</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OFF DUTY WALMART - PR FRED</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WALMART - PR FRED</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/28/2023 18:10:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/28/2023 18:10:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/10/2023 07:17:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 18:10:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:10</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; This incident was recorded utilizing the AXON Digital Recording System Installed in marked patrol unit, U-19, along with the agency-issued body-worn cameras assigned to TPR Hernandez #7266, TFC Bauer #6719, TFC White #7132, S/T Ditoto #5416, CPL Warrick #6324, and CPL Brill #5032&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Summary:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Traffic stop resulting in a K-9 scan yielding a positive alert. A probable cause search yielded possession of controlled dangerous substances (CDS) not Cannabis.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Evidence: &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;One Ziploc bag containing five (5) pipes containing suspected Cocaine residue.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;One Ziploc bag containing one (1) black plastic scale containing suspected Cocaine residue.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;One Ziploc bag containing two (2) partially cut orange straws containing suspected Cocaine residue.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;One Ziploc bag containing one (1) metal spoon containing suspected Cocaine and/or Heroin residue.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;One Ziploc bag containing one (1) glass vial containing suspected Phencyclidine (PCP) residue.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Narrative:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On September 28, 2023, at approximately 1800 hours, I was patrolling the Prince Frederick area in my assigned marked patrol vehicle, U-19. I observed a red Hyundai Sonata parked in front of 180 Main St, Prince Frederick, MD 20678. The Hyundai was occupied by two subjects. The driver appeared to be a black male, and the passenger appeared to be a black female. Both subjects were observed smoking an unknown substance inside the vehicle in the parking lot of the business. The red Hyundai was bearing a Maryland registration plate that read, &amp;quot;9EF2357.&amp;quot; A search of the tag revealed the registered owner, Steven Kartney Smith (B/M DOB: 12/05/1988), to be revoked. From my observation of the male subject in the driver seat, he appeared to be the registered owner. I was unable to capture the driver&amp;#39;s face, since he pulled into the parking lot and was facing away from Main St. When I drove past the vehicle, the driver turned his head towards the driver side window and stared at me while I drove past him. I was able to confirm the driver and passenger to be smoking inside the vehicle. Due to the distance between both vehicles, I was unable to see what exactly both subjects were smoking.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; A few minutes later, I observed the same red Hyundai driving on Main St passing Armory Rd in Prince Frederick, MD 20678. The red Hyundai came to a complete stop at the intersection between Main St and Maryland RT 4. The red Hyundai was in the left turn lane, and did not have its left turn signal activated. The light turned green, and the driver made a left turn to go towards southbound Maryland RT 4. It should be noted that the driver never activated his left turn signal at any moment. I activated my emergency equipment to include my lights and siren, and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle at approximately 1809 hours. The red Hyundai pulled into the &amp;quot;Walmart&amp;quot; parking lot located at, 150 N Solomons Island Rd, Prince Frederick, MD 20678. Before coming to a complete stop, TFC Bauer #7266 was stationary in his unmarked patrol unit, U-16, and was able to identify the driver to be the registered owner of the vehicle, Steven Smith. The Hyundai came to a complete stop in the parking lot of the Prince Frederick Walmart. TFC Bauer asked the on-duty Maryland State Police Prince Frederick Emergency Dispatcher to run Smith for codes. Smith was later revealed to be a known drug user.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Upon a driver side approach of the vehicle, I made contact with the driver who was confirmed to be Smith. I advised Smith I pulled him over for not activating his left turn signal at the intersection. I asked Smith to provide his driver&amp;#39;s license and registration. It should be noted that Smith was actively smoking a cigarette at the time I initially made contact with him, and he appeared to be nervous. Smith was able to provide his registration card, as well as his insurance card. Smith advised his driver&amp;#39;s license was in his book bag, which was in the rear portion of the vehicle. Smith asked if he could reach for his book bag in order to obtain his driver&amp;#39;s license. I told Smith he was good to slowly reach over and grab his book bag. While Smith opened his book bag, TFC Bauer was standing on the passenger side of the vehicle. TFC Bauer observed a gun to be inside the book bag, and immediately advised Smith to stop reaching inside the bag. From my point of view, I was unable to see the gun. Smith immediately dropped the book bag and advised it was a paintball gun. Smith raised his hands up in the air, and cooperated with all commands. I opened the driver side door, and advised Smith to slowly unbuckle his seat belt. Smith unbuckled his seat belt, and slowly exited the vehicle as instructed to do so. Smith was placed in handcuffs and was advised he was detained. I escorted Smith to the front of my patrol car while TFC Bauer and TFC White #7132 assured the gun was a paintball gun. A few moments later, TFC Bauer advised the gun was in-fact a paintball gun.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; It should be noted that upon my approach of the vehicle, I observed the vehicle to be unkept and dirty. There was a lot of trash throughout the entire car. There were clothes in the back seat, and bags of trash. I also noticed a bunch of opened cigarette boxes laying on the floor of the vehicle. I also noticed that three (3) of the four (4) door handles on the vehicle were completely missing. The only handle that was still attached to the vehicle was the front passenger door handle. The back passenger door was later found to not open.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; After the gun was revealed to be a paintball gun, I spoke to TFC White regarding a K-9 scan. TFC White and I went over the criminal indicators that were observed during my interaction with Smith. The following criminal indicators were observed/revealed: nervousness (fresh lit cigarette, repeatedly asking the same questions, and looking around), cigarette smoking, unkept vehicle (trash and clothes spread throughout the vehicle), handles/knobs missing (all door handles missing except for the front passenger door), and Smith being a known drug user. TFC White conducted a K-9 scan of the red Hyundai at approximately 1812 hours. Immediately after the K-9 scan was initiated, Smith became more nervous. Smith began looking around after the K-9 was deployed. Smith repeatedly asked why TFC White was conducting a K-9 scan. I went to my patrol vehicle while the K-9 scan was administrated. Immediately after getting inside my vehicle, the K-9 scan resulted in a positive alert. I got out of my vehicle, and Smith asked if I identified the paintball gun. Smith asked why the K-9 was scanning the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Before conducting a probable cause search of the Hyundai, Smith asked what my probable cause was for a K-9 scan. I advised Smith that I observed multiple indicators to justify a scan. Smith asked what the indicators were, but I advised Smith I would go over the entire stop with him after everything was completed. The probable cause search of the vehicle was conducted at approximately 1813 hours. Immediately into the search, at approximately 1813 hours, TFC Bauer located one black plastic scale containing a white powdered substance suspected of being Cocaine residue. TFC Bauer located the scale inside the same book bag that the paintball gun was in. I then located one self-made glass pipe/smoking device which was covered in a black burnt substance suspected of being burnt Cocaine. The glass pipe was located in the front driver side door panel compartment. A lighter was observed laying on the driver seat. TFC Bauer later located two orange cut straws containing a white powdered substance suspected of being Cocaine. The straws were located inside the glove box where Smith&amp;#39;s registration card was.&amp;nbsp; I later found three pipes containing suspected Cocaine residue. Inside the pipes were copper wires. The three pipes were located under the driver seat. Along with the pipes, a metal spoon was located under the driver seat. The metal spoon contained a white substance suspected of being Cocaine and/or Heroin. The bottom side of the spoon appeared to be burned, and had a hardened black substance. It should be noted that a box of baking soda was discovered under the driver seat. The box was opened, and there was white powder all over the driver side floor carpet. An empty bottle of &amp;quot;Jose Cuervo&amp;quot; tequila was discovered under the driver seat, but Smith did not appear to be under the influence of alcohol. I located a purple bag containing trash in the back center seat of the vehicle. I dumped all the contents, and revealed a pipe containing a white powdered substance suspected of being Cocaine. I later located one glass vial containing suspected Phencyclidine (PCP) residue in the back pocket of the driver seat. I opened the glass vial to confirm the substance was PCP. Upon opening the glass vial, I was immediately hit with a strong and pungent chemical smell. I continued searching the rest of the vehicle, but did not find any other items. The searched was completed at approximately 1831 hours. The above listed controlled dangerous substance (CDS) was seized, and placed in my patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; After completing the search, Smith&amp;#39;s vehicle was locked and secured. I transported Smith to the Maryland State Police Prince Frederick barrack for a debrief at approximately 1845 hours. TFC Bauer read Smith his Miranda Rights at approximately 1902 hours. Smith waived his rights, and advised he would answer any questions. Smith signed the MSP Form 180, and he was later debriefed and interviewed by Corporal Warrick. I was in the same room where Smith was interviewed, but I was working on his paperwork, so I was not engaged in the conversation. I also stepped out of the room for approximately half of the interview. Upon completion of the debrief and interview, Smith was transported to the Calvert County Detention Center located at, 325 Stafford Rd, Barstow, MD 20610.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; A statement of charges and probable cause were completed for the possession of a controlled dangerous substance of schedule II, to wit: Cocaine and Phencyclidine (PCP) (1_1111 CR 5-601(a)(1)). Smith was also issued citations for failing to activate his turn signal when making a left turn, and for driving on a revoked license. Smith was provided a copy of all issued paperwork. After issuing all paperwork, I responded to the Maryland State Police Prince Frederick Barrack to process the seized CDS.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; A vehicle search report (VSR) was completed in Delta Plus.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; All event occurred in Calvert County, MD.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 07:02:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7266</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 02:11:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brendan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7132</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bauer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6719</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hunt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kemery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5162</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5829</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hernandez-Miguel</LastName>
            <FirstName>Pavel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7266</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523536</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>12</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/28/2023 18:09:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:52:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7266</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 06:52:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:54:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 19:07:12</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>43564</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>SMITH</LastName>
               <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kartney</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/05/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13234006E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>12/15/2014 01:43:24</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>SMITH</LastName>
               <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kartney</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/05/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13234006E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/15/2014 01:43:24</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1785</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Parkers Creek</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Port Republic</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20676</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.5337</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.522288</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>586</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0506</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/15/2014 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>771</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4818</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/05/2018 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>432</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8420</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/14/2017 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>968</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1626</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/14/2016 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:54:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:54:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:54:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:54:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:54:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:54:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:52:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7266</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 06:52:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>128612</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 07:00:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7266</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 07:00:54</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/02/2021 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5NPET46CX8H390884</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2008</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HYUN</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SON</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>MAR</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>MAR</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9EF2357</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2022</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>6</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:56:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7266</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 02:06:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Five (5) pipes containing suspected cocaine residue.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>254731</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:57:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7266</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 02:06:52</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) scale containing suspected cocaine residue.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>254732</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:58:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7266</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 02:07:14</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Two (2) cut straws containing suspected cocaine residue.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>254733</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:58:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7266</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 02:08:29</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) spoon containing suspected cocaine and/or Heroin residue.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>254734</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 06:59:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7266</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/12/2023 02:09:11</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) glass vial containing suspected Phencyclidine (PCP) residue.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>254735</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>J</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/06/2023 11:44:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/06/2023 11:44:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/10/2023 07:17:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 11:44:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:10</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On November 2, 2023, I received a laboratory report for the Controlled Dangerous Substances (CDS) that were seized during the traffic stop that occurred on September 28, 2023, with Steven Kartney Smith (B/M DOB: 12/05/1988). The laboratory report revealed Smith was in possession of cocaine (schedule II) and Phencyclidine (PCP) (Schedule II). Of all the items seized, only two items were analyzed. The silver colored metal spoon with residue was analyzed, which revealed a trace amount of Cocaine. The glass bottle with a black plastic top containing liquid and plant material residue was also analyzed, which revealed a trace amount of Phencyclidine.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; This analysis was conducted on November 2, 2023, by Maryland State Police Forensic Scientist III D. Stemple. I have attached a copy of the laboratory report to this report.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Case closed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; All events occurred in Calvert County, MD.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7266</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 11:46:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7266</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 12:16:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5829</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hernandez-Miguel</LastName>
            <FirstName>Pavel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7266</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>