<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-029364</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/19/2023 22:13:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/19/2023 22:13:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/19/2023 21:24:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Vehicle fled an attempted traffic stop. After getting good vehicle registration and successfully identifying driver, Troopers went to listed address and spoke with subject's mother, fianc and the subject. Subject was extremely irate the entire time, refused all paperwork and was informed his continued actions of aggression and refusal to take part in the business of a traffic stop could lead to additional criminal charges.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 22:13:04</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/25/2023 09:29:37</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>EVD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I97 / CRAIN HWY N</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>596238</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 22:13:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 06:52:55</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>596238</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I97</StreetName>
         <City>Millersville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>HWY</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <CrossStreetSuffixCode>N</CrossStreetSuffixCode>
         <Longitude>-76.64122</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.12805</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>7401-7800 I97 / 460-463 CRAIN HWY N</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>6901-7400 I97 / 471-479 CRAIN HWY N</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>6801-7400 I97 / 460-463 CRAIN HWY N</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>7401-7900 I97 / 464-470 CRAIN HWY N</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/19/2023 22:13:03</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/19/2023 22:13:03</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/24/2023 16:00:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 22:13:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:06:42</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;In-Car Camera Operational. Trooper #7362 BWC camera was functioning and used during this incident.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-0e365bad-7fff-7e44-d5cb-9dbeeb51f19e"&gt;PHYSICAL EVIDENCE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to the nature of the incident, no physical evidence was held for processing.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-0e365bad-7fff-7e44-d5cb-9dbeeb51f19e"&gt;SCENE PROCESSING:&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A&amp;nbsp;traffic stop was attempted on Northbound Interstate 97 in the area of Veterans highway&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;led to a white Ford Explorer bearing Maryland registration 3FE7757 fleeing and eluding a marked Maryland State Police vehicle with its emergency lighting and siren systems activated directly behind it in an effort to affect a traffic stop.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-0e365bad-7fff-7e44-d5cb-9dbeeb51f19e"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-0e365bad-7fff-7e44-d5cb-9dbeeb51f19e"&gt;COMPLAINANT/VICTIM:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;State of Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-0e365bad-7fff-7e44-d5cb-9dbeeb51f19e"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-0e365bad-7fff-7e44-d5cb-9dbeeb51f19e"&gt;NARRATIVE:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-0e365bad-7fff-7e44-d5cb-9dbeeb51f19e"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;On August 19, 2023, at approximately 2122 hours, I, Trooper Litz #7362, was traveling Northbound on Interstate 97 in the area of Veterans Highway in Anne Arundel County, Maryland. While traveling Northbound in lane 3, I observed a white SUV traveling Norhtbound behind me in lane 1 at a high rate of speed and passing other vehicles. The white SUV then passed my marked patrol vehicle at a high rate of speed before approaching a dark-colored sedan in lane 1 and remaining less than 1 car length directly behind the dark-colored sedan for approximately 8 seconds. At this time, I was able to identify the vehicle as a white Ford Explorer bearing Maryland registration 3FE7757. While the white Explorer passed me, I was able to observe the driver to be a black male with short hair and glasses. The white Explorer then moved from lane 1 into lane 2 directly in front of a silver sedan before continuing to travel into lane 3. At no time did the white SUV use it&amp;#39;s turning signals to safely indicate the lane changes to other drivers on the highway. Once in lane 3, in front of my marked patrol vehicle and with no other cars between us, the white Explorer began to accelerate at a high rate of speed and began passing multiple cars. For approximately 11 seconds, the white Explorer traveled at a minimum speed of 82 miles per hour while in lane 3, frequently accelerating faster than that. I was able to determine the white Explorer&amp;#39;s minimum speeds by traveling behind the vehicle and sustaining a fixed speed in my marked police vehicle while observing the white Explorer&amp;#39;s distance changes in relation to my vehicle.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The white Explorer then approached a black SUV in lane 3 and, again, remained less than 1 car length behind the black SUV for approximately 2 seconds. The white Explorer then moved into lane 2 without using its turning signals, at which point the white Explorer increased its speed to 92 miles per hour. Upon approaching a black sedan in lane 2 while traveling 92 miles per hour, the white Explorer once more created a distance of less than 1 car length between itself and the vehicle in front of it. The white Explorer then moved into lane 3 and began to accelerate once more.&amp;nbsp;I moved directly behind the white Explorer and, while traveling at 94 miles per hour with no distance change between our vehicles, activated my emergency lighting and siren equipment in an effort to affect a traffic stop on the white Explorer. Upon me doing so, the white Explorer maintained its speed and did not indicate intentions to slow down. The white Explorer then continued to pass multiple vehicles and moved into lane 2. While traveling Northbound in lane 2, the white Explorer still did not show intentions or attempts to pull over or slow its speed for the purposes of a traffic stop. Upon the white Explorer continuing northbound at a high rate of speed and passing other cars, I moved my patrol vehicle to the right shoulder and did not pursue the white Explorer due to safety concerns for other vehicles traveling on the highway.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Upon safely coming to a stop in the shoulder area, I notified the Police Communications Officer (PCO) of the events that occurred, and I was able to perform a METERS/NCIC search of the vehicle registration. When the results came back, and using the registered owner&amp;#39;s Maryland issued driver&amp;#39;s license picture, I was able to confirm the identification of the driver as the registered owner, Malik Lee Dixon-Coates (B/M DOB: 01/02/2002). The results of the searches showed that Dixon-Coates&amp;#39; license through Maryland had been revoked, and the vehicle&amp;#39;s registration had been suspended. I was also able to view the listed address, which was in the Maryland State Police (MSP) Glen Burnie barrack&amp;#39;s area of responsibility. The listed address was North of where the incident occurred and was in the direction the white Explorer was traveling. I informed the PCO I would be en route to the residence for further investigation, at which point Trooper First Class (TFC) Caldwell #6865 also showed himself en route to the residence to assist.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;At approximately 2140 hours, myself and TFC Caldwell arrived at 219 Foxmanor Lane Glen Burnie Maryland, 21061. Upon arrival, I spoke with Dixon-Coates&amp;#39; mother, Robin Nodie Dixon (B/F DOB: 05/13/1965), who was identified by her Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license. I introduced myself and asked her if Dixon-Coates lived at the residence. She confirmed he did. I asked her if Dixon-Coates was in the residence at that moment. She informed me he was not. I asked her if Dixon-Coates was currently driving a white Ford Explorer. She informed me he was. At this time, I informed Dixon of the events that previously occurred, and asked her if she could provide a good phone number for Dixon-Coates. She informed me she did, and went to retrieve her phone. Shortly after, Dixon returned to the door along with a female who claimed to be Dixon-Coates&amp;#39; fianc&amp;eacute;. Dixon-Coates&amp;#39; fianc&amp;eacute; informed me that Dixon-Coates was on his way home from the Annapolis Mall, which is where he works. This correlates with the fact that Dixon-Coates was traveling Northbound on Interstate 97 from the Annapolis area, from his place of work towards his residence. Dixon went inside the residence and attempted to contact Dixon-Coates. While separated from Dixon, Dixon-Coates&amp;#39; fianc&amp;eacute; informed me that Dixon-Coates was dropping a friend off prior to returning home from work.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Dixon returned with Dixon-Coates on the phone, and speakerphone was activated, so I could talk to Dixon-Coates. When asked if he was in the manner previously discussed in an effort to take care of any medical emergencies, Dixon-Coates informed me he was dropping off a friend so that he could then himself drive home. I informed Dixon-Coates that I would be issuing citations to him, at which point he informed me he would not be returning home and did not intend to receive any paperwork I had for him. Dixon-Coates went on to say that I should not be &amp;quot;At my [Dixon-Coates] fucking house. What he should be, is doing literally whatever the fuck he needs to do to leave my house and go somewhere else, because there is no more talking to him.&amp;quot; Dixon-Coates also went on to state that &amp;quot;... If I get home, and he&amp;#39;s still there, I&amp;#39;m going to be absolutely fucking livid.&amp;quot; Dixon-Coates then addressed me personally and stated &amp;quot;So, Officer who-ever-the-fuck you are, you can leave my house immediately.&amp;quot; I then received Dixon-Coates&amp;#39; phone number from Dixon in an effort to keep only the involved parties involved and open a line of communication that does not involve coming to Dixon-Coates&amp;#39; residence any further that night.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; Upon conversations with Dixon and Dixon-Coates&amp;#39; fianc&amp;eacute; coming to an end, they both asked for my information at which point I intended to provide them with it and an incident number related to the nights events. At approximately 2156 hours, while I was retrieving the requested information, Dixon-Coates arrived at the residence. I started to introduce myself to Dixon-Coates, but was interrupted by him stating &amp;quot;Fuck you. Move.&amp;quot; Dixon-Coates then stated &amp;quot;...I don&amp;#39;t give a fuck. You don&amp;#39;t come to my house. So Fucking leave and get the fuck out my face.&amp;quot; Dixon-Coates addressed his fianc&amp;eacute; and asked her to go inside the house.&amp;nbsp; Dixon-Coates then faced me and stated &amp;quot;Get the fuck away from my house. I don&amp;#39;t give a fuck what you have to say, don&amp;#39;t have to say shit. Get the fuck away... All I want to see is you leave and go. Nothing. I don&amp;#39;t want to hear what you have to say.&amp;quot; Once more I tried to introduce who I am, at which point Dixon-Coates interrupted me and stated &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t give a flying fuck.&amp;quot; He also informed me that &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m not accepting shit.&amp;quot; and anything I had for him, he preferred I &amp;quot;throw that shit in the fucking trash.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; At that time, I returned to my vehicle to issue the proper traffic citations. Due to a serious collision requiring both me and TFC Caldwell to respond to another location, I could not charge Dixon-Coates with the criminal charges on criminal citations at that time. I did, however, inform Dixon-Coates of my intentions to file other charges against him at a later date. While I was explaining the traffic citations to Dixon-Coates at his front step, he did not acknowledge me or look away from his phone, where he was watching videos. When I asked if he had any questions for me, Dixon-Coates asked me &amp;quot;When you gonna leave?&amp;quot; I informed him I needed to make sure there were no further questions before leaving. Dixon-Coates informed me multiple times that I could leave. I attempted to hand Dixon-Coates the paperwork, at which point he stated &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m not taking it.&amp;quot; I placed all pertinent paperwork on the step directly in front of his feet, to which he stated &amp;quot;I didn&amp;#39;t receive it. Now get the fuck off of my property, Bitch.&amp;quot; Dixon-Coates also stated &amp;quot;Don&amp;#39;t come near my house again.&amp;quot; TFC Caldwell and I then left the residence.&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-0e365bad-7fff-7e44-d5cb-9dbeeb51f19e"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;All events listed above occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-0e365bad-7fff-7e44-d5cb-9dbeeb51f19e"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;I&amp;nbsp;request this case remain open pending summons/warrant issuance by the Commisioner&amp;#39;s office of Anne Arundel County, Maryland for charges of 1_0043 Obstructing &amp;amp; Hindering.&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 08:56:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 11:35:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Caldwell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tahir</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6865</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derek</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5951</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Litz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Simon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7362</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518812</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 06:59:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 06:59:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518812</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15647</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15647</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:02:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:02:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518812</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:03:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:03:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518812</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:04:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:04:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518812</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:05:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:05:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518812</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15566</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15566</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:06:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:06:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518812</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15558</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15558</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:07:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:07:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518812</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3097</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3097</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:08:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:08:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518812</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:08:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:08:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518812</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16616</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16616</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:09:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:09:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518812</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0043</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>A</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>A</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0043</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:25:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:25:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518812</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>12</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14594</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>12</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14594</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:28:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:28:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518812</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>13</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16604</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>13</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 21:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16604</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 07:29:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 07:29:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 08:52:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 08:52:57</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>385590</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dixon-Coates</LastName>
               <FirstName>Malik</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/02/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/20/2023 08:50:20</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M420</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dixon-Coates</LastName>
               <FirstName>Malik</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/02/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M420</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/20/2023 08:50:20</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>413</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3773</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 08:52:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 08:52:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 08:52:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 08:52:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 08:52:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156297</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 08:55:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 08:55:15</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FMHK8D83CGA00786</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2012</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>XPL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3FE7757</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/20/2023 14:02:53</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/20/2023 14:02:53</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/24/2023 16:00:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 14:02:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:06:42</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On August 20, 2023, at approximately 1230 hours, I, Trooper Litz #7362, applied for charges of Obstructing &amp;amp; Hindering against Malik Lee Dixon-Coates (B/M DOB: 01/02/2002). At approximately 1300 hours, a Criminal Summons was granted by Commissioner #7046 of Anne Arundel County, Maryland for the charges. At approximately 1335 hours, myself and Senior Trooper Tenorio #6321 arrived at 219 Foxmanor Lane Glen Burnie Maryland, 21061 with the summons paperwork, as well as additional traffic charges from the incident that occurred on the night before. After the first attempt to have someone come to the door, there was a subject that looked through one of the upstairs windows of the residence, but no one came to the door. After 2 more attempts on the doorbell and 1 attempt of knocking on the door, Dixon-Coates answered the door. Dixon-Coates immediately stated &amp;quot;I told you to leave my place, didn&amp;#39;t I?&amp;quot; When I attempted to explain my reason for being there was to serve the summons, Dixon-Coates interrupted me and said &amp;quot;No.Leave. Bye.&amp;quot; then shut the door.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Upon Dixon-Coates closing the door, I proceeded to explain all paperwork that was to be given to him at an audible level that was to be heard through the residence&amp;#39;s door and/or windows. I left all pertinent paperwork slightly under the front door&amp;#39;s floor mat after noting Dixon-Coates&amp;#39; refusal to sign on his copies. Having acknowledged that I was there and refusing to speak/listen further, I felt it appropriate to leave the premise having Dixon-Coates considered advised about the summons and additional traffic citations. A copy of the summons is attached to this report as well.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; All events listed above occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Having served all summons and/or charges, I request this case be closed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 14:03:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 14:25:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derek</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5951</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Litz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Simon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7362</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>