<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-029146</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/17/2023 22:49:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/17/2023 22:49:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/17/2023 22:27:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/17/2023 22:27:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI arrest of Burt Aaron Foskey</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 22:49:40</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/21/2023 00:51:41</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>3804</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>963</SubBeat>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 22:49:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/18/2023 22:57:42</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>3804</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>12502</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>OCEAN</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>OCEAN CITY</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>963</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-75.11858000000025</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.339210037628376</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WAWA</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>50 EB / WAWA</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/17/2023 22:49:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/17/2023 22:49:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/21/2023 00:37:56</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 22:49:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:06:30</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Maryland State Police- Berlin Barrack &amp;ldquo;V&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;MSP Unmarked vehicle V-18 is equipped with a mobile recording device&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Trooper is also outfitted with a body worn camera&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; (Videos are labeled: 23MSP029146)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Burt Aaron Foskey&lt;br /&gt; License #: MD ID MD-10273883502&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 12/16/1978&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 12/16/1978&lt;br /&gt; Times of Arrest: 2243 hrs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; DUI #: 23-96-248&lt;br /&gt; PBT Results: Refused&lt;br /&gt; Intox Results: Refused&lt;br /&gt; Subsequent Offender: YES&lt;br /&gt; Accident Involved: NO&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration&lt;br /&gt; - Trained through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration as an SFST Instructor&lt;br /&gt; - Trained by the Maryland State Police in Enhanced DUI Enforcement&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;nbsp;Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE)&lt;br /&gt; - Distinguished graduate from the University of Maryland&amp;rsquo;s DUI Institute&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On August 17, 2023, at approximately&amp;nbsp;2227 hrs., I, TFC Lane #6577 of the Maryland State Police-Berlin Barrack &amp;quot;V&amp;quot;, was on routine patrol in the area of Keyser Point Road and Route 50, located in Ocean City, Worcester County, Maryland. At that time, I was in my unmarked patrol vehicle, V-18, traveling south on Keyser Point, when I observed a green/gray Dodge Grand Caravan traveling north. Upon the van passing me, I observed it to have an inoperable left tail light. Upon observing the violation, I performed a U-turn and positioned my patrol vehicle directly behind the van, at which time I was able to identify its registration as, Kansas-846HXM. I activated my emergency lights, and conducted a traffic stop on the van. Upon activating my lights, the van came to a complete stop in the parking lot of the CVS, located at 12510 Ocean Gateway.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; I exited my patrol vehicle and approached the drivers side window.I made contact with the male driver, at which time I identified myself and advised the driver the reason for the stop. Upon contact with the driver, I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle. I asked the driver for his license, registration, and the insurance to the vehicle. At that time, the driver provided a Maryland ID card, identifying him as, Burt Aaron Foskey-DOB 12/16/1978.&amp;nbsp;While speaking with Foskey, I observed his eyes to be extremely glassy and bloodshot with a gazed look. While looking for the registration and insurance, Foskey and the female passenger became very erratic, and appeared frantic. During my initial contact, I observed numerous empty cans of beer and liquor bottles spread throughout the van. I asked Foskey how much alcohol he had, to which he stated with a slurred speech, &amp;quot;I haven&amp;#39;t had nothing, I just got off work dude&amp;quot;. After obtaining Foskeys information, I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine MVA checks.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; After conducting routine MVA checks, I returned to Foskey&amp;#39;s vehicle. At that time, I asked him to step out, and stand on the sidewalk in front of his vehicle. At the front of his vehicle, I asked him again how much alcohol he had, to which he stated, &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ve only had one beer when I got off work, I&amp;#39;m just trying to get the fuck home&amp;quot;. When asked what kind of beer it was, Foskey stated, &amp;quot;I drank a fuckin shark&amp;quot;. Foskey later advised it was a 12 oz &amp;quot;Landshark&amp;quot;. Foskey later stated that he had a couple after work.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Foskey to submit to Standard Field Sobriety Test&amp;#39;s(SFST&amp;#39;s) to which he consented.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The evaluation was performed on the sidewalk of the CVS, where Foskey had come to a complete stop. Foskey appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries that would prevent him from taking any tests. The weather was clear, and it was approximately 79 degrees out. Lighting conditions consisted of parking lot lamps, my headlights, and my flashlight.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (_6_/_6_ clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. A silver pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12-15 inches from Foskey&amp;rsquo;s eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Foskey&amp;rsquo;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. He was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked him if he understood the instructions and he stated &amp;quot;yes.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 2. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 3. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; *Note: Foskey even had vertical nystagmus, which I know to be a sign of a high dose of an alcoholic beverage, due to my training, knowledge and experience as a State Trooper.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WALK AND TURN (_6_/_8_ clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Prior to Foskey performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Foskey was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Foskey was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Foskey was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Foskey was to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, I explained and demonstrated for Foskey to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. I again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Foskey was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Foskey if he understood the test and he stated, &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;1.) Starts too soon-Attempted to start the test before being instructed to&lt;br /&gt; 2.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Lost balance &amp;ndash; Foskey was never able to stand heel to toe during the instructional phase&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;1.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 8, and 9.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;2.) Raised arms by more than six inches from his side to aid in his balance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;1.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on all 7 steps&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Raised arms by more than six inches from his side to aid in his balance&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Took 7 steps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;Turn:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;1.) Improper &amp;ndash; Didn&amp;#39;t keep his front foot planted&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND (_3_/_4_ clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Prior to Foskey performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Foskey was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, Foskey was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand-two), and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Foskey if he understood the test and he stated &amp;quot;yes.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;Balance and Count Stage:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;Seconds 0-10:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;1.) Raised arms more than six inches from his body to maintain his balance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;2.) Put foot down at 1001, 1006, and 1007. After putting his foot down. Foskey kept changing feet, and was only able to hold his foot up for a second before he had to put it back down. To his inability to balance on one foot, and out of safety for him, I ended the test.&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Swayed body more than three inches to the left and right while balancing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;Seconds 11-20:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;Didn&amp;#39;t make it that far&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;Seconds 21-30:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;Didn&amp;#39;t&amp;nbsp;make it that far&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;Foskey was offered the opportunity to submit to a Preliminary Breath Test. Foskey stated, &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m fucking high as a firecracker, I just drunk the bitch soon as I got here&amp;quot;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Foskey was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from Foskey&amp;#39;s breath and person&lt;br /&gt; * Eyes glassy and bloodshot&lt;br /&gt; * Slow and slurred speech&lt;br /&gt; *&amp;nbsp;Admission to having alcohol&lt;br /&gt; * Empty containers of alcoholic beverages in his vehicle&lt;br /&gt; * My observed signs of impairment as he performed the psychophysical tests.&lt;br /&gt; * Refusing the PBT test&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I arrested Foskey for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 2243 hrs. Foskey then was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. While on scene, I played the English audio version of the DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Foskey via the MVA&amp;rsquo;s official website. At the conclusion of the DR-15 audio, I verbally repeated and reviewed the possible suspensions and sanctions that can be imposed by the MVA per the DR-15 form. Foskey refused to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the same at approximately 2257hrs.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Inside Foskey&amp;#39;s vehicle, I observed 9 empty bottles of &amp;quot;Fireball&amp;quot; whiskey, and several various empty cans of beer. Most of the empty bottles were between the drivers seat and the center console.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;INTOXIMETER RESULT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; REFUSED&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Foskey was later given all proper paperwork and released to his sober friend from the Barrack. Foskey was polite and cooperative throughout&amp;nbsp;the entire process.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 23:25:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 01:47:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7100</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7062</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Messick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7451</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lane</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6577</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518593</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/17/2023 22:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518593</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/17/2023 22:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518593</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/17/2023 22:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518593</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17020</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/17/2023 22:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17020</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518593</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/17/2023 22:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19731</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518593</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16833</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/17/2023 22:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16833</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>44</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 23:20:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 23:03:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>222397</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Foskey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Burt</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Aaron</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/16/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/22/2019 11:57:26</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B630</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Foskey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Burt</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Aaron</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/16/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B630</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/22/2019 11:57:26</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>104</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Halsey</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21804</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.598416</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.34196</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>102</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>59th</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>a</SubNumber>
               <City>Ocean City</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21842</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.067799</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.382984</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>397</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3733</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 23:03:22</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 23:03:22</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6577</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6577</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/18/2023 23:05:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>