<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-022010</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/19/2023 14:42:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/19/2023 14:42:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/19/2023 14:20:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/19/2023 14:20:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUIDWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 14:42:51</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/07/2023 07:15:19</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>BISHOPVILLE RD/ WORCESTER HWY</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>616831</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 14:42:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 14:42:52</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>616831</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Bishopville</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Bishopville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>HWY</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.219494</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.428743</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>9800-9995 BISHOPVILLE RD / 12657-13101 WORCESTER HWY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10000-10040 BISHOPVILLE RD / 12642-12656 WORCESTER HWY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/19/2023 14:42:49</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/19/2023 14:42:49</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/06/2023 00:11:50</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 14:42:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:20</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI / DWI arrest suspect: MICHAEL HARRISON DAY&lt;br /&gt; Arrest was audibly &amp;amp; visually recorded on MVR and BWC - Labeled &amp;quot;23MSP022010&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 06/19/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 1442 hours&lt;br /&gt; Maryland Soundex: D-000-603-298-131&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; DUI Citation #: 6C50JFH&lt;br /&gt; Barrack DUI Folder #: 23-96-173&lt;br /&gt; Case #: 23-MSP-022010&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TRAINING / CERTIFICATIONS:&lt;br /&gt; Trained and certified to conduct NHTSA Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police Training Academy.&lt;br /&gt; Trained and certified to conduct Preliminary Breath Tests through the Maryland State Police Training Academy.&lt;br /&gt; Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; Trained and certified in Enhanced DUI Enforcement: The Complete Arrest though the Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; Trained and certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement through the Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; Trained and certified as a Basic Breath Test Operator utilizing the Intoximeter EC/IR II through the Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PHASE ONE - VEHICLE IN MOTION:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On 06/19/2023, I (TFC M. Mitchell #6296) was operating in my official capacity as a Maryland State Police Trooper, operating marked MSP vehicle &amp;quot;V-27&amp;quot;. At approximately 1418 hours I was conducting traffic direction at the intersection of Worcester Highway (US Route 113) and Whaleyville Road (MD Route 610) due to a traffic signal not functioning properly. At that time I was seated in my patrol vehicle facing southbound when I observed a vehicle to my right with the occupants waving their arms outside the vehicle attempting to get my attention. I looked over at them and they pointed at a vehicle which was turning right to go southbound and had swung wide and nearly collided with the center guardrail at my location, crossing the yellow fog line by about 4 to 5 feet. I observed it to be a black Subaru with Maryland registration plates. The occupants waving their arms continued to point at that vehicle and shout that he was drunk and had been swerving all over the road. I then pulled my patrol vehicle into the southbound lanes and accelerated to catch up to the Subaru. I caught up to the Subaru near the intersection of Bishopville Road (MD Route 367) and observed it driving in lane 1 and drift to the right so much that its right tires drove on top of the dotted white lines connecting to lane 2. The Subaru then drifted left and back into lane 1 until finally merging into the left turn lane and proceed to make a left turn onto eastbound Bishopville Road. As it was making its turn, it drove beyond the white fog line and onto the right shoulder by at least 2 feet, nearly colliding with the guardrail at that location. I immediately activated my emergency lights and siren to initiate a traffic stop. The vehicle stopped a few moments later in the grass on the right side of Bishopville Road. I advised barrack communications of my traffic stop, identifying the vehicle as a black Subaru Outback displaying MD registration &amp;quot;2CR8080&amp;quot;. I exited my patrol car and contacted the operator and sole occupant of the vehicle through the driver&amp;#39;s window.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PHASE TWO - PERSONAL CONTACT:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Upon my initial contact with the operator, I identified myself, the reason for the traffic stop, and advised him that the stop was being audibly and visually recorded. I then asked him for his license and registration, which he provided after briefly searching through paperwork in the vehicle. His Maryland license identified him as Michael Harrison Day, DOB 02/19/1947. While speaking with Day, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. Additionally, I noticed that his eyes were glassy and bloodshot, and his speech was very slurred.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; While waiting for Day to retrieve his license and registration card, I asked him how much he had to drink that day and he responded &amp;quot;a couple of drinks&amp;quot; and when I asked what he had drank he said &amp;quot;beers&amp;quot;, later stating he had &amp;quot;two beers&amp;quot; at home in Salisbury. I now asked him to step out of his car and speak with me in front of his vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; As I spoke with Day in front of his vehicle I now clearly detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and/or person. I asked him if he would consent to standardized field sobriety tests, and he consented to take them.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PHASE THREE - PRE-ARREST SCREENING:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; While speaking with Day outside I observed his eyes were still bloodshot and glassy, and his speech was still slurred. He was wearing a long sleeve light jacket, jeans, and sneakers. He appeared to be in good overall health.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Screening Questions:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Medications taken?&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Gabapentin for nerve pain in his hand and neck.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Medical conditions?&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Nerve damage in his neck.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Injuries?&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Nerve pain following operation on his back.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The SFSTs were performed in a nearby driveway, and he was turned away from flashing lights and passing traffic in order to prevent optokinetic nystagmus. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. The area was illuminated by daylight. The weather was clear and calm.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues were observed&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;** Day struggled to follow my instructions to keep his eyes focused on my pen. I had to attempt the test several times.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 1. Day displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 2. Day displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 3. Day displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN: 7 of 8 clues were observed&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Day attempted to start walking multiple times before being told to start.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Day could not maintain his balance during the Instructional Phase as his feet broke apart from the instructed and demonstrated position multiple times.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Day stepped off-line by a foots width on multiple steps throughout the test.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Day missed heel-to-toe on multiple steps throughout the test.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Day took the wrong number of steps, taking 14 steps on his first 9. 11 steps on his second 9.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Day stopped the test prior to attempting the turn in order to ask me how many steps he was supposed to take.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Day did not complete the turn properly, as he did not keep his lead foot planted on the ground and pivoted with both feet to turn.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; ONE LEG STAND: 3 of 4 clues were observed&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Day swayed from side to side and forward and backwards.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Day put his foot down multiple times.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Day raised his arms more than 6 inches from his sides.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I offered Day the preliminary breath test, which he consented to take. I administered the test with a result of .22 BrAC.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; OBSERVATIONS / INDICATORS OF IMPAIRMENT:&lt;br /&gt; 1. Swerved out of lane twice, nearly striking guardrails both times.&lt;br /&gt; 2. Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage.&lt;br /&gt; 3. Glassy, bloodshot eyes.&lt;br /&gt; 4. Slurred speech.&lt;br /&gt; 5. Admitted to consuming multiple alcoholic beverages recently.&lt;br /&gt; 6. HGN: 6 of 6 clues&lt;br /&gt; 7. WAT: 7 of 8 clues&lt;br /&gt; 8. OLS: 3 of 4 clues&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; THE ARREST:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Due to my observations, and the results of the above tests, I believed Day to be under the influence of alcohol and unable to safely operate a motor vehicle. I placed him under arrest for DUI at 1442 hours on 6/19/23. In my patrol vehicle I played Day the MVA&amp;#39;s DR-15 Advice of Rights form in English from the MVA&amp;#39;s website. At its conclusion, Day agreed to chemical breath testing at 1457 hours. I transported Day to the Berlin Barrack the intoximeter test.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; CHEMICAL BREATH TESTING:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Day remained under direct observation for at least 20 minutes prior to the chemical breath testing. Corporal Snell #6191 conducted the chemical breath testing utilizing the Intoximeter EC/IR II at 1511 hours. The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of .22 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; DISPOSITION:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Day was issued all appropriate citations and provided copies of all pertinent documents. He was picked up from the barrack by his daughter.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6296</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 04:43:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6296</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 05:27:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mitchell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6296</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Snell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6191</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mitchell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6296</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mitchell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6296</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511446</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/19/2023 14:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6296</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 04:33:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6296</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 04:34:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511446</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/19/2023 14:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6296</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 04:33:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6296</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 04:34:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511446</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/19/2023 14:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6296</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 04:33:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6296</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 04:35:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>76</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6296</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 04:33:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:06</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>381615</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Day</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Harrison</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/19/1947 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/04/2023 04:24:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Day</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Harrison</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/19/1947 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/04/2023 04:24:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>735</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0957</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/04/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6296</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 04:36:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6296</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 04:36:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6296</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 04:36:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6296</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 04:36:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6296</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 04:33:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6296</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 04:33:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154811</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6296</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/04/2023 04:37:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6296</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/04/2023 04:37:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/04/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>13</StatusCode>
         <VIN>4S4BRBKC0D3220949</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>SUBA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>OUT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2CR8080</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicMonth>10</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>