<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-028947</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/16/2023 03:13:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/16/2023 03:13:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/16/2023 02:32:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/16/2023 02:32:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>White DUI // IL 495 @ US RT 1</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/16/2023 03:13:17</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/29/2023 02:50:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>25 MM CAPITAL BELTWAY SB, COLLEGE PARK</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>704009</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/16/2023 03:13:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 04:16:41</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>704009</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>25</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm Capital Beltway Sb College</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PARK</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.9252755</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0180596666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/16/2023 03:13:13</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/16/2023 03:13:13</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/29/2023 02:21:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/16/2023 03:13:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:04:54</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;strong&gt;Defendant: Camille Christine White&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 08/18/2000&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 08/16/2023&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 0308 hours&lt;br /&gt; MVR Statement: This incident was recorded on BWC and Q-31 MVR.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;DUI #: 23-176&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Training and Experience:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; *Standardized Field Sobriety Test through the Maryland State Police Academy.&lt;br /&gt; *Preliminary Breath Test Operator Certified through the Maryland State Police Academy.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Narrative:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Phase 1: Vehicle in Motion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On 08/16/2023 at approximately 0233 hours, I, Trooper Woodworth #7681, was on duty and operating in my official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper on the Interloop I-495 in the area of US Route 1, College Park, Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland, when I observed a silver Honda CRV traveling at a high rate of speed while passing my patrol vehicle. I observed the vehicle then traveling in lane 3 rapidly approach a passenger vehicle and overtake the vehicle, straddling the dotted white line dividing lane 3 and lane 4. The vehicle then drifted to the left and began straddling the dotted white line dividing lane 2 and lane 3. The vehicle then abruptly made a lane change to lane 4 from lane 3, nearly striking a tractor trailer that was traveling in lane 3. At this time, I activated my emergency equipment to initiate a traffic stop on the vehicle. After activating my equipment, the vehicle had a delayed response and was slow to apply the brakes and even increased speed upon attempting to stop the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Phase 2: Personal Contact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Upon approach, I proceeded to the passenger side, front window to make contact with the driver. I observed the driver looking at me through the passenger side window but conducted herself as if the passenger window was down. I had to motion to the driver to roll down the window at which point, I made contact with the driver who I later identified as Camille Christine White (W/F DOB: 08/18/2000) by her Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license. Upon asking for White for her driver&amp;#39;s license, registration and proof of insurance, White retrieved her driver&amp;#39;s license and appeared to have forgotten to retrieve the registration and insurance information. While speaking with White, I noticed dilated pupils, bloodshot and glassy eyes, as well as movements that appeared slow and lethargic. I proceeded back to my patrol vehicle to begin entering her information at which point, TFC. Strine #6972 made a driver&amp;#39;s side approach and made contact with White. Upon returning to the vehicle, TFC Strine advised he also observed dilated pupils and stated that upon attempting to retrieve insurance information, White forgot what she was looking for on two separate occasions. At this time, TFC Strine radioed for additional units for Standardized Field Sobriety Testing. Once additional units arrived, I proceeded to the driver&amp;#39;s side of the vehicle and asked White to exit her vehicle for&amp;nbsp;Standardized Field Sobriety Testing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Phase 3: Pre Arrest Screening&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Upon speaking with White outside the vehicle, TFC Strine detected a moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath. In my screening, I asked White if she was taking any medications which she listed Wellbutrin, Zoloft, Camictal and Doxepin. At this time, White stated that she had previously attempted to take her own life.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus: 4 of 6 clues observed.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; To begin, I asked White if she was wearing any contacts and if she had taken any medications other than the ones she previously mentioned. I utilized the tip of my ink pen as the stimulus and held it approximately 12-15 inches away from White&amp;#39;s face and asked if she was able to see it, which she nodded yes. I instructed White to follow the stimulus with her eyes and her eyes only and to not move her head and asked if she understood the instructions to which she nodded yes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Lack of smooth pursuit - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Walk and Turn: 6 of 8 clues observed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;To begin, I instructed and demonstrated White to stand with her left foot directly in front of her right foot, touching heel to toe, with her hands down by her side, and to remain in this position until told to begin. I then instructed and demonstrated the test by taking 3 heel to toe steps on a straight line while counting my steps out loud. Once I reached my third step, I kept my lead foot planted and began taking a series of small steps around my lead foot, before taking 3 more heel to toe steps back in the opposite direction. I instructed White that I took 3 for&amp;nbsp;demonstrational purposes and that she will be taking 9 heel to toe steps. At this time, White asked for clarification, to which I explained the test again, and she verbally restated the test, showing that she understood the test.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;1. Cannot balance during instructions - White stepped out of the starting position and remained out of the starting position until instructed to begin the test.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;2. Misses heel to toe - White missed every heel to toe step during the test going both directions.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;3. Steps off line - White steps off of the line on all 13 steps by placing her right foot to the right of the line and her left foot to the left of the line.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;4. Wrong number of steps - White took a total of 13 steps in the first set of 9 and 10 steps on the second set of 9&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5. Improper Turn - White did not complete the turn as instructed and took one large step to turn around&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;6. Stops walking - White stopped walking after making the turn and had to be reminded to take the 9 steps back&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;One Leg Stand: 4 of 4 clues observed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;To begin, I instructed White to stand feet together and hands down by her side. I then instructed and demonstrated the test by picking up a foot and lifting it approximately 6 inches off of the ground, while keeping my foot parallel to the ground and counting outloud by one-thousands. I then asked White if she understood the instructions and she stated that she did.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 1. Sways - White swayed constantly from left to right during seconds 0-10 and 11-20.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 2. Raises arms - White raised her arms more than 6 inches away from her body during seconds 0-10, and seconds 11-20.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 3. Hopping - White hopped during seconds 0-10 and 11-20 of the test&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 4 Puts foot down - White puts her foot down during seconds 11-20 and seconds 21-30.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Preliminary Breath Test:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; TFC Strine offered White a Preliminary Breath Test which she refused to take.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Arrest:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Due to the above stated facts, I placed White under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0308 hours. TFC Strine asked White if she had any weapons on her which she said she did not, and I placed her in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. TFC Strine conducted a mouth check of White to ensure no foreign objects were in her mouth.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I then called out the beginning mileage of my patrol vehicle and transported White to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack for DUI processing. Upon arrival at the barrack, I recorded my ending mileage and upon removing White from the vehicle, I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from White&amp;#39;s person and breath. I then conducted a secondary search of White&amp;#39;s person in front of my supervisor. Once the search was complete, I took White into the processing area and began reading the DR-15 Advice or Rights and TFC Strine provided White with a copy to follow along with. White read over the DR-15 and at approximately 0340 hours signed refusing to take the Evidentiary Test. At this time, White was given the opportunity to make a phone call but stated that she did not remember any phone numbers. White was informed that if no one was able to pick her up from the barrack that she would be taken to jail. At this time, White asked if there was any way that she could get the medications that she is prescribed and TFC Strine informed her that there was not and offered to call EMS for White which she declined. TFC Strine again asked if there was anyone she could call, and she said no. At this time, TFC Strine asked White again if she was sure that she did not want EMS to which White responded, &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m gonna kill myself if you call them&amp;quot;. At this time, TFC Strine called for EMS and they responded to the barrack. White refused their service and would not let them touch her. White then asked if she could call her mom and was allowed to make the call to her. While on the phone with her mom, White admitted that she had been consuming alcohol to her mom. At this time, White stated that she was feeling nauseous and that she was going to vomit. At this time, TFC Strine placed a trash bin in front of White and she proceeded to vomit on the floor, missing the trash bin. At this time, TFC Strine and I escorted White to the holding cell to get a drink of water. I then escorted White to the patrol vehicle to transport her to Laurel Regional Hospital. Beginning and ending mileage were recorded. I then took White to the emergency entrance and informed the staff that she was being emergency petitioned. At this time, hospital employees admitted White. I issued White the appropriate documentation and citations for the incident, and released her to Laurel Regional Hospital for an emergency petition.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I request this case be closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 04:35:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7681</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 13:51:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Strine</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6972</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>NIKODEMSKI</LastName>
            <FirstName>JONATHAN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7510</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Albaugh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Josiah</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7339</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Parsons</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5657</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Woodworth</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kory</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7681</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518394</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/16/2023 02:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7681</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518394</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/16/2023 02:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7681</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518394</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/16/2023 02:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7681</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518394</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/16/2023 02:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7681</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518394</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/16/2023 02:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7681</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518394</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15558</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/16/2023 02:32:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15558</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7681</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 04:31:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7681</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 13:31:03</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>385308</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>White</LastName>
               <FirstName>Camille</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christine</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/18/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/17/2023 00:00:59</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>White</LastName>
               <FirstName>Camille</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christine</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/18/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/17/2023 00:00:59</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1586</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Lancaster</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>GRN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Annapolis</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21401</Zip5>
               <Zip4>6465</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.54144</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.018211</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 13:31:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 13:31:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 13:31:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 13:31:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7681</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 04:25:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156202</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7681</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 04:34:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7681</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 04:34:37</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>7FARW2H94KE042488</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CR-V</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>FL</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>16BGDN</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>4</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>