<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-023654</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/01/2023 20:41:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/01/2023 20:41:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/01/2023 20:05:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/01/2023 20:05:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Assault in progress as a result of a road rage incident.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/01/2023 20:41:56</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3033</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 13:11:16</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>699614</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/01/2023 20:41:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 00:28:45</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>699614</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Green Valley</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Frederick</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.25355</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.43619</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>5350-5448</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/01/2023 20:41:54</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/01/2023 20:41:54</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/10/2023 23:56:56</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/01/2023 20:41:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:27:46</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Cpl. Sean Slattery // B-22 In Car Camera - Available // Body Camera - Available&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Attachments:&lt;br /&gt; None&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Suspects:&lt;br /&gt; Deonte Dwayne Spriggs DOB 05/10/1991&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Brian Elwood Thiele DOB 05/19/2004&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Victims:&lt;br /&gt; Deonte Dwayne Spriggs DOB 05/10/1991&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Statement:&lt;br /&gt; Spriggs stated that he was traveling on eastbound I-70 West of MD RT 75 behind a silver Nissan. Spriggs advised that the Nissan began to brake check him which he did not appreciate due to the rainy weather conditions. Spriggs then moved his tractor trailer into lane 2 beside the silver Nissan. Spriggs then rolled down his window and began to yell at the driver of the Nissan. Spriggs advised the Nissan began to drive erradically. Spriggs then moved his truck close to the line dividing lane 2 and 3 but paid careful attention not to cross it. Finally, Spriggs decided to exit at MD RT 75 in order to remove himself from the situation. Spriggs then noticed that the Nissan crossed over the grass so that he could exit onto Rt 75 as well. Spriggs then noticed that the silver Nissan parked next to him in a closed traffic lane at MD RT 75. The driver and passenger exited the vehicle and began to yell at Spriggs. Spriggs advised that he was not sure if he or one of the other individuals opened the door to his truck but somehow it was open. Spriggs tried to grab a screw driver to defend himself but was unable to find it. Spriggs then stated he was pulled out of the truck by the suspect, later identified as Brian Thiele. Spriggs advised that the two began to physically fight and he ended up on the ground with Thiele&amp;#39;s arm around his neck.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Brian Elwood Thiele DOB 05/19/2004&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Statement:&lt;br /&gt; Thiele advised that he was the passenger in a silver Nissan. He noticed that in lane 2 a tractor trailer tried to run his vehicle of the roadway twice. The tractor trailer pulled off at the exit for MD RT 75 and the Nissan followed. Thiele stated that he exited the Nissan when they pulled next to the tractor trailer to advise the driver of how dangerous his actions were. Thiele then stated that the driver of the tractor trailer, later identified as Deonte Spriggs, exited the truck and jumped on Thiele. Thiele was able to push him off and took a defensive stance against Spriggs. Thiele advised that Spriggs said &amp;quot;I got something for you&amp;quot; and went back into his truck. Thiele stated that he saw Spriggs pull a Glock 17 from a bag inside the truck so he grabbed Spriggs before he could fully grasp the gun. Thiele and Spriggs then had another physical altercation where Thiele ended up putting Spriggs in a headlock.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Scene Processing:&lt;br /&gt; The entire fight is captured on B-22&amp;#39;s in car camera and my body worn camera. No gun was located on scene or in Spriggs&amp;#39; truck. The footage shows Thiele and the driver of the Nissan, Brian Kush, standing outside their vehicle speaking with Spriggs. Spriggs then opens his door and exits the vehicle. It is unclear from the footage if Spriggs exits on his own power or if he is pulled out by Thiele. Spriggs then puts his shoulder into Thiele&amp;#39;s midsection and pushes him into the Nissan. Thiele begins to punch Spriggs in the back several times. Spriggs then picks up Thiele and slams him to the ground. Thiele puts Spriggs into a headlock with his left arm around Spriggs neck.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At this point, I arrive to the fight and assist to break it up. A small red mark was observed on Thiele&amp;#39;s neck. No other obvious injuries were observed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Neighborhood Check:&lt;br /&gt; Due to the location of the crime, no neighborhood check was conducted.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Narrative:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:12px"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;On July 1, 2023 at approximately 1940 hours, I was dispatched to a motor vehicle collision on MD RT 75 at Jones Rd (2023-00267457.) I was coming from a previous collision, 2023-00267441, which occurred on MD RT 340 at Gene Hemp Rd. I took eastbound 340 from the original collision and entered eastbound 70. The most direct route to the second collision was to take northbound 75 from eastbound I-70. I got off the exit for 75 and stopped behind several vehicles at the light for MD RT 75. The left lane was closed for construction but I observed a silver Nissan parked inside the construction barrels.&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Thiele and the driver of the Nissan, Brian Kush, standing outside their vehicle speaking with Spriggs. Spriggs then opens his door and exits the vehicle. It is unclear from the footage if Spriggs exits on his own power or if he is pulled out by Thiele. Spriggs the puts his shoulder into Thiele&amp;#39;s midsection and pushes him into the Nissan. Thiele begins to punch Spriggs in the back several times. Spriggs then picks up Thiele and slams him to the ground. Thiele puts Spriggs into a headlock with his left arm around Spriggs neck.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;At this point I intervened to separate the two. I was able to loosen Thiele&amp;#39;s grip on Spriggs neck enough where Spriggs could break free. I then restrained Spriggs as he was still agitated and wanted to continue the fight. Kush began to yell profanities and racial slurs at Spriggs. I advised Kush that he cannot say those things and ordered him back in his vehicle. I also moved Spriggs away from the other two involved so that everyone could calm down. I overheard Thiele advise that Spriggs had a gun. Spriggs advised that he was reaching for a large screwdriver to use as protection since the fight was two on one. Spriggs allowed me to look into his truck and I did not observe any handguns.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Once Spriggs was calm, I directed Kush and Thiele to move their vehicle further ahead to create more distance between the fighting parties. I then directed Spriggs to move his truck out of the lane of travel and onto the shoulder ahead. I spoke with Kush who advised that he was driving the Nissan on I-70 just West of mile marker 62. He observed Spriggs&amp;#39; tractor trailer behind him and thought Spriggs was following him too close. Kush then tapped the brakes to indicate to Spriggs that he was too close. Kush advised the tractor trailer moved next to him into lane 2 and began to force Kush&amp;#39;s Nissan off the road. Kush advised that this happened twice and it prompted him to call 911. Kush advised while speaking with 911, Spriggs&amp;#39; tractor trailer was exiting onto MD RT 75. The 911 operator advised Kush not to follow Spriggs but Kush did not take this advise. Kush was unsure of the vehicle tag number and wanted to properly identify the vehicle for 911. Kush advised that he pulled up next to the tractor trailer and his stepson, Thiele, exited the vehicle. Kush also exited and the three parties, Kush, Thiele and Spriggs began argueing. Kush advised that Spriggs then jumped out of the vehicle and attacked Thiele. Kush stated that Spriggs had a gun but further interview proved that Kush did not have any first hand information on that statement. His only basis was from what Thiele had told him.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I then spoke with Thiele who provided the above statement. I spoke with Spriggs who provided the above statement. Based on Thiele&amp;#39;s statement I asked Spriggs if he ever got back into the truck once the fight had began. Spriggs confirmed that once he got out of the truck he never got back into it until he was directed to by me. This was contradictory to Thiele&amp;#39;s statement that Spriggs went back into his truck to grab a gun. I spoke with Kush and asked if he observed Spriggs get back into his truck at any point after he initially jumped out. Kush advised that he did not think Spriggs ever got back into his truck until after I arrived. Again this was in direct conflict with Thiele&amp;#39;s statement.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Thiele and Spriggs were both offered medical services but they both declined. Thiele and Spriggs both stated that they did not wish to have criminal charges filed at this time. They were sent on their seperate ways and provided the case number.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All event occurred in Frederick County, MD&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I request this case be closed lack of prosecution.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 01:05:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 15:25:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brendan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7132</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1652</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Slattery</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6111</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513093</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>11</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/01/2023 20:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 00:29:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 00:29:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 00:30:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>63123</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>SPRIGGS</LastName>
               <FirstName>DEONTE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>DWAYNE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/10/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.12339364E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>06/16/2015 16:47:02</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S162</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D530</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>SPRIGGS</LastName>
               <FirstName>DEONTE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>DWAYNE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/10/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.12339364E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S162</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D530</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/16/2015 16:47:02</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6647</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Knottwood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21214</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.568408</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.368258</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>20</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Paula</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Rosedale</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21237</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.472597</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.353839</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>991</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1397</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/16/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>991</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1397</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/16/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 00:33:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 00:36:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>19</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 00:35:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>381458</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Thiele</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elwood</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/19/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/02/2023 00:34:55</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Thiele</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elwood</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/19/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/02/2023 00:34:55</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4120</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hill Haven</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Vale</City>
               <StateCode>NC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>28168</Zip5>
               <Zip4>9764</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-81.364926</Longitude>
               <Latitude>35.568198</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>828</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>578</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8983</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 00:35:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6111</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 00:36:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>