<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-016207</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/06/2023 20:19:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/06/2023 20:19:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/06/2023 19:44:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/06/2023 19:44:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI / DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/06/2023 20:19:02</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/05/2023 11:20:48</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I695 / I95 ETL N</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>586421</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/06/2023 20:19:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 21:46:59</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>586421</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I695</StreetName>
         <City>Rosedale</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetSuffixCode>N</CrossStreetSuffixCode>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IL @ 33</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L I695 /  I95 EAST SIDE RIGHT SHOULDER</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 IL / 0-0 I95 ETL N LS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L I695 /  I95 ETL N</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IL @ XT 33</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L I695 /  I95 RAMP</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IL RAMP TO 95 SB</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL RAMP TO 95 NB RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 0-0 I95 ETL N</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L I-I695 RAMP TO S/B I-95</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IL @ XT 33 RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/06/2023 20:19:01</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/06/2023 20:19:01</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/13/2023 07:51:59</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/06/2023 20:19:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:54:52</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI ARREST&lt;br /&gt; Case #: 23-MSP-016207&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Incident recorded on body worn camera and in-car camera.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Ashleigh Brittany BROOKS&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 03/14/1989&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 05/06/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 2020&lt;br /&gt; MD License #: MD10272222740&lt;br /&gt; DUI #: 23-252&lt;br /&gt; REPEAT OFFENDER&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TRAINING/CERTIFICATES&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Apprehended over 200 DUI/DWI Arrests to date.&lt;br /&gt; IACP National Training Conference on Drugs, Alcohol, and Impaired Driving 2019, 2020, 2021, 2022.&lt;br /&gt; DRE Instructor, November 2022.&lt;br /&gt; Distinguished graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute 2019.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Maryland Department of Transportation Medically Impaired Driver Detection December 2018.&lt;br /&gt; Collision Reconstruction, March 2018.&lt;br /&gt; SFST Instructor, February 2018.&lt;br /&gt; Drug Recognition Expert, July 2017.&lt;br /&gt; Maryland Department of Transportation DUI Enforcement Award, 2016, 2017, 2018.&lt;br /&gt; Maryland Department of Transportation Impaired Driving Conference, October 2016.&lt;br /&gt; Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.), September 2016.&lt;br /&gt; Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, August 2016.&lt;br /&gt; National Traffic Incident Management Responder Training, March 2016.&lt;br /&gt; Advanced Collision Investigation, March 2016.&lt;br /&gt; Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, October 2014.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 05/06/2023 at approximately 1946 hours, I, TFC Bunger # 6459, currently assigned to the Maryland State Police Golden Barrack, was dispatched to a single vehicle collision in the area of Inner Loop I-695 at I-95 (East). Upon arrival at approximately 2007 hours, I observed a sliver Ford Taurus bearing Maryland registration 7EY2912 disabled partially in lanes one and two.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The ford had heavy damage to the front bumper and both front quarter panels. Based on the tire marks and fluid trail, the Ford collided with the right shoulder concrete barrier and then came to rest in lanes one and two. The Ford&amp;rsquo;s steering column and side curtain airbags had deployed. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I approached the driver of the vehicle, who was seated on the left shoulder guardrail. She was identified by her Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license as Ashleigh Brittany BROOKS 03/14/1989. While speaking with BROOKS, I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. I also observed that her speech was slurred, her movements slow and uncoordinated, her eyelids drooping, and her eyes appeared to be glassy and bloodshot.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A check through MVA determined that her license was valid. She had no open warrants.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; BROOKS appeared to be having difficulty maintaining her balance while seated and was swaying forwards and backwards. When I asked her to describe the collision, she advised that she was coming from the Charm City Buffet and heading home but could not recall what happened. I observed that she had cuts on both hands from the crash, swelling on her left hand, blood in her nose and on her forehead. BROOKS advised that she had not been wearing &amp;nbsp;her seat belt but did not need medical treatment. She had also refused medical treatment from the fire department prior to my arrival.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed in the left shoulder of I-695. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of daylight. The weather was clear and approximately 75 degrees&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Glasses or Contacts &amp;ndash; None.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Medical Conditions &amp;ndash; None. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Injuries &amp;ndash; Injuries sustained in the collison..&lt;br /&gt; Medications &amp;ndash; None.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of a pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus. It was held approximately 12-15 inches from BROOKS&amp;rsquo; eyes, slightly above her eye level. BROOKS was instructed to look straight ahead, keep her head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with her eyes. BROOKS was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. BROOKS pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Vertical nystagmus was not present. BROOKS swayed in a circular pattern throughout the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN (8/8 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. BROOKS was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. BROOKS was then instructed to place her hands flat at her sides and remain in that position until told to begin. BROOKS was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, she was instructed to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, BROOKS was instructed to complete the second series of nine (9) steps in the same heel to toe fashion. BROOKS was instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, count every step aloud, and once she began the test she was not to stop walking until the test was completed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; BROOKS performed this test wearing sandals.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS immediately lost her balance and stepped to her left and required multiple attempts to get back into the starting position. She then lost her balance again and did not return to the starting position.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS attempted to start the test before being instructed to do so, completing one step.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st Nine)&lt;br /&gt; On step one, BROOKS attempted to reset her feet in a heel to toe fashion. She attempted this three times before &amp;nbsp;beginning the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; On step two, BROOKS stepped backwards. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS missed heel to toe on steps 4, and 12 -20&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS stepped off line on step 4, 6 10, 12,18.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS stopped on step 21 and asked if she was supposed to turn.&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS raised her arms approximately forty-five degrees from her sides for balance throughout the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS completed 21 steps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TURN&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS performed a walking turn while stepping backwards..&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (2nd Nine)&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS missed heel to toe on steps 1-2, 4-18.&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS stepped off line on steps 1-2, 5-9, 12-13.&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS kept her arms raised approximately forty-five degrees from her side for balance throughout the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS completed 19 steps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. BROOKS was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by hersides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise a foot of her choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, watch the raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, etc&amp;hellip;) and to not put her foot down until the end of the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS swayed from side to side.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10:&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS swayed from side to side.&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS bent her raised foot at the knee and held it behind her body.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS put her foot down approximately eight seconds into the test.&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS raised her arms between forty-five degrees from her sides and shoulder height for balance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20:&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS swayed from side to side.&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS kept her arms raised between forty-five degrees from her sides and shoulder height for balance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; BROOKS put her foot down and lost her balance approximately twenty seconds into the test. She then stumbled to her left. At this time the test was ended for safety.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; BROOKS did not count.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ARREST&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the totality of circumstances, I had reason to believe BROOKS was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Vehicle colliding with the right shoulder concrete barrier.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Slow, uncoordinated movements.&lt;br /&gt; Slurred speech.&lt;br /&gt; Glassy, bloodshot eyes.&lt;br /&gt; Drooping eyelids.&lt;br /&gt; Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on her breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; Clues during Standardized Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (6/6), WAT (8/8), OLS (3/4).&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Due to the number of observations, I concluded BROOKS was driving under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a vehicle safely.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At approximately 2020 hours, I placed BROOKS under arrest for driving while under the influence. I immediately notified the barrack, and searched her person for weapons and contraband. While inspecting the vehicle, I observed damage to the windshield indicative of a forehead strike above the steering wheel. Based on the likelihood of serious injury from this type of collision, I requested that medics respond to the scene to evaluate BROOKS. Baltimore County Fire Department Medic 203 responded to the scene. BROOKS refused medical treatment. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; BROOKS was read her DR-15 Advice of Rights. At approximately 2110 hours, BROOKS refused to take an alcohol concentration test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; INTOXIMETER RESULT&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Refusal&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; BROOKS was released to her mother. The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage was still emanating from her breath and person.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; She was issued the following citations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; CITATIONS:&lt;br /&gt; 21-901(b) Negligent driving.&lt;br /&gt; 21-901.1(a) Reckless driving.&lt;br /&gt; 21-201(a1) Failure to obey traffic control device.&lt;br /&gt; 21-309(b) Unsafe lane change.&lt;br /&gt; 26-102(b) Directing or permitting vehicle contrary to law.&lt;br /&gt; 21-902(a1i) Driving under the influence of alcohol.&lt;br /&gt; 21-902(b1i) Driving while impaired by alcohol.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The defendant was issued copies of the following documents:&lt;br /&gt; -Citations ( listed above )&lt;br /&gt; -DR-15 Advice of Rights.&lt;br /&gt; -DR-15a&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All documents were forwarded to the Baltimore County, State&amp;#39;s Attorney Office.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/04/2023 17:49:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6459</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/04/2023 17:49:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bunger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gregory</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6459</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wilson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4772</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bunger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gregory</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6459</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bunger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gregory</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6459</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505626</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/06/2023 20:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 21:46:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6459</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 21:58:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505626</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15558</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/06/2023 20:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15558</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 21:46:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6459</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 21:58:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505626</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/06/2023 20:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 21:46:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6459</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 21:58:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505626</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/06/2023 20:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 21:46:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6459</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 21:58:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505626</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/06/2023 20:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 21:46:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6459</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 22:02:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505626</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/06/2023 20:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 21:46:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6459</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 22:00:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505626</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/06/2023 20:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17272</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 21:46:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6459</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 21:58:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 21:46:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378608</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>BROOKS</LastName>
               <FirstName>ASHLEIGH</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>BRITTANY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/14/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 21:34:41</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A242</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>BROOKS</LastName>
               <FirstName>ASHLEIGH</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>BRITTANY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/14/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A242</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 21:34:41</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>CLEMENTINE</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>3D</SubNumber>
               <City>ROSEDALE</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21237</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 22:05:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 22:05:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 22:05:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 22:05:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 21:55:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6459</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 21:55:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153647</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6459</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 21:46:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6459</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 21:46:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FAHP2J84FG193744</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>TAU</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4D</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7EY2912</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>