<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-030187</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/27/2023 01:42:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/27/2023 01:42:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/27/2023 01:16:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/27/2023 01:16:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI 23- 216</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 01:42:53</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5948</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 04:04:14</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>E CHURCHVILLE RD/ MOORES MILL RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>531256</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 01:42:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 01:12:06</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>531256</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Churchville</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Bel Air</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.32383</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.54458</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1200-1222 E CHURCHVILLE RD / 0-0 MOORES MILL RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 E CHURCHVILLE RD / 0-0 MOORES MILL RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/27/2023 01:42:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/27/2023 01:42:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/01/2023 04:28:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 01:42:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:38</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Defendant: Castillo, Rafael E&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 8/27/2023&lt;br /&gt; License Number: NJ - C07766386502732&lt;br /&gt; DUI Number: 23-216&lt;br /&gt; Case Number: 23-MSP-030187&lt;br /&gt; Recording: D-27 is equipped with BWC/MVR. Interaction was captured.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TRAINING / CERTIFICATES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I am a certified police officer in the State of Maryland with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection at the Maryland State Police Academy. My training has led to numerous arrests for impaired driving. I am trained by the Maryland State police to administer standardized field sobriety tests. I am a certified Preliminary Breath test operator through the Maryland State Police. I am a graduate of the Advance Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement course (A.R.I.D.E.). I was recognized as a DUI Law Enforcement Awardee by the Maryland Highway Safety Office. I am a certified Advanced Collision Investigator through the Maryland State Police. I attended the Maryland Impaired Driving Conference in 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On 8/27/2023 at approximately 0116 hours I, TFC McMachan #6940 of the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barracks was on duty, and operating Maryland State Police marked patrol vehicle D-27 in the area of eastbound Churchville Road at Moores Mill Road. At this time I observed a gray Toyota Rav4 bearing New Jersey registration V50PWY traveling in lane one, unable to maintain its lane. I observed the passenger side tires drift into lane two and immediately returned to lane one on two occasions. I observed the Toyota straddle lanes one and two for an extended period of time. The Toyota made a lane change from lane one to lane two. I observed the driver&amp;#39;s side tires of the Toyota drift from lane two, into lane one, and immediately back into lane two on two occasions. I activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the Toyota.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the operator, stated the reason for the stop and requested his license and registration card. The operator was identified through his New Jersey issued driver&amp;#39;s license as Rafael E Castillo (DOB:2/28/1973 5/M). Castillo and his passenger advised they were following the vehicle in front of them to their house. I asked them where they were coming from to which, they advised the &amp;quot;VFW.&amp;quot; I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the Toyota. Castillo&amp;#39;s eyes appeared to be bloodshot, watery and glassy. I asked Castillo how much he had to drink tonight to which, he stated &amp;quot;Not that much.&amp;quot; I asked Castillo to place a numerical value on alcoholic beverages he consumed tonight to which, he stated &amp;quot;I just had a chaser.&amp;quot; Castillo added &amp;quot;I wasn&amp;#39;t really drinking.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on my observations from above, I requested Castillo perform standardized field sobriety tests to which, he agreed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed in front of my patrol vehicle. The surface was dry, level and free from any obvious debris. The forward facing emergency lights of all patrol vehicles on scene were deactivated for the duration of field sobriety.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Castillo the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; Glasses/Contacts: No&lt;br /&gt; Blind in either eye: No&lt;br /&gt; Injuries/Illnesses: Castillo advised he has lower back pain from an accident and from being a mechanic. I asked Castillo if his pain was severe or tolerable to which, he stated &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m fine.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; Medical disorders/disabilities: None&lt;br /&gt; Medication: &amp;quot;Tylenol&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; Recent Head Trauma: No&lt;br /&gt; Under the care of a Doctor other than routine check-up: No&lt;br /&gt; Under the care of a Dentist other than routine check-up: Castillo advised he got a tooth pulled out approximately two months ago&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While speaking with Castillo, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 CLUES):&lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Castillo&amp;#39;s eyes. Castillo was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Castillo&amp;#39;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I asked Castillo if he understood the instructions to which, he stated yes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Throughout the duration of the test, Castillo attempted to look at the stimulus utilizing his peripheral vision, rather than follow and focus on the stimulus until told to stop on five occasions. I had to re instruct Castillo on numerous occasions to follow and focus on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop, to which, he advised this was not an easy test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN (6/8 CLUES):&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Castillo performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Castillo was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe, and to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until instructed to begin. Castillo was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. He was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, Castillo was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of smaller steps around with his rear foot to turn 180 degrees facing the opposite direction. He was, again, explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Castillo was instructed that once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; It should be noted when Castillo first stepped out of the instructional position, he stated &amp;quot;I have no balance right now because I&amp;#39;m tired.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Cannot keep balance&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Misses heel to toe&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Steps off line&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Raises arms&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 4.) Incorrect number of steps&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Steps off line&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Raises arms&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Turn: Completed Incorrectly - Castillo failed to take a series of smaller steps to turn around but rather, turned around in a military fashion.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; It should be noted on Castillo&amp;#39;s first step he stepped off the line, raised his arms and almost fell. Castillo used my patrol vehicle to hold himself up.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ONE LEG STAND (3/4 CLUES):&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Castillo performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice approximately 6 inches off the ground. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Castillo if he understood the instructions to which, he stated &amp;quot;I think I do.&amp;quot; I reexplained the test to Castillo. Castillo advised he had a wound and varicose veins. I asked Castillo why he did not mention these when I first asked him to which, he stated &amp;quot;you didn&amp;#39;t ask me none of that.&amp;quot; I asked Castillo if he would like to attempt the test to which, he agreed. I asked Castillo if he needed me to reexplain the test to which, he stated yes. I reexplained the test to Castillo for a third time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Sways&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Raises arms&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Puts foot down&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Sways&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Raises arms&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Puts foot down&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Sways&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Raises arms&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Puts foot down&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PBT - .13&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to the observations from above, I determined Castillo was unable to operate a vehicle safely and placed him under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at 0142 hours. Castillo was secured in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barracks for processing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I read Castillo the DR-15 Advice of Rights in English. He was also provided a copy to read along. At approximately 0214 hours, Castillo signed the DR-15 Advice of Rights, refusing to submit to the evidentiary breath test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Castillo was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released on his own recognizance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I request this case be closed by arrest.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 01:23:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6940</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 03:07:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>O'Donald</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jesse</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7284</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McMachan</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6940</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stec</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5182</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McMachan</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6940</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McMachan</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6940</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519636</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/27/2023 01:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 01:11:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6940</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 01:13:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>50</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 01:11:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6940</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 01:14:07</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389109</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Castillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Rafael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>E</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/28/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/30/2023 01:07:22</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C234</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R140</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Castillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Rafael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>E</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/28/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C234</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R140</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/30/2023 01:07:22</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Pretoria</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Passaic</City>
               <StateCode>NJ</StateCode>
               <Zip5>07055</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2207</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-74.139452</Longitude>
               <Latitude>40.86699</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 01:14:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 01:14:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 01:14:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 01:14:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 01:12:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6940</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 01:12:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157566</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6940</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 01:21:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6940</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/30/2023 01:21:55</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>13</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JTMBK4DV9C5110312</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2012</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>RAV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>NJ</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>v50pwy</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>4</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>