<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-022052</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/19/2023 23:51:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/19/2023 23:51:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/19/2023 23:26:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/19/2023 23:26:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>06/20/2023 01:00:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>Jacquelyn Avila-Cacique was arrested for DUI/ DWI. DUI Folder #23-96-174</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 23:51:55</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 17:57:33</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY/ MAN O WAR LN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>698633</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 23:51:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/05/2023 17:03:08</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>698633</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>OCEAN </StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>BERLIN</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21811</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>W</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.14416</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.337463</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/19/2023 23:51:53</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/19/2023 23:51:53</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/18/2023 17:09:02</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/19/2023 23:51:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUI Folder # 23-96-174&lt;br /&gt; SUSPECT: Jaquelyn Avila-Cacique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;LICENSE #&amp;nbsp;MD/ A-142-356-017-025&lt;br /&gt; DUI CITATION # 3LR0VPH&lt;br /&gt; SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER: No&lt;br /&gt; ACCIDENT INVOLVED: No&lt;br /&gt; VIDEO: Maryland State Police; Axon Evidence Video ID #: 23MSP022052. BWC Utilized.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;ul style="list-style-type:square"&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I am trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of 2021.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of 2020.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I have apprehended more than 80 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Phase #1 - Vehicle In Motion:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On June 19, 2023, at approximately 2326 hours, I, Tfc. Pinto #7212 was on duty, operating unmarked Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle V-9, patrolling in the area westbound Ocean Gateway east of Golf Course Road, Ocean City, Worcester County Maryland in lane 2 and I observed a red Nissan Rogue bearing Maryland registration, &amp;ldquo;8EK1039,&amp;rdquo; traveling westbound on Ocean Gateway east of Golf Course Road and pass my patrol vehicle in lane 1. I remained behind the red Nissan and I observed the vehicle cross the solid yellow line into the left turn cement divider area by approximately one (1) tires width, and drift back into lane 1. I observed the red Nissan continue westbound on Ocean Gateway east of Elm Street, cross the solid yellow line, with the driver&amp;rsquo;s side tires, into the median area, by approximately one (1) tires width, and slowly drift back into lane 1. Once the red Nissan traveled to westbound Ocean Gateway at Elm Street, I observed the vehicle cross the solid yellow line into the median area, with the driver&amp;rsquo;s side tires, by approximately (2) tires width, and drift back into lane 1. I remained behind the red Nissan at westbound Ocean Gateway east of Stephen Decatur Highway and I observed the vehicle cross the solid yellow line into the median area, with the driver&amp;rsquo;s side tires, by approximately one (1) tires width, and weave back into lane 1. The red Nissan continued westbound on Ocean Gateway at Stephen Decatur Highway and I observed the vehicle cross the solid white line into the left turn lane, by approximately a half (1/2) of a tire&amp;rsquo;s width, coming within three (3) feet of side swiping dark colored dodge truck, and swerving into lane 1. I continued behind the red Nissan at westbound Ocean Gateway east of Keyser Point Road when I observed the vehicle cross the solid yellow line, into the median area, by approximately one (1) tires width, and swerve back into lane 1. The red Nissan continued to travel westbound on Ocean Gateway at Keyser Point Road and I observed the vehicle cross the solid yellow line, into the median area, by approximately one (1) tires width, and swerve back into lane 1. The red Nissan crossed the solid white line, into the left turn lane, by approximately one (1) tires width again, at westbound Ocean Gateway west of Keyser Point Road, at the median crossover. &amp;nbsp;The red Nissan continued westbound on Ocean Gateway at Man O War Lane in lane 1 and I observed the vehicle cross the solid yellow line by half (1/2) the tires width, into the median area, and swerve back into lane 1. I remained behind the red Nissan at westbound Ocean Gateway east of Man O War Lane when I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the red Nissan. The red Nissan came to a stop in the right turn lane at westbound Ocean Gateway east of Grays Corner Road. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Phase 2 - Personal Contact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Upon contact with the driver of the vehicle at the front driver&amp;rsquo;s side open window, I immediately detected the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the passenger compartment of the vehicle. I identified myself, and explained to the driver the reason for the traffic stop. While explaining the reason for the stop, the driver provided her license. I asked the driver for her registration. While the driver retrieved her registration, I identified the driver as Jacquelyn Avila-Cacique (W/F 01/08/2000) by her Maryland Driver&amp;rsquo;s license. I asked Avila-Cacique for her registration. While Avila-Cacique retrieved her registration, I asked her if she still lived at the Salisbury address on her license and she advised she did. Avila-Cacique then handed me a copy of her insurance card to the vehicle and I asked her a second time for the registration for the red Nissan. While Avila-Cacique retrieved the registration, I asked her where she was traveling from and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Ocean City.&amp;rdquo; I asked the driver where in Ocean City she was traveling from and she stated, &amp;ldquo;2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; Street.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique for the place she was traveling from on 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; Street and when she responded her speech was slurred and I had trouble understanding her. I asked Avila-Cacique to repeat herself and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Caribbean Pool bar.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique how many alcoholic beverages she consumed before driving and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Umm a couple, I don&amp;rsquo;t remember.&amp;rdquo; While speaking with Avila-Cacique, I observed her eyes to be glassy. I advised Avila-Cacique to continue to look for her registration card and to hold it out the window once she locates it. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I returned to my patrol vehicle, conducted routine checks on Avila-Cacique and asked for back-up for Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Phase #3 - Pre-Arrest Screening&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I deactivated my front emergency equipment. I approached the driver&amp;#39;s window of the red Nissan and retrieved the registration of the red Nissan. I asked Avila-Cacique to step out of her vehicle to continue my investigation and she complied. &amp;nbsp;While Avila-Cacique stepped from her vehicle I advised her I want to put her through some tests to make sure she is okay to drive. I asked Avila-Cacique to step to the front of her vehicle and she complied. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;While at the front of the red Nissan, I observed Avila-Cacique to be wearing a black sweatshirt, gray yoga pants, and gray Van shoes. I also detected the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Avila-Cacique&amp;rsquo;s breath and person.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;I advised Avila-Cacique I was going to ask her some questions and while I did so I asked her to stand with her feet together and hands by her side and she complied. I asked Avila-Cacique how many alcoholic beverages she consumed this evening and she stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not sure.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique around about how many alcoholic beverages she consumed and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Maybe three four.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique where she consumed the alcoholic beverages and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Um they were probably uh Wicomico Street.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique what&amp;rsquo;s on Wicomico Street and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Crawl Bar.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique if that is where she was currently traveling from right now and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes right now yes.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique what type of alcoholic beverages she consumed and she stated, &amp;ldquo;They were just like um hard tea.&amp;rdquo; Avila-Cacique then advised the hard tea were called Surf Sides. &amp;nbsp;I asked Avila-Cacique what size the alcoholic beverages were and she advised they were a twelve ounce can. I asked Avila-Cacique what time she consumed her last alcoholic beverages, advised her it was currently 2333 hours, and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Uh my last drink was um around like um maybe ten thirty.&amp;rdquo; Avila-Cacique then advised she drank water since. I asked Avila-Cacique what time she started consuming alcoholic beverages and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Umm maybe six thirty.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique if she has any physical disabilities and she stated, &amp;ldquo;No, other than me being like um visually impaired, I wear contacts.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila if she can see since she has her contacts in and she stated, &amp;ldquo;yes.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique if she had any physical abilities again and she stated, &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique if she has any medical disabilities and she stated, &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique if she has any recent injuries that would prevent her from walking in a straight line or standing on one leg and she stated, &amp;ldquo;No no no.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique if she was currently on any medications and she stated, &amp;ldquo;No, other than Clairton.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique if she wears contacts and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; I held a ten approximately twelve inches from her face and asked Avila-Cacique if I held a pen approximately twelve inches from her face if she can see it, &amp;ldquo;I can see it right now yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. &amp;nbsp;was asked to stand with her feet together and hands by her side. A pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Avila-Cacique&amp;rsquo; eyes, slightly above eye level. Avila-Cacique was instructed to look straight ahead at my pen and instructed to follow the pen with her eyes and eyes only. When asked if she understood the instructions, Avila-Cacique stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique if she had any questions and she stated, &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo; Avila-Cacique&amp;rsquo; pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I observed there was no resting nystagmus.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lack of smooth pursuit: Present in both eyes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation: Present in both eyes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees: Present in both eyes&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;For information purposes, I continued to detect the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Avila-Cacique breath and person while conducting the test. I also observed Avila-Cacique eyes to be glassy and observed her to be chewing gum. I requested Avila-Cacique to remove the gum from her mouth and she complied. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Walk and Turn&amp;nbsp;(5/8)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Weather: Clear and Dry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Surface: Flat and free from debris&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; The next test was the Walk and Turn test, Avila-Cacique was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot, touching heel to toe on the white solid road line. Avila-Cacique was instructed to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. When asked if she understood, Avila-Cacique stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Avila-Cacique was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step. Avila-Cacique was told to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Avila-Cacique was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Avila-Cacique was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. I advised Avila-Cacique I was taking three (3) steps for instructional purposes, but she was to take nine (9) steps. Avila-Cacique was instructed once she began the test keeping her hands down by her sides, looking down at her feet, and to count every step out loud. When Avila-Cacique was asked if she understood she stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique if she had any questions and she stated, &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Avila-Cacique lost balance, stepped out of starting position right after getting into starting position, by moving her left leg next to her right.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Walking Stage (1st Nine): &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Actual # of Steps: 10 Steps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Stepped Off Line: Steps 2, 5, 6&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Missed Heal to Toe: Steps 7 and 8&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raised Arms for Balance: Step 6&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Turn: Avila-Cacique stopped on step ten, looked at me, and asked, &amp;ldquo;Now go back right.&amp;rdquo; I advised Avila-Cacique to walk back how I explained and demonstrated. Avila-Cacique than began to walk the second set of nine steps backwards.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Walking State (2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;Nine):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Avila-Cacique took the second set of nine steps by stepping backwards.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Missed Heal to Toe: Steps 3, 5, 7&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stepped off Line: Steps 4, 6, 8&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Arms for Balance: Step 4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;One Leg Stand&amp;nbsp;(3/4 Clues)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Weather: Same as Above&lt;br /&gt; Surface: Same as Above&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Prior to Avila-Cacique performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Avila-Cacique was instructed to stand with her feet together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, watch her foot, keep her toe pointed forward, keep her hands at his sides, to count out loud by thousands (one-one thousand, two- one thousand), and to continue the test until told to stop. Avila-Cacique was asked if she understood and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Put Foot Down: 0-10 seconds, 11-20 seconds,&amp;nbsp;21-30 seconds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Raised Arms for Balance: 0-10 seconds, 11-20 seconds, 21-30 seconds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Sways: 0-10 seconds, 11-20 seconds, 21-30 seconds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alphabet Test (F to T):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;I asked Avila-Cacique if she was familiar with the English alphabet and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique if she graduated high school and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Yea.&amp;rdquo; I asked Avila-Cacique to say the Alphabet starting at F and end at T.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Avila-Cacique stated, &amp;ldquo;FGHI,&amp;rdquo; paused, and stated, &amp;ldquo;JKLMNOPQRSTU you just said T.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Count Backwards (59 to 36):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Avila-Cacique was asked to count backwards starting at 59 and end at 36.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Avila-Cacique stated, &amp;ldquo;59, 58, 57, 56, 55, 54, 53, 52, 51, 50, 49, 48, 49, 48, 47, 46, 45, 44, 43, wait, 44, 45, 43, 42, 41, 40, 39 &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preliminary Breath Test&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;I read Avila-Cacique her MSP Form 102 and explained the reasons for using a preliminary breath test and asked Avila-Cacique if she wanted to submit a breath sample. Avila-Cacique agreed to submit to the Preliminary Breath Test and submitted a breath sample of a 0.18 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;While interacting with Avila-Cacique during Standardized Field Sobriety I continued to detect the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. I also continued to observe her eyes to be glassy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Arrest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Based on the following totality of circumstances, I had reason to believe Avila-Cacique was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Avila-Cacique failed to obey a properly placed traffic control device.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Avila-Cacique&amp;rsquo;s breath and person.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Avila-Cacique&amp;rsquo;s eyes were glassy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Avila-Cacique completed Standardized Field Sobriety Test unsatisfactory.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At 2347 hours, I placed Avila-Cacique under arrest. I then placed Avila-Cacique into the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. I then entered my patrol vehicle and detected the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage that was not present prior to placing Avila-Cacique inside.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;I transported Avila-Cacique to the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack &amp;ldquo;V&amp;rsquo;, located at 9758 Ocean Gateway, Berlin, Worcester County, Maryland.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;DR-15 Advice of Rights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;While at the Barrack, I placed a paper copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights in front of Avila-Cacique and I played the MVA Audio version of the DR-15 from the MVA website and asked Avila-Cacique to follow along.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;After the DR-15 was completed, Avila-Cacique advised me at 0019 hours that she agreed to submit to take an intoximeter test, to measure her&amp;nbsp;breath alcohol concentration per 210 liters of breath.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Intoximeter Test&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sergeant Harper, a certified EC/IR II operator, checked Avila-Cacique&amp;rsquo;s mouth for foreign objects and nothing was located. At 0028 hours, Sergeant Harper administered the breath test&amp;nbsp;with a result of 0.16 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Avila-Cacique was processed and advised not to drive for 12 hours. Avila-Cacique was given her paperwork and citations and released to a valid sober driver from the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Charges&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driving Vehicle While Under the Influence of Alcohol (3LR0VPH)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driving Vehicle While Under the Influence of Alcohol Per Se (3LS0VPH)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driving Vehicle While Impaired by Alcohol (3LT0VPH)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Negligent Driving (3LV0VPH)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reckless Driving (3LW0VPH)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driver Fail to Obey a Properly Placed Traffic Control Device Instructions (3LX0VPH)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;For information purposes, Avila-Cacique was polite and cooperative during the entire interaction.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Case Closed by Arrest.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;All above events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/05/2023 12:23:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/05/2023 17:15:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jenkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7357</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511488</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/19/2023 23:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/05/2023 17:02:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/05/2023 17:03:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>23</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/05/2023 17:02:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:57</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>381739</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Avila-Cacique</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jacquelyn</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/08/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/05/2023 16:52:46</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A142</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J245</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Avila-Cacique</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jacquelyn</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/08/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>A142</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J245</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/05/2023 16:52:46</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>501 </StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Chelsea </StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury </City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21804</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.56607</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.358778</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>735</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3202</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/05/2023 17:11:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/05/2023 17:11:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/05/2023 17:03:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/05/2023 17:03:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154861</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/05/2023 17:14:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/05/2023 17:14:48</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5N1AT2MT3HC875039</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>RGE</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>RED</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8EK1039</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>11</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>