<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-031961</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/11/2023 17:20:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/11/2023 17:20:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/11/2023 16:35:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/11/2023 16:35:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI investigation.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 17:20:07</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6083</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/01/2023 17:12:21</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>706637</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 17:20:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 22:31:29</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>706637</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>5166</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Powellville</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Pittsville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21856</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.373241</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.331323</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/11/2023 17:20:04</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/11/2023 17:20:04</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/12/2023 03:17:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 17:20:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6083</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/01/2023 17:12:20</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Crime: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Driving Under the Influence&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defendant:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Justin Michael Leister&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Date of Birth:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;nbsp;01/01/1988&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Date of Arrest:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;nbsp;09/11/2023&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Time of Arrest:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;1718 hours&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;License#:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;MD10274099400&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUI #:&lt;/strong&gt; 23-54-188&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;DUI Citation&lt;/strong&gt; #: 3YM0VNY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Case #:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;23-MSP-031961&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subsequent Offender:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;No.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accident Involved:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;No&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;CDS Involved:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;No&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;BODY-WORN AXON CAMERA:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=6aab5472b12147e7b984ffdc1537819e&amp;amp;partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1&lt;br /&gt; https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=45ca4b5ff0924cf7954088389164f62c&amp;amp;partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;REAR AXON CAMERA: &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=51781f0ea32942a798ad418f51cead33&amp;amp;partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Narrative:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Phase One - Vehicle in Motion:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;On September 11,&amp;nbsp;2023, at approximately 1635 hours, I, Trooper First Class Graves #7199, was operating MSP marked patrol vehicle&amp;nbsp;E-22, equipped with an in-car camera. I was dispatched to 5166 Powellville Road, Pittsville, Maryland 21850 for an off duty Worcester County Deputy out with an individual he believed to have been driving while impaired. Upon my arrival to the scene I made contact with the complainant identified as Deputy Gardner #6004. Gardner informed myself that he was traveling in the area of Mt Hermon Road and Laws Road near a construction zone when he observed traffic violations and erratic driving of a white Honda CRV displaying Maryland Registration 5EH7737. Deputy Gardner proceeded to follow the vehicle and would pace the vehicle at speeds over 100 miles per hour and observe the vehicle passing other vehicles on solid yellow road markers. Gardner would follow the Honda CRV all the way to the Adkins Pond (located at 5166 Powellville Road) until it parked in a parking lot and the male operator proceeded to exit the vehicle with an alcoholic beverage in hand, Gardner thengave directions to the male operator to place the alcoholic beverage on the ground and sit at the picnic table under a canopy to wait for local law enforcement&amp;#39;s arrival. Gardner then called the local Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack for assistance.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Phase Two - Personal Contact:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Upon my initial approach, I observed the White Honda CRV displaying Maryland Registration 5EH7737 parked in the parking lot I would also observe the Four Loko alcoholic beverage now on the ground beside the vehicle. I would approach the driver, who was now seated on a park bench under the canopy, identified myself and explained the reason for the investigation. I would later identify the operator of the vehicle as Justin Michael&amp;nbsp;Leister (2/M, DOB: 01/01/1988). I immediately noticed that he displayed glassy and bloodshot eyes, and his&amp;nbsp;speech appeared to be slurred, but he was speaking very rapidly and appeared to be nervous.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I would ask if Leister had in fact arrived in the vehicle and exited the vehicle with an alcoholic beverage in his hand when the Deputy had approached him to which he would inform myself he had. Leister also stated he wanted to apologize to the deputy for driving recklessly as he was in a rush and wanted to reach his destination in order to calm down.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I would ask Leister how much of the alcoholic beverage he had consumed prior to driving, to which he would advise he had consumed &amp;quot;a few sips&amp;quot; of the Four Loko alcoholic beverage. I advised Leister that I wanted to conduct field sobriety to which he agreed to do so.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Phase Three - Pre-Arrest Screening:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Leister again how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed, which he repeated he had only consumed &amp;quot;a few sips&amp;quot; of his Four Loko. While Leister&amp;nbsp;spoke, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating&amp;nbsp;from his&amp;nbsp;breath and person.&amp;nbsp;I asked Leister&amp;nbsp;how long ago he had consumed his last alcoholic beverage, Leister advised that the last alcoholic beverage he had consumed was the night prior to this incident. I would ask Leister if he had consumed/ingested any other controlled dangerous substances prior to driving to which he would advise he had not.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on my observations and Leister&amp;#39;s own statements, I asked him to submit to a series of Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, which he agreed. I requested Leister to stand on the other side of the canopy. The concrete floor was relatively level and free of any obvious debris.&amp;nbsp; The weather conditions were clear.&amp;nbsp; Leister was wearing clothing, leggings, a short sleeve t shirt, but no shoes (Leister would advise myself that he did not have shoes).&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; To be noted I did observe Leister having burns on the top of his feet as well as his arms, he would advise he did not need assistance from Emergency Medical Services and it was from a prior incident.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to administering the tests, I asked Leister&amp;nbsp;if he wore prescription eye glasses or contacts, which he stated he does. Leister&amp;nbsp;would advise he was perscribed medications and identified them as Olanzapine and Buspar that he takes daily. I asked Leister&amp;nbsp;if he suffered from any medical injuries or illnesses&amp;nbsp;that would prevent him from walking, turning, or standing. Leister&amp;nbsp;advised he had no injuries that would prevent him from any of the tests but would inform myself he had Sciatica and a Stigmatisms in his eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;The first test administered was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I explained the test to Leister. Leister&amp;nbsp;advised he&amp;nbsp;understood my instructions and did not have any questions. Prior to beginning the test, I&amp;nbsp;held my pen twelve (12) to fifteen (15) inches from Leister&amp;#39;s nose, slightly above&amp;nbsp;eye level. During the test, Leister&amp;nbsp;displayed equal pupil size and equal tracking in both eyes, I did not observe any resting Nystagmus. While conducting the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test, I observed the following clues:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 2. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 3. Onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degree - Present in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A check for Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was conducted with Negative results.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;A total of six (6) clues were observed during this test.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;The second test administered was the Walk and Turn Test:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I explained and demonstrated the test to Leister. Prior to my instruction, I advised Leister&amp;nbsp;to stand on the imaginary straight line with his right foot in front of his left, with his right heel touching his left toes and to keep his arms down at his sides. I advised Leister&amp;nbsp;to remain in that position until instructed to begin the test. Leister&amp;nbsp;advised he understood and did not have any questions. While continuing with my explanation and demonstration of the test,&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Leister&amp;nbsp;started too soon one (1) time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I repeated my instructions to Leister&amp;nbsp;and advised him to return to the instructional position I had instructed him to stand in until told to start the test, which he did.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Upon completion of my explanation and demonstration of the test, Leister&amp;nbsp;advised he understood and did not have any questions&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;During the first set of steps:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Stepped off-line: step 6&lt;br /&gt; -Raises arms parallel to the ground on step 9&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - Performed an improper turn by shuffling both feet to turn 180 degrees.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;During second set of steps no clues were observed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;A total of four (4) clues were observed during this test.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;The third test administered was the One Leg Stand Test&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I explained and demonstrated the test to Leister. Upon completion of my&amp;nbsp;explanation and demonstration, Leister advised he understood and had no&amp;nbsp;questions.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Sways to his left at 5 seconds and again at 21 seconds.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; No other clues were observed during this portion of the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;A total of one (1) clue was observed during this test.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While I returned back to Leister after retrieving the Preliminary Breath Test, I picked up the Four Loko and would observe that the beverage was almost empty. I would then ask Leister if he had only consumed &amp;quot;sips&amp;quot; of the beverage, why it was almost empty, to which he replied, &amp;quot;I didn&amp;#39;t realize that, whatever is missing is what I had to drink.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Upon completion of the tests, I offered Leister&amp;nbsp;to submit to a Preliminary Breath Test, which he agreed. Leister&amp;nbsp;submitted to the Preliminary Breath Test with a result of 0.13 BrAC.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on my training at the Maryland State Police Academy, ARIDE training, knowledge, experience and prior DUI arrests, I placed Leister under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol at approximately 1718 hours. Leister&amp;rsquo;s oral cavity was checked upon arrest and was free of any foreign objects. A search was conducted on Leister&amp;rsquo;s person while on scene and upon arrival to the Maryland State Police Barrack. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Leister&amp;#39;s vehicle was taken into custody by Johns Auto Body Towing and taken to their tow lot.&amp;nbsp;I transported Leister to the MSP Salisbury Barrack for further processing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;While in route to the Barrack Leister became irate and would state the following:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - &amp;quot;... If I could literally just walk down there, calm myself down, went home I would have been fine. I would have been long enough to get the alcohol out of my system, no one would have ever caught me driving, I would have been fine.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;quot; &amp;hellip;and left when my blood alcohol was fine..&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;quot; Do you not realize I was 3 minutes away from walking down there, calming myself down, till the alcohol was out of my system, got in my car and got off.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;quot; I can&amp;#39;t get a god-damn brake and that why I drove like that.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Upon arrival at the barrack, Leister&amp;nbsp;was read and allowed to read his DR-15 &amp;quot;Advice of Rights&amp;quot; at approximately 1818 hours, where Leister agreed&amp;nbsp;to submit to the Alcohol Concentration Test. Leister&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;agreed to submit to the Intoximeter Test, with a result of 0.11 BrAC at approximately 1826 hours.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Intoximeter Test was administered by Certified Intoximeter Operator Cpl. Smith #6083. Leister was issued a DR-15A and a Temporary Driver&amp;#39;s License valid for forty-five (45) days. Leister&amp;#39;s Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license was not confiscated and turned into the MVA due to the fact he was not in possession of it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;While at the MSP Salisbury Barrack Leister would make the following statements:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;quot; I didn&amp;#39;t get caught driving, your lackey that was off duty caught me driving, that doesn&amp;#39;t count.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;quot;You have to be on Duty to catch a drunk driver.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -&amp;quot;No Police Officers saw me driving other than the off duty police officer.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;While Leister awaited for his mother to arrive to the barrack he would make the following statements:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;quot; I did zoom by like 3 people at a time in the wrong lane..&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;quot; I knew he was following me, because he was going 112 too, and for me that is two people going 112 that is twice the danger. You know what if he wrecked behind me, killed himself or somebody else killed them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Leister was issued the appropriate citations and&amp;nbsp;released from the barrack to a valid sober driver.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Leister was released from the barrack on the following citations:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 1. TA-21-902(A1ii)- Driving Vehicle while Under the Influence of Alcohol Per Se.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 2. TA-21-902(a1i)- Driving Vehicle while Under the Influence of Alcohol&lt;br /&gt; 3. TA-21-902(b1i) - Driving Veh. While Impaired by Alcohol&lt;br /&gt; 4. TA-21-901.1(b)- Negligent Driving&lt;br /&gt; 5. TA-21-901.1(a)- Reckless Driving&lt;br /&gt; 6. TA-16-112(c)- Failure of Individual on Highway to Display License to Uniformed Police on Demand&lt;br /&gt; 7. TA-21-801(a)- Driving Vehicle in Excess of Reasonable and Prudent Speed on Highway&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 8. TA-21-303(b)- Improper Passing of Overtaken Vehicle&lt;br /&gt; 9. TA-21-201(a1)- Driver Failure to Obey Properly Placed Traffic Control Device instructions&lt;br /&gt; 10. TA-21-309(b)- Driver Changing Lanes when Unsafe.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;I request this Case be&amp;nbsp;closed by arrest.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Wicomico County, MD.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7199</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 22:35:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7199</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 08:26:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pollmeier</LastName>
            <FirstName>Benjamin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6075</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Graves</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bradley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7199</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bruce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6083</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Graves</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bradley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7199</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Graves</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bradley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7199</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>521413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/11/2023 17:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7199</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 22:25:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7199</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 22:32:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>521413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/11/2023 17:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7199</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 22:25:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7199</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 22:33:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>521413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/11/2023 17:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7199</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 22:25:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7199</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 22:33:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>C</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7199</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 22:25:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7199</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 22:34:12</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>341121</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Leister</LastName>
               <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/01/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/20/2022 08:43:56</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L236</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J235</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Leister</LastName>
               <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/01/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L236</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J235</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/20/2022 08:43:56</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1807</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Emerson</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21801</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.589427</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.393099</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>251</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6982</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/20/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7199</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 22:34:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7199</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/11/2023 22:25:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7199</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/11/2023 22:25:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/01/2023 16:00:28</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/01/2023 16:00:28</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/01/2023 17:12:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7199</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/01/2023 16:00:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/01/2023 17:12:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ATTACHMENTS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DR-15- Advice of Rights&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; DR-15A- Certificate Order of Suspension&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; MSP 33Intoximeter Test Results&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Citations Issued to Leister&lt;br /&gt; CAD Detail.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; all events occurred in Wicomico County Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7199</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/01/2023 16:02:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7199</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/01/2023 16:04:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bruce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6083</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Graves</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bradley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7199</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>