<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-019207</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/29/2023 14:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/29/2023 14:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/29/2023 14:53:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/29/2023 14:53:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Police Information -  Homeland Security Investigations Agents forwarded case information regarding subjects attempting to ship suppressors to Maryland.  No local criminal leads developed.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/29/2023 14:54:38</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2916</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/15/2023 10:34:41</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>Target Residence</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>695821</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/29/2023 14:54:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/30/2023 10:48:17</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>695821</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>4517</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mountain</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Pasadena</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21122</Zip5>
         <Zip4>5305</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.493495</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.107253</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/29/2023 14:54:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/29/2023 14:54:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40R</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>06/15/2023 10:34:41</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/29/2023 14:54:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2916</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/15/2023 10:34:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; In May 2023, Firearms Enforcement Investigators were relayed information from Homeland Security Investigations &amp;ndash; Baltimore Region regarding information related to potential firearms violations.&amp;nbsp; The information provided indicated in April 2022 US Customs and Border Protection identified a parcel/package at a New York facility destined for a residence at 4517 Mountain Road, Pasadena, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; The recipient of the package was listed as Eneyda Garcia.&amp;nbsp; The package was identified to contain a firearm suppressor.&amp;nbsp; The package was seized due to Federal regulation and not delivered.&amp;nbsp; The owner was notified, but did not respond and the item was destroyed.&amp;nbsp; In May 2023 a second parcel containing a firearm suppressor was identified and seized in the same manner as the first.&amp;nbsp; Federal Investigators made observations of the target residence and found two vehicles registered to Jose Israel Franco Martinez of Lanham, Maryland parked at that location.&amp;nbsp; Investigators determined Franco Martinez and Garcia have a joint bank account.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; S/T S. DiToto initiated an investigation into the subjects involved in this case utilizing Law Enforcement reproduces and Maryland MVA, the subjects involved were Jose Israel Franco Martinez (DOB: 01/10//1967) and Eneyda Arcely Garcia Melchor (DOB: 04/15/1989).&amp;nbsp; S/T S. DiToto conducted checks of both subjects with assistance from the Maryland Gun Center and determined neither was prohibited from possessing firearms or ammunition.&amp;nbsp; Additional checks of DNR, RAPID, MAFSS, and other resources including social media sites revealed no further information associating Garcia Melchor or Franco Martinez with firearms or firearms violations.&amp;nbsp; Checks were conducted through multiple resources to identify any other associated persons to both the Pasadena and Lanham addresses.&amp;nbsp; No other subjects were identified and no indicators of possible criminal activity were observed.&amp;nbsp; Through the course of this investigation, no violations of Maryland law were occurring and as the package was not delivered, the Federal violations had already been disrupted by the Agencies involved.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;FEU Investigators relayed this information to the HSI Agent and offered continued support as needed with any part of their investigation. No further investigative action at this time. Case closed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5416</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/30/2023 10:44:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5416</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/30/2023 10:44:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sawa</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2916</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ditoto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5416</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>