<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-027699</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/05/2023 10:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/05/2023 10:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/05/2023 10:10:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/05/2023 10:10:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>White male suspect damaged a mechanical flagpole and a U.S. Flag</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/05/2023 10:54:19</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1773</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 08:59:14</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>CTP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>MDOP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>685271</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/05/2023 10:54:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/05/2023 13:16:30</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>685271</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>11407</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Samuel Bowen</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21811</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.161923</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.34232</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>ZOOM CAR WASH</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/05/2023 10:54:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/05/2023 10:54:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1201</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/21/2023 00:15:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/05/2023 10:54:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:06:37</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SCENE PROCESSING:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Due to the complete capturing of the crime on video surveillance, nature of the crime and the identification of the suspect, no neighborhood check was performed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;As I stretched the flag to it&amp;#39;s full length/ width I observed random quotes and other writing on one of the white stripes in black ink. In the center of the flag, I discovered a black &amp;quot;Sharpie&amp;quot; pen with a blue Capital One Master Card credit card inscribed &amp;quot;Charles W Himmel Jr&amp;quot;. On the revere side, also written in black ink(presumably by the same Sharpie pen, &amp;quot;443-752-1467&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Call Me&amp;quot; with an arrow drawn from &amp;quot;Call Me&amp;quot; to the inscribed name, &amp;quot;CHARLES W HIMMEL JR&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I photographed the damaged property and attached the photographs to this report. I obtained video surveillance on a flash drive and stored it in evidence. I obtained the invoices to repair the damage to the flag pole equipment and replace the 20&amp;#39; x 38&amp;#39; Garrison-sized, U.S. Flag, which totaled $2,315.74&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The damages we incurred&amp;nbsp;totaled $2,315.74, as a result of Mr. Charles Himmel&amp;#39;s actions on August 4th, 2023. The breakdown of the cost are as follows:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Replace the 20x36 Nylon Garrison Flag = $1,237.24&lt;br /&gt; 2. Cost of flag pole repair = $800.00&lt;br /&gt; 3. Cost to re-key and repair&amp;nbsp;the flagpole access door = $278.50&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;SUSPECT:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Charles Warne Himmel JR&lt;br /&gt; 100 Craig Road&lt;br /&gt; Airville, PA 17302&lt;br /&gt; 443-752-1467&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;NARRATIVE:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 8/5/2023 at approximately 1010 hours, I was dispatched to Zoom Car Wash, 11407 Samuel Bowen Blvd, Worcester County, Maryland for Malicious Destruction of Property.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Upon arrival, I contacted John Abent, the Zoom Car Wash manager who led me to where the 20&amp;#39; x 38&amp;#39; garrison-sized U.S. Flag that was lying on the grass, on the north-portion of Zoom Car Wash property (facing US Route 50). I observed a broken 1/8&amp;quot; stainless steel cable protruding from the access door on the flag pole. The access door was on the ground and damaged from being forcefully removed from the flagpole. I also observed miscellaneous items and random metal parts strewn about. As I stretched the flag to it&amp;#39;s full length/ width I observed random quotes and other writing on one of the white stripes in black ink. I also found lying on center of the flag, a black &amp;quot;Sharpie&amp;quot; pen with a blue plastic Capital One Master Card credit card inscribed &amp;quot;Charles W Himmel Jr&amp;quot;. On the revere side of the card, also written in black ink(presumably by the same Sharpie pen, &amp;quot;443-752-1467&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Call Me&amp;quot; with an arrow drawn from &amp;quot;Call Me&amp;quot; to the inscribed name, &amp;quot;CHARLES W HIMMEL JR&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;John Abent had full access to the video surveillance that we reviewed which showed a white male, later identified as Charles Warne Himmel Jr, operating a white 2017 Chevrolet Equinox, PA Registration: KDC6682, which was registered to Ashly Rabecca Himmel (Charles Himmel&amp;#39;s wife). Himmel spent approximal 2.5 hours on the Zoom Car Wash property, walking to various areas, collecting rope, various tools, parts, etc, while speaking to someone on his mobile phone Later, we discovered that Himmel was speaking to his father during this time. The video shows Himmel forcing open the flag pole access door and he used the rope, which he then attached a snap link to the flag pole cable and the other end to the front of the white SUV. In the video, Himmel enters the white SUV, which then moves in reverse, which broke the 1/8&amp;quot; stainless steel cable to which the U.S. Flag was attached. When the cable broke, the U.S. Flag immediately fell to the ground. The video then shows walking around the flag which is now on the ground and all over the area. Himmel is also shown returning the tools and parts and other various items to where he found them before eventually leaving the property.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I called the telephone number given and spoke to Himmel, who advised that he was operating a white Chevrolet SUV in the area of the Zoom Car Wash during the time of the video surveillance recording. I took a photograph of the suspect from the video surveillance and I observed that the image of the white male displayed matched the image of the PA DMV driver&amp;#39;s license photograph of Charles Warne Himmel JR. who resides in Airville, PA. I had identified the suspect and was awaiting the cost of the damage to the property to then submit a statement of probable cause and a statement of charges for the appropriate crime.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Several days later, before I had yet received any invoices or estimates of the cost od damages, I learned that the owners of Zoom Car Wash took it upon themselves to post all pictures of the suspect&amp;#39;s image, the damaged and destroyed property(evidence of the crime) to the Facebook social media website and asked the public to help identify the suspect. I spoke to Abent, who advised that he had nothing to do with the posting of the images to the internet. Abent then advised that he had spoken to Himmel because of the Facebook post, who apologized for damaging the flag pole and the U.S. Flag. According to Abent, Himmel advised that Himmel observed the U.S. Flag was at half-staff and he believed, &amp;quot;America&amp;nbsp;needs to see this beautiful flag&amp;quot;, to honor the flag and military veterans who have served, to include Himmel&amp;#39;s father. (To raise the flag all the way up).&amp;quot; According to Abent, Himmel advised that Abent had not taken his prescribed medications for Bi-Polar Disorder and he had not been in a proper mindset during this episode at Zoom Car Wash. This appears to be the reason Himmel left his credit card at the scene. To pay for whatever damage that his actions caused. I&amp;#39;m referring to the &amp;quot;Call Me&amp;quot; and arrow to his name on the credit card.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;This is two paragraphs from John Abent&amp;#39;s email to me, describing a long telephone discussion in &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;bold italics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; with Himmel:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Earlier today, on 08/15/2023, Mr. Charles Himmel, called me asking me for the above totals, so he could make restitution to Zoom Carwash. He explained to me once again how sorry he was for his actions. He also explained how he was just released from his doctors care and that he suffers from a Bipolar&amp;nbsp;disorder and that he had stopped taking his medications prior to the August 4th incident. He said he stopped&amp;nbsp;his medication because&amp;nbsp;it made him feel high all the time.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;quot;In an earlier conversation with Mr. Himmel Jr. on Tuesday, August 8th, 2023 he explained to us that what he was really trying to do was to raise the flag because&amp;nbsp;he believed &amp;quot;America&amp;nbsp;needs to see this beautiful flag&amp;quot;. This intent was confirmed by us from the audio we captured of him talking to his &amp;quot;dad&amp;quot; on the phone. Both Charles Holland Jr. and myself clearly heard him on the phone telling his dad that he needed about, &amp;quot;another 30 minutes to get the flag raised.&amp;quot; At the time we heard this we first thought he was confused but after talking to him, he again&amp;nbsp;expressed that his desire was to raise the flag not drop it.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;John Abent, stated that on 8/15/2023 Himmel called Abent by telephone to again apologize and ask for the total cost of damages to pay full restitution. Himmel has accepted full responsibility and has apologized numerous times for all damages and trouble that he caused to Zoom Car Wash property. The below in bold italics is from the same email, (which I have attached to this report), requesting no charges be submitted against Himmel.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;quot;To Corporal Lenz......As we all now know things did not go as he planned, and that coupled with his bipolar confusion only made matters worse. He did however leave his name, the names of all his family and his credit card because&amp;nbsp;he accepted responsibility for his actions that night.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After discussing the matter with Mr. Charles Holland, one of the owners, it was decided that we do not wish to press charges against Mr. Charles Himmel Jr. and we accept his offer to make full restitution as long as he also sought medical help, which he already fulfilled&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Today, in his phone call he promised to send us a check for the full amount and as such we consider the matter closed, while fully expecting to receive his check in the mail shortly.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; We thank you for your expert advice throughout this trying time, and appreciate your efficient&amp;nbsp; and timely handling of this case and hope that the States Attorney would consider this as a resolved civil matter between Zoom Carwash and Mr. Charles&amp;nbsp;Himmel Jr. and not pursue any criminal charges.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; We do believe the Lord is directing us and helping us turn this most trying matter into something good. We are also planning a re-dedication ceremony some time in the near future and hope that you also might consider taking part in that ceremony with us.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The victim considers this matter resolved as a civil matter and does not wish for this to be pursued any further as a crime.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Case closed.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/05/2023 13:19:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4839</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 01:37:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lenz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4839</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517143</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>CO193</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/05/2023 10:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>CO193</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/05/2023 13:19:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4839</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/05/2023 13:19:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 01:50:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 01:51:41</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>385488</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Himmel</LastName>
               <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Warne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/01/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/19/2023 01:49:55</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H540</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Himmel</LastName>
               <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Warne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/01/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H540</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/19/2023 01:49:55</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>752</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1467</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 01:51:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240020020</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>Zoom Car Wash</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 22:37:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4839</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 22:37:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 22:46:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4839</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 22:46:56</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>20' x 38' Mil Spec Garrison Flag/ Battle Ensign</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>999</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>1237.24</PropertyValue>
         <Value>1237.24</Value>
         <SerialNumber>NONE</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>253050</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>MUL/COL</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>MUL/COL</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>Apex Flags Inc</Make>
         <Model>Nylon 20' x 38' U.S. Flag</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 22:53:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4839</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 22:54:01</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Flag Pole Access Door</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>71</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>278.5</PropertyValue>
         <Value>278.5</Value>
         <SerialNumber>NONE</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>253051</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>SIL</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>SIL</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>UNK</Make>
         <Model>Flag Pole Access Door</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 22:57:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4839</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 22:57:16</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>1/8" Stainless Stl Cable</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>71</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>800</PropertyValue>
         <Value>800</Value>
         <SerialNumber>N/A</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>253052</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>SIL</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>SIL</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>Unk</Make>
         <Model>1/8" Stainless Stl Cable</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/20/2023 01:51:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4839</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/20/2023 01:51:53</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>white/ black Flash Drive</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>819</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>1</PropertyValue>
         <Value>1</Value>
         <SerialNumber>NONE</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>253058</Property_ID>
         <Make>Staples</Make>
         <Model>16mb Flash Drive</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>