<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-032914</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40P</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/19/2023 13:41:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/19/2023 13:41:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/19/2023 13:41:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/19/2023 13:41:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>CDS IMPORTATION INVESTIGATION</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/19/2023 13:41:37</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4812</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/15/2024 11:55:13</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DSM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>707403</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/19/2023 13:41:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 09:05:26</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>707403</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>6903</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Adelphi</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Hyattsville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.95134</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.974428</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/19/2023 13:41:33</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/19/2023 13:41:33</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40P</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/15/2024 11:55:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/19/2023 13:41:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On Tuesday, September 19, 2023, at the Louisville, Kentucky UPS Hub, Customs Border Protection Officer Garcia seized UPS shipment 94220RGXQMZ with tracking number 1Z94220R0445289135. The shipment was also placed on hold by CBPO GARCIA due to a prior port seizure. The one (1) piece shipment was manifested as &amp;quot;COOKWARE ORNAMENT PENCIL HOLDER PENCIL N&amp;rdquo; with a manifested weight of 13 lbs. and a $13.00 USD declared value. The shipment originated in Guatemala City, Guatemala and was en-route to Hyattsville, Maryland, USA. Upon inspection, several wooden crafts were discovered. An intrusive examination, based on authority provided to them through United States Code, Title 19, Section 482, revealed a white, powdery substance inside 3 of the wooden crafts. The substance was tested with the Tru-Narc device and had a positive result for Cocaine, a Schedule II Controlled Dangerous Substance. The Cocaine in the craft was weighed at a total of 1.1 kilograms. The Cocaine in crafts were placed and sealed inside an evidence bag and weighed for a gross weight of 1.2 kilograms. The shipping box and remainder of shipment were detained for potential controlled delivery. Weights and testing witnessed by CBPO Garcia and CBPO Johnson. Homeland Security Investigations Louisville was notified via e-mail. The parcel was subsequently transferred to HSI Baltimore. HSI Baltimore contacted the Metropolitan Area Drug Task Force to transfer the parcel and further the investigation with a controlled delivery. The parcel displayed the following sender and receiver addresses: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;SHIPPER:&lt;br /&gt; KARLA MERCEDES 55531821 KARLA MERCEDES CHIQUIMULA 01012 GUATEMALA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;SHIP TO:&lt;br /&gt; CARLOS MERCEDES (202) 627-9942 CARLOS MERCEDES 6903 ADELPHI RD HYATTSVILLE MD 20782 UNITED STATES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;HSI agents contacted law enforcement representatives in Maryland. At that time, the parcel, was seized and stored on United States Customs and Border Protection property form number 2023419600446101. HSI Special Agent Keller contacted Sgt R. McNeely #4812 of the Maryland State Police and members of the Metropolitan Area Drug Task Force in relation to the furtherance of this investigation. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On September 20, 2023, at approximately 1204 hours, I (Det. Diggs#309) took possession of the parcel from Special Agent Tony Williams at the request of HSI Baltimore S/A Keller. I transported the parcel to the MADTF office, located in Greenbelt, Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County Maryland for confirmation field-testing which returned positive. On September 20, 2023, members of MADTF and I performed an inventory of the shipped property from Guatemala. During that time, I confirmed that it contained approximately 1.2 kilograms of Cocaine concealed in three woodened crafts. This is a significant amount of CDS (Cocaine) that, based on my training, knowledge and experience as a narcotics Detective warrants distribution.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Members of MADTF and I then re-packaged approximately 1.2 kilograms of Cocaine inside the parcel for a controlled delivery. On September 21, 2023, at approximately 0900 hours, members of MADTF went to the area 6903 Adelphi Road, Hyattsville, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20782 to establish surveillance for a controlled delivery of the parcel.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On September 21, 2023, at approximately 1030 hours, an undercover Police Officer posing as a UPS delivery driver conducted a controlled delivery of the parcel containing the Cocaine (refer to Det. Navarro supplement). The parcel was left on the front step of the residence by the undercover officer. Members of the Metropolitan Area Drug Task-force and assisting law enforcement personnel maintained constant surveillance on the parcel, both during and after the controlled delivery.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At 1045 hours while monitoring the front door to the residence of 6903 Adelphi Road, Hyattsville, Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland Detective Moreno #5652 of the Metropolitan Area Drug Task Force observed an unknown Hispanic male wearing a red shirt and blue jeans exiting the residence with a dog. While exiting the residence the unknown Hispanic male took possession of the delivered parcel and was observed walking to a white Honda Civic sedan bearing Maryland registration 3FA0493 parked in the driveway of 6903 Adelphi Road. Detective Moreno #5652 observed the unknown Hispanic male walk to the rear of the white Honda Civic sedan opening the rear trunk compartment of the vehicle.Detective Moreno #5652 also observed the unknown Hispanic male place the parcel/shipment containing the Cocaine inside the trunk compartment of the white Honda Civic bearing Maryland registration 3FA0493, closing the trunk to the vehicle afterwards. Detective Moreno #5652 along with other members of the Metropolitan Area Drug Task Force continued to observe the unknown Hispanic male while he was outside the vehicle. The unknown Hispanic male walked around the perimeter of the home with the dog before returning inside the residence of 6903 Adelphi Road.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;At 1118 hours Detective Moreno #5652 observed the same Hispanic male wearing a gray shirt and blue jeans, along with an unknown Hispanic female wearing a black shirt and blue jeans exit the front door of the residence of 6903 Adelphi Road. Both individuals approached the white Honda Civic sedan. The female entered the driver&amp;#39;s side and the male entered the passenger side of the vehicle bearing Maryland registration 3FA0493.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;At 1124 hours Sgt, McNeeely blocked the vehicle in the driveway (refer to Sgt. McNeely supplement.) Moments later MSP S.T.A.T.E. arrived at 6903 Adelphi Road, Hyattsville, Prince Georges County, Maryland and detained both individuals. While being detained the unknown Hispanic female, later identified as Sandra Patricia Ramos Mejia (DOB: 5/8/90) wearing black shirt and blue jeans was still in possession of the keys to the white Honda Civic sedan bearing Maryland registration 5DF4608 along with a Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license. The male occupant was later identified by his CASA ID card as Avidan De Jesus Ramirez-Lopez (DOB: 4/5/85). Ramirez-Lopez retrieved the CASA ID card from 6903 Adelphi Road while being accompanied by Sgt. McNeely and S/T Moreno, with his consent.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The unknown Hispanic male was Both Ramirez Lopez and Ramos Mejia were transported back to the MSP College Park Barrack to be interviewed. Ramirez Lopez was read his Advice of Miranda Rights from the MSP 180 form at 1235 hours by S/T Moreno #5652 in Spanish as the interpreter. Ramirez Lopez signed the form and&amp;nbsp; waived his right to have an attorney being present and agreed to speak with us. Upon questioning, he admitted to removing the UPS parcel containing the Cocaine from the front steps and placing it in the white Honda with MD registration 3FA0493, which was parked in the driveway of the residence.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Upon further questioning he admitted to meeting an unknown male at a bar several months prior to this date who asked if he would like to make some extra money on the side? Ramirez Lopez responded &amp;quot;No.&amp;quot; However, he did give the unknown male his phone number upon request. Ramirez Lopez advised that he eventually received a call from the same unknown male who paid him a $1000 to deliver a box for the first time to an unknown location approximately three weeks prior to this date (9/21). Ramirez Lopez stated that he suspected what was in the parcel but did not ask any questions. I showed Ramirez Lopez a picture of a Carlos Tomas Mercedes, who was discovered through investigative means to be associated with the 6903 Adelphi Road address where he resided. Ramirez Lopez advised he did not know Mercedes. I asked if I could search his Samsung phone, and he gave written consent. A search of Ramirez Lopez&amp;#39;s phone revealed the phone number; &amp;quot;(301) 437&amp;ndash;3534&amp;quot; which was listed under &amp;quot;Tito&amp;quot;. Through investigative means I discovered that the phone number belonged to Carlos Tomas Mercedes. Once I advised Ramirez Lopez of that information, he decided to take full responsibility for the parcel of Cocaine and advised he knew Mercedes and &amp;quot;Tito&amp;quot; was one and the same person. Ramirez Lopez advised he did not want any trouble with Mercedes, would rather go to jail and was willing to take full responsibility for the parcel of Cocaine. At that point the interview was terminated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ramirez Lopez will be charged accordingly with;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;*CDS: IMPORT INTO STATE (COCAINE, SCHEDULE 2) {Which holds an estimated street value of $275,000}&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;**CDS: POSS W /INTENT TO DISTRIBUTE (COCAINE, SCHEDULE 2)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;CDS: POSSESSION NOT CANNIBUS (COCAINE, SCHEDULE 2)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;*The above charge is based on COCAINE, which was imported from &lt;strong&gt;Guatemala City, Guatemala&lt;/strong&gt; and was destined to &lt;strong&gt;Hyattsville, Maryland, USA.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#f3f3f3"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;**Based on my training, knowledge, experience, amounts, weights, packaging methods and other circumstances of the case, I recognized the above-mentioned CDS: Cocaine to be indicative of purposes for distribution.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The white Honda Civic was towed by N&amp;amp;S towing to the MSP College Park Barrack and was followed by Inspector Whetstone to maintain custody. A search and seizure vehicle warrant was authored and was subsequently granted by the Honorable Judge E. Nyce for the above-mentioned Honda Civic. Removed from the Honda was the following items for further processing and investigation;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;-CARDBOARD BOX (Trk. # 1Z94220R0445289135) CONTAINING the Cocaine with crafts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;-BLACK SAMSUNG PHONE (IMEI:350026/55/373534/2)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;-BLACK SAMSUNG PHONE WITH BLUE CASE (IMEI:357388863377592)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;The above-mentioned mobile phones were seized from the passengers side of the vehicle for further investigation and download pending a search and seizure warrant.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;$1260 was seized from Ramirez Lopez as drug assets forfeiture.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;$100 / 1 -$100, $50 / 2 - $100, $20 / 44 $880, $10 / 17 - $170, $1 / 10 - $10&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Ramirez-Lopez was subsequently transported to Upper Marlboro DOC for processing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ALL EVENTS OCCURRED IN PRINCE GEORGE&amp;#39;S COUNTY MARYLAND&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>TF0309</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 13:30:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0309</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 15:14:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40P</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McNeely</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4812</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40P</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>DIGGS</LastName>
            <FirstName>GARWOOD</FirstName>
            <InternalID>TF0309</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522367</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0233</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/21/2023 13:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0233</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>TF0309</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 09:04:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0309</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 09:04:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522367</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/19/2023 13:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>TF0309</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 09:16:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0309</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 09:16:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>TF0309</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 09:46:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0309</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 10:37:17</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388693</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>RAMIREZ LOPEZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>AVIDAN</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/05/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/25/2023 09:45:56</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R562</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A135</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>RAMIREZ LOPEZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>AVIDAN</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/05/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R562</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A135</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/25/2023 09:45:56</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6903</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Adelphi</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hyattsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.95134</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.974428</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>675</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7835</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>TF0309</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/05/2023 10:37:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>TF0309</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 09:04:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0309</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 09:04:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>TF0309</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 10:37:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0309</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 10:37:54</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>275000</PropertyValue>
         <Value>275000</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>254698</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1140</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>TF0309</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 10:37:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0309</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 10:37:54</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>275000</PropertyValue>
         <Value>275000</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>254698</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1140</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/16/2023 09:34:31</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/16/2023 09:34:31</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40P</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/15/2024 11:55:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP4812</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/16/2023 09:34:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On 9/21/2023, the Metropolitan Area Drug Task Force assembled to conduct a controlled delivery of approximately 1.2 kilograms of cocaine to 6903 Adelphi Road, Hyattsville, Maryland 20782.&amp;nbsp; During this operation, I was the group supervisor and was also assigned to conduct surveillance.&amp;nbsp; During this time, I was parked in the area of Adelphi Road and Underwood Road.&amp;nbsp; At approximately 1030 hours, an undercover Police Officer conducted a delivery of the parcel and left it on the front step of the residence.&amp;nbsp; At approximately 1045 hours, surveillance personnel who had &amp;quot;the eye&amp;quot; advised over the radio that a Hispanic male wearing a red shirt and blue jeans had exited the residence, picked up the parcel, and placed it in the trunk of a white Honda Civic that was parked in the driveway.&amp;nbsp; The Honda was bearing Maryland registration 3FA0493.&amp;nbsp; The male subject then went back into the residence.&amp;nbsp; At approximately 1118 hours, S/T Moreno advised that the Hispanic male and a Hispanic female had exited the residence.&amp;nbsp; The Hispanic male at the time was wearing a black shirt and blue jeans.&amp;nbsp; S/T Moreno advised the female had gotten into the driver&amp;#39;s seat and the male had gotten into the front passenger seat of the white Honda.&amp;nbsp; At that time, I responded to 6903 Adelphi Road and pulled my the vehicle into the driveway behind the white Honda.&amp;nbsp; I exited my vehicle wearing an external vest carrier clearly marked with &amp;quot;State Trooper&amp;quot; in large bright yellow lettering on the front and back.&amp;nbsp; I pulled my weapon from its holster and kept it at the &amp;quot;Sul position&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp; I identified myself as &amp;quot;State Police&amp;quot; and gave clear verbal commands for the occupants to exit the vehicle and place their hands in the air.&amp;nbsp; At that time, both occupants exited the vehicle with their hands in the air.&amp;nbsp; Approximately one minute later, members of the MSP S.T.A.T.E. Team arrived at the scene and detained both subjects without incident.&amp;nbsp; At that time, the vehicle was secured.&amp;nbsp; While attempting to identify the male subject, he advised that his identification card was in the house.&amp;nbsp; The male subject gave investigators consent to enter the residence with him to retrieve his identification.&amp;nbsp; I, along with S/T Moreno, escorted the male subject into the residence and retrieved his wallet from his bedroom and then exited the residence.&amp;nbsp; At that time, the subject was identified as Avidan De Jesus Ramirez-Lopez by his &amp;quot;CASA ID Card&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp; I followed S/T Moreno and Detective Mitchell back to the MSP College Park Barrack as they transported the subjects.&amp;nbsp; It should be noted that at the date and time of this operation I was not issued a body worn camera.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Once at the Barrack, I assisted with processing.&amp;nbsp; The female subject who was identified as Sandra Patricia Ramos was released from the Barrack without criminal charges.&amp;nbsp; The male subject, Avidan De Jesus Ramirez-Lopez was charged accordingly and transported to the Prince George&amp;#39;s County Detention Center by Detective Diggs.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4812</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/16/2023 09:39:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4812</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/16/2023 10:27:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40P</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Massoni</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5467</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40P</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McNeely</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4812</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/06/2023 13:38:09</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/06/2023 13:38:09</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/15/2024 11:55:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5652</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/06/2023 13:38:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On September 21, 2023 at approximately 0900 hours, I Senior Trooper Moreno #5652, currently assigned to The Metropolitan Area Drug Task Force (MADTF) was assigned to maintain surveillance of the targeted residence located at 6903 Adelphi Road, Hyattsville, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20782 and monitor actives going to or from the residence.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On September 21, 2023, at approximately 1030 hours, I S/T Moreno observed the undercover deliver the targeted UPS parcel, bearing tracking number 1Z94220R0445289135 to the targeted residence. I observed the undercover place the targeted parcel on the front outside entrance of the targeted residence&amp;#39;s front step. I observed the undercover return to his undercover vehicle and leave the targeted area. I was then assigned to maintain visual custody of the targeted Parcel and report its final destination.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On September 21, 2023, at approximately 1045 hours, I S/T Moreno observed a Hispanic male wearing a red shirt, blue jeans with short hair, who was later identified as Avidan De Jesus Ramirez LOPEZ with a date of birth of 4/5/85 through his Maryland issued Casa ID. LOPEZ picked up the targeted parcel as he walked out of the front entrance of the targeted residence with a small dog on a leash. I continued observing LOPEZ examining the target parcel, prior to taking custody of the targeted parcel. LOPEZ was observed walking the targeted parcel to the trunk area of a white Honda Civic sedan, bearing Maryland registration 3FA0493, which was in the driveway of the targeted residence. I observed LOPEZ open the rear trunk compartment of the above listed vehicle and observed LOPEZ place and secure the targeted parcel in the trunk compartment, by closing the trunk. LOPEZ continued walking the small dog on the leash completely around the targeted residence area, concluding back to the front entrance of the targeted residence, were LOPEZ reentered the residence.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On September 21, 2023, at approximately 1118 hours, I S/T Moreno observed LOPEZ once again exiting the targeted residence from the front entrance way, but now wearing a gray shirt and blue jeans with a Hispanic female wearing a black shirt and blue jeans, who was later identified by her Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license to be Sandra Patricia Ramos MEJIA with a date of birth of 5/8/90. I then observed both parties walking to the above listed vehicle still in the targeted resident driveway. I observed MEJIA entering and occupy the driver seat and LOPEZ was observed entering and occupy the front passenger side seat of the above listed vehicle which still maintained the targeted parcel in its trunk compartment. I observed LOPEZ and MEJIA attempt to back out of the targeted driveway with the above vehicle from the targeted residence.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On September 21, 2023, Ramirez Lopez was transported back to the MSP College Park Barrack to be interviewed. At 1235 hours I, Senior Trooper Moreno #5652 read in Spanish Ramirez Lopez&amp;rsquo;s Advice of Miranda Rights from the MSP 180. Ramirez Lopez signed the form and waived his right to have an attorney being present and agreed to speak with us. Upon questioning, he admitted to removing the UPS parcel containing the Cocaine from the front steps and placing it in the white Honda with MD registration 3FA0493, which was parked in the driveway of the residence.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Upon further questioning he admitted to meeting an unknown male at a bar several months prior to this date who asked if he would like to make some extra money on the side? Ramirez Lopez responded &amp;quot;No.&amp;quot; However, he did give the unknown male his phone number upon request. Ramirez Lopez advised that he eventually received a call from the same unknown male who paid him a $1000 to deliver a box for the first time to an unknown location approximately three weeks prior to this date (9/21). Ramirez Lopez stated that he suspected what was in the parcel but did not ask any questions. I showed Ramirez Lopez a picture of a Carlos Tomas Mercedes, who was discovered through investigative means to be associated with the 6903 Adelphi Road address where he resided. Ramirez Lopez advised he did not know Mercedes. I asked if I could search his Samsung phone, and he gave written consent. A search of Ramirez Lopez&amp;#39;s phone revealed the phone number; &amp;quot;(301) 437&amp;ndash;3534&amp;quot; which was listed under &amp;quot;Tito&amp;quot;. Through investigative means I discovered that the phone number belonged to Carlos Tomas Mercedes. Once I advised Ramirez Lopez of that information, he decided to take full responsibility for the parcel of Cocaine and advised he knew Mercedes and &amp;quot;Tito&amp;quot; was one and the same person. Ramirez Lopez advised he did not want any trouble with Mercedes, would rather go to jail and was willing to take full responsibility for the parcel of Cocaine. At that point the interview was terminated.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5652</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/06/2023 13:39:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5652</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/28/2023 14:12:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40P</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McNeely</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4812</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Moreno</LastName>
            <FirstName>Manuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5652</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>