<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-017734</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/18/2023 23:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/18/2023 23:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/18/2023 22:43:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/18/2023 22:43:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop with CDS not and 10-55.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/18/2023 23:08:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 12:46:24</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>694711</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/18/2023 23:08:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 02:27:51</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>694711</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Prospect</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Hurlock</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21643</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>S</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.860621</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.628743803341045</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/18/2023 23:08:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/18/2023 23:08:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/08/2023 19:01:30</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/18/2023 23:08:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:52</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Maryland State Police - Easton Barrack (I), Marked Patrol Vehicle I-59 which is equipped with a mobile recording device.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Defendant: Anthony Shane Vinson &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Date of Birth: 09/03/1987&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Date of Arrest: 05/18/2023&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Time of Arrest: 2313&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;MD SDX: V525067765687&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Trooper&amp;rsquo;s Training/Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Eastern Shore Criminal Justice Academy, the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Centreville Police Department and the Maryland State Police.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) through the Eastern Shore Criminal Justice Academy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Certified Field Training Officer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Caroline County Deputy for four years and six months, reaching the rank of Deputy First Class.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li aria-level="1" dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Maryland State Trooper for 10 months.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Phase 1: Vehicle in Motion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;On Thursday, May 18, 2023, at approximately 2243 hours, I, Trooper C. Cooper #7501, was on patrol in the area of Route 392 at Route 331, Hurlock, Dorchester County, Maryland 21643.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;While sitting at the intersection I looked both ways to ensure that it was clear for me to travel through the intersection. As I looked down Route 331 to the south I observed a vehicle traveling in my direction without any headlights on. As the vehicle traveled closer to my location I observed the high beams of the vehicle flash. The vehicle was later identified as a 2010 Lincoln Town Car, gold in color, displaying Maryland registration 2AY7896.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;I then conducted a traffic stop of the vehicle in a parking lot just off of Prospect Street. As I approached the vehicle I observed the operator/sole occupant of the vehicle, later identified as Anthony Vinson, looking back at me. I then requested a K-9 respond to my location.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Phase 2: Personal Contact&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Once I got to the driver&amp;rsquo;s side window and made contact with Anthony, I observed a hypodermic syringe lying on his lap. I also observed there to be a wet spot on Anthony&amp;rsquo;s pants in his groin area which resembled him urinating on himself. When I observed the syringe I advised Anthony to exit the vehicle, at which time he did. I then placed Anthony in handcuffs and advised him that he was being detained. Note as Anthony exited the vehicle, the hypodermic syringe fell to the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;I then read Anthony his Miranda Rights. At the end Anthony agreed to speak with me. I inquired about the syringe and Anthony stated that it was his girlfriend&amp;rsquo;s (Amanda Shanahan). Anthony went on to state that the syringe was used for injecting controlled dangerous substances. Anthony also admitted that just prior to me pulling him over he observed a baggie on the center console of the vehicle and he swept it to the floor. Anthony also stated that anything found within the vehicle was not his and provided me with consent to search his person which yielded negative results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;After my initial questioning of Anthony I returned to the vehicle and observed a single wax fold lying on the driver&amp;rsquo;s side floor. I then conducted a probable cause search of the vehicle and located a glass smoking device containing suspected methamphetamine residue within the center console, along with a clear plastic straw containing suspected cocaine residue within the cup holder of the vehicle. All items previously mentioned were identified as a controlled dangerous substance and/or paraphernalia through my training, knowledge and experience.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Also noted during the search Anthony voluntarily stated that he had purchased what he thought was &amp;ldquo;Molly&amp;rdquo; two days prior, which he consumed but it actually ended up being methamphetamine. Anthony went onto state that if were to ingest drugs it would not be by injection because he would rather snort it or pop a pill.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;After the probable cause search I then advised Anthony that I needed him to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) and he agreed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Phase 3: Pre-Arrest Screening&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;The evaluation was performed on flat level ground which was free of debris. It was approximately 60 degrees and dark. Anthony was wearing pants, a leather jacket and slider style sandals. I asked Anthony the following questions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Medical Conditions - Anthony stated he had none.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Injuries - Anthony stated he had none.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (2/4 Clues):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test. The tip of my finger was used as the test&amp;rsquo;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Anthony&amp;rsquo;s eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. His pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. Anthony was asked if he understood the test and the instruction to which he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Not observed.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Vertical Nystagmus - Not observed.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Walk and Turn (3 / 8 Clues):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Prior to Anthony performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Anthony was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. He was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and remain in that position until told to begin. He was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. He was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Anthony was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, take a series of small steps to turn around and completely turn around. Anthony was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. He was instructed that once she began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. Anthony was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he states, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Anthony did not remain in the instructional position and I had to advise him to get back into it prior to starting the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Anthony missed heel to toe during the first nine.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Turn:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Anthony completed the turn satisfactorily.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;After completing the turn Anthony stepped off line and nearly lost his balance (leaned to the left), and then completed the remaining steps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;One Leg Stand ( 1 / 4 Clues):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Prior to Anthony performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. He was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice (right foot), off the ground approximately six (6) inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. He was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;I had to advise Anthony on three separate occasions to put his foot down while demonstrating the test to him. After Anthony had previously stated he understood I had to redemonstrate the test for him to ensure he properly understood. While completing the test Anthony raised his arms for balance and placed his foot down. At completion of the test Anthony apologized for his performance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Preliminary Breath Test (PBT): .00&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Arrest:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Based on the following, I had reason to believe Anthony was driving a motor vehicle under the influence:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;-Bloodshot, glassy eyes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;-Erratic behavior (Crying, Agitated, Calm)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;-Clues during field sobriety test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;-Controlled dangerous substances located during the probable cause search.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Due to the observations, I concluded that Anthony was driving while impaired by a possible controlled dangerous substance. At approximately 2313 hours, on Thursday, May 18, 2023, I placed Anthony under arrest and placed him in the front seat of my patrol vehicle per department policy. While on scene Anthony was provided a copy of the DR-15 and advised to follow along while the audio version was played. At the completion of the recording Anthony agreed to take the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;I then transported Anthony to the Maryland State Police - Easton &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rdquo; Barrack. Once at the Barrack, Cpl. Moore conducted the intoximeter test and later advised me that Anthony provided a breath sample which concluded a .00. I then contacted Trooper J. Koehler who is a certified Drug Recognition Expert (DRE) to see if he could conduct an evaluation of Anthony. Trooper J. Koehler responded to the barrack for the evaluation. While waiting for Trooper J. Koehler to arrive, Anthony was placed within a holding cell at the barrack. During this time Anthony&amp;rsquo;s demeanor/mood changed numerous times. Anthony was observed to be crying, yelling and extremely calm all within minutes of each other. This type of behavior was observed during the entire time Anthony was in police custody.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;Once Trooper J. Koehler was at the barracks, Anthony agreed to speak with him. Trooper J. Koehler requested Anthony to conduct a test for his evaluation and Anthony agreed. At the completion of the evaluation, Trooper J. Koehler explained to Anthony that he had concluded Anthony was under the influence of a controlled dangerous substance (stimulant and/or narcotic analgesic). Trooper J. Koehler requested that Anthony submit to a blood draw and he agreed to do so. (See Trooper J. Koehler&amp;rsquo;s supplement report for further information.)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;I then transported Anthony to the University of Maryland Shore Regional Health - Easton. Once at the hospital contact was made with a nurse on staff in the emergency room, Hannah Hutchinson. Hannah completed the blood draw at approximately 0247 hours. During the blood draw Anthony voluntarily stated that he was going to &amp;ldquo;pop for meth and his doctor knows that.&amp;rdquo; All vials containing Anthony&amp;rsquo;s blood were packaged according to policy and procedure and later placed in the mail to be sent to the Chemical Test Unit. Note that while we were at the hospital, Anthony requested that his wrist be looked at because he was claiming it was broken due to the handcuffs being placed on him too tightly. The emergency room doctor evaluated Anthony and stated it was not broken but still ordered for an X-ray to be conducted. The X-ray results showed that Anthony&amp;rsquo;s wrist was not broken.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;I then transported Anthony to the Vienna Volunteer Fire House where he was provided a copy of all criminal and traffic citations. Anthony only signed for the DR-15 Advice of Rights and refused to sign for all other documentation regarding the criminal citations.&amp;nbsp; Anthony was released to a sober driver at approximately 0430 hours.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;All evidence seized during the probable cause search was later transported to the Maryland State Police - Easton &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rdquo; Barrack, where it was packaged and stored according to policy and procedure.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b189da8e-7fff-2c7a-ed44-17bf4fda6db8"&gt;All events occurred in Dorchester County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 04:10:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7501</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 04:10:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rideout</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jacob</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7059</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Walker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Drew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7010</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dadds</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5551</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cooper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Connor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7501</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507166</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/18/2023 22:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 02:29:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7501</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 02:34:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507166</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/18/2023 22:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 02:32:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7501</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 02:34:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507166</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>5 3550</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/18/2023 22:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>5 3550</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 02:34:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7501</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 02:34:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 02:53:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:20</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>1567</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>VINSON</LastName>
               <FirstName>ANTHONY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>SHANE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/03/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2013 09:33:14</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>V525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>VINSON</LastName>
               <FirstName>ANTHONY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>SHANE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/03/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>V525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2013 09:33:14</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6869</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Delmar</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Delmar</City>
               <StateCode>DE</StateCode>
               <Zip5>19940</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.617739</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.468829</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>115</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>LILLIAN</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>HEBRON</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.68771</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.42012</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>302</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>236</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8298</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>548</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5971</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2013 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 02:53:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 02:53:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 02:53:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 02:29:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7501</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 02:29:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 03:10:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7501</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 03:10:30</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>(1) Wax fold stamped Rite Aid</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>248998</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>D</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.02</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 03:13:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7501</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 03:13:18</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Hypodermic syringe</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>100</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249002</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 03:13:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7501</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 03:13:18</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Glass smoking device with methamphetamine residue</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>100</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249003</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 03:13:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7501</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 03:13:18</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Plastic straw with cocaine resiude</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>100</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249004</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/09/2023 18:40:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/09/2023 18:40:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/08/2023 19:01:30</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/09/2023 18:40:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:52</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On Saturday, September 9, 2023, I, Trooper C. Cooper #7501, received the blood kit results in reference to this case from Sgt. C. Del Vecchio.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Upon review of the blood kit result it was found that the defendant, identified as Anthony Vinson, had the following controlled dangerous substances in his blood:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - Benzoylecgonine&lt;br /&gt; - Fentanyl&lt;br /&gt; - Delta-9 THC&lt;br /&gt; - Carboxy THC&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Due to Vinson already being charged the night of the traffic stop, no further charges will be filed. It is planned to serve Vinson with a copy of the blood results and a Maryland Advice of Rights (DR-15) on September 13, 2023, when the case is to be heard in Dorchester County District Court. I was unable to make contact with Vinson in court, therefore the appropriate paperwork was sent via certified mail to his Delmar, Delaware address. I request this case be closed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; All above events occurred in Dorchester County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case Status: CLOSED</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7501</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/09/2023 18:43:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7501</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 11:10:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dadds</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5551</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cooper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Connor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7501</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>