<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-022772</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/24/2023 23:15:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/24/2023 23:15:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/24/2023 22:56:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/24/2023 22:56:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI - 23-043- Ronald Wilt</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/24/2023 23:15:53</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/27/2023 14:13:49</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>698863</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/24/2023 23:15:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/25/2023 04:02:12</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>698863</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Amish</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Grantsville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21536</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-79.185381</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.701032</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/24/2023 23:15:50</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/24/2023 23:15:50</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/27/2023 00:02:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/24/2023 23:15:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:00</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="line-height:2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driver:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Ronald Lee Wilt&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;MD OLN:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;MD-10272257006&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;DUI #:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;23-043&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Video:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;My body worn camera and in-car cameras were activated.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Subsequent Offender:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;No.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On 6/24/2023 at approximately 2255 hours, I, TFC. Bradley was traveling west on U.S. Rt. 40 near New Germany Road in my marked patrol vehicle (W-30), behind two other vehicles.&amp;nbsp; The vehicle directly in front of me was a white SUV and the vehicle in front of it was a dark-colored van, both traveling west.&amp;nbsp; As we continued, I observed the dark-colored van swerving left to right within its lane, crossing the white fog line multiple times and the yellow center lines twice, from there to Pennsylvania Avenue on Rt. 40.&amp;nbsp; As we passed Pennsylvania Avenue, I activated the forward facing camera in my patrol vehicle to capture the van&amp;#39;s driving.&amp;nbsp; The white SUV turned left onto Rt. 495, and I began to travel directly behind the van.&amp;nbsp; The van continued to drift left to right within its lane and crossed the yellow center lines or drove directly on top of them with its left side tires four more times before we reached Amish Road on U.S. Rt. 40.&amp;nbsp; When the van crossed the yellow center lines just west of Shade Hollow Road, I observed the front of the van abruptly swerve right to correct and re-enter its lane.&amp;nbsp; As we approached Amish Road, I activated my emergency equipment to conduct a traffic stop on the blue Dodge Caravan displaying Maryland registration: 20164M2.&amp;nbsp; The Dodge turned left onto Amish Road and drifted at approximately 5 miles per hour for approximately 500 feet before coming to a stop on the right side of Amish Road just off of U.S. Rt. 40.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I approached the driver of the vehicle who was later identified as Ronald Lee Wilt, via driver&amp;#39;s side approach.&amp;nbsp; As I passed the second row seating of the van, I observed a large gray cooler on the rear passenger seat and a Busch Light beer can on the floor.&amp;nbsp; I made contact with Wilt at the driver&amp;#39;s door and immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; I advised Wilt the reason of the traffic stop and asked how many drinks he had that night.&amp;nbsp; He replied, &amp;quot;Uhhh, probably four or five.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked Wilt for his driver&amp;#39;s license and registration for the vehicle, but he could only provide his license.&amp;nbsp; I asked him where he was coming from, he replied, &amp;quot;hilltop.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I returned to my patrol vehicle and deactivated my front emergency lights before returning to the Dodge.&amp;nbsp; Upon returning to the driver&amp;#39;s door, I found Wilt to be on an active phone call and I asked him to exit the vehicle and requested he submit to field sobriety tests.&amp;nbsp; He terminated the call and agreed to testing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; The evaluation was performed in front of Wilt&amp;#39;s vehicle on Amish Road.&amp;nbsp; The asphalt surface was flat and free of debris.&amp;nbsp; Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight, my patrol vehicles spotlight, the headlamps of Wilt&amp;#39;s vehicle, as well as the headlamps of my patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp; The weather was clear and approximately 62 degrees Fahrenheit.&amp;nbsp; Wilt was wearing a brown colored sweatshirt, blue jean pants and brown boots.&amp;nbsp; Wilt appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any physical injuries, limps or limb ailments.&amp;nbsp; Wilt&amp;#39;s back was faced towards his vehicle.&amp;nbsp; I asked him the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;How many alcoholic beverages consumed before driving that night: &amp;quot;&lt;/strong&gt;Probably drank about 6, 7. Ain&amp;#39;t gonna lie to you.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Where were the drinks consumed:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Step-daughter&amp;#39;s house&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;What time was your last drink:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;10-15 minutes ago&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Physical or medical disabilities:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;No&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Recent Injuries:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;No&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Medications:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Thyroid medication.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Glasses/Contacts:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;No/none observed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As I spoke with Wilt outside the vehicle, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person and observed his eyes were bloodshot and glassy.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN) TEST (6/6 CLUES OBSERVED)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. &amp;nbsp;My black ballpoint pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Wilt&amp;#39;s eyes. &amp;nbsp;Wilt was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the stimulus with his eyes only until told to stop.&amp;nbsp; Wilt&amp;rsquo;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking.&amp;nbsp; Wilt advised he understood the instructions.&lt;br /&gt; 1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Wilt displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; 2.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Wilt displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; 3.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Wilt displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Wilt did not display vertical nystagmus.&lt;br /&gt; * Wilt had to be reminded to follow the pen with his eyes five times during the test.&lt;br /&gt; * Wilt had to be reminded to keep his head still one time during the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;WALK AND TURN TEST (5/8 CLUES OBSERVED):&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Prior to Wilt performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test was to be conducted.&amp;nbsp; Wilt was instructed to place his right foot in front of his left and touch heel to toe.&amp;nbsp; He was instructed to place his hands at his side and to remain in that position until told otherwise.&amp;nbsp; Wilt told me he is &amp;quot;bow-legged&amp;quot; which prevented him from getting his right foot directly in front of his left.&amp;nbsp; I asked him to get it as close to directly in front he could and asked if he understood, to which he stated he did.&amp;nbsp; Wilt was advised to take nine (9) steps straight out in front of him, touching heel to toe on every step.&amp;nbsp; He was to keep his hands down at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. &amp;nbsp;On the ninth step he was instructed to keep his lead foot planted and take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn 180&amp;deg; without stopping.&amp;nbsp; I demonstrated and explained the second series of steps to be performed identically as I did for the first series.&amp;nbsp; Wilt was told once he started the test, he was not to stop until the test was completely finished. &amp;nbsp;After explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked Wilt if he understood the instructions, to which he replied he did.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructional stage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Wilt lost balance one time during the instructional stage.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;First Nine:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Wilt&amp;nbsp;stepped off line on step 5 of the first nine.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 2. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Wilt raised his arms during the first nine.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;The Turn:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Nothing to report.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Second Nine:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Wilt stopped walking at the beginning of the second nine.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Wilt missed heel-to-toe on steps 6 and 8 of the second nine.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Wilt stepped off line on steps 1 and 7 of the second nine.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ONE-LEG STAND TEST (3/4 CLUES OBSERVED BEFORE REFUSAL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Prior to Wilt performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted.&amp;nbsp; Wilt stated that he may have trouble balancing on one leg because of right knee pain. However, he agreed to watch me demonstrate then decide if he wanted to participate.&amp;nbsp; Wilt was instructed to stand with his feet together and his hands down to his sides while the instructions were given and also during the test.&amp;nbsp; He was told not to begin the test until he was instructed to start, and after the test had been demonstrated. &amp;nbsp;When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately six (6) inches. &amp;nbsp;While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, keep his toe pointed forward, watch his raised foot, and count aloud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand two, one thousand three...) and to continue the test until told to stop (30 seconds).&amp;nbsp; Wilt said that he understood all the instructions and that he believed he could perform the test.&amp;nbsp; He balanced on his left leg with his right leg raised.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Seconds 0-10:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Wilt placed his foot once during the first ten seconds.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Wilt raised his arms during the first ten seconds.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Wilt swayed during the first ten seconds.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At approximately the seven-second mark, Wilt placed his foot down and advised he did not want to continue.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT):&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; At approximately 2312 hours, I asked Wilt to submit to a PBT, he agreed.&amp;nbsp; The PBT results were 0.186 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ARREST/DR-15 ADVICE OF RIGHTS:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Due to the facts above, I placed Wilt under arrest for DUI at approximately 2313 hours.&amp;nbsp; At approximately 2316 hours, he spit a nicotine pouch out of his mouth and I checked his mouth for any other foreign objects, however, none were observed.&amp;nbsp; Wilt was handcuffed in the front due to shoulder pain and tightness. I placed Wilt in the front right seat of my patrol vehicle and advised him of&amp;nbsp; DR-15 Advice of Rights to a chemical breath test using the English audio recording of the DR-15 advice of rights from the MVA website.&amp;nbsp; I provided Wilt a physical copy of the DR-15 to read along with, if he chose to do so.&amp;nbsp; At approximately 2327 hours, Wilt agreed to submit to breath test and was transported to the Cumberland barrack.&amp;nbsp; Wilt&amp;#39;s wife, Elizabeth, was on scene at this time and took possession of the Dodge.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;INTOXIMETER RESULT:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; The breath test was administered by Cpl. Diehl #5745 on 6/25/2023 at approximately 0002 hours.&amp;nbsp; Two sufficient samples of Wilt&amp;#39;s breath were obtained.&amp;nbsp; The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of 0.16 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; As I made contact with Wilt throughout the night/morning, I continued to detect the strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person and observed his eyes were bloodshot and glassy.&amp;nbsp; Wilt was provided with his paperwork, advised not to drive for 12 hours and given ride home where he was released to his wife, Elizabeth Ann Wilt.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; All above events occurred in Garrett County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 04:05:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7189</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/26/2023 06:15:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kline</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7112</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7189</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shrout</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2951</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7189</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7189</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>512208</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/24/2023 23:13:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 02:48:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7189</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/25/2023 04:02:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>65</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 02:48:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>380808</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Wilt</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/22/1958 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13722693E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 02:37:20</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R543</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Wilt</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/22/1958 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13722693E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>W430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R543</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 02:37:20</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3338</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Amish</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Grantsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21536</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.212929</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.669189</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>895</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3966</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 04:03:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 04:03:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 04:03:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 02:50:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7189</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/25/2023 02:50:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154501</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 02:48:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7189</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/25/2023 02:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1D4GP45R25B400102</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2005</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CVN</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLU</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>20164M2</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>