<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-017518</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/17/2023 11:51:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/17/2023 11:51:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/17/2023 11:51:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/17/2023 11:51:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>NCMEC Cyber Tip 159045523 / 115626698 / 127961555 / 138780197</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 11:51:34</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/01/2023 12:48:52</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>CAC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>HANOVER CCU</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>694281</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 11:51:35</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 12:05:36</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>694281</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Hanover Ccu</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/17/2023 11:51:32</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/17/2023 11:51:32</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>09/01/2023 12:48:36</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 11:51:34</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/01/2023 12:48:36</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments&lt;br /&gt; - NCMEC Cyber Tips 159045523 / 115626698 / 127961555 / 138780197&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Narrative&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 05/08/2023, The Maryland Internet Crimes Against Children Task Force was assigned National Center for Missing and Exploited Children (NCMEC) Cyber Tip 159045523, which indicated a user uploaded suspected child pornography to the internet via Twitter.&amp;nbsp; This Cyber Tip was assigned to TFC Zachary Crowe #6726, Maryland State Police, Maryland ICAC Task Force, for investigation.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TFC Crowe reviewed Cyber Tip 159045523, which provided the following information related to the suspect: &lt;div style="margin-left:40px"&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Phone: +12404623256&lt;br /&gt; Email Address: giovanniobeng1@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt; Screen/User Name: Pluggutheplug&lt;br /&gt; ESP User ID: 1469104834506805257&lt;br /&gt; Profile URL: https://twitter.com/Pluggutheplug&lt;br /&gt; IP Address: 172.58.189.1 (Registration) 12-10-2021 00:41:27 UTC&lt;br /&gt; Full Name: PYT GOAT&lt;br /&gt; Description: The best&lt;br /&gt; *TFC Crowe would note the abbreviation &amp;quot;PYT&amp;quot; is commonly used as a search term related to files constituting child ponography and is an acronym for &amp;quot;Pretty Young Thing,&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Pretty Young Teen.&amp;quot; GOAT is another acronym commonly meaning &amp;quot;Greatest of All Time.&amp;quot;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Cyber Tip 159045523 contained two video files, which were reported by Twitter to contain child pornography.&amp;nbsp; TFC Crowe reviewed these files and observed only one file to constitute child pornography, as that term is defined by Maryland law.&amp;nbsp; The single file constituting child pornography is described below: &lt;div style="margin-left:40px"&gt;&lt;u&gt;File Name&lt;/u&gt;: 59HmI_X8EYQ2CP33&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Description&lt;/u&gt;: This is a 52 second color video that depicts a teenage male engaged in vaginal intercourse with a juvenile female.&amp;nbsp; The female is nude from the waist down, and based on her lack of development, she is reasonably believed to be 12-15 years of age.&lt;/div&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TFC Crowe conducted a review of the additional materials provided by Twitter. Upon reviewing the direct messages sent and received by the suspect, it became evident the suspect is selling pornographic videos and images via Twitter. When asked about age ranges, the suspect claims to have pornographic materials &amp;quot;ages 11 and up.&amp;quot; It appears the suspect utilizes Cashapp and PayPal to collect payment for links to either Dropbox or Mega which contain the requested materials.&amp;nbsp; This is further evidenced by a number of photos located within the &amp;quot;direct message attachments&amp;quot; file provided by Twitter, where TFC Crowe observed numerous screenshots showing confirmation of payment that were sent to the suspect.&amp;nbsp; There is also a screenshot that appears to be a &amp;quot;Menu&amp;quot; saved to the suspects &amp;quot;Notes&amp;quot; application, which states: &lt;div style="margin-left:40px"&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TWITTER MENU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Reg Dropbox of mega $15 premium $25&lt;br /&gt; Tele [Telegram] links 1 for $15 2 for $25&lt;br /&gt; All full voids on my account unlimited access $30&lt;br /&gt; Onlyfans girl Dropbox $15&lt;br /&gt; Twitter page full vids $7 10 for $15 25 $20&lt;br /&gt; 20 voids of your choice $15&lt;br /&gt; Special request $N/A&lt;br /&gt; My personal tele with all voids $20&lt;/div&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While continuing to review the direct messages, TFC Crowe located a message from an additional Twitter user claiming the suspect had posted a video of her without her consent. According to this user&amp;#39;s complaint, she was 16 years old at the time the video was created. The additional user provided self produced images of herself to the suspect as proof.&amp;nbsp; Through open source information available to the public, including social media, TFC Crowe was able to identify this individual as Samantha Arrietta (DOB: 11/22/2004). Though the victim is now an adult, she claims she was under the age of 18 at the time of production.&amp;nbsp; These images/videos were saved to her Snapchat account, which was hacked and the images/videos were uploaded to the internet.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Upon further review, TFC Crowe noticed Cyber Tip 159045523 was linked to three additional Cyber Tips (115626698 / 127961555 / 138780197) by the same email address, giovanniobeng1@gmail.com (TARGET EMAIL ADDRESS). Cyber Tip 138780197 was assigned to TFC Crowe in December of 2022, and the additional Cyber Tips were assigned to an additional investigator (See MSP Case Number: 22-MSP-007223).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TFC Crowe reviewed Cyber Tip 138780197, which was initiated by Instagram when a user distributed suspected child pornography to another user via instant message.&amp;nbsp; Cyber Tip 138780197 provided the following information relevant to the suspect: &lt;div style="margin-left:40px"&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 02-22-2003&lt;br /&gt; Approximate Age: 19&lt;br /&gt; Email Address: giovanniobeng1@gmail.com (Verified)&lt;br /&gt; Screen/User Name: badjointsunlimitted22&lt;br /&gt; ESP User ID: 49136675041&lt;br /&gt; IP Address: 2607:fb90:ea96:6aa:74f1:e41e:77ef:b8df (Login)&lt;br /&gt; 11-12-2022 16:59:49 UTC&lt;/div&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TFC Crowe contacted the Prince George&amp;#39;s County Police Department regarding additional tips linked to this reported account by the email address, giovanniobeng1@gmail.com, and learned that detectives had already contacted the suspect, Brendan Giovanni Agyin, related to this investigation.&amp;nbsp; An internet safety talk was conducted and the case was closed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Because this incident took place prior to PG County&amp;#39;s contact with the subject, TFC Crowe is requesting this case be suspended until additional CyberTips post-dating the suspect&amp;#39;s last encounter with law enforcement become available.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CASE STATUS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Suspended</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 12:06:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6726</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/30/2023 08:35:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Crowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6726</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>