<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-020770</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/10/2023 03:44:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/10/2023 03:44:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/10/2023 03:28:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/10/2023 03:28:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>A two vehicle collision led to DUI/DWI arrest</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 03:44:55</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5368</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/15/2023 09:13:23</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>CAP BELT OL A HWY/ SAINT BARNABAS RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>697354</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 03:44:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/11/2023 20:14:14</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>697354</AddressId>
         <StreetName>N/B Capital Beltway S/O St.barnabas Rd</StreetName>
         <City>Oxon Hill</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20745</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.986534167</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.8064815</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/10/2023 03:44:53</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/10/2023 03:44:53</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/15/2023 09:13:24</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 03:44:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;This incident was recorded audibly and visually on BWC. L-23 is equipped with MVR. Refer to ACRS.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Ramirez Marroquin, Pedro Antonio&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 08/22/1998&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 06/10/2023&lt;br /&gt; Times of Arrest: 0405 Hours&lt;br /&gt; DUI # 23-180: (Forestville Barrack)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;*&lt;/strong&gt;Trained and certified to operate the Preliminary Breath Test through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; *Trained in&amp;nbsp;Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;hr /&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On 05/29/2023 at approximately 0329 hours, I was dispatched to N/B Capital Beltway in the area of MD-210, Oxon Hill, Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland, in reference to a collision.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Upon my arrival at approximately 0339 hours, I observed a disabled silver Honda Civic bearing Maryland registration (4FB7339) in lane two (2). I also observed a disabled grey Jeep Wrangler bearing Florida registration (T95EK) with side damage on the left shoulder facing southbound.&amp;nbsp;I made contact with the driver of the grey Jeep Wrangler who was identified as Roland, Steven Michael, DOB: 09/13/1966, W/M. Roland advised that he observed the silver Honda Civic driving on the right shoulder with left turn signal activated. Roland then advised that the silver Honda Civic proceeded to make a left turn as if making a U-turn and collided with him.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the driver of the silver Honda Civic and immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. The driver was identified by a photo of his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license that was located on his cellphone as Ramirez Marroquin, Pedro Antonio, DOB: 08/22/1998, H/M. I questioned Ramirez Marroquin about what happened and made sure that he did not need medical attention. Ramirez Marroquin stated that his vehicle had a mechanical issue and could not stop in time. Ramirez Marroquin later revealed that he was trying to make a left turn to get to Langley Park and admitted that it was his fault. As I was speaking with Ramirez Marroquin, I observed his eyes to be bloodshot, and glassy. I also observed his speech to be slurred. I asked him when was the last time he had consumed alcoholic beverages and he denied at first and later admitted, &amp;quot;a couple hours ago.&amp;quot; I then asked him what kind of drinks he had consumed and he stated, &amp;quot;Two normal beers.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; A routine check on NCIC and METERS revealed that Ramirez Marroquin&amp;#39;s driver license was suspended and vehicle registration was also suspended.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to Ramirez Marroquin exhibiting signs of impairment, I asked him to submit to the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, to which he agreed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the left shoulder N/B Capital Beltway just north of MD-210. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 60 degrees and lights consisted of surrounding pole lights and my flashlight. Ramirez Marroquin appeared to be in good physical condition. (Reference below for further information regarding Ramirez Marroquin&amp;#39;s injuries and medications).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Ramirez Marroquin the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; Injuries - Left ankle.&lt;br /&gt; Medication - No.&lt;br /&gt; Contact lenses - No.&lt;br /&gt; Glasses - No.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Ramirez Marroquin&amp;#39;s eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Ramirez Marroquin&amp;#39;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking, and no resting Nystagmus was observed. I asked Ramirez Marroquin if he understood the instructions, and he stated, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; 2) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; 3) The Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Vertical Nystagmus - Not observed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;WALK AND TURN (8/8 clues observed)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Ramirez Marroquin performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Ramirez Marroquin was instructed to imagine a straight line and put his left foot on the imaginary line, place his right foot directly in front of his left foot, and touch heel to toe. After he assumed the instructional position, he was advised to keep his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Ramirez Marroquin was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Ramirez Marroquin was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Ramirez Marroquin was again explained, and I demonstrated that the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Ramirez Marroquin was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Ramirez Marroquin if he understood the test, and he stated, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;(Footwear: Black boots).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1) Unable to maintain balance - he broke his feet while I was explaining the instructions to him more than three (3) times&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2) Starts too soon - he was instructed not to start walking, but he then started walking while I was explaining the instruction more than three (3) times&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st nine):&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1) Stops while walking - he stopped walking after missing step six (6) and started bending down and touching his toes multiple times&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2) Misses heel-to-toe - he missed every step he took&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3) Step off the line - he did not walk in a straight line&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;4) Uses arms to balance - he raised his arms almost the entire time&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 5) Incorrect amount of steps - he took ten (10) steps&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (2nd nine):&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1) Stops while walking - he stopped walking after turning around from the first nine (9)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2) Misses heel-to-toe - he missed every step he took&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3) Step off the line - Not observed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;4) Uses arms to balance - he raised his arms almost the entire time&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5) Incorrect amount of steps - he took ten (10) steps after instructing to take nine (9) steps back&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Turn:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Completed improperly.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Ramirez Marroquin was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down at his sides while the instructions were given during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, one thousand-three), and continue the test until told to stop. Ramirez Marroquin was asked if he understood the test and Ramirez Marroquin stated that he understood.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After instructing him to begin, he was crouching down and put his left foot on his right knee. After demonstrating the proper way to do it for him, he proceeded to do reverse left foot raise. I then explained and demonstrated again and asked if he understood the instructions. Ramirez Marroquin that he understood. He then proceeded to do it correctly, but later did reverse left foot raise again and also put his left foot on his right knee.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; 1) Putting Foot down - Observed&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; 2) Swaying - Observed&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; 3) Hopping - Not observed&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; 4) Raising Arms - Observed&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After completing the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, I asked&amp;nbsp;Ramirez Marroquin if he would be willing to take the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) and I advised that it would not be admissible in Court. Ramirez Marroquin refused to take the PBT.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ARREST/ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reasons to believe Ramirez Marroquin was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and on the person&lt;br /&gt; *Eyes were glassy and bloodshot&lt;br /&gt; *Slurred speech&lt;br /&gt; *Admission to consuming alcoholic beverages earlier prior to driving&lt;br /&gt; *Causing the accident&lt;br /&gt; *Poor performance on Walk and Turn and One Leg Stand&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Ramirez Marroquin was arrested for DUI/DWI at 0405 hours. After putting him in the front seat of my patrol vehicle, he bluntly stated that he would not drink and drive again if he could get released now. Ramirez Marroquin was then transported to the Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack. While en route to the barrack, I played the English audio DR-15 Advice of Rights form via the MVA&amp;rsquo;s official law enforcement website to him in its entirety. At the conclusion of the DR-15, Ramirez Marroquin verbally refused to submit to the intoximeter test (06/10/2023 at 0434 hours) and late signed the form indicating the same.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I conducted the observation period on Ramirez Marroquin in its entirety, starting with his time of arrest. I escorted Ramirez Marroquin into the arrest processing room and remained in his custody until the time of releasing him.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CHARGES&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Ramirez Marroquin was charged with the following citations:&lt;br /&gt; 1. DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL (0ZQ0YJK)&lt;br /&gt; 2. DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL (0ZR0YJK)&lt;br /&gt; 3. NEGLIGENT DRIVING (0ZS0YJK)&lt;br /&gt; 4. DRIVING ON SUSPENDED LICENSE (0ZT0YJK)&lt;br /&gt; 5. UNSAFE LANE CHANGE (0ZV0YJK)&lt;br /&gt; 6. SUSPENDED REGISTRATION (0ZW0YJK)&lt;br /&gt; 7. FAIL TO DISPLAY LICENSE (0ZX0YJK)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms. Rammirez Marroquin was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to his mother and sister. He was polite, respectful, and cooperative throughout the process.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Prince George&amp;#39;s County, MD.&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:19:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/15/2023 08:13:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Arioso</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7268</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sorenson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5368</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thienhom</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bryce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7518</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510205</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/10/2023 03:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:15:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/11/2023 20:15:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510205</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/10/2023 03:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:15:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/11/2023 20:15:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:17:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>379549</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ramirez Marroquin</LastName>
               <FirstName>Pedro</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Antonio</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/22/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/11/2023 20:07:14</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R562</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P360</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ramirez Marroquin</LastName>
               <FirstName>Pedro</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Antonio</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/22/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R562</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P360</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/11/2023 20:07:14</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2127</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Rolander</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hyattsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20783</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2158</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.969729</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.996693</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>242</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1648</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:17:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:17:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:17:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:17:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:17:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>56</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:23:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>379551</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Roland</LastName>
               <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/13/1966 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/11/2023 20:23:47</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R453</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Roland</LastName>
               <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/13/1966 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R453</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/11/2023 20:23:47</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1701</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Bonita Bluff</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Ruskin</City>
               <StateCode>FL</StateCode>
               <Zip5>33570</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3218</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-82.457632</Longitude>
               <Latitude>27.72736</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>813</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>629</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7791</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:23:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:23:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:23:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:15:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/11/2023 20:15:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154017</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:24:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/11/2023 20:24:31</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2HGFC2F53GH577628</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2016</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CIV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4FB7339</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154019</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>VI</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/11/2023 20:24:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/11/2023 20:24:58</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C4HJXFNXNW123157</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>WRG</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>FL</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>T95EK</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>