<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-026099</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/22/2023 00:41:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/22/2023 00:41:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/22/2023 00:26:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/22/2023 00:26:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The driver was arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 00:41:07</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4783</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/26/2023 11:19:48</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>701663</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 00:41:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 17:44:37</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>701663</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Mayhew Inn</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Oakland</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21550</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>HWY</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-79.342803</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.492884</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/22/2023 00:41:06</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/22/2023 00:41:06</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/22/2023 20:39:05</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 00:41:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:29:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p&gt;*In-Car Camera, W-17 operable.&lt;br /&gt; *Body-Worn Camera operable.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Melody Lynne Trecartin&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Date of Birth: 12/07/1962&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Date of Arrest: 07/22/2023&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Time of Arrest: 0040 hours&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;License#: F945832 / West Virginia Driver&amp;#39;s License&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;DUI#: 23-057&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *I am trained to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; *I am trained and certified to conducted preliminary breathalyzer tests by the Maryland State Police.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; *I have successfully completed the Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement Course in November 2020.&lt;br /&gt; *I have successfully completed the Drug Recognition Expert Course and have been certified as a DRE (#&amp;nbsp;38230)&amp;nbsp;by the International Association of Chiefs of Police as of June 2023.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 07/22/2023 at approximately 0026 hours, I was on duty in uniform operating MSP marked unit W-17. I was traveling southbound on Garrett Highway, north of Mayhew Inn Road, Oakland, Garrett County, MD 21550. I observed a vehicle directly in front of me traveling southbound on Garrett Highway, north of Mayhew Inn Road, Oakland, Garrett County, MD 21550. I observed the vehicle cross the solid white fog line on three (3) occasions. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle continued to travel at a steady speed for approximately 30 seconds, turned onto Mayhew Inn Road and came to a stop on the right shoulder of Mayhew Inn Road, Oakland, Garrett County, MD 21550. The vehicle was a silver Dodge Ram bearing West Virginia registration &amp;quot;58C179.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Upon making contact with the driver, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. I observed her eyes were bloodshot and glassy, her speech was thick and slurred, and her body movements to be slow and lethargic. The driver appeared to be disoriented and confused. I identified the driver as Melody Lynne Trecartin (W/F DOB: 12/07/1962) by her West Virginia Driver&amp;#39;s license. I informed Trecartin of the reason for the stop. Trecartin stated, &amp;quot;I was fine.&amp;quot; I asked Trecartin where she was coming from. Trecartin stated, &amp;quot;Um....McHenry.&amp;quot; I asked Trecartin where in McHenry she was coming from. Trecartin stated, &amp;quot;Uh...actually Honi Honi.&amp;quot; I asked Trecartin how many alcoholic beverages she had to drink. Trecartin stated, &amp;quot;I had a couple of drinks.&amp;quot; I asked Trecartin what kind of alcoholic beverages she had drank. Trecartin appeared to be confused by the question and stated, &amp;quot;What kind of drinks? Uh...I had maybe two beers and a couple...No that&amp;#39;s just a couple of beers.&amp;quot; I observed Trecartin struggle to retrieve her driver&amp;#39;s license from her wallet. Trecartin was finally able to retrieve her driver&amp;#39;s license and handed it to me. I had to remind Trecartin to retrieve her registration card. Trecartin retrieved her registration card and handed it to me.&amp;nbsp;I asked Trecartin&amp;nbsp;to attempt&amp;nbsp;field sobriety tests which she agreed. I observed Trecartin grab the driver side door of the vehicle with her right hand to steady herself as she stepped out of the vehicle. While speaking with Trecartin&amp;nbsp;away from the vehicle, I continued to smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE&amp;nbsp;3)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The evaluation was performed in a parking lot off of the right shoulder, in front of Trecartin&amp;#39;s vehicle. The surface was dry, relatively level, and free of any debris. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlights, my patrol vehicle&amp;#39;s headlights, Trecartin&amp;#39;s vehicle&amp;#39;s headlights, and my flashlight. My patrol vehicle&amp;#39;s forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Trecartin&amp;nbsp;appeared to be in good physical condition.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;I asked Trecartin&amp;nbsp;the following questions:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Glasses or Contacts - Yes. Trecartin advised she occasionally wears reading glasses.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Medical Conditions - No.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Injuries - Yes. Trecartin advised she has Arthritis in her back and had fallen. Trecartin advised she also rides horses.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Medications - Yes. Trecartin advised she occasionally takes medication however, did not advise what kind she takes.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my finger was used as the test&amp;rsquo;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Trecartin&amp;rsquo;s eyes, slightly above eye level. Trecartin&amp;nbsp;was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Trecartin&amp;nbsp;was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Trecartin&amp;nbsp;if she was able to see the tip of the stimulus, and if she understood the test. Trecartin&amp;nbsp;replied &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo; to both questions.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation - Present in both eyes.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Note* I did not observe Vertical Gaze Nystagmus.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Walk And Turn (6/8 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Prior to Trecartin&amp;nbsp;performing the test, I&amp;nbsp;explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Trecartin&amp;nbsp;was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Trecartin&amp;nbsp;was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in the position until told to begin. Trecartin&amp;nbsp;was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Trecartin&amp;nbsp;was to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, Trecartin&amp;nbsp;was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Trecartin&amp;nbsp;was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series of nine (9) steps. Trecartin&amp;nbsp;was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by his sides, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. Trecartin&amp;nbsp;stated she understood the instructions and was able to complete the test.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Trecartin was unable to maintain balance by stepping offline by more than one half inch on one&amp;nbsp;(1) occasion.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walking Stage (1&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;Nine)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Stepped offline by more than one half inch. (Steps 1-8).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Raised arms away from torso by more than 6 inches. (Steps 4-8).&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Improper amount of steps. (8&amp;nbsp;steps).&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Stopped the test. (Step 8).&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walking Stage (2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;Nine)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Stepped offline by more than one half inch. (Steps 1-9).&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Raised arms away from torso by more than 6 inches. (Steps 1-9).&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Turn: Unsatisfactory. (Trecartin&amp;nbsp;pivoted on the balls of both feet and took an adjustment step to complete the turn).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;One Leg Stand (3/4 Clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Prior to Trecartin&amp;nbsp;performing the test, I&amp;nbsp;explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Trecartin&amp;nbsp;was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Trecartin&amp;nbsp;stated she understood the instructions and was able to complete the test.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Seconds 1-10:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Raised arms away from torso by more than 6 inches (Seconds 2-8).&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Sways (Seconds 3-8).&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Puts foot down (Second 8).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Seconds 11-20:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Raised arms away from torso by more than 6 inches. (Seconds 13-20).&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Seconds 21-30:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Raised arms away from torso by more than 6 inches (Seconds&amp;nbsp;21-24 and 28- 30).&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Puts foot down (Second 24).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Note* Trecartin&amp;nbsp;put her foot down on second 8 and did not raise it again until second 13. Trecartin put her foot down on a second occasion on second 24 and did not raise her foot again until second 28.&lt;br /&gt; Note* Trecartin refused to take the preliminary breath test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Based on the following, I believed Trecartin&amp;nbsp;was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;*Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *My&amp;nbsp;observed signs of impairment as she performed field sobriety tests.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Glassy and bloodshot eyes, thick and slurred speech.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Slow and lethargic body movements.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Disoriented and confused.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Trecartin&amp;#39;s admission to consuming alcoholic beverages.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Trecartin&amp;#39;s admission to coming from the Honi Honi Bar.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Trecartin&amp;nbsp;was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0040 hours&amp;nbsp;and was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. Trecartin was transported to the Maryland State Police McHenry Barrack for processing.&amp;nbsp;Trecartin&amp;#39;s mouth was checked at approximately 0040 hours. While at the barrack, Trecartin was read the DR-15 Advice of Rights at approximately 0115 hours, at the conclusion of reading the DR-15, Trecartin agreed to take the intoximeter test. Sgt Bittinger # 0199&amp;nbsp;administered the test at approximately 0125 hours,&amp;nbsp;which resulted in a (BrAC) of .16.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Trecartin was given all copies of pertinent paperwork, charging her with (TA 21-902 (a1i) Driving under the influence of alcohol, (TA 21-902 (a1ii) Driving under the influence of alcohol per se, (TA 21-902 (b1i) Driving while impaired, (TA 21-902 (c1i) Driving so far&amp;nbsp;impaired by alcohol, can not drive safely,&amp;nbsp;(TA 21-901.1 (a) Reckless Driving, (TA 21-901.1 (b) Negligent Driving, and (TA 21-201 (a1) Failure to obey a traffic control device.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;All events occurred in Garrett&amp;nbsp;County, Maryland.&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 18:50:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 20:32:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zais</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6241</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kline</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7112</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bond</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0200</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Poland</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kurt</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7213</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515544</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/22/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515544</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/22/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515544</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/22/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515544</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/22/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515544</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/22/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515544</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/22/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515544</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/22/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>60</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 17:54:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:50</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383224</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Trecartin</LastName>
               <FirstName>Melody</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/07/1962 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/22/2023 17:53:47</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T626</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M430</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Trecartin</LastName>
               <FirstName>Melody</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/07/1962 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T626</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M430</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/22/2023 17:53:47</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1049</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Feather</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Terra Alta</City>
               <StateCode>WV</StateCode>
               <Zip5>26764</Zip5>
               <Zip4>7379</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-79.495192</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.5431</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>474</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7662</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 19:39:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:06</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 19:39:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:06</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 19:39:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:06</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 17:47:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155374</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 17:57:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 17:57:23</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C6RR7GM3GS124056</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2016</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>R15</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>PK</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>WV</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>58C179</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>5</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>