<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-017747</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/19/2023 00:13:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/19/2023 00:13:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/18/2023 23:35:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/18/2023 23:35:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI TS - 23-273</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 00:13:58</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/26/2023 09:32:35</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>HOPEWELL AVE/ BACK RIVER NECK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>694444</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 00:13:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 22:23:13</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>694444</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Hopewell</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Essex</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.44824</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.31233</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1535-1599 HOPEWELL AVE / 111-111 BACK RIVER NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/19/2023 00:13:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/19/2023 00:13:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/24/2023 12:54:11</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 00:13:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:54:31</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*This stop was captured on in-car and body worn camera*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUI #: 23-273&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CASE #: 23-MSP-017747&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUSPECT: Fearson, 4&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;, Frederick Samuel (W/M DOB: 04/25/2001)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VICTIM: Society&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NARRATIVE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;On May 18, 2023 at approximately 2321 hours, I was on duty and in uniform operating unmarked MSP vehicle P-11. I was on routine patrol in the area of Eastern Boulevard and Stevens Road, Baltimore County, Maryland, when I first observed the suspect vehicle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 1 &amp;ndash; VEHICLE IN MOTION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;I first observed the suspect vehicle exit the parking lot of The Landing Strip, a bar in the Bowleys Quarters area, as I was traveling east on Eastern Boulevard. As the vehicle exited the parking lot and turned right to proceed west, I observed the vehicle exited the parking lot at a high rate of speed causing the tires to spin and dirt to be kicked up into the air and onto the roadway. After the vehicle passed my location, I proceed to turn around and attempted to catch up to the vehicle. The vehicle continued to accelerate at a high rate of speed down Eastern Boulevard while passing several other vehicles. Due to the vehicles speed, I was unable to catch up to the vehicle until the intersection of Old Eastern Avenue but I never lost sight of the vehicle as I was continuing to catch up to it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; When the vehicle approached the intersection of Old Eastern Avenue, it abruptly changed lanes from lane 3 into the left turn lane and then abruptly slammed on its brakes causing the vehicle to come to a jolting stop in the middle of the intersection and past the solid white stop lines while waiting to turn left onto Old Eastern Avenue. When the light turned green, the vehicle again rapidly accelerated as it turned and the vehicle turned onto the opposite side of traffic over the double yellow center line. The vehicle continued to accelerate around a curve and up a slight hill while still on the wrong side of the road. As we got to the top of the hill in the area of Kitty Hawk Road, the vehicle slowly drifted back to the right as another vehicle was approaching from the opposite direction. After the roadway straightened, the vehicle again began to accelerate as we were now driving through a residential area with a posted speed limit of 30 MPH. While behind the vehicle, I was able to obtain a pace of 62 MPH in the posted 30 MPH zone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; While I was behind the vehicle, I also observed it rocking back and forth several times while touching the lane lanes on either side of the vehicle several times. During the pace of the vehicle, it slowly drifted to the left on five separate occasions with one time being as another vehicle was passing in the opposite direction. As we approached the intersection of Stemmers Run Road and Back River Neck Road, the vehicle again came to an abrupt stop at the red traffic signal preparing to turn left onto Back River Neck Road. When the vehicle stopped, it stopped with the front half of the vehicle over the solid white stop line and in the crosswalk at the intersection. When the light turned green, the suspect vehicle continued to make a left turn onto Back River Neck Road and again accelerated out of the turn. When the suspect vehicle was turning, it again cut the turn short and almost struck the concrete center median strip before correcting at the last minute.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; At that time, I activated my emergency equipment to conduct a lawful traffic stop on the suspect vehicle. When I activated my emergency equipment, the suspect vehicle continued to accelerate for a few seconds before the driver finally realized I was behind them. After the vehicle began to slow its speed, it continued to drive through several intersections and past several parking lots before making a right turn onto Hopewell Avenue and stopping in the middle of the roadway. The vehicle was a gray Mercedes E300 bearing Maryland registration 2EL5557.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 2 &amp;ndash; PERSONAL CONTACT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;I made a driver side approach to the vehicle and made contact with the driver and two other passengers. When I approached the vehicle, the windows were already down and the driver was already holding his license. When I explained to the driver why I had stopped him, he simply stated, &amp;ldquo;OK.&amp;rdquo; When I asked the driver what was going on to understand why he might have been driving on the opposite side of the road, he stated, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know.&amp;rdquo; The driver also stated that he was unaware he was speeding or driving on the wrong side of the road. As I was speaking with the driver, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the passenger compartment of the vehicle. I further observed the driver&amp;rsquo;s speech was low and mumbled, and his eyes were glossy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; When I asked the driver to retrieve his registration car, I continued to ask other questions to divide his attention. When I asked the driver where they were coming from that night, he originally stated, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m coming from uhm&amp;hellip;,&amp;rdquo; and never finished responding as he was looking at a stack of papers in his lap. When I asked the driver again, he stated that they were coming from a friend&amp;rsquo;s house. When I confronted the driver about leaving The Landing Strip, he then stated that he was at a friend&amp;rsquo;s house, went to Landing Strip to pick up his passengers, and was then on the way to drop them off. The driver also denied consuming any alcoholic beverages that night. The driver was identified by his Maryland issued driver&amp;rsquo;s license as Frederick Samuel Fearson, 4&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; (W/M DOB: 04/25/2001). Fearson was also the registered owner of the vehicle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 3 &amp;ndash; PRE-ARREST SCREENING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Based on my observations and conversations with Fearson, I asked him to exit the vehicle and speak with me further about the indicators of impairment I had observed. Fearson agreed to exit the vehicle. When Fearson exited the vehicle, I observed a red wristband on his left wrist similar to what is provided by bars when you pay for entry. Fearson again stated that he had just picked his passengers up from the bar and had not been drinking. When I asked Fearson about the wristband, he stated that he had to get one to get into the bar but again denied drinking. When I asked Fearson about his driving, he claimed that he was unaware he was on the wrong side of the road and asked me to clarify exactly when. After I explained it, Fearson then stated that he cut the corner too short but thought he immediately corrected. While I was speaking with Fearson outside his vehicle, I continued to detect the heavy odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person and noticed that his speech was slightly slurred the more he spoke.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Based on my further observations and conversations with Fearson, I asked him to perform standardized field sobriety tests to confirm he could safely operate a motor vehicle. Fearson agreed to submit to the tests. The tests were performed in front of Fearson&amp;rsquo;s vehicle were the ground was level and free from debris. The weather at the time was clear and approximately 53 degrees Fahrenheit. Fearson at the time was wearing a pullover hoodie, jeans, and laced sneakers. Fearson was also wearing a hat at the time that he was asked to remove so I could more clearly see his eyes. Fearson stated that he did not wear contacts or glasses, did not take any medications, and did not have any injuries or impairments that affected his balance or ability to walk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instructions: The subject is told to stand with their feet together and their arms down at their side. A stimulus (ink pen) is held approximately twelve to fifteen inches from the subjects&amp;rsquo; face, and they are asked to follow the stimulus with their eyes only and not to move their head. Prior to beginning the test, I ask the subject if they understand the instructions. I initially check for equal pupil size, resting nystagmus, and equal tracking. I next check for lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees. Finally, I check for vertical nystagmus. Both eyes are checked twice for each clue.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Results: &lt;strong&gt;6/6&lt;/strong&gt;. Fearson had brown eyes that were glossy. Fearson appeared drowsy. All clues were distinct. Vertical gaze Nystagmus was also present. Fearson was asked to sit on the hood of his vehicle while I performed the test due to our height difference.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;WALK AND TURN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instructions: The subject is told to stand with their right foot in front of their left foot in a heel to toe manner. They are told to stay in that position and keep their arms at their side until being told to begin the test. I ask to make sure they understand and then begin explaining and demonstrating the test. The subject is instructed to take nine heel-to-toe steps on a straight, imaginary line. On the ninth step, they are instructed to leave their lead foot planted and take a series of small steps to turn 180 degrees. They are then told to take an additional nine heel-to-toe steps back down the same imaginary line. They are told to watch their feet, count their steps out loud, keep their hands at their side, touch heel-to-toe on every step, and to not stop walking until the test is completed.&amp;nbsp; I then ask if they understand the instructions before having them begin the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Results:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Starts Too Soon: &lt;/strong&gt;Fearson began walking almost immediately after being placed into the starting position even though I had told him not to just seconds prior. When I placed Fearson in the starting position for a second time, he again began walking and was told for a third time to wait to begin the test. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cannot Keep Balance: &lt;/strong&gt;Fearson was wobbling and demonstrating poor balance while in the starting position, causing him to lose his balance and stumble out of the starting position one time as I was still demonstrating the test. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Miss heel-to-toe: &lt;/strong&gt;Fearson missed heel-to-toe on step 3 and6 of the second set of steps, with a gap between his heel and toe. Every other step, Fearson was placing his heel of his lead foot next to the toe of his back foot. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steps Off Line: &lt;/strong&gt;Fearson was slightly crossing his feet as he walked, stepping off line for every step.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Turn:&lt;/strong&gt; Performed unsatisfactorily. Fearson quickly turned using both feet rather than taking small steps around his lead foot as instructed. Turned in the opposite direction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stops Walking:&lt;/strong&gt; Fearon paused and stopped walking after the turn to ask about how to complete the test, even after he stated that he understood the instructions. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other:&lt;/strong&gt; Slow and deliberate steps. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total Clues: 6/8&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ONE LEG STAND&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instructions: The subject is instructed to stand with their feet together with their hands at the side while I explain the instructions and demonstrate the test. They are told to raise either foot of their choice approximately six inches off the ground. They are told to begin to count, one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-three&amp;hellip;etc. They are told to continue counting until I tell them to stop. They are told to watch their feet, to count out loud, to keep their arms at their side, and to not put their foot down. I then ask if the subject understands the instructions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Results:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sway:&lt;/strong&gt; Fearson swayed his body and legs throughout the entire test. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hops:&lt;/strong&gt; After approximately 10-15 seconds, Fearson began to hop to the left as he lost his balance prior to putting his foot down.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Puts Foot Down:&lt;/strong&gt; Fearson put his foot down on 6 separate occasions, struggling to keep his foot up for more than a few seconds at a time. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other:&lt;/strong&gt; Fearson began the test by raising his left leg and standing on his right foot. Extremely slow count, only reaching a count of 9. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total Clues: 3/4&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;While on scene, Fearson was asked if he would submit to a preliminary breath test. I am certified by the Maryland State Police and the State of Maryland Office of the Chief Medical Examiner to conduct preliminary breath tests with the use of the Alco Sensor. This is the approved preliminary breath test for the State of Maryland. Urie agreed to submit to submit to the test. The result of the test was .13.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Based on my observations, as well as my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper and Drug Recognition Expert, I placed Fearson under arrest for driving under the influence at approximately 2342 hours. Fearson was polite and cooperative during my entire interaction with him. Fearson was secured in my vehicle to be transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack for processing. During a search incident to arrest, I located a small black and silver electronic smoking device in Fearson&amp;rsquo;s left front pants pocket. Fearson stated that the device was a &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; pen, which I know based on my training, knowledge, and experience as a Drug Recognition Expert to be a synthetic form of Cannabis. Fearson further stated that he had last smoked a few hours prior. Fearson&amp;rsquo;s vehicle was secured in a parking spot on the street and his personal belongings, including some loose cash, his wallet, and keys, were secured on his person. The passengers from the vehicle had already called for a friend to pick them up from the scene, and then respond to the Barrack to pick up Fearson after he was released.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Fearson was quiet while on the way to the Barrack, but I continued to detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. We arrived at the Barrack at approximately 2349 hours. After arriving at the Barrack, Fearson was provided a copy of his DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along as an audio recording from the Motor Vehicle Administration website was played for him. During the audio, Fearson was looking down at floor while the form was sitting on the table to his right, not appearing to be following along. After the recording, Fearson stated that he did not have any questions and that he understood the form. Fearson agreed to submit to an alcohol concentration test at approximately 0007 hours, May 19,2023. TFC Riba Tankari #7058, a certified intoximeter operator, performed the test. The result was .12.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DISPOSITION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Fearson was released from the Barrack to a sober driver after being charged accordingly and provided copies of all paperwork.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/22/2023 12:30:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 12:30:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507179</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/18/2023 23:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 22:22:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 22:24:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 22:22:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:13</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377487</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Fearson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Frederick</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Samuel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/25/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>IV</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>05/19/2023 21:58:27</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F636</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Fearson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Frederick</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Samuel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/25/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>IV</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>F625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F636</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/19/2023 21:58:27</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>236</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9607</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 22:25:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 22:25:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 22:23:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 22:23:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>