<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025487</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/17/2023 00:32:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/17/2023 00:32:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/16/2023 23:38:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/16/2023 23:38:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect was arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 00:33:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2362</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 10:39:10</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>20285 MD-5,GREAT MILLS</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>701142</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 00:33:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 05:26:13</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>701142</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Point Lookout</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Great Mills</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20634</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.500714</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.237629</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/17/2023 00:32:59</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/17/2023 00:32:59</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/19/2023 06:14:32</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 00:33:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:29:00</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car camera operational. BWC utilized.&lt;br /&gt; Calvin Duane Morgan&lt;br /&gt; Maryland SOUNDEX: M-625-108-155-977&lt;br /&gt; Breath Test Result: .13 BrAC&lt;br /&gt; DUI Citation #: 0N80YJL&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; DUI Tape #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-025487 (Axon View XL Software).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the&lt;br /&gt; Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland&lt;br /&gt; State Police.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; NARRATIVE:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION-&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On July 16, 2023, at approximately 2338 hours, I, Trooper Holder (#7505), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating marked MSP vehicle T-35 on southbound Maryland Route 5 just south of Flat Iron Rd. I was traveling southbound, on patrol. At that time, I observed a silver SUV fail to come to a complete stop at the blinking red traffic light at the intersection from Great Mills Rd to northbound MD Rt 5. The silver SUV made a right hand turn onto northbound MD Rt 5. I made a U-turn and began traveling northbound on MD Rt 5 to catch up to the vehicle. While behind the same vehicle, I observed the vehicle to have an inoperable tag light. The vehicle made a left hand turn onto Flat Iron Rd.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TRAFFIC STOP&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I activated the emergency lights to my patrol vehicle, initiating a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle came to a stop on Flat Iron Rd. The vehicle was a silver Jeep Patriot bearing Virginia Registration VRY1287.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT-&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the driver via the driver&amp;#39;s side door, and I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I informed the driver the reason for the stop and requested his driver&amp;#39;s license and registration card. The driver advised me that he didn&amp;rsquo;t have a license but had an identification card. Once the driver retrieved his identification card and provided it to me, I was able to identify the driver as Calvin Duane Morgan (DOB: 12/25/1978). The front seat passenger was identified as Danielle Renita Thompson (DOB: 05/08/1990). Morgan denied having any alcoholic beverages as did Thompson.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As Morgan spoke, I made the following observations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. I observed his eyes to be glassy and bloodshot.&lt;br /&gt; 2. Morgan displayed a glazed look/expression on his face as he communicated with me.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Morgan. I returned to the Jeep and requested Morgan exit the vehicle and walk to the rear of it, to which he complied. While at the rear of his vehicle, I continued to speak with Morgan. As Morgan spoke, I smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I informed Morgan that I wanted him to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST&amp;#39;s) to determine any impairment, which he agreed to submit to.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING-&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed in front of my patrol vehicle on Flat Iron Rd. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and vehicle headlamps. I asked Morgan if he had any significant medical issues with his body which would prevent him from performing the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests or if he had taken any medication prior to driving. Morgan responded: &amp;quot;No.&amp;quot; Morgan appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any limps or any limb ailments.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Morgan was wearing a black shirt, blue jeans, and black boots.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Morgan displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; 2. Morgan displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; 3. Morgan displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ADDITIONAL OBSERVATION:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was not observed during this test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **WALK AND TURN: 6 of 8 clues**&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Morgan could not maintain his balance during the Instruction Phase of the test. Morgan&amp;#39;s feet broke from the start position on two occasions. Morgan stumbled backwards.&lt;br /&gt; 2. Morgan started the test before being told to do so on two occasions.&lt;br /&gt; 3. Morgan took a total of 3 steps during the first series and took a total of 4 steps during the second series, which were both contrary to my instructions.&lt;br /&gt; 4. Morgan missed heel-to-toe on all steps during the first and second series. All missed steps were of more than half an inch.&lt;br /&gt; 5. Morgan used his arms up for balance during the entire duration of the first series of steps greater than 6&amp;quot;. Morgan used his arms for balance on the second series of steps on steps 1 and 2 greater than 6&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt; 6. Morgan did not complete the turn in a satisfactory manner by using both feet to walk around to start the second series of steps which was contrary to my instructions. Morgan was supposed to plant his lead foot and take a series of small steps to complete the turn.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **ONE LEG STAND: 3 of 4 clues**&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Morgan&amp;#39;s body swayed to his right when&amp;nbsp;he lifted his left foot on count 3.&lt;br /&gt; 2. Morgan placed his foot down at count 3.&lt;br /&gt; 3. Morgan raised his arms for the entire test greater than 6&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **ADDITIONAL OBSERVATIONS**&lt;br /&gt; It should be noted that Morgan stated he was going to use his right foot for the test, however; he used his left foot. Additionally, Morgan started the test without being told to do so and didn&amp;#39;t fully complete the test by stopping the test before being told to do so. Morgan voluntarily attempted to take the test again after the first attempt. When Morgan began taking the test again he swayed from left to right. Morgan finished the test to its entirety on the second attempt.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After the conclusion of all Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Morgan the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Morgan refused a preliminary breath test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PBT RESULT: REFUSED&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ARREST&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Morgan was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.&lt;br /&gt; * Glazed look/expression on face.&lt;br /&gt; * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; * My observed signs of impairment as he performed SFST&amp;#39;s.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I determined that Morgan was impaired by the presence of an alcoholic beverage in his system that adversely affected his ability to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. I placed Morgan under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0005 hours on 07/17/2023. At 0006 hours, I visually inspected the inside of Morgan&amp;#39;s mouth to check for foreign objects and observed a tongue piercing. Aside from the tongue piercing, that could not be removed, no other foreign objects were found.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Morgan was played the DR-15 form on the English audio version on the MVA website in the front seat of my patrol car. At 0031 hours, on July 17, 2023, Morgan agreed to submit to an Intoximeter Test and signed the DR-15.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Thompson was released from the scene and received a ride from a family member. Morgan&amp;#39;s vehicle was released to his son-in-law, Clayton Timothy Norris (DOB: 01/15/2000).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TRANSPORT&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Morgan was subsequently transported to the Leonardtown Barrack for the intoximeter test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **INTOXIMETER RESULT**:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; An Intoximeter operator was available at the Leonardtown Barrack.&lt;br /&gt; At 0107 hours on 07/17/2023, two (2) sufficient samples of Morgan&amp;#39;s breath were obtained. Sgt. Barlow #0063 was the breath test operator. The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of 0.13 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Morgan later admitted to having a Monico before driving and stated that he thought he would be a 0.08 BrAC.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; RELEASE&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Morgan was provided all forms and citations. Morgan was released to the custody of a sober driver.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; CHARGES&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Morgan was charged with the following citations:&lt;br /&gt; 1. Driving While Under The Influence Of Alcohol.&lt;br /&gt; 2. Driving under the Influence Per Se.&lt;br /&gt; 3. Driving While Impaired By Alcohol.&lt;br /&gt; 4. Reckless Driving.&lt;br /&gt; 5. Negligent Driving.&lt;br /&gt; 6. Failure to obey a Traffic Control Device.&lt;br /&gt; 7. Failing to stop at a stop line.&lt;br /&gt; 8. Inoperable tag light.&lt;br /&gt; 9. Failure to display a license.&lt;br /&gt; 10. Driving without a license.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in St. Mary&amp;#39;s County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:42:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7505</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 00:05:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5920</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Holder</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7505</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514929</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 23:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7505</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514929</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 23:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7505</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514929</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 23:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7505</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514929</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 23:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7505</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514929</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 23:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7505</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514929</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 23:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7505</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514929</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17023</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 23:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17023</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7505</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514929</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15640</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 23:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15640</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7505</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514929</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 23:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7505</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514929</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/16/2023 23:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19731</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7505</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>44</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:38:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>74597</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Morgan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Calvin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Duane</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/25/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/22/2015 01:47:52</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C415</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Morgan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Calvin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Duane</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/25/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C415</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/22/2015 01:47:52</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>25132</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>THREE NOTCH</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>UNIT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>C</SubNumber>
               <City>Hollywood</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20636</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.582569</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.358785</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>25425</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sotterley</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hollywood</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20636</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.545578</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.365506</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>997</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6126</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/06/2017 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>481</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7048</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/20/2017 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>481</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2819</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/01/2016 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>481</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2819</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/22/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:38:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:38:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:38:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 03:34:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:09</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>253332</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Thompson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Danielle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Renita</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/08/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/24/2019 03:35:10</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T512</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Thompson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Danielle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Renita</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/08/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T512</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/24/2019 03:35:10</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>46528</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Valley</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>3001</SubNumber>
               <City>California</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20619</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.4652836</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.2694915</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>237</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5890</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/24/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PA</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 03:34:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>23</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 03:36:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:09</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382710</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Norris</LastName>
               <FirstName>Clayton</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Timothy</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/15/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/17/2023 03:35:53</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C435</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Norris</LastName>
               <FirstName>Clayton</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Timothy</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/15/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>N620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C435</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/17/2023 03:35:53</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 03:36:05</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 03:38:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:14</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382712</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Morgan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Earrol</MiddleName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/17/2023 03:38:40</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Morgan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Earrol</MiddleName>
               <SLastName>M625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/17/2023 03:38:40</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 03:38:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7505</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 02:36:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155208</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7505</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 05:29:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7505</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 05:29:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C4NJPBA1HD101859</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>PAT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>VRY1287</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehicleValue>0</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>