<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-034392</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/01/2023 00:23:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/01/2023 00:23:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/30/2023 23:57:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/30/2023 23:57:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>10/01/2023 03:15:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>Traffic stop and DUI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/01/2023 00:23:12</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 16:34:11</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>708581</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/01/2023 05:15:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 06:12:55</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>708581</AddressId>
         <StreetName>BALTIMORE AVE AND BRANCHVILLE RD</StreetName>
         <City>College Park</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20740</Zip5>
         <Longitude>-76.931862</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.99744</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/01/2023 00:23:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/01/2023 00:23:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/27/2023 02:16:44</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/01/2023 00:23:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 16:27:14</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;strong&gt;The following incident was captured on my state issued BWC, Title 23-224. ID 23-MSP- 034392 and 23-225, ID 23-MSP-034392.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to the nature of the traffic stop, there were two operators of the vehicle.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case #23-MSP-034392&lt;br /&gt; DUI #23-224&lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Reyes, Andrea Estephania&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case #23-MSP-034392&lt;br /&gt; DUI #23-225&lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Romero, Edwin Eduardo&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;CERTIFICATION AND TRAINING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; ****Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration****&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Narrative:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On September 30, 2023, at approximately 2357 hours, I, Trooper Esuma #7574, was on patrol duty on Baltimore Ave, in the area of Branchville Road, College Park, Maryland, when I observed a black Honda Fit, bearing Maryland registration &amp;quot;9ED5886&amp;quot; with no lights, upon closer observation, I also observed that the vehicle was displaying an expired registration. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE ONE)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; When the vehicle finally came to a stop on the right shoulder on Baltimore Ave and MD 193, while still in my patrol vehicle, I observed the operator jump out of the driver seat into the back seat and the front seat passenger assumed the driver seat. I came up to the vehicle introduced myself to the both occupants and advised them about the driver passenger switched I just observed while seating in my patrol vehicle. While speaking with both occupants of the vehicle, I smelled a very strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle. Both occupants provided very inconsistent statements while responding to my questions about the driver passenger switch.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE TWO)&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the female operator that had switched to the rear passenger seat. She was identified by word of mouth as:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Andrea Estephania Reyes&lt;br /&gt; DOB: 08/11/1992&lt;br /&gt; Hispanic female&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I advised Reyes that she was the initial driver of the vehicle and I observed her switch from the driver seat to the rear passenger seat. Reyes admitted making the switch, and she said it is because she has to throw-up. Reyes also said she is two (2) months pregnant. At this point, I could smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Reyes breath as she spoke with me from the rear passenger window.&amp;nbsp; Reyes&amp;#39; speech was slurred, her eyes were glassy and bloodshot. Reyes was very inconsistent with the statements she made, while responding to me.&lt;br /&gt; I demanded Reyes driver&amp;#39;s license, Reyes said it was in her purse, Reyes later said it is with the male subject that assumed the driver seat. After several attempts to locate Reyes&amp;#39; driver&amp;#39;s license or get her name, Reyes finally advised that she does not possess a driver&amp;#39;s license.&amp;nbsp; Reyes admits she had consumed one shot &amp;quot;Long Island&amp;quot; alcoholic beverage about two (2) hours prior to our encounter. Reyes later advise that the male subject was so drunk that he was not able to drive and that was why she was driving the vehicle. Reyes gave me multiple different names, and lied about having a driver&amp;#39;s license, meanwhile she does not possess a driver&amp;#39;s license. Reyes advised that she drove because she had to use the bathroom.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to above observations, I advised Reyes that I will be running her through Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, she agreed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE THREE)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on sidewalk between Baltimore Ave, and MD 193. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and lighting consisted of streetlight from a pole that was at the location and my flashlight.&amp;nbsp;I asked Reyes if she had any medical conditions that could prevent her from taking the tests? Reyes said &amp;quot;No&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Reyes displayed a lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; 2. Reyes displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; 3. Reyes displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; 4. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was not observed during this test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **WALK AND TURN TEST: 6 of 8 clues**&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Before the test, I put Reyes in the instructional position. I explained and demonstrated the walk and turn test. Reyes said she understood the instructions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Reyes could not maintain her balance during the Instructional Phase. Reyes&amp;#39; feet kept breaking from the start position on two different instances, also, she stumbled from side to side.&lt;br /&gt; 2. Reyes attempted to begin the test twice while I was still demonstrating, despite being told to remain on the instructional position until told to begin.&lt;br /&gt; 3. Reyes took a total of 14 steps during the first series and did not perform the second series of the test.&lt;br /&gt; 4. Reyes missed heel-to-toe on the entire test.The missed steps were of more than half inch.&lt;br /&gt; 5. Reyes used her arms for balance during the entire test.&lt;br /&gt; 6.&amp;nbsp;Reyes did an improper turn after the first series of steps she took, and she did not complete the test. Reyes performed the test contrary to instructions.&lt;br /&gt; ***Reyes was unable to follow my instructions. Reyes broke from the starting position multiple times and stumbled around while she was performing the test. Reyes did not complete the second series of the walk and turn***.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **ONE LEG STAND: 2 of 4 clues**&lt;br /&gt; Before the test, I put Reyes in the instructional position. I explained and demonstrated the one leg stand test. Reyes said she understood the instructions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; When Reyes was advised to begin the test, Reyes started walking down and counting one thousand one and so forth, instead of raising of: placing her hands by her side, raising what ever leg she was comfortable with six inches above the ground, with her foot parallel to the ground, looking at the feet the entire test and counting out loud from one thousand one, one thousand two until told to stop as I instructed her.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; During the entire test, I could smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Reyes breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)&lt;br /&gt; PBT was not offered.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ARREST:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to the above observations, I concluded that Reyes was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and drug and could not safely operate th motor vehicle. I placed Reyes under arrest for driving under the influence of drugs and alcohol at 0022 hours. I conducted a search of her person and she was placed in my patrol vehicle. I conducted a mouth check for Reyes. DR-15 was read upon arrival at the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack. At the conclusion the of the DR-15, Reyes accepted to submit to the Intoximeter test. While at the barrack, no female was available for a secondary search of Reyes&amp;#39; person, so I conducted a modified secondary search of her person under the supervision of Sgt Smith (Duty officer).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; INTOXIMETER:&lt;br /&gt; .18 BraC.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I issued Reyes all the necessary paperwork, DUI and DWI citations and released her to a sober driver.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All these events occurred in Prince George&amp;#39;s county, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE ONE)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; When the vehicle finally came to a stop on the right shoulder by MD route 193, while still in my patrol vehicle, I observed the front seat passenger assumed the driver seat after the driver jumped to the passenger back seat. I came up to the vehicle introduced myself to the both occupants and advised them about the driver passenger switched I just observed while seating in my patrol vehicle. While speaking with both occupants of the vehicle, I smelled a very strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle. Both occupants provided very inconsistent statements while responding to my questions about the driver passenger switch, about driver&amp;#39;s license and registration of the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE TWO)&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with male subject that assumed the driver seat from the front passenger seat of the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Romero, Edwin Eduardo&lt;br /&gt; DOB: 06/09/1994&lt;br /&gt; Hispanic male.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The keys were still in the ignition of the vehicle and Romero had his seat belt buckled assuming total control of the vehicle. When I asked about the driver passenger switch Romero responded that &amp;quot;at the end of the day everything is okay&amp;quot; Romero eyes were bloodshot, his speech very slur and his statements were very inconsistent. Romero handed me his driver&amp;#39;s license but still advised that he was looking for it to hand it to me. I asked Romero about a screwdriver that was on the driver seat and Romero picked it up and brought out his glasses, then responded that the &amp;quot;screwdriver is for his phone, while showing me his glasses&amp;quot;. I advised Romero that those were his glasses not his phone, but he still kept showing me the glasses and insisting it was his phone. Romero was very incoherent in his speech and I smelled a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath, while he spoke with me. Be advised the female former driver admitted that she wanted to throw up, that was why she switch driving roles with Romero. Romero refused consuming any alcoholic beverage but during our entire encounter and while speaking with Romero, I could detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to above observations, I advised Romero that I will be running her through Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, he agreed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE THREE)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on sidewalk between Baltimore Ave, and MD 193. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and lighting consisted of streetlight from a pole that was at the location and my flashlight.&amp;nbsp;I asked Romero if he had any medical conditions that could prevent her from taking the tests? Romero said &amp;quot;No&amp;quot;. Romero insisted that he could not see the tip of my pen without his glasses, Romero advised that he was &amp;quot;nearsighted&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Romero displayed a lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; 2. Romero displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; 3. Romero displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; 4. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was not observed during this test.&lt;br /&gt; Be advised Romero did not follow my instructions, and he kept on moving his head from side to side instead of following the tip of my pen with just his eyes as instructed, almost preventing me from observing clues.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **WALK AND TURN TEST: 2 of 8 clues**&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Before the test, I put Romero in the instructional position. I explained and demonstrated the walk and turn test. Romero said she understood the instructions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Romero used his arms for balance during the entire first series of nine steps and midway during the second series of the test.&lt;br /&gt; 2.&amp;nbsp;Romero did an improper turn after the first series of nine steps. Romero performed the turn contrary to instructions.&lt;br /&gt; ***Romero broke from the starting position one time while I was demonstrating and explaining the test. Romero also stumbled around while he was performing the test***.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **ONE LEG STAND: 2 of 4 clues**&lt;br /&gt; Before the test, I put Romero in the instructional position. I explained and demonstrated the one leg stand test. Romero said he understood the instructions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Romero did not keep his arms by his side. Romero raised his arms more than six inches for balance.&lt;br /&gt; 2. Romero swayed from side to side during the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; During the entire test, I could smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Romero&amp;#39;s breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)&lt;br /&gt; PBT was not offered.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ARREST:&lt;br /&gt; Due to the above observations, I concluded that Romero was attempting to operate a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and later found out that Romero had an alcohol restriction &amp;quot;J&amp;quot; on his driver&amp;#39;s license. I placed Romero under arrest for attempting to drive under the influence of alcohol at 0036 hours. I conducted a search of his person, and he was placed in Cpl Kemp patrol vehicle for transportation to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack for processing. I conducted a mouth check on Romero. DR-15 was played in the patrol vehicle and at the conclusion the of the DR-15, Romero refused to submit to the Intoximeter test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; INTOXIMETER:&lt;br /&gt; Refused.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I issued Romero all the necessary paperwork, DUI citations and released her to a sober driver.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All these events occurred in Prince George&amp;#39;s county, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 07:40:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7574</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/24/2023 04:25:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kemp</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5753</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6084</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Esuma</LastName>
            <FirstName>Smith</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7574</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523850</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/30/2023 23:57:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 06:59:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7574</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 06:59:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523850</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/30/2023 23:57:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 07:02:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7574</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 07:02:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 07:14:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7574</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 07:58:36</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389213</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Reyes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Andrea</FirstName>
               <DOB>08/11/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/01/2023 05:40:24</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A536</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Reyes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Andrea</FirstName>
               <DOB>08/11/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A536</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/01/2023 05:40:24</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4407</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Romlon</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Beltsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20705</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.924477</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.03132</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 07:58:36</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 07:58:36</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 07:58:36</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 07:58:36</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 07:18:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7574</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 07:50:43</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389215</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Romero</LastName>
               <FirstName>Edwin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Eduardo</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/09/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/01/2023 06:21:30</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R560</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E350</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Romero</LastName>
               <FirstName>Edwin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Eduardo</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/09/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R560</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E350</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/01/2023 06:21:30</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2202</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Chapman</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hyattsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20783</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4907</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.973555</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.980015</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 07:50:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 07:50:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 07:50:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 07:50:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 06:59:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7574</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 06:59:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157611</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7574</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 07:38:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7574</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 07:38:40</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3HGGK5H40LM710483</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FIT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9ED5886</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2022</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>4</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>