<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013839</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/19/2023 03:27:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/19/2023 03:27:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/19/2023 02:51:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/19/2023 02:51:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Subject was stopped in the middle of an intersection. Driver was arrested for DUI and released from the barrack without incident.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 03:27:58</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0104</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 12:22:10</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>LEONARDTOWN RD/ MATTAWOMAN BEANTOWN RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>691234</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 03:27:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 05:34:58</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>691234</AddressId>
         <StreetName>A/O Matt. Beantown Road and Route 5</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Waldorf</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20601</Zip5>
         <Zip4>2030</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.881596</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.614616</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/19/2023 03:27:55</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/19/2023 03:27:55</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/25/2023 07:59:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 03:27:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:28</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;This incident was a recorded on an in-car and body-worn camera system (H-13).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Charges:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;TA 21-1003(d) &amp;ndash; Stopping vehicle in intersection (2T60T54).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;TA 21-902(a1i) &amp;ndash; Driving vehicle under the influence of alcohol (2T70T54).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;TA 21-902(a1ii) &amp;ndash; Driving vehicle under the influence of alcohol per se (2T80T54).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;TA 21-902(b1i) &amp;ndash; Driving vehicle while impaired by alcohol (2T90T54).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;TA 21-901.1(b) &amp;ndash; Negligent driving (2TB0T54).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driver:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah, Kojo (DOB: 09/04/1983).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FIRST DUI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;DUI# 23-071&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NARRATIVE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On Wednesday, April 19, 2023, at approximately 0303 hours, I, TFC Foster #6937, while operating unmarked MSP patrol vehicle H-13, responded to the area of Mattawoman Beantown Road and Route 5 (Leonardtown Road), Waldorf, Charles County, MD 20601 to check the welfare of an individual who was &amp;ldquo;passed out behind the wheel&amp;rdquo; of his vehicle, which was stopped in the middle of the intersection. Upon my arrival, I observed a blue GMC Terrain bearing MD registration 2EA2692 stopped in the middle of the intersection, perpendicular to northbound Route 5 in the path of lane one. Emergency Medical Services personnel (Charles County Ambulance 399) were on scene and assessing the driver, whom was still seated in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat with the Terrain still running. I was advised by Charles County Sherriff&amp;rsquo;s Office deputies, who were on scene prior to my arrival, that the Terrain was still in &amp;ldquo;Drive&amp;rdquo; when they arrived on scene. The deputies provided me the driver&amp;rsquo;s license, and I was able to identify him as Amponsah Efah, Kojo (DOB: 09/04/1983).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;While EMS personnel was attending to Amponsah Efah, I, while at his open passenger&amp;rsquo;s side door, asked him where he was coming from. He stated he &amp;ldquo;just went out to have a good time.&amp;rdquo; I asked where he had gone and, after several seconds of silence, he responded, &amp;ldquo;I went to a strip club.&amp;rdquo; I asked him where the strip club was and he advised, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s in Clinton.&amp;rdquo; I asked Amponsah Efah what time he left the strip club. He stated, &amp;ldquo;I left.. I left a bit and I.. I just.. I just trying to relax.&amp;rdquo; While speaking with Amponsah Efah, I observed he was extremely disheveled and disoriented, stumbling of his words, and struggling to formulate coherent sentences. I further observed his eyes were bloodshot and glassy, his speech was heavily slurred, and his movements were very lethargic. I also detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from inside of the vehicle. I asked Amponsah Efah how much he had to drink. Amponsah Efah paused for approximately 20 seconds before responding. During his pause, he would open his mouth as if he were going to speak but then close it and, at one point, began to smirk. Throughout his pause, he was staring off, not looking at anyone or anything, as if he were thinking about what his response was going to be. After his 20 second pause, Amponsah Efah finally responded with, &amp;ldquo;I just want to relax. I didn&amp;rsquo;t mean to create this scene.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;As it appeared EMS personnel was finishing up their tests, I approached Amponsah Efah via the driver&amp;rsquo;s side of his vehicle. EMS personnel advised Amponsah Efah that his vitals were normal and asked if he wanted medical attention. Amponsah Efah refused any further medical assistance. After EMS personnel finished with their services, I asked Amponsah Efah where his keys were, so that I could shut his vehicle off. He struggled for a few moments, reaching into both front pant pockets, until acquiring his keys and handing them over to me. Once his keys were secured, I asked Amponsah Efah again, how much he had to drink tonight. He responded, &amp;ldquo;Nothing. I&amp;rsquo;m just.. I&amp;rsquo;m just.. you know.&amp;rdquo; I asked Amponsah Efah if he wore contacts and he replied, &amp;ldquo;No. I&amp;rsquo;m.. I&amp;rsquo;m ok. I just.. I just parked.&amp;rdquo; Amponsah Efah was advised his vehicle was in &amp;ldquo;drive&amp;rdquo; and he responded, &amp;ldquo;I wasn&amp;rsquo;t driving.&amp;rdquo; I asked Amponsah Efah he would be willing to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. He advised, &amp;ldquo;I can do a sobriety test. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I can do a sobriety test.&amp;rdquo; At that point, I instructed Amponsah Efah to exit his vehicle and he complied.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;While outside of his vehicle, I observed a large, pie-plate sized, wet stain on his yellow shirt in his chest area. I asked Amponsah Efah he knew what the stain was from. He responded, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m just tired, just exhausted.&amp;rdquo; I also observed Amponsah Efah&amp;rsquo;s belt buckle was undone and asked him why it was undone. He immediately brought his hands to his belt buckle, as if he were going to secure his belt buckle, and responded, &amp;ldquo;Just.. Just to.. relieve the pressure on my waist.&amp;rdquo; After his response, he removed his hands from his belt buckle, having just fumbled with it, and left his buckle undone. I asked Amponsah Efah when his last drink was and he replied, &amp;ldquo;I drank a Jameson.&amp;rdquo; He continued, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to keep my drinking low.&amp;rdquo; While outside of his vehicle, I further detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. In order to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests in a safer location, I positioned my patrol vehicle on the right shoulder of northbound Route 5, just north of Mattawoman Beantown Road. I also had Charles County Deputies move Amponsah Efah&amp;rsquo;s vehicle over in the same location. As I escorted Amponsah Efah over toward my vehicle, he asked, &amp;ldquo;Am I arrested?&amp;rdquo; I advised him he was not and that we were just walking over to the shoulder to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;While in front of my patrol vehicle, with the forward-facing emergency lights deactivated, I explained and demonstrated the Standardized Field Sobriety tests to Amponsah Efah. The three tests administered to Amponsah Efah were the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test, the Walk and Turn Test, and the One Leg Stand Test. All three tests were performed on a level surface, free of debris, in cool weather. Amponsah Efah was wearing a yellow t-shirt, black jeans, and black tennis shoes. Amponsah Efah advised he had no medical conditions nor pertinent injuries that would hinder him from performing the tests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;During the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test, Amponsah Efah displayed six clues of impairment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah lacked smooth pursuit in both eyes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah had distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah had onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;*Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was administered and was observed to be present in both eyes. Also, throughout the duration of the test, I had to remind Amponsah Efah to refrain from moving his head several times, even after explaining the instructions to him prior to the test and him stating he understood. Also, throughout the test, he would grunt, smirk, and even randomly laugh. I also asked Amponsah Efah if he taken any medications and he replied, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m.. I&amp;rsquo;m.. I code. I write programs.&amp;rdquo; He continued, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m tired,&amp;rdquo; and then started to laugh. He further stated, &amp;ldquo;I had a long day,&amp;rdquo; and advised all he was alcohol.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I explained the Walk and Turn Test to Amponsah Efah and he stated he understood. While instructing him to place his left foot on the solid white shoulder line, he stumbled forward, taking several choppy steps and then regaining his balance. Ultimately, he adhered to my instructions and was placed in the instructional position. The test was performed utilizing the solid white shoulder line as a guide.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;During the Walk and Turn Test, Amponsah Efah displayed seven clues of impairment. While providing instructions for the test, I was forced to repeat my instructions several times, as Amponsah Efah continued to interrupt me for clarification. He would attempt to clarify, multiple times, the same portion of instruction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;During the instructional stage, Amponsah Efah could not maintain his balance while in the instructional position. Amponsah Efah broke heel to toe and placed his right foot next to his left foot, off of the line. Amponsah Efah did this several more times and was placed back into the instruction positional prior to walking. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah used his arms for balance throughout the duration of the test. At one point, Amponsah Efah raised his arms above his shoulders, fully extended. He held this position throughout the remainder of the test. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah stepped off the line on steps three, six, and eight of the first series of steps. On step three, Amponsah Efah, with his right foot planted on the line, stepped off of the line to left with his left foot. He took several seconds to regain his balance and place his left foot back on the line behind his right foot. He repeated this again on step six; however, instead of stepping off the line with his left foot, he did so with his right foot. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah stopped while walking during the first series of steps. Amponsah stopped on his seventh step and stayed in that position for approximately 30 seconds, conducting breathing exercises, until he felt balanced enough to continue with the test. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah completed an incorrect number of steps. Amponsah Efah counted his instructional position as step one, and counted from there till he stopped while walking on step eight. When he continued walking, he started the count over at one and took an additional 10 steps. In total, he took 17 actual steps on the first series of steps before I instructed him to execute the turn, as it was apparent he would not attempt it. After his turn, Amponsah Efah took an additional 14 steps on the seconds series of steps. The grand total of steps taken throughout the test was 31 steps. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah performed an improper turn. While keep both feet pinned to the white line, he pivoted, turning to his right, and never picking up either foot. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:13px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah missed heel to toe on all but four steps throughout the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I explained and demonstrated the One Leg Stand Test to Amponsah Efah, which he stated he understood; however, he attempted to start the test three times before I finished my instruction. Each time, he was advised not to start until I instructed him to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;During the One Leg Stand Test, Amponsah Efah displayed four clues of impairment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah put his foot down on counts four, nine, 14, and 25.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah hopped on counts nine, 28, and 29.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah swayed throughout the test, in all directions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:13px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah used his arms throughout the duration of the test. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah was offered a preliminary breath test, which he refused to submit to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Amponsah Efah was placed &lt;strong&gt;under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol at 0327 hours.&lt;/strong&gt; Immediately after completing the search incident to arrest, Amponsah Efah advised he needed to urinate. I asked Amponsah Efah if he could hold his bladder for another 20 minutes until we arrived at the Barrack. While asking him this, Amponsah Efah proceeded to urinate on himself in front of my vehicle. Amponsah Efah was then placed into my patrol vehicle and transported to the Maryland State Police La Plata Barrack for further processing. While en route to the Barrack, Amponsah Efah asked what he did, and I explained to him he was stopped in the middle of the intersection. He then began laughing and trying to advise me of something. He advised, &amp;ldquo;I took this stomach thing.&amp;rdquo; He then laughed again, and advised it was for easing his bowels, and then continued laughing. He continued laughing off and on throughout the drive to the Barrack. While at the Barrack, Amponsah Efah was advised of his &lt;strong&gt;DR-15, Advice of Rights, at 0405 hours.&lt;/strong&gt; Amponsah Efah agreed to submit to an intoximeter test. The test was administered by Sgt. Young #6101, with a result of &lt;strong&gt;.17 BrAC at 0426 hours.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amponsah Efah was released from the Barrack to a sober driver. Upon his release, Amponsah Efah was issued several citations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The GMC Terrain was towed from the scene by Riverside towing and taken to their tow lot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;During his time in custody, Amponsah Efah was polite, cooperative, and in a relatively happy demeanor. He laughed throughout his entire time in custody, and was extremely talkative. Also, Amponsah Efah urinated on himself once and almost did a second time during the intoximeter test but was able to hold his bladder. When allowed to go to the bathroom, he advised he &amp;ldquo;soiled himself.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All events occurred in Charles County, MD.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Case Closed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 11:19:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6937</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 07:19:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Foster</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6937</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Young</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6101</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Foster</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6937</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Foster</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6937</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503253</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16862</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/19/2023 03:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16862</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:33:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6937</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 05:39:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503253</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/19/2023 03:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:33:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6937</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 05:39:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503253</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/19/2023 03:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:33:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6937</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 05:39:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503253</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/19/2023 03:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:33:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6937</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 05:39:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503253</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/19/2023 03:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:33:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6937</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 05:39:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:33:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374721</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Amponsah Efah</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kojo</FirstName>
               <DOB>07/25/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>6.89395316E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/19/2023 05:23:41</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A515</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Amponsah Efah</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kojo</FirstName>
               <DOB>07/25/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>6.89395316E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>A515</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/19/2023 05:23:41</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2393</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Windsor Park</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Waldorf</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20602</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2159</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.892341</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.599788</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>653</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4640</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:39:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:39:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:39:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:39:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:35:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6937</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 05:35:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152134</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6937</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:41:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6937</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 05:41:01</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3GKALTEV8LL111151</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>TRN</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>TO</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2EA2692</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>11</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>