<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-001384</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/12/2023 09:57:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/12/2023 09:57:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/12/2023 09:56:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/12/2023 09:56:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Felon in possession of firearms</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/12/2023 09:57:10</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0965</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/20/2023 09:44:30</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>149744</AddressId>
      <City>MDC123</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/12/2023 09:57:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/17/2023 08:10:06</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>149744</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>9</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>SUNDAY</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>PERRYVILLE</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.98282850365725</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.56941576323227</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/12/2023 09:57:05</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/12/2023 09:57:05</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40R</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/17/2023 11:58:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/12/2023 09:57:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:50</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On Monday January 9, 2023 at approximately 2238 hours, Trooper Starr #7289, responded to 17 Pinder Ave in Elkton for a report of a male walking about the neighborhood with a sawed-off shotgun and knocking on the door of 17 Pinder Ave. The caller, who wished to remain anonymous, stated that there was a male subject walking around the neighborhood with a sawed-off shotgun and that someone was banging on the door of the residence at 17 Pinder Ave.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Upon Tpr. Starr arriving on scene he located a Hyundai Sonata displaying Maryland registration 4DG8567 parked in front of 17 Pinder Ave which was occupied by a female in the driver seat, and a male in the passenger seat. The driver and registered owner of the vehicle was identified as Nicole Marie Thomas (W/F DOB 08/20/1985), and the male passenger was identified as James Dexter Williams Jr (W/M DOB 02/03/1988). Both James and Nicole were requested to exit the vehicle and were patted down for offensive weapons. As James exited the vehicle from the passenger seat, a green and gold shotgun shell was observed in the front passenger side door jam within reach of where James was sitting. James and Nicole were asked why there was a shotgun shell in the vehicle and Nicole stated that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t own firearms and that she didn&amp;rsquo;t know why it was in the vehicle. James also stated that he didn&amp;rsquo;t know why the shotgun shell was in the vehicle, and that he doesn&amp;rsquo;t own any firearms due to him being a convicted felon and is prohibited from owning firearms.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The Gun Center was contacted at approximately 2310 hours. They confirmed that James is prohibited from owning firearms and/or firearm ammunition due to a previous felony conviction of controlled dangerous substance possession the with intent to distribute and possessing a rifle/shotgun while prohibited. Due to the initial call of James walking around the neighborhood with a shotgun, him being prohibited from owning firearms and firearm ammunition, and a loaded shotgun shell being observed in the front passenger side door jam next to where James was sitting upon Tpr. Starr&amp;#39;s arrival, a probable cause search of the vehicle was conducted at approximately 2312 hours.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;A search of the rear trunk revealed a white fitted bed sheet which was wrapped around a disassembled black and chrome Maverick Arms model 88 12-gauge shotgun (serial number: #MV01042J). An examination of the shotgun revealed two loaded green and gold shotgun shells loaded into the magazine tube. Another loaded green and gold as well as a loaded red and gold shotgun shell was also located wrapped in the bed sheet next to the shotgun. A wanted check of the shotgun came back negative.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;James was subsequently placed under arrest at approximately 2316 hours for possession of a shotgun and firearm ammunition while prohibited. He was transported back to the Maryland State Police North East Barrack for processing. The Gun Center recommended the following charges against James: Rifle/Shotgun Possession with Felony Conviction (CJIS Code 1_1610), Rifle/Shotgun Possession- Disqualification (CJIS Code 1_0439), and Illegal Possession Ammunition (CJIS Code 1_1285). Nicole was also transported back to the North East Barrack to be interviewed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Once back at the barrack Nicole stated that upon police arrival at 17 Pinder Ave, James twisted her arm behind her back and shoved a controlled dangerous substance down the front of her pants. A female Cecil County Deputy was subsequently requested to perform a strip search of Nicole. A search of Nicole revealed a clear plastic baggie containing a white rock-like substance suspected Methamphetamine. During an interview, Nicole stated that Methamphetamine is James preferred drug of choice, and that he is currently unemployed, so he relies on income from selling controlled dangerous substances. She also stated that she recently observed James carrying a chrome object wrapped in a yellow or white sheet into their garage at their residence, but that she was not positive what the object was. This remains consistent with the black and chrome shotgun located in the trunk which was wrapped in a white bed sheet.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Based on the above incident Cpl. List obtained a search warrant for Williams residence for the possession of firearms by a convicted drug felon. Upon arriving at the residence investigators knocked and announced loudly for any occupants to respond to the front door for approximately two minutes. Forced entry was made into the residence through the front door. No occupants were found inside the residence and complete search was conducted by investigators. As the result of the search shotgun ammunition was located. The residence was secured by investigators upon leaving and a copy of the search warrant and inventory was placed on tv stand just inside front door.&lt;br /&gt; Case Closed by arrest for initial incident.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP2111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 08:16:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP2111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/17/2023 08:21:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sawa</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2916</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40R</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>List</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2111</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490764</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0439</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/13/2023 08:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0439</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP2111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 08:12:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP2111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/17/2023 08:38:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP2111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 08:14:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>225290</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Williams</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dexter</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/03/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/22/2019 00:21:30</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Williams</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dexter</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/03/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/22/2019 00:21:30</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1416</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>OLD PHILADELPHIA</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>ELKTON</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.89291047791353</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.60414977904554</Latitude>
               <SubBeat>552</SubBeat>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sunday</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Charlestown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21914</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.983607</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.569458</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>907</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5298</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/27/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP2111</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 08:14:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP2111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 08:12:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP2111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/17/2023 08:12:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>