<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-026295</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/23/2023 23:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/23/2023 23:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/23/2023 23:46:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/23/2023 23:46:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 23:56:31</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/27/2023 09:37:16</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MD-100 EB TO TELEGRAPH NB / TELEGRAPH RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>577885</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 23:56:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/26/2023 01:27:00</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>577885</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Md-100</StreetName>
         <City>Severn</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.68734</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.14886</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 MD-100 / 0-0 TELEGRAPH RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/23/2023 23:56:28</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/23/2023 23:56:28</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/26/2023 02:35:03</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 23:56:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:29:43</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-eec79ca0-7fff-3d75-7106-07cf2161a1d6"&gt;DUI #: P-23-095&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-eec79ca0-7fff-3d75-7106-07cf2161a1d6"&gt;CASE #: 23-MSP-026295&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-eec79ca0-7fff-3d75-7106-07cf2161a1d6"&gt;DEFENDANT: Mario Estrada Garcia&amp;nbsp; (MD10272832549)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-eec79ca0-7fff-3d75-7106-07cf2161a1d6"&gt;*THIS INCIDENT WAS RECORDED ON MY IN-CAR AND BODY WORN CAMERA SYSTEMS*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-eec79ca0-7fff-3d75-7106-07cf2161a1d6"&gt;NARRATIVE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On 07-23-2023, at approximately 2346 hours I, Senior Trooper D. Bartch #5301 was in marked patrol unit P-24, on the right shoulder of eastbound Route 100 West of Route 170, Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; I was outside my vehicle facing westbound operating Laser Unit Pro 3 PL14777 monitoring traffic traveling eastbound. I observed a vehicle that appeared to be traveling going above the posted speed limit. I activated hand held Pro 3 laser unit PL-14777 and received a speed of 71mph in a clearly posted 55mph zone. I pulled out onto the roadway and began to pursue the vehicle. I then activated my emergency equipment and stopped the vehicle at eastbound Route 100 East of Route 170, Anne Arundel County, Maryland. The vehicle was identified by its Maryland registration as 9FD2388 a white Ford F-150.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I exited my patrol vehicle and made contact with the driver and I identified myself. I advised him that the traffic stop was being visually and audibly recorded, reason for the stop and asked for his license and registration to the vehicle. The driver was identified by his Maryland driver license as Mario Estrada Garcia (H/M) DOB 07-28-1974. While speaking with Garcia, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. I asked Garcia if he had any alcoholic beverages, and he stated he had 2 drinks. Based on the odor of alcohol, I asked Garcia to exit and come to the rear of his vehicle.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Based on my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, I suspected Garcia was impaired by alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. Garcia agreed to submit to standardized field sobriety testing. The tests were performed on the right shoulder of eastbound Route 100 East of Route 170 in an area that was level and free of debris. The weather was clear, and the test began at approximately 2350 hours. Garcia advised me that he had no present injuries, and did not wear glasses or contacts. Garcia also confirmed that he could see my stimulus (pen) in front of his face.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-eec79ca0-7fff-3d75-7106-07cf2161a1d6"&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-eec79ca0-7fff-3d75-7106-07cf2161a1d6"&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Instructions: Garcia was told to stand with his feet together and his arms down at his side. A stimulus (ink pen) was held approximately twelve to fifteen inches from Garcia&amp;#39;s face, and he was asked to follow the stimulus with his eyes only and to not move his head. Prior to beginning the test, I asked Garcia if he understood the instructions. Garcia answered yes, I initially checked for equal pupil size, resting nystagmus, and equal tracking. I, next checked for lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees. Lastly, I checked for vertical gaze nystagmus. Both eyes were checked twice for each clue.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;6/6. VGN present. Both Garcia&amp;#39;s pupils were equal in size and equally tracking the stimulus. Resting nystagmus was not present. Nystagmus was observed in each eye during all three observations.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-eec79ca0-7fff-3d75-7106-07cf2161a1d6"&gt;WALK AND TURN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Instructions: Garcia was told to stand with his right foot in front of his left foot in a heel to toe manner. He was told to stay in that position and keep his arms at his side until being told to begin the test. I asked Garcia if he understood, and he answered yes. I began explaining and demonstrating the test. Garcia was instructed to take nine heel to toe steps on a straight line. On the ninth step, he was instructed to leave his lead foot planted and take a series of small steps to turn 180 degrees. Garcia was told to then take an additional nine heel to toe steps back down the same line. He was told to gaze down at his feet, count the steps out loud, keep his hands at his side, touch heel to toe on every step, and to not stop walking until the test is complete. I asked Garcia if he understood the instructions before beginning and Garcia answered yes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At the beginning of the test Garcia could not stay in the instructional phase.&amp;nbsp; On the first series Garcia took 13 steps, stopped the test and looked at me and stated &amp;quot;Good?&amp;quot; I again advised him to do it as I explained to him. Garcia did not complete the turn as instructed. Garcia turned to his right and started on the second series of steps. On the second series of steps Garcia again took 13 steps and stopped the test. I asked Garcia how many steps he took and Garcia stated &amp;quot;9&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-eec79ca0-7fff-3d75-7106-07cf2161a1d6"&gt;ONE LEG STAND&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Instructions: Garcia was instructed to stand with his feet together and his hands at his side while I explained the instructions and demonstrated the test. Garcia was told to raise either foot of his choice approximately six inches off the ground while keeping it parallel to the ground. He was told to begin to count, one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-three&amp;hellip;etc. Garcia was instructed to continue counting until I told him to stop. He was told to gaze down at his feet, to count out loud, to keep his arms at his side, and to not put his foot down. I then asked if Garcia understood the instructions. Garcia answered yes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;While I was explaining the test Garcia would twice lift his right foot up and try to begin the test before I was finished the instructions. I again had to advise Garcia each time to stop and stay in the instructional phase as I already instructed him to do. Garcia started the one-leg stand and started to walk heel-to-toe steps and at step 5 I stopped Garcia. I again had to explain the test to Garcia. Garcia then raised his right foot barely off the ground and was not counting out loud. I again advised Garcia to count out loud. Garcia raised his arms more than six inches to help him balance and then dropped his foot at count 5. I then stopped the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Based on my observations and my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, Garcia was placed under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol at approximately 2354 hours. I secured Garcia in my patrol vehicle and transported him to the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie barrack for processing. We arrived at the barrack at approximately 0002 hours. I escorted Garcia into the barracks Troopers room, and he was provided a copy of his DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along as a spanish audio version was played to him out loud in its entirety. I asked Garcia if he understood the form, and he answered yes. At approximately 0019 hours, Garcia consented to submit to the intoximeter test. Anne Arundel County Cpl G. Whisman., a certified intoximeter operator, administered the test. The result of the test was .11 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&amp;nbsp; Garcia was placed in a temporary holding cell while the remainder of the paperwork and citations were completed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I transported Garcia to his residence at 97 Greenway St NW, Glen Burnie, Maryland 21061 and was released. Garcia was provided with all appropriate paperwork and citations. Garcia&amp;#39;s driver&amp;#39;s license was confiscated and submitted to the MVA along with a DR-15A form.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-eec79ca0-7fff-3d75-7106-07cf2161a1d6"&gt;All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 02:28:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/26/2023 01:25:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Baldi</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6907</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wiest</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4939</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bartch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5301</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515740</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/23/2023 23:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 02:04:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 02:04:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>48</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 02:13:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:24</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383325</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Garcia</LastName>
               <FirstName>Mario</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Estrada</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/28/1974 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/24/2023 02:11:55</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Garcia</LastName>
               <FirstName>Mario</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Estrada</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/28/1974 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/24/2023 02:11:55</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>97</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>NW</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Greenway</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>NW</StreetSuffixCode>
               <SubTypeCode>BLDG</SubTypeCode>
               <City>Glen Burnie</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21061</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3531</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.627742</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.165404</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>667</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>895</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6595</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 02:13:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:17</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 02:13:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:17</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 02:13:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:17</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 02:13:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:17</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 02:04:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 02:04:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>