<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-031224</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/05/2023 13:33:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/05/2023 13:33:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/05/2023 12:58:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/05/2023 12:58:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Missing Person Report</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 13:39:12</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6562</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/16/2023 21:31:28</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>MP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>706043</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 13:39:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 14:39:59</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>706043</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>400</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mcleod</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Stevensville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21666</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-76.31768</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.016599</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/05/2023 13:39:09</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/05/2023 13:39:09</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>80</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>09/16/2023 21:31:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 13:39:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6562</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/16/2023 21:31:28</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;Unmarked S-12&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On 09/05/2023 at approximately 1302 hours, I, Trooper First Class Maranto #7116 of the Maryland State Police Centreville barrack was on patrol in full uniform, operating unmarked MSP vehicle S-12. I was dispatched to 400 Mcleod Lane, Stevensville, Maryland 21666, for the report of a missing person.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Upon my arrival, I made contact with the complainant. I asked for her information. A Florida Driver&amp;#39;s License positively identified her as Shan Kathleen Chien (A/F DOB: 02/21/1956) of 400 Mcleod Lane, Stevensville, Maryland 21666. I asked Shan what had occurred today. Shan advised that her sister currently lives with her at the address. Her sister fled the residence on 09/01/2023 in between the hours of 1000-1700. Shan last saw her at 1000 hours before she left the house, and returned home at 1700 hours. I asked for her sister&amp;#39;s information. A Michigan Driver&amp;#39;s License positively identified Kitty Sung-Chun-Shaun Shi (A/F DOB: 05/15/1961) who previously resided at 20771 Garden Lane, Ferndale, Michigan 48220.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Shan advised that her sister Kitty was schizophrenic, however she had never been diagnosed with any disease because she refused to go to the hospital. Shan advised that Kitty had grown up in Michigan and worked for a company in Detroit for 25 years, and after her husband passed, she began having difficulty with the situation. Her mental capability deteriorated. Shan stated that she then moved in with her brother who lived at 21145 Hickory Forest Way, Germantown, in Montgomery County, Maryland. On 03/14/2022, Kitty was reported missing to the Montgomery County Police Department after she had walked off. Kitty was not found again until October/November in Orlando, Florida by authorities.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Shan told me that Kitty moved into their Stevensville address in April of 2023, and had been living there since. Shan advised that Kitty would talk to people, who do not exist. Shan stated that Kitty did mention she was going to visit her brother recently, but Kitty has no means of transportation, or a cellular device. Shan advised that she is worried about her sister, because she usually goes hitchhiking to get to her destination. I asked Shan if she suspected Kitty of using alcohol, controlled dangerous substances, or any other narcotics, and she stated &amp;quot;No, she&amp;#39;ll have a glass of wine with dinner, but nothing more than that.&amp;quot; Shan did advise that she had been previously EP&amp;#39;ed (Emergency Petition) at a hospital in Prince George&amp;#39;s County, and another hospital which she was not sure the name of.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Shan described Kitty as a 5 foot, 110 pounds, short black hair, who usually wears plaid shirts. She does not have any scars, marks, or tattoos. She may be carrying a small amount of currency, as well as a tan bag. She usually wears long sleeve plaid shirts, as well as pants or jeans. Shan advised that the rest of her family had been notified by her, and she would contact the barrack if anyone gets in touch with her. I gave Shan the case information, as well as the barrack information and advised I would be in contact with her if any updates came.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; A search of the area after leaving the residence resulted in negative location of Kitty. This information was passed on to the Queen Anne&amp;#39;s County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Office, as well as the Maryland Transportation Authority Police. I also contacted the state police Child Recovery Unit. I spoke with Sgt. Flory, who obtained the information from me and created a Missing Person&amp;#39;s poster. She advised she shared the poster on Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, and all surrounding police departments. I also contacted the Montgomery County Police Department, and obtained their report for when she went missing in March 2022. I also got the contact information for the investigating Detective. I spoke with Detective Alyson Dupouy, of the Montgomery County Police Department who handled the case back in March 2022. Alyson advised that Kitty had began working at a kitchen in Orlando, Florida shortly after leaving Maryland. The kitchen gave Kitty a job because they thought she was homeless. The kitchen staff advised that she only wanted to be paid in cash, and did not wish to give out personal information. An Orlando Police Department officer recognized her, which is how they later identified her through a Crime Stoppers Missing Person poster. Kitty seemed to be healthy, dressing fine, and had an apartment. She did not seem in distress.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Upon reading the report taken by Montgomery County Police, I obtained the following information from the report:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;quot;On 04/08/2022 Herbert Shih called MCP to report his 60 year old sister, Kitty Shi, had gone missing again. Herbert told Officer Berry that he last saw his sister at his house on 03/14/2022 and that this is the third time since 2019 that his sister has gone missing for an extended period of time. The writer spoke with Herbert who said that his sister appears to be normal despite being very paranoid and schizophrenic, and that it is because of the illness/her belief that the government could track her, that she does not have a cell phone or credit cards. The victim does not drive but travels everywhere on mass transit. The writer has checked with several bus companies, none of which have any record of her as a passenger recently. The writer also checked with Amtrak Train Police Department and was informed that they last record they have of her being on the train was from February of this year when she took a train ride from Washington DC to Boston and back, a one day trip.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Kitty was entered in NCIC on 09/05/2023 at the Centreville Barrack. If any information comes available, a supplement will be completed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I request this case be closed, due to lack of investigational leads.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; All events occurred in Queen Anne&amp;#39;s County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 14:52:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/08/2023 16:53:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Passwaters</LastName>
            <FirstName>Chase</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7367</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Baker</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6562</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Maranto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7116</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>62</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 14:45:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 15:29:07</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>387071</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>A</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Shi</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kitty</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Sung-Chun-Shaun</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/15/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14929642E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>09/05/2023 14:45:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Shi</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kitty</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Sung-Chun-Shaun</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/15/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14929642E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/05/2023 14:45:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>400</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mcleod</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Stevensville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21666</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.31768</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.016599</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>M</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 14:45:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 14:45:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>67</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 14:51:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 14:51:21</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>387072</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>A</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>CHien</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kathleen</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/21/1956 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/05/2023 14:51:12</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>CHien</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kathleen</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/21/1956 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/05/2023 14:51:12</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>400</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mcleod</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Stevensville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21666</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.31768</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.016599</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>850</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8688</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 14:51:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 14:51:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>