<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013893</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/19/2023 13:35:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/19/2023 13:35:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/19/2023 13:35:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/19/2023 13:35:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Sexual Child Abuse</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 13:35:34</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2124</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/01/2023 10:10:19</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SAS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>691287</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 13:35:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/20/2023 10:48:10</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>691287</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>23</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Amanda</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Smithsburg</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.581629</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.660591</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/19/2023 13:35:29</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/19/2023 13:35:29</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/01/2023 10:10:00</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 13:35:34</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;strong&gt;ATTACHMENTS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Washington County CPS Intake Worksheet, placed in case file.&lt;br /&gt; 2.) CD of recorded forensic interview with victim, placed in MSP Hagerstown Property.&lt;br /&gt; 3.) CD of recorded interview with the suspect, placed in MSP Hagerstown Property.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;NARRATIVE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On 4/13/2023, I, Sgt. Angermeier was notified by Washington County CPS of an incoming case of alleged child sex abuse. It was alleged a 16 year old female disclosed that her 18 year old biological brother had sexually assaulted her in 2018-2021.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; SEE THE BELOW INTERVIEW NOTES FROM CPS SUPERVISOR RACHEL MAZLOUM. FOR WORD FOR WORD OF THE INTERVIEW, SEE THE RECORDED INTERVIEW ON CD.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 4/19/2023 at approximately 1448 hours, CPS Worker Lauren Harbaugh interviewed Kathleen (age 16) using the ChildFirst Forensic Interviewing Protocol. The interview was video recorded. CPS Supervisor Rachel Mazloum and MSP Sgt. Adam Angermeier observed the interview.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker began by orienting Kathleen to the interview room and process. Worker transitioned to rapport building. She has danced since she was 3 and does ballet, jazz, tap, etc. She also plays the trumpet in band. Worker completed narrative practice with her regarding her most recent jazz class. She shared she also likes to go to the gym. She also started working at an ice cream shop. Kathleen was able to provide detail and was articulate. She appears developmentally appropriate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker asked about her household members. She lives with her mom (Kim), dad (Jim) and brother (Kelton). She denied doing much with her father and she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like when he helps her with homework and she is much closer with her mother. Her and her mom go shopping and watch TV and make things together and talk. There is nothing she noted not liking to do with her mother. She noted she doesn&amp;rsquo;t talk to Kelton much. She said it is &amp;ldquo;awkward&amp;rdquo; with him now and she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like to be alone with him, because of the &amp;ldquo;things he used to do to me&amp;rdquo;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker asked more about what he used to do. She said he used to try to &amp;ldquo;sexually assault&amp;rdquo; her when she was younger. She said this started in 2018, she thinks she was 11 years old and she didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to do. It happened for a few years. The last time was July 4, 2021. She said on that day she was finally done with it and she told her parents. Before this she didn&amp;rsquo;t want to tell them because she was worried about what her parents would say or if it would make it worse with her brother. She said she was getting bruises so she couldn&amp;rsquo;t do it anymore.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; She said on July 4, 2021 she went to a pool party and that night she came to his room and was talking to him and he got upset and pinned her down and was trying to &amp;ldquo;rape&amp;rdquo; her. He would do it when he was mad at her and she didn&amp;rsquo;t like it and she would scream and tell him to stop. Worker asked more about July 4. He got mad because they were arguing about his dog. He pinned her down in front of his computer desk on the ground. He was trying to &amp;ldquo;force&amp;rdquo; her clothes off and trying to rape her. She was trying to force her clothes back on and she was screaming and trying to get away. She can&amp;rsquo;t remember if he got her clothes off. He tried to pull his pants down but the rest of his clothes were on. She said in the past he tried to get her to touch his &amp;ldquo;private part&amp;rdquo; and he would try to force her to do this. He always &amp;ldquo;tried&amp;rdquo; to rape her but was never successful.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker asked about the first time something happened. They were on a trip in Montana and had a big hotel room with two rooms. Her and her brother were forced to share a bed. In the middle of the night she woke up and felt him trying to put his hand in her pants. He was &amp;ldquo;trying&amp;rdquo; to touch her inappropriately and she felt &amp;ldquo;sick&amp;rdquo; for a week afterwards. He never said anything afterwards. He was touching her private parts. This went on for maybe 10 minutes. It was on the outside and inside of her and she felt pain and disgusted.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; She said there were times at her house and times at a family cabin in West Virginia. They were forced to share a bed again and he was trying to get her to touch him. He was saying things to try to force her. He was grabbing her arm and forcing her. She said she didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to do and was sick to her stomach. She thinks this was the second time something happened and this may have been in August or September. They had gone to Montana in July.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At her house she used to go downstairs and watch TV on the projector. He would try to &amp;ldquo;do things&amp;rdquo; to her when she was watching TV. She said if her parents were upstairs he would do it. Sometimes it was almost every day. If they were home alone he would do it in different places in the home.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker asked about a time that stands out the most. She said one time she was sleeping and he came into her room and was standing there and trying to get her to &amp;ldquo;do stuff&amp;rdquo;. She threw him on the floor and the thinks it woke her parents up. He was trying to touch her and get her to touch him. He would say things but she can&amp;rsquo;t remember what he would say. He would try to pin her down and get him to touch her in ways he wanted.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; She talked about him trying to force her hands down his pants. She said he would force her to touch his &amp;ldquo;dick&amp;rdquo;. His dick was &amp;ldquo;hard&amp;rdquo;. She said sometimes she would threaten to call her parents and sometimes he would throw her phone. Sometimes that would make him stop. There would be a few months at a time he would stop and other times it would happen almost every day. By the time it stopped it was about once a month.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; She showed her mom bruises that he gave her and Kathleen struggled with telling her mom completely what happened. Kathleen didn&amp;rsquo;t tell her mom until recently everything that happened. In 2021 she told her mom some of the things he had done. They talked to him and gave him a warning and he stopped doing it.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; She said when it happened every day this would be when her mom started working, especially in the summer time. Her mom started working in Fall, 2018 and then she wasn&amp;rsquo;t home and that made it worse. She used to watch Friends in the basement.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; She said there were a few times it was &amp;ldquo;close&amp;rdquo; for him to rape her. He would try to &amp;ldquo;force&amp;rdquo; her down and &amp;ldquo;do things&amp;rdquo;. He would try to force his &amp;ldquo;dick&amp;rdquo; in her when he was pinning her down. She said she felt him trying to force it in her. He also tried to put it in her mouth.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Kathleen shared that it also happened at her grandparents house and he would try to touch her or make him touch her. Her grandparents live in Ijamsville near Frederick.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker presented the anatomically correct drawings of the male and female. Kathleen circled the male penis as the &amp;ldquo;dick&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;private part&amp;rdquo; and the female vagina, breasts, and butt and mouth as places he touched. He would try to look at her breasts and touch her breasts. Most of the time he would try to force his clothes off and she would try to force them back on. Sometimes he was able to get her clothes off and one time her ripped one of them from forcing it off. When these incidents happened, his clothes would be on unless he pulled his pants down enough for her to &amp;ldquo;grab him&amp;rdquo;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; She has a better relationship with him now but she can&amp;#39;t forget about it. She has a fear that all men would be like that she she was scared for a long time. She began to cry. She denied that this happened with anyone else.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker exited the interview room to speak to observers and then re-entered the room. Worker asked about the incidents at her house and if she has always lived in the same house. She said yes. Worker asked about him touching parts of her body at her house. She said yes and most of the times happened at her house. He was able to touch her vagina in their house. There were times that he forced her to touch him at their house. Worker asked with him trying to rape her, what he did. He would force her down and try to &amp;ldquo;stick his dick in me&amp;rdquo;. His dick would touch her vagina but it would not go in, as she would move away as much as she could. Worker asked about the bruises. He would throw her on the ground or hit her or pinch her skin or throw her down and that is what would give her bruises. She had bruises on her side, hips, and arms. On her side he bruised her because he was trying to force off her bra.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker asked about anyone walking in, since earlier Kathleen said that was a reason he would stop. Kathleen said no one ever walked in. Kathleen said there were times she was downstairs and someone would walk downstairs and they could hear foot steps. She said she has told her boyfriend and parents but hasn&amp;rsquo;t told them anything different. She told a friend a few months before she told her parents. She has told some of her closest friends. She said she jumps and freaks out easily if people touch her so she told the people closest to her about why.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Worker exited the interview room again to speak to observers and then re-entered. Worker ended the interview reverting to neutral topics. Kathleen talked about wanting therapy and her struggles with fear of men. She said her boyfriend is the first boy she isn&amp;#39;t scared with.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Also on 4/19/2023 at approximately 1630 hours, I, Sgt. Angermeier interviewed the suspect, Kelton Bullock at the MSP Hagerstown Barrack conference room. Kelton agreed to a recorded interview. He was read his Advice of Miranda Rights and he advised he understood his rights and elected to speak to me without an attorney present.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Kelton if he knew when he was at the Hagerstown Barrack for an interview. (His father James called him from the CAC and told him to come to the barrack.) Kelton advised he wasn&amp;#39;t sure why. I advised him it was regarding some of the things his sister, Kathleen, has brought to our attention regarding sexual abuse. He stated, &amp;quot;Okay.&amp;quot; I asked him if he wanted to tell me about that. He stated, &amp;quot;So um, I don&amp;#39;t exactly remember when, it was before Covid, I was I believe 13, the first thing I remember was we were at our cabin (In West Virginia), my sister and I were in the other bed, I remember in the morning, I don&amp;#39;t know, you know, we just kind of were touching each other.&amp;quot; I asked Kelton if he touched her vagina and he advised, yes. I asked him if he inserted his fingers into her vagina and he stated, &amp;quot;No.&amp;quot; I advised him that was not what his sister said happened.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I advised Kelton that Kathleen stated the sex abuse went on for several years and sometimes every day and Kelton took a very long pause to collect his thoughts. He then stated, &amp;quot;I mainly remember it in the summer when my mom was at work.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I advised Kelton that Kathleen stated that at times he would be very aggressive with her and he stated, &amp;quot;Yeah, sometimes I get out of control.&amp;quot; I asked him if he would be aggressive with anything else and he advised, no.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Kelton if he is addicted to sex and porn and he stated, &amp;quot;Sometimes, yeah.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Kelton if Kathleen ever touched his penis and he stated, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot; I asked him if he would have an orgasm and he stated, &amp;quot;No, not that I can remember.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Kelton if his penis ever entered the inside of Kathleen&amp;#39;s vagina and he stated, &amp;quot;Not that I can remember.&amp;quot; I advised Kathleen stated that he took her clothes off and his penis touched the outside of her vagina. I asked Kelton if that statement was correct and he stated, &amp;quot;Yeah.&amp;quot; I asked him why he didn&amp;#39;t insert his penis and he advised he tried to stop himself and advised he knew what he was doing was wrong.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Kelton if he ever touched her anus and he stated, &amp;quot;I think so.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Kelton if Kathleen would tell him to stop or she did not want to, when he was doing these things and he stated, &amp;quot;Yeah, she would say stop, or she would yell, sometimes she would hit me.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Kelton stated he was watching porn at age 13.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The interview then concluded. See the recorded interview on CD for further details.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 4/27/2023, I authored charges for Kelton Bullock and dropped them off at the District Court Commissioners Office.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 4/28/2023, I was advised by the Commissioners Office that an arrest warrant as issued for Kelton. I contacted Master Trooper Bussard of the Washington County Warrant Task Force and he advised the warrant was entered.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 4/30/2023, I was advised that Kelton had turned himself into the Washington County Sheriffs Office and arrested by Deputy Brandon Dillman.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Washington County, MD, Montana, and West Virginia.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5544</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 08:50:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5544</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/01/2023 09:47:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Martin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Angermeier</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5544</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 1103</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/19/2023 13:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5544</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 12:03:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5544</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/28/2023 09:26:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503307</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3 3600</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/19/2023 13:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5544</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 12:03:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5544</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/28/2023 09:26:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>16</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5544</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 10:03:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374821</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bullock</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kathleen</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/25/2006 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/20/2023 09:59:37</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K345</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bullock</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kathleen</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/25/2006 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K345</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/20/2023 09:59:37</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>23</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Amanda</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Smithsburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.581629</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.660591</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5544</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/28/2023 09:18:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5544</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 12:07:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:01</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374828</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bullock</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kelton</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>James</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/22/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/20/2023 12:06:54</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K435</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bullock</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kelton</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>James</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/22/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K435</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/20/2023 12:06:54</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>23</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Amanda</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Smithsburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.581629</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.660591</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5544</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/26/2023 11:58:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>