<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-018068</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/20/2023 23:46:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/20/2023 23:46:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/20/2023 23:28:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/20/2023 23:28:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Minor motor vehicle collision. At fault driver found to be intoxicated. Driver refused all Field Sobriety Tests and breath test.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 23:46:49</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/03/2023 22:30:56</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY/ RACETRACK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>265849</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 23:46:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 04:38:19</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>265849</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21811</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.16789</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.346564</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10834-11222 OCEAN GTWY / 10103-10106 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 W/O MCDONALDS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 PRIOR TO 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>50 EB/ RACETRACK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>TURN LANE ONTO 589 FROM W/B 50</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 /589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>50 WB/ 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>50 /589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50 PRIOR RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 10833-11221 OCEAN GTWY / 10107-10110 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11224-11264 OCEAN GTWY / 10103-10106 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10833-11221 OCEAN GTWY / 10107-10110 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10833-11221 OCEAN GTWY / 10103-10106 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11223-11263 OCEAN GTWY / 10103-10106 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 / RT 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11201-11397 OCEAN GTWY / 0-0 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/20/2023 23:46:46</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/20/2023 23:46:46</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/01/2023 09:58:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 23:46:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:54:40</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;DATE OF OFFENSE:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Saturday, May 20th, 2023&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;CASE NUMBER:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;23-MSP-018068&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;DUI FILE #:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;23-96-128&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;STOP RECORDED:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Yes, stop recorded on body worn and in car camera systems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;PHOTOS:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;No photos taken.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;REASON FOR STOP:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;MSP Berlin Troopers were dispatched to a motor vehicle collision in the area of W/B RT 50 prior to RT 589. Upon arrival, I learned that the victim stopped at the intersection for a red light. The at fault vehicle failed t stop in time and rear ended the victim. The at fault driver displayed signs of impairment. Driver admitted to drinking 8 beers but refused all SFSTs and breath test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;No, First offense.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;SUSPECT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Alleman, George Vincent&amp;nbsp; 10/30/1966&lt;br /&gt; 1522 Sappington Dr,&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Gambrills, MD 21054&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;VEHICLE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; MD - 8CVT22 Silver Honda Civic&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;Passenger:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Alleman, Darliene Louise 01/09/1969&lt;br /&gt; 1522 Sappington Dr,&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Gambrills, MD 21054&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Victim:&lt;br /&gt; Driver:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Isadora Mayumi Ichihara Dos Reis Dipaolo&amp;nbsp; 02/17/1992.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 707 Ramsey CT Apt 302&lt;br /&gt; Salisbury, MD 21904&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Passenger:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Dipaolo, Michael Anthony&amp;nbsp; 06/13/1991&lt;br /&gt; 707 Ramsey CT Apt 302&lt;br /&gt; Salisbury, MD 21904&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Vehicle:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; MD - 8EK5274 Blue, 2019, Hyundai Elantra&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TEST (SFSTs) RESULTS:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;REFUSED&amp;nbsp;ALL TESTS.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN):&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;REFUSED&amp;nbsp;ALL TESTS.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;WALK AND TURN:&lt;/strong&gt;REFUSED&amp;nbsp;ALL TESTS.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;ONE LEG STAND:&lt;/strong&gt;REFUSED&amp;nbsp;ALL TESTS.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;BREATH TEST RESULTS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Knowingly refused Breath Test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;NARRATIVE:&lt;br /&gt; PHASE 1. (Pre-stop observations)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On Saturday, May 20th, 2023, MSP Berlin Troopers were dispatched to respond to the area of RT 50 prior to RT 589 in reference to a motor vehicle collision.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Upon my arrival, a Worcester County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Deputy was on scene. I observed a Silver Honda Civic parked on the shoulder behind a blue Hyundai Elantra.&amp;nbsp;Both vehicles appeared to have minor damage. The Honda had front end damage and the Hyundai had rear end damage. The driver of the Honda Civic, later identified by his MD license as&amp;nbsp;Alleman, George Vincent JR. 10/30/1966, was standing by his vehicle with the Worcester County Deputy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;PHASE 2.(Personal Contact)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; As I spoke with George, I observed him to have glassy bloodshot eyes, heavily slurred speech and the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his breath and person. I asked George what happened. He stated &amp;quot;The light started to change real quick and I tried to stop and poot. Bumped him in the butt.&amp;quot; I then requested George&amp;#39;s license, registration, and insurance for the accident report. George stated that his wife had all of that information. George&amp;#39;s wife was later identified as&amp;nbsp;Alleman, Darliene Louise 01/09/1969. I then asked George if he was driving. George stated yes, he was driving, but it is his wife&amp;#39;s car.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then made contact with the driver of the Hyundai who was identified by her Maryland License as&amp;nbsp;Isadora Mayumi Ichihara Dos Reis Dipaolo&amp;nbsp; 02/17/1992. Isadora stated that they stopped at the red light, and George ran into them. As I spoke with the victims, the Deputy also advised me that he believed George was under the influence of alcohol.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The registered owner of the vehicle was the front seat passenger. He was identified as&amp;nbsp;Dipaolo, Michael Anthony&amp;nbsp; 06/13/1991. As I gathered the information for the accident report, Michael stated that George came right over to him (Michael) and stated that he (George) had been drinking.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As I spoke with George and Darliene again, George stated that he was just hoping to work things out with the victims and that he would pay for the damages rather than going through insurance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-b52957a9-7fff-a1f6-d382-ca92ec457703"&gt;PHASE 3. (Pre-arrest screening)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Based on the above circumstances, I attempted to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) on George.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked George to walk to the front of the vehicles with me. I observed George to appear off balance and wobbling as he walked, and for him to walk with a wide stance. I also noticed that George was wearing flip-flop style shoes. I observed that the flip-flop on his right foot was not on correctly. All of his toes were on the same side of the strap, rather than his big toe separated from the other toes by the strap. As a result, the sole of the shoe was at an angle from his foot.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked George how much he had to drink tonight. George stated he had 8 beers and that he was not going to lie to me. He stated he was drinking Coors Light at a friend&amp;#39;s house. I asked George what time he started drinking and when he stopped. George mumbled but appeared to be struggling to recall what time he started and stopped drinking. I then asked George what time he got to his friend&amp;#39;s house. George stated about 7 PM. I then asked what time his last drink was. George stated 8PM. He stated that he only drank for about an hour. I asked George if he knew what time it was and he stated he did not. I asked George if he had anything to drink either before or after being at his friend&amp;#39;s house and he stated he did not.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked George if he wears glasses or contacts. He stated he has bad hearing but does not wear glasses or contacts. I then asked George if he had any other physical disabilities. George stated that he has a back problem. I asked what he&amp;nbsp; meant by that, if it was just sore or if he had an injury. George stated it was just &amp;quot;from being old and age.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; George stated he has worked for the government his whole life. I asked him what specifically he did for the government. He then stated he worked for Anne Arundel County. I then asked him again what specifically he does. He stated he used to work construction, but now he is retired but he also still works construction for the county.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then explained to George that I can tell he has alcohol in his system and that I was going to place him through SFSTs. George stated that he doesn&amp;#39;t have to drive and asked if someone else could drive. I explained that I still needed to do these tests because he was already driving. I asked George if he would be willing to cooperate and do the tests for me. George agreed to submit to the tests.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked George if he had ever done SFSTs before. George stated he had not, and that he could not do the tests because he has all kinds of balance issues. George struggled to say the word equilibrium, calling it his eagle-lee-bruh and then ick-uh-lee-bri. George stated that he &amp;quot;can not hear because he can not hear.&amp;quot; He stated that because he can not hear, it messes up his balance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked if he would be willing to try these tests. I explained that the first test is an eye test and is not for checking his balance. George stated that it does. I then attempted to explain the instructions for the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) test. I advised George that for the moment, all I wanted him to do was stand with his feet together, so his heels and toes are touching and stand with his hands down by his sides. I demonstrated this as I explained it to George. I then asked if he understood the instructions so far. George stated no, he did not. I then explained it again and showed George how I was standing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; George then stated he was wearing flip-flops, and he could not do it. He then asked if he could take his flip-flops off. I advised him he could. George then attempted to kick the flip-flop that was not on his foot correctly, off of his foot. It would not come off since all of his toes were shoved into the one side. After several attempts of kicking the flip-flop off of his foot, and it not coming off, George stated he couldn&amp;#39;t do it, and mumbled something. He then paused and was silent for a moment before stating come on, indicating he wanted to do the test. I asked to confirm, that he now did not want to take his shoes off. He then stated it won&amp;#39;t come off, and mumbled more unintelligible remarks, appearing puzzled as to why his flip-flops would not come off his feet.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then attempted to explain the test again to George. George then asked what I was going to do, and stated &amp;quot;If you&amp;#39;re going to lock me up, lock me up.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I then asked if he wanted to do tests. He stated that he wanted to but he can&amp;#39;t. I then began explaining the HGN test again. George interrupted me and asked if he could take his shoes off. I again stated he could if he wanted to. George then stated no, he couldn&amp;#39;t do it, and that he was sorry. He stated he could not do the test because it hurts his back. He stated that he thinks he was doing it the wrong way, and asked to stand in the grass. I explained that I did not want him in the grass so he did not trip or fall because the grass could be uneven.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; George then asked if he could stand facing a different direction, but on the pavement. I allowed it and attempted to explain the HGN instructions again. As I began the instructions, George asked if he was getting locked up. I advised him that it depended on how he did on the tests. George then stated that he was done with it, and to just lock him up. George stated &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m a firm believer in getting locked up. I don&amp;#39;t give a shit.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the above evidence, I placed George under arrest. Throughout my contact with George, he continued to have heavily slurred speech, and the strong odor of an acholic beverage coming from his breath and person. George&amp;#39;s speech was so slurred it was difficult to understand what he was saying at times.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In an effort to get George and his wife home safely, I asked George if he had someone he could call to come pick him up. George stated that his daughter lives in Princess Ann, MD. He stated his daughter&amp;#39;s name was Jordyn and asked for me to try and call her on his cell phone. I attempted to look through his phone to find Jordyn.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In his phone there was a contact listed as &amp;quot;Jordy.&amp;quot; I asked George if that was the number. George stated no it was not, her name was Jordyn, not Jordy, and that I was in the wrong place. I asked George several times if it was Jordy, showing him the contact. George began to get angry stating it was not the right contact. I looked through all the &amp;quot;J&amp;quot; contacts and there were no &amp;quot;Jordyn&amp;quot; listed. I explained to George that there was no &amp;quot;Jordyn&amp;quot; in his contacts. At this time, George then stated it was &amp;quot;Jordy.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After making arrangements for the passenger, and vehicle, and getting the victims in the incident the paperwork for the accident, I then transported George to the MSP Berlin barrack. As I transported George, I played the DR-15 audio from the MVA website, through my vehicle speakers with the volume turned up loud so that George could hear it. I explained to George to listen to the form and listen carefully because it explains his rights and consequences. George stated that he was not going to take the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At the completion of the DR-15 form, I asked George if he wished to submit to a breath test. George stated no, he did not. George refused the breath test at 12:13 AM.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to other arrests and a medical emergency inside the barrack, I completed the paperwork inside my patrol car. Throughout the encounter, George continued to have heavily slurred speech and the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his breath and person.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; George made several statements indicating that he knew he was intoxicated and should not have been driving. George stated that his wife asked him to go out tonight, and that in order to keep his wife happy, he did drive. George stated &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ll take the blame for it.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; George was charged and issued appropriate paperwork. He as then released to his daughter.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 06:15:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5911</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/30/2023 16:06:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phillips</LastName>
            <FirstName>Riley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7211</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Woo</LastName>
            <FirstName>Johnathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5911</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shockley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4814</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Woo</LastName>
            <FirstName>Johnathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5911</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Woo</LastName>
            <FirstName>Johnathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5911</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507500</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/20/2023 23:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 14:04:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5911</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/23/2023 14:07:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>56</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>C</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 14:04:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377662</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Alleman</LastName>
               <FirstName>George</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Vincent</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/30/1966 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>05/22/2023 04:55:05</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A455</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Alleman</LastName>
               <FirstName>George</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Vincent</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/30/1966 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>A455</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/22/2023 04:55:05</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1522</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sappington</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Gambrills</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21054</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1057</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.678381</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.081993</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 14:12:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 14:12:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 14:12:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 14:12:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/23/2023 14:04:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5911</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/23/2023 14:04:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>