<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-018849</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/27/2023 00:29:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/27/2023 00:29:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/27/2023 00:11:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/27/2023 00:11:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/Accident</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/27/2023 00:29:11</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5364</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 12:04:15</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>GEORGIA AVE/ E 495 TO S 97 RAMP</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>623451</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/27/2023 00:29:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 02:24:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>623451</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>495</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Capital Beltway</StreetName>
         <City>Silver Spring</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20901</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetNumber>97</CrossStreetNumber>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>AVE</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-77.040629</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.013268</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/27/2023 00:29:09</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/27/2023 00:29:09</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/06/2023 08:13:00</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/27/2023 00:29:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:53:39</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MSP marked patrol vehicle N-5 in-car camera/body camera operational&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defendant: Ever Alexis Portillo Perez&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date of Birth: 11/25/1995&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maryland Identification Card: C62416918&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date of Arrest: 05/27/2023&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time of Arrest: 0049 hours&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUI #: 23-122 (Rockville Barrack)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRAINING/CERTIFICATIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I am trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I am trained and certified to conduct preliminary breathalyzer tests by the Maryland State Police.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I am trained and certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.)&amp;nbsp; through the Maryland State Police&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On May 27th, 2023 at approximately 0011 hours, I, Trooper Yarbrough (#7291) of the Maryland State Police Rockville Barrack was dispatched to the ramp from northbound Georgia ave to the I/L 495 for a bumper in the roadway. Upon my arrival I noticed a gray bumper sitting on the ramp with dirt, rocks, and debris. The bumper was displaying Maryland Registration 14039CL which came back to a gray Dodge Charger. There was no vehicle in the immediate vicinity of the bumper. While I was out with the bumper on the ramp I remembered seeing a vehicle on the I/L 495 at Colesville road on the right shoulder missing a bumper approximately 15 minutes prior. I removed the bumper from the roadway and went to the area of the I/L 495 at Colesville road. Upon my arrival in te area I noticed a gray Dodge Charger missing its rear bumper disabled on the right shoulder.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I made contact with the driver, who was sitting in the driver&amp;#39;s seat of the charger with te engine running. I smelled&amp;nbsp;a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his person. I identified the driver as Ever Alexis Portillo Perez (H/M DOB: 07/25/1995) by his Maryland Identification Card and passport (C62416918). While talking to the driver, I observed Mr. Portillo Perezs&amp;#39; eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. Mr. Portillo Perez was&amp;nbsp;lethargic and was slow to perform any moving action.&amp;nbsp;When asked about the consumption of alcohol, Mr. Portillo Perez stated he had a few beers.&amp;nbsp;I than asked Mr. Portillo Perez to&amp;nbsp;perform some Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Mr. Portillo Perez agreed to take the tests.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;While talking to Mr. Portillo Perez, in an ambient environment, I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I requested Mr. Portillo Perez to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The tests were performed in front of my patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp;The surface was dry, level, and clear from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of the streetlamps, my patrol vehicles headlights, and flashlight. The patrol vehicle&amp;#39;s forward emergency lights were deactivated during all tests. Mr. Portillo Perez was positioned in a manner to ensure that&amp;nbsp;passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. Mr. Portillo Perez appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any physical injuries. I asked his the following questions:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Physical Injuries: None.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Medical Conditions: None&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Medications: None&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Glasses and/or Contacts: Glasses&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The first test performed was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Mr. Portillo Perezs&amp;#39; eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head stationary while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with only his eyes until told to stop. Mr. Portillo Perez acknowledged he understood the test. His pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. Mr. Portillo Perez moved his head multiple times from the stationary position to follow the stimulus.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of Smooth Pursuit: Present in both eyes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Onset of nystagmus prior to 45-degrees.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WALK AND TURN (6/8 clues observed):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Prior to Mr. Portillo Perez performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted.&amp;nbsp;Mr. Portillo Perez was instructed to place his left foot on an imaginary straight line and place his right foot on the same line in front of his left foot with his&amp;nbsp;heel touching his&amp;nbsp;toe.&amp;nbsp;Mr. Portillo Perez was to place his&amp;nbsp;hands flat at his&amp;nbsp;sides and to remain in that position until told to begin.&amp;nbsp;Mr. Portillo Perez was instructed to take nine (9) steps on the straight line touching heel to toe on every step.&amp;nbsp;Mr. Portillo Perez was told to keep his&amp;nbsp;hands flat at his&amp;nbsp;side, keep his&amp;nbsp;eyes focused on his&amp;nbsp;feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step,&amp;nbsp;Mr. Portillo Perez was demonstrated and explained to keep his&amp;nbsp;lead foot on the straight line, and to take a series of small steps around his&amp;nbsp;lead foot with his&amp;nbsp;rear foot to turn completely around.&amp;nbsp;Mr. Portillo Perez was then explained and demonstrated that the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series of nine (9) steps.&amp;nbsp;Mr. Portillo Perez was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed.&amp;nbsp;Mr. Portillo Perez was instructed to keep his&amp;nbsp;hands down by his&amp;nbsp;side, look down at his&amp;nbsp;feet, and count each step out loud. After explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked&amp;nbsp;Mr. Portillo Perez if he completely understood the instructions, and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; The results were as follows:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Mr. Portillo Perez missed heel to toe on all the 4th and 6th steps on the&amp;nbsp;second set of instructed nine steps.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Mr. Portillo Perez performed an improper turn.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Mr. Portillo Perez could not maintain balance during the instruction stage.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Mr. Portillo Perez took 8&amp;nbsp;steps on the first and 8&amp;nbsp;steps on the&amp;nbsp;second set of instructed nine steps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Mr. Portillo Perez stopped the test before and after making the turn.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Mr. Portillo Perez attempted to start the test too soon.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Prior to Mr. Portillo Perez performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Mr. Portillo Perez was instructed to stand with his&amp;nbsp;heels together and hands down by his&amp;nbsp;sides while the instructions were given. Mr. Portillo Perez was instructed to not begin the test until he was instructed to do so, and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to keep his&amp;nbsp;hands down by his&amp;nbsp;side and raise the foot of his&amp;nbsp;choice off the ground approximately six inches. While his&amp;nbsp;foot was raised, he was to keep his&amp;nbsp;leg straight, watch his&amp;nbsp;raised foot, and count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Mr. Portillo Perez was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; Mr. Portillo Perez raised his left foot. The results were as follows:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Mr. Portillo Perez put his foot down on multiple&amp;nbsp;occasions.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Mr. Portillo Perez swayed back and forth.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Mr. Portillo Perez stopped the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I offered Mr. Portillo Perez a preliminary breath test and he refused.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARREST:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; At 0049 hours Mr. Portillo Perez was placed under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of&amp;nbsp; Alcohol. A search incident to arrest revealed that Mr. Portillo Perez had no contraband on his&amp;nbsp;person and nothing was in his&amp;nbsp;mouth. Mr. Portillo Perez was then transported to the Maryland State Police Rockville Barrack for further processing.&amp;nbsp;Mr. Portillo Perez was advised of his&amp;nbsp;DR-15 Advice of Rights in Spanish utilizing the MVA website recording. Additionally, Mr. Portillo Perez was provided a copy and shown both the Spanish and English side to read over.&lt;br /&gt; At 0156 hours (05/27/2023), Mr. Portillo Perez accepted to submit to the chemical breath test. Results were .12 BAC.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Probable Cause Search/Processing:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Upon my approach of the vehicle a strong odor of marijuana was emitting from the vehicle.&amp;nbsp;A probable cause search of the vehicle resulted in the contraband listed below. I recognized the contraband to be marijuana based on my training, knowledge, and experience from the Maryland State Police Academy and prior CDS arrests. The contraband was located in the center console of the vehicle. The driver was issued a Civil Citation at the scene (1Z46654000).&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Processing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; One Ziploc baggie containing 6 grams of suspected marijuana in a metal blue grinder.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; One Ziploc baggie containing suspected marijuana CBD wax.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The contraband was transported to Maryland State Police Rockville Barrack and processed per MSP policy. Property #&amp;#39;s: P-340144.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELEASE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Mr. Portillo Perez was issued all appropriate citations and paperwork. Mr. Portillo Perez was released to a sober driver.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I request the case be closed by arrest. All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:33:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7291</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 05:27:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Satterfield</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daryea</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7216</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Yarbrough</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7291</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Saucerman</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4873</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Yarbrough</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7291</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Yarbrough</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7291</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508283</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15408</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/27/2023 00:49:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15408</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:25:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7291</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 02:29:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508283</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15436</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/27/2023 00:49:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15436</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:25:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7291</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 02:29:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508283</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/27/2023 00:49:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:25:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7291</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 02:29:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508283</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/27/2023 00:49:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:25:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7291</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 02:28:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508283</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/27/2023 00:49:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:25:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7291</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 02:28:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508283</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/27/2023 00:49:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:25:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7291</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 02:27:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508283</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/27/2023 00:49:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:25:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7291</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 02:27:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508283</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/27/2023 00:49:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:25:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7291</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 02:26:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:25:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378198</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Portillo Perez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ever</FirstName>
               <DOB>11/25/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 02:16:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P634</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E160</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Portillo Perez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ever</FirstName>
               <DOB>11/25/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P634</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E160</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 02:16:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>201</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>300</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3795</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:31:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:31:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:31:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:25:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7291</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 02:25:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153486</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 02:25:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7291</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 02:25:42</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2C3CDXBG0EH208990</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CHA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>14039CL</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/30/2023 23:52:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7291</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/30/2023 23:52:14</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>15</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Blue metal grinder with suspected marijuana.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249623</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>6</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7291</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/30/2023 23:52:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7291</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/30/2023 23:52:49</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>15</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Suspected marijuana CBD wax. </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>249624</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>XX</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>