<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-014106</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/21/2023 03:25:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/21/2023 03:25:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/21/2023 02:52:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/21/2023 02:52:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The driver was placed under arrest for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/21/2023 03:25:06</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0104</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 10:54:32</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>691585</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/21/2023 03:25:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 05:57:27</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>691585</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Washington Ave @ Crain</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>La Plata</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20646</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.980588</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.568314</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/21/2023 03:25:03</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/21/2023 03:25:03</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/24/2023 04:59:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/21/2023 03:25:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:28</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p&gt;In-Car Camera and Body Worn Camera Operational&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Karissa Liana Johnson&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 02/22/1990&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 04/21/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 0319 hours&lt;br /&gt; MD SDX: MD-10273734272&lt;br /&gt; DUI #: 23-075&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Officer&amp;rsquo;s Training/Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;* Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; * Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement through the Charles County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Office.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;*Repeat Offender* No&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Scene Processing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; During the search incident to arrest, I located one hand-rolled cigarette containing suspected cannabis in Johnson&amp;#39;s right front short pocket.&amp;nbsp;During the wing span search of the vehicle, I located one multi-colored glass smoking device containing suspected cannabis on the passenger seat. The item was recovered and placed on property held P-343718 and held according to MSP policy and procedure.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Property:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The following items were stored in a heat sealed bag, and stored on MSP Forms 67 and 63 according to MSP policy:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Item A: One clear ziplock bag labeled A containing one hand-rolled cigarette containing suspected cannabis. Weight: 0.7 grams.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Item B: One clear ziplock bag labeled B containing one multi-colored glass smoking device containing suspected cannabis. Weight: Residue.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 04/21/2023, at approximately 0252 hours, I (TFC Cress #7102) was traveling on S/B Rt. 301, in the area of Marshall Corner Rd., in my unmarked vehicle, H-08, in lane 2. While traveling S/B, I observed a gray Sport Utility Vehicle (SUV) traveling in front of me on S/B Rt. 301, in the area of Marshall Corner Rd. in lane 2. The gray SUV continued to increase speed. On S/B Rt. 301, near Hickory Ln., I observed the gray SUV to be traveling above the posted speed limit of 55 MPH. I activated my Kustom Golden Eagle II (Serial # 50003504) and obtained a speed of 90 MPH in a posted 55 MPH zone. Without losing sight of the vehicle, I activated my emergency equipment and stopped the gray Buick Enclave, bearing MD registration 3DY7836, on Washington Ave., near Rt. 301, La Plata, Charles&amp;nbsp;County, Maryland.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I approached the vehicle on the driver&amp;#39;s side and made contact with the female&amp;nbsp;driver. I advised the driver the reason for the stop and asked to see her driver&amp;rsquo;s license and vehicle registration. The driver was identified through her Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license as, Karissa Liana Johnson AA/F DOB: 02/22/1990). I asked Johnson why she was traveling at 90 MPH and Johnson stated &amp;quot;I was just trying to get home&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;I was out late&amp;quot;, and &amp;quot;I was going fast&amp;quot;. Johnson advised she was traveling from Annapolis where she was &amp;quot;hanging out with some girlfriends&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp;While speaking with Johnson, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from inside the vehicle&amp;#39;s driver/passenger compartment area and observed Johnson to have glassy and bloodshot eyes.&amp;nbsp;Due to the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle, I asked Johnson if she consumed any alcoholic beverages and Johnson stated &amp;quot;not in the car, I did have some earlier&amp;quot;. I asked Johnson when did she consume her last alcoholic beverage and Johnson stated &amp;quot;probably around 1am&amp;quot;. I&amp;nbsp;advised Johnson I needed her to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests to which she complied.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder in front of Johnson&amp;#39;s vehicle. It was dry and approximately 60 degrees with clear&amp;nbsp;skies. I asked Johnson the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Medical Conditions - None&lt;br /&gt; Injuries - None&lt;br /&gt; Medication - None&lt;br /&gt; Concussion - None&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As she&amp;nbsp;spoke, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath. Johnson stated she consumed &amp;quot;three lemon crushes&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (4/6 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Johnson&amp;#39;s eyes. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Her pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. She&amp;nbsp;was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. Johnson was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash; None&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;4.)&amp;nbsp; Vertical Nystagmus &amp;ndash; None&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;WALK AND TURN (1/8 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to Johnson performing the test, I&amp;nbsp;explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Johnson was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. She was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. She&amp;nbsp;was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. She&amp;nbsp;was instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Johnson was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Johnson was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. She&amp;nbsp;was instructed&amp;nbsp;once she began the test she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her sides, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. Johnson was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;/u&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Nothing observed.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;/u&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Johnson stopped after her ninth step.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Turn:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Performed correctly.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Nothing observed.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Prior to Johnson performing the test, I&amp;nbsp;explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. She&amp;nbsp;was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Johnson was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated,&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;/u&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Nothing observed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Balance and Count Stage:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Johnson put her foot down on second 16 and kept it down for 3 seconds. Johnson raised her arms more than six inches from her sides on seconds 17 through 20.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Johnson counted up to 16 after 30 seconds had elapsed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I offered Johnson to take the Preliminary Breath Test to which she complied. Preliminary Breath Test result was .15 BrAC.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Johnson was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;-Strong odor of alcoholic beverage on breath&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;-Glassy and bloodshot eyes&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;-Clues during Field Sobriety Testing&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Admission to alcohol consumption&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Positive preliminary testing.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Due to the number of observations, I concluded Johnson was driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely.&amp;nbsp; At approximately 0319 hours, I placed Johnson under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. During a search incident to arrest, I located one hand rolled cigarette containing suspected cannabis in Johnson&amp;#39;s right front short pocket. Johnson was placed in the front passenger seat of my MSP assigned vehicle, H-08, per department policy. During a wing span search of the vehicle, I located one multicolored glass smoking device on the passenger seat. Johnson and the CDS was transported to the Maryland State Police La Plata&amp;nbsp;Barrack for processing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Johnson was charged on a Uniform Civil Citation for possession of personal use amount of cannabis (5Z46651533). This was Johnson&amp;#39;s first Civil Citation for personal use amount of cannabis.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I was able to recognize the CDS through my training, knowledge, and experience in the Maryland State Police Academy and prior drug arrests.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;The DR-15 Advice of Rights was read to Johnson at which time she elected to submit to the Intoximeter Test at 0346 hours. The test was administered by Cpl. Manning #6421 at 0411 hours. The test result was&amp;nbsp;.12 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;INTOXIMETER RESULT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;***.12 BrAC***&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Johnson made a few disparaging remarks to myself and a fellow trooper.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Johnson was transported to the Charles County Detention Center and released to their custody. Johnson was given copies of all pertinent paperwork.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Charles&amp;nbsp;County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:55:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 03:14:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fuller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7440</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alphrin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5237</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cress</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jon-Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7102</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503520</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/21/2023 03:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 05:58:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 05:58:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503520</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/21/2023 03:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 00:56:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 00:59:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503520</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/21/2023 03:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 00:57:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 00:59:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503520</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/21/2023 03:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 00:58:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 00:59:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503520</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/21/2023 03:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 00:58:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 00:58:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503520</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/21/2023 02:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:00:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 01:00:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503520</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15647</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/21/2023 02:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15647</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:00:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 01:00:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503520</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>CIVIL 5-601</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/21/2023 03:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>CIVIL 5-601</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:10:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 01:10:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:09:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374964</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Karissa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Liana</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/22/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/21/2023 23:18:37</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Karissa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Liana</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/22/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/21/2023 23:18:37</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9601</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Charles</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>La Plata</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20646</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.976002</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.570179</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>868</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7742</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:09:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:09:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:09:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:09:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:09:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 05:58:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 05:58:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152219</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:20:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 01:20:20</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/21/2023 23:12:55</DateOfInfo>
         <DateOfInfo>04/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>KL4CJASB0KB764303</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>BUIC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ENC</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3DY7836</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3DY7836</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehConditionCode>F</VehConditionCode>
         <VehDamageCode>0</VehDamageCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:13:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 01:13:42</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One hand rolled cigarette containing suspected cannabis.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>247633</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.7</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:15:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 01:15:55</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One multi colored glass smoking device containing suspected cannabis residue.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>247634</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.01</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7102</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 01:16:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7102</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 01:16:55</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One multi colored glass smoking device.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>100</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>247635</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>MUL/COL</PrimaryColor>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>