<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-024509</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/08/2023 22:41:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/08/2023 22:41:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/08/2023 22:18:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/08/2023 22:18:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 22:41:09</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2864</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 09:02:03</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN HWY/ EDEN ALLEN RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>529687</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 22:41:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/28/2023 16:35:32</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>529687</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Eden</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.650679</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.281474</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EDEN ONE STOP</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>14604-14840 OCEAN HWY / 31708-31724 EDEN ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>14605-14839 OCEAN HWY / 31708-31724 EDEN ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB 13 SO EDEN ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 OCEAN HWY / 0-0 EDEN ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/08/2023 22:41:08</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/08/2023 22:41:08</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/07/2023 09:00:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/08/2023 22:41:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:29:10</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Camera&amp;rsquo;s operation, stop recorded via body camera and X-21 in car camera.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Tymeka Michelle Sturgis&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 05/20/1982&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 07/08/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 2229 hours&lt;br /&gt; MD SDX: S-362-809-603-381&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;DUI #: 23-95-035&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;On Saturday, July 8, 2023 at approximately 2218 hours, I, Trooper First Class Hunt #6939, was sitting stationary at the intersection of southbound Route 13 and Eden Allen Road. At that time, I observed a vehicle traveling southbound Route 13 in lane one that was approaching my location that had an inoperative passenger side headlight. I got behind the vehicle in lane one and observed the vehicle to be a red Nissan Altima bearing Maryland Registration &amp;ldquo;8DB8419&amp;rdquo;. I activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the Altima, southbound Route 13 south of Eden Allen Road. The vehicle stopped on the right shoulder. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;I made contact with the driver via the drivers side of the vehicle, I stated who I was and that the traffic stop was being audio and visually recorded. I advised the driver that the reason for the traffic stop was because she had an inoperable passenger side headlight to which she immediately stated, &amp;ldquo;Do I? this is the third time this week I have went through this.&amp;rdquo; I then requested her driver&amp;rsquo;s license and registration to which she complied. The driver was identified by her Maryland Driver&amp;rsquo;s License as, Tymeka Michelle Sturgis (DOB:05/20/1982, B/F). I then asked Sturgis if the address was her current address and she stated that it was not but provided me with her current address. I asked Sturgis if she was going back home to which she stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; While speaking with Sturgis at the driver&amp;rsquo;s side of her vehicle, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle and her breath and person. I also observed her eyes to be bloodshot, glassy and watery and her speech to slurred. I asked Sturgis how many alcoholic beverages she had consumed prior to driving and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Huh?&amp;rdquo; I then asked again and she stared straight forward and stated, &amp;ldquo;Um, I just had like a seltzer.&amp;rdquo; I then asked Sturgis how long ago it was that she had consumed the seltzer and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Um, three hours ago.&amp;rdquo; While speaking with Sturgis I also observed a blue &amp;ldquo;Solo&amp;rdquo; cup on the passenger seat with ice in it. I then advised Sturgis that I would be back with her momentarily and returned to my vehicle and requested that another unit respond to my location. Within minutes of my request, Trooper Revel arrived on scene to assist. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;A check&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt; through the MVA database revealed that Sturgis license was valid in Maryland. Upon Trooper Revel arriving on scene, I made my second approach to Sturgis&amp;rsquo; vehicle and requested that Sturgis exit the vehicle. Upon arriving at Sturgis vehicle, I observed that she had freshly lit a cigarette and was drinking Gatorade. Sturgis used the driver&amp;rsquo;s side door to assist her in exiting the vehicle and stated, &amp;ldquo;I just had like a little seltzer beer.&amp;rdquo; While speaking with Sturgis at the front of her vehicle, I again detecte the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. I asked Sturgis what kind of seltzer she had consumed and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Um, White Claw.&amp;rdquo; I then asked Sturgis how long ago she had consumed the White Claw and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Like three and a half hours ago.&amp;rdquo; I asked Sturgis where she had consumed the beverage and she stated, &amp;ldquo;At a friends house in Fruitland.&amp;rdquo; Sturgis then stated that she &amp;ldquo;Had to pee so bad.&amp;rdquo; I asked Sturgis if she would perform standardized field sobriety to which she agreed. &amp;nbsp;I asked Sturgis on a scale of 1-10 where she felt she would rank her level of intoxication to which she stated, &amp;ldquo;Not no 10, maybe like a 3.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of Route 13. The surface was level and free from any debris. The weather was clear and approximately 77 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of the vehicles headlights as well as my flashlight. Sturgis was positioned facing away from any of the emergency vehicles. My patrol vehicle&amp;rsquo;s emergency lights were deactivated during all tests as were the other emergency vehicles on scene. Sturgis did not display any major visible injuries when walking from her vehicle. Sturgis was wearing Jean shorts, a dark blue shirt with a yellow strip on the sleeves and a black sneakers.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Sturgis the following questions:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Medical Conditions &amp;ndash; Edema in her legs.&lt;br /&gt; Injuries &amp;ndash; None&lt;br /&gt; Medication &amp;ndash; None. After completing the walk and turn test Sturgis stated she takes medication for the fluid in her legs and the pain.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sturgis was not wearing glasses at the time of the stop.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Sturgis&amp;rsquo; eyes. Sturgis was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. I observed Sturgis&amp;rsquo; pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. Sturgis was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. Sturgis was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;I asked Sturgis if she was able to see the tip of my pen and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; I then asked Sturgis to use her right index finger and touch the tip of my pen, and she complied.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash;Present in both eyes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Vertical Nystagmus - not present&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Sturgis was reminded on 3 separate occasions to keep her head straight and move her eyes and her eyes only.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Prior to Sturgis performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Sturgis was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Sturgis was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Sturgis was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Sturgis was instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Sturgis was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Sturgis was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Sturgis was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her sides, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. Sturgis was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Nothing to repot. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Walking Stage (1st Nine):&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Sturgis stepped off line to the right on steps 5, 6, 7, and8. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;2.) Sturgis missed heel to toe by more than one inch on steps 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, and 8. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;3.) Sturgis stopped while walking at step 9 to ask for instructions as to what to do next. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Turn: Turn completed unsatisfactory. Sturgis used both feet to turn. &amp;nbsp;Sturgis turned to her right and faced lane two. Sturgis was reminded to face the direction she had came from. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Sturgis missed heel to toe by more than one inch on steps 1 through 9. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clue observed)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Prior to Sturgis performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Sturgis was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, one thousand-three) and to continue the test until told to stop. Sturgis was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Sturgis kept her left foot planted and raised her right foot.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Nothing to report.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Sturgis put her foot down on counts 1004 and 1007. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;2.) Sturgis raised her hands by more than 6 inches from her side throughout the entire test. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;At count 1007 Sturgis stated that it hurt her legs to continue. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;While on scene, Sturgis elected to submit to a preliminary breath test with results of .11 BRAC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Upon completing standardized field sobriety tests I again asked Sturgis how long ago her last drink was to which she stated, &amp;ldquo;Three and a half hours ago.&amp;rdquo; I then asked Sturgis if she had anything to eat today and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Not since lunch time.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ARREST&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Sturgis was driving a motor vehicle under the influence:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from vehicle/breath.&lt;br /&gt; * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Admitting to consuming alcoholic beverages.&lt;br /&gt; * Clues during standardized field sobriety testing.&lt;br /&gt; * Positive preliminary testing&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to the number of observations, I concluded Sturgis was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 2239 hours, I placed Sturgis under arrest for driving while under the influence. Sturgis then stated &amp;ldquo;Just for one white claw?&amp;rdquo; Sturgis then requested that we get her purse and cellphone from her vehicle. Sturgis was placed in the front passenger seat of my vehicle. While on scene, Sturgis was read the DR-15 Advice of Rights in English on 7/8/2023. At approximately 2252 hours, elected to refuse to submit to the breath test. While Trooper Revel retrieved the items she had requested from her vehicle, he advised me that there was an unopened White Claw in plain view on the passenger seat. The vehicle was tagged, locked and remained on the shoulder of the road. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;A secondary search was conducted upon arrival at the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack and revealed no contraband. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;INTOXIMETER RESULT:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;REFUSAL &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;While being processed at the Princess Anne Barrack, Sturgis openly stated that she had consumed a large White Claw, not a small one. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Sturgis was provided with all the pertinent paperwork and released to a sober driver.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;All events occurred in Somerset County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 18:42:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6939</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/03/2023 02:11:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Revel</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7146</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wright</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7521</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hunt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colbey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6939</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513949</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/08/2023 22:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 18:28:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6939</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/28/2023 18:28:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>41</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 18:33:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:09</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>255568</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sturgis</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tymeka</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/20/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/16/2019 13:23:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S362</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sturgis</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tymeka</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/20/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S362</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/16/2019 13:23:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11344 </StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>San Domingo</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Mardela Springs</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21837</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.727508</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.509394</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>909</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Clarke</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Pocomoke City</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>2181</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.574087</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.069861</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>603</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2406</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/16/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 18:33:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 18:33:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6939</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 18:28:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6939</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/28/2023 18:28:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>