<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-043570</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/10/2023 01:21:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/10/2023 01:21:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/10/2023 01:01:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/10/2023 01:01:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>12/10/2023 02:30:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>Jason Thomas Stitely Jr. was arrested for DUI/DWI. 23-96- 342.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 01:21:45</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1464</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/26/2023 12:58:32</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN EXPY/ RACETRACK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 01:21:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 03:56:40</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>EXPY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.170578</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.38053</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 E/O 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB/ 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 PRIOR 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MERGING OFF OF 90 INTO OCEAN PINES</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB BETWEEN BRIDGE AND OCEAN PINES EXIT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB PAST 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11083-11086 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1296-1352 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/10/2023 01:21:43</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/10/2023 01:21:43</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 18:28:01</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 01:21:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:19</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;DUI Folder # 23-96-342&lt;br /&gt; SUSPECT: Jason Thomas Stitely Jr.&lt;br /&gt; LICENSE # MD-10272359981&lt;br /&gt; DUI CITATION # 42F0VPH&lt;br /&gt; SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER: No&lt;br /&gt; ACCIDENT INVOLVED: No&lt;br /&gt; VIDEO: Maryland State Police; Axon Evidence Video ID #: 23MSP043570. BWC Utilized.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - I am trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).&lt;br /&gt; - I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of 2021.&lt;br /&gt; - I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of 2020.&lt;br /&gt; - I have apprehended more than 100 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;NARRATIVE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;-PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION-&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 12-10-2023 at approximately &amp;nbsp;0101 hours, I (TFC Pinto #7212), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating unmarked MSP vehicle V-9 in the area of Maryland Route 90 westbound near Mile Marker 8 at the base of the Isle of Wight Bay Bridge (Ocean Pines). I was stationary, monitoring all westbound traffic, with my driver&amp;rsquo;s door window open. At that time, I visually observed a vehicle traveling westbound on the Isle of Wight Bay Bridge, through my rear-view mirror, and &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;audibly heard the sound of a vehicle striking the rumble strips&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; on the bridge. I observed the same vehicle appeared to be traveling above the posted speed limit. Using my Golden Eagle II radar unit (serial # DE-11799), in rear stationary mode, I obtained a speed of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;68 MPH in the posted 55 MPH Zone.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; The vehicle was the only vehicle in the rear radar beam at the time the speed was obtained. Once the same vehicle &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;passed my location, I observed it to be a gold Honda passenger car traveling westbound of my location. I safely entered the roadway and made the following observations on the same vehicle:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;MD RT 90 EAST OF MD RT 589 TO MD RT 589&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. The vehicle continued to travel above the maximum posted speed limit by traveling 65, 66, and 68 MPH in a posted 55 MPH zone. The speeds were obtained by using Golden Eagle II radar unit (serial # DE-11799) in front same direction mobile mode. The vehicle was the only vehicle was the only vehicle in the front radar beam when speeds were obtained.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;TRAFFIC STOP&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I activated the emergency lights to my patrol vehicle, initiating a traffic stop on Maryland Route 90 at Maryland Route 589. The vehicle was a gold Honda Accord bearing Maryland registration 9FC4764. The vehicle came to a stop on Maryland Route 90 at Maryland Route 589.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;-PHASE II PERSONAL CONTACT-&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the driver via the passenger side door, and I immediately smelled the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. I explained the reason for the stop and the driver handed me his license. I asked the driver for the registration and he handed me an old temporary Maryland registration. I advised the driver that he was handing me a temporary registration. I advised the driver that I observed his vehicle registration to the back of the glove box. The driver was identified as Jason Thomas Stitely Jr. (W/M 08/26/1994) by his Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license. &amp;nbsp;I asked Stitely if he lived at the Showell address on his license and he responded, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; I asked Stitely where he was traveling to and he responded, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m headed home.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;I asked Stitely where he was traveling from and he responded,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Well I was in Ocean City, I was taking my friends home, um they were at Fager&amp;rsquo;s, I dropped them off in West Ocean City, came back up state, um trying to get home.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;I asked Stitely how many alcoholic beverages he consumed, and he replied, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;I had one a long long time ago, I promise, I do not drink a alcohol.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As Stitely spoke, I made the following observations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. I intentionally observed his eyes to be&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;glassy and bloodshot&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Stitely&amp;rsquo;s &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;speech was slurred.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. &amp;nbsp;Stitely was wearing a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;purple wristband&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;on her right wrist with the writing &amp;ldquo;Fager&amp;rsquo;s Island&amp;rdquo; on it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. Stitely advised he consumed one (1) alcoholic beverage before driving.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Stitely.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I later returned to the Honda and requested Stitely to exit the vehicle and walk to the front of his vehicle to which he complied. While at the front of my patrol vehicle, I continued to speak with Stitely and advised him that I wanted to put him through Standardized Field Sobriety Tests and he agreed to submit to tests.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; During my interaction with Stitely in front of his vehicle, I asked him the following and he responded with the following:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. I asked Stitely how many alcoholic beverages he consumed this evening, and he replied,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Tonight Total Two, .&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. I asked Stitely where he consumed the alcoholic beverages, and he responded,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;They were at the Purple Moose and the Cork Bar, I had one beer and I had two sodas at the Cork bar. I had one beer and two sodas at the Purple Moose. They were probably at about 4:30 and 5:30 PM.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. I asked Stitely what type of alcoholic beverages he consumed and he replied, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;They were one Natural Light and one Natural Light.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 4. I asked Stitely what time he consumed his last alcoholic beverage, advised him it was currently 0111 hours, and he replied,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Um, honestly probably Seven-thirty at the latest.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As Stitely spoke, I made the following observations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. I detected the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. I observed Stitely eye&amp;rsquo;s to be blood shot and glassy.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;-PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING-&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed in the shoulder area in front of Stitely&amp;rsquo;s vehicle. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s head lamps. Weather was clear. I asked Stitely if he has any physical disabilities, and he replied,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;No, no sir.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;I asked Stitely if he has any medical disabilities, and he stated,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;No sir.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;I asked Stitely if he had any recent injuries, and he replied,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;Not at all.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;I asked Stitely if he was on any medications, and he replied,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;I asked Stitely if he wears glasses or contacts, and he responded,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;No sir.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Stitely was wearing a red Christmas Sweater, blue jeans, and black tennis shoes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Stitely displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. Stitely displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 3. Stitely displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**WALK AND TURN: 2 of 8 clues**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Stitely could not keep his balance while in the instructional stage of the test. Stitely shifted his right foot slightly to the right to catch his balance.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 2. Stitely stopped walking on step 1 during the second series. After turning, he placed his right foot next to his left and stopped before starting second series of steps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**ONE LEG STAND: 1 of 4 clues**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Stitely&amp;rsquo;s body swayed to the left and right between 11 to 20 seconds&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ADDITIONAL TESTING&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**ALPHABET TEST**:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Stitely advised that he had a high school education and that he was capable of reciting the English alphabet and numbers. I instructed Stitely to recite from the letter &amp;#39;F&amp;#39; to the letter &amp;#39;T&amp;#39;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Stitely conducted the alphabet test satisfactorily&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;**COUNT TEST**:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I instructed Stitely to count backwards from 59-36.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Stitely conducted, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&amp;ldquo;59-58-57-56-55-54-53-52-51-50-49-48-47-46-45-44-43-42-41.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;Stitely was instructed to stop at 36 and he stopped at 36.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Stitely the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Stitely refused to submitted to a preliminary breath test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ARREST&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Stitely was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;* Driving vehicle over the maximum posted speed limit. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;* Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;* Eyes glassy and bloodshot.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;* Stitely&amp;rsquo;s speech was slurred at times during our interaction. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;* Admission to consuming two (2) alcoholic beverage prior to operating a motor vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;* Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;* My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I determined that Stitely was impaired by the presence of an alcoholic beverage in his system that adversely affected his ability to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests properly can also adversely affect the person&amp;rsquo;s ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. I placed Stitely under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0121 hours on 12-10-2023.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Stitely was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Stitely was given his Advice of Rights via the audio version of the DR-15 Form (played through the patrol vehicle&amp;#39;s laptop speakers). A copy of the DR-15 Form was placed directly in front of Stitely, in his lap. At the conclusion of the audio version, Stitely refused to submit to the intoximeter test at approximately 0133 hours. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;TRANSPORT&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Stitely was subsequently transported to the Berlin Barrack for processing. During transport, the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Stitely continued to be strong.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;RELEASE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Stitely was provided all forms and traffic citations prior to his release. Stitely was released to a sober driver.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CHARGES&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Stitely was charged with the following citations:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (42F0VPH)&lt;br /&gt; 2. Driving Vehicle While Impaired By Alcohol (42G0VPH)&lt;br /&gt; 4. Negligent Driving (42H0VPH)&lt;br /&gt; 5. Reckless Driving (40V2JPH)&lt;br /&gt; 6. Exceeding the Maximum posted Speed Limit 55 MPH (68/55 MPH Zone) (42K0VPH)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 03:54:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 03:54:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Benjamin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7043</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Drew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533044</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/10/2023 01:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 04:13:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 04:14:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 04:13:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 04:15:44</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>395271</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Stitely</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Thomas</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/26/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>12/14/2023 04:02:21</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S334</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Stitely</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Thomas</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/26/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>S334</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/14/2023 04:02:21</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11710</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Worcester</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Showell</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21862</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1103</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.211509</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.401103</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>513</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0422</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 04:15:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 04:15:44</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 04:15:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 04:15:44</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 04:14:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 04:14:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159836</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7212</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 04:16:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7212</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 04:16:38</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1HGCR2F8XFA143098</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ACCORD</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GLD</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9FC4764</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>12</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>