<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-038590</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/02/2023 02:18:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/02/2023 02:18:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/02/2023 01:55:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/02/2023 01:55:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was stopped for moving violations and was found to be driving under the influence.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/02/2023 02:18:54</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0457</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/12/2023 11:00:42</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FRD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>0-0 US-220 SB EXIT 47 RAMP 8,CUMBERLAND</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>711775</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/02/2023 02:18:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/17/2023 17:18:46</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>711775</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>0-0</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Us-220 Sb Exit 47</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RAMP</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-78.71995</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.67406</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/02/2023 02:18:53</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/02/2023 02:18:53</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>52</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/18/2023 06:55:58</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/02/2023 02:18:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSPQ031</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 11:32:03</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Attachments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DR-15&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; DR-15A&lt;br /&gt; INTOXIMETER REFUSAL SLIP&lt;br /&gt; TRAFFIC CITATIONS&lt;br /&gt; DRIVING RECORD/METERS&lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE REGISTRATION/METERS&lt;br /&gt; PHOTOCOPY OF DRIVERS LICENSE/REGISTRATION&lt;br /&gt; FRONT PHOTO OF SUBJECT&lt;br /&gt; DETENTION LOG&lt;br /&gt; INTOXIMETER WORKSHEET&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The DUI Number for the following incident is 23MSP038590/23-104.&lt;br /&gt; C-19 is equipped with an in-car camera and was operational at the time of the incident.&lt;br /&gt; TFC T. Michael is issued a body camera (00017189) and was operational at the time of the incident.&lt;br /&gt; C-19 is equipped with an in-car radar system, which was functioning and calibrated per MSP policies and standards.&lt;br /&gt; C-19 is a marked police unit.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;VIOLATION (Vehicle in Motion):&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On Thursday, November 2, 2023, at approximately 0155 hours, I was located in a stationary position on the right shoulder of westbound I-68 in the area of the 57-mile marker in Allegany County, Maryland. A lookout was provided by the Maryland State Police - Cumberland Barrack of a maroon passenger car swerving on the roadway by a concerned citizen in the area of the 52-mile marker. I proceeded to attempt to catch up to the vehicle in order to make my own observations. Westbound I-68 east of exit 47, I observed a maroon Saturn Ion passenger vehicle bearing Maryland registration 5EL4682 swerving repeatedly and erratically, across the fast lane and slow lane of travel (shoulder to shoulder) twice.&amp;nbsp; The maroon passenger car drove in the middle (over the white dotted line) separating the fast lane and slow lane. The maroon passenger vehicle drove back into the slow lane and crossed over the solid white fog line onto the right shoulder by more than two tire widths.&amp;nbsp; In the area of exit 47, the maroon passenger vehicle abruptly swerved from the slow lane into the fast lane by half of the car&amp;rsquo;s width before swerving back into the fast lane. The maroon passenger vehicle again crossed the solid white fog line on the right shoulder.&amp;nbsp; The vehicle was identified as a maroon 2004 Saturn Ion bearing Maryland registration, 5EL4682. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;At that time I activated my emergency lights and siren in order to stop the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; The Saturn Ion pulled to the right shoulder approximately .5 mile east of exit 46 (Naves Cross Roads).&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Personal Contact)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I exited my vehicle and conducted a driver side approach and made contact with the driver. &amp;nbsp;I advised the driver that I was a Maryland State Trooper, that he was being audibly and visually recorded and my identification number. &amp;nbsp;I advised the driver why I stopped him.&amp;nbsp; I observed a small, female African American child in the front passenger seat of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; The child was not secured in the required child safety seat or booster seat for her age and/or weight.&amp;nbsp; While speaking to the driver, I observed that he was smoking a freshly lit cigarette.&amp;nbsp; The driver advised the reason for the erratic driving was because his daughter, later identified as Chyna awoke in the front passenger seat (under 8 not secured car seat) and he became distracted with attempting to comfort her.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The driver provided a Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license D-340-357-044-599 identifying himself as Jaden Alexander Dudley, B/M, DOB 07/31/2000.&amp;nbsp; The driver assumed this identity throughout the investigation. &amp;nbsp;While speaking to the driver I detected the strong odor of burnt marijuana, based upon my training, knowledge and experience to be emanating from his breath and person. The driver&amp;#39;s eyes were red/glassy/bloodshot and his speech was soft, slurred and delayed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I returned to my patrol vehicle in order to advise the Maryland State Police and request an additional police unit.&amp;nbsp; Cpl. D. Diehl #5745 (C-26) arrived on scene at approximately 0200 hours.&amp;nbsp; At that time, based on the driving observations, driver observations on initial contact and the strong odor of burnt marijuana, I conducted a second approach to the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; I made contact with the driver and asked him to exit the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; The driver had some initial concerns for his daughter safety and after I assured him that the other Trooper would keep a watchful eye on her, he complied and exited the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; The driver advised that he did not drink any alcoholic beverages, however he did smoke marijuana, &amp;ldquo;one blunt&amp;rdquo; approximately 3 to 4 hours prior to the traffic stop. &amp;nbsp;I asked the driver to conduct the Standardized Field Sobriety Test and he advised he was &amp;ldquo;cool with that.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Pre-Arrest Screening)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I am trained and certified to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. &amp;nbsp;The tests were performed on the right shoulder of westbound I-68 prior to exit 47.&amp;nbsp; The surface of the roadway was flat and free from debris. Note that the area was illuminated by overhead lighting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Defendants Attire:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The driver was wearing jeans and a black &amp;ldquo;hoodie style&amp;rdquo; sweatshirt. The driver was wearing tennis shoes at the time of the stop that he deemed to be comfortable wearing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Physical injuries:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The driver did not advise me of any recent injuries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Medication:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The driver advised that he did not take any prescription medications.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eyesight:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The driver advised that he could see the tip of my finger and did not complain of any vision impairments.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Medical Conditions: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The driver did not advise me of any additional medical conditions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #1 Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The driver stated that he could see the stimulus.&amp;nbsp; I advised the driver that I needed him to follow the stimulus with his eyes and eyes only.&amp;nbsp; I advised the driver that his head was to remain stationary. &amp;nbsp;The stimulus was held 12-15 inches from the driver and just above eye level.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;-&amp;nbsp;The driver had equal pupil size and tracking ability. The driver did not display lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **I had to advise the driver on three occasions throughout the testing to not move his head while following the stimulus. **&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;0 out of 6&lt;br /&gt; Stimulus: Illuminated tip of finger&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #2: Walk and Turn&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The driver was placed in the instructional stage, which was demonstrated to the driver as standing with his right foot in front of the left foot, touching heel-to-toe and arms placed at his sides. The driver was advised not to deviate from the instructional position, and was advised not to begin the test until told do so.&amp;nbsp; I then proceeded to demonstrate the test by taking three heel to toe steps on line, turn around keeping one foot on line, and return three heel to toe steps.&amp;nbsp; I explained to the driver that he would have to take nine heel to toe steps and return taking another nine heel to toe steps. I explained that the three steps I took were for demonstration purposes only.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The driver was not able to maintain the instructional position.&amp;nbsp; After placing the driver into the instructional position, he began to sway and loose balance.&amp;nbsp; The driver had to take a side step and maintained that position throughout the instructional phase.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - Instructional position &amp;ndash; The driver could not maintain the heel to toe position and lost balance.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; First series of nine steps:&lt;br /&gt; 1. Offline&lt;br /&gt; 2. Offline, stopped and restarted the test&lt;br /&gt; 3.&lt;br /&gt; 4. Left arm raised&lt;br /&gt; 5.&lt;br /&gt; 6. Heel/Toe, Offline&lt;br /&gt; 7.&lt;br /&gt; 8.&lt;br /&gt; 9. Stopped&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - The driver took a total of 12 steps&lt;br /&gt; - The driver performed the turn unsatisfactory due to the not keeping the lead foot planted.&amp;nbsp; The driver had to keep both feet shoulder width apart, shuffle stepping while turning in the opposite direction.&lt;br /&gt; - The driver could not recall how to conduct the remainder of the test. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Second series of nine steps:&lt;br /&gt; 1. Heel/Toe&lt;br /&gt; 2. Heel/Toe, Offline&lt;br /&gt; 3. Heel/Toe&lt;br /&gt; 4. Right arm raised&lt;br /&gt; 5.&lt;br /&gt; 6.&lt;br /&gt; 7. Left arm raised&lt;br /&gt; 8. Left arm raised&lt;br /&gt; 9. Left arm raised&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - The driver took a total of 14 steps&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;7 out of 8&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #3 One Leg Stand&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The driver was told to stand with his heels together and arms placed at his sides and instructed not to begin the test until told to do so. The test was explained and demonstrated to the driver by explaining that I wanted him to raise one leg, whichever he felt most comfortable with, approximately six inches off the ground, foot pointed out.&amp;nbsp; The driver was also instructed to keep both legs straight and to keep his eyes on the elevated foot. While holding that position, count aloud, one thousand and one, one thousand and two, one thousand and three, and so forth until told to stop. &amp;nbsp;The driver stated that he understood the instructions and agreed to perform the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - The driver stood on his right foot from approximately 20 seconds then shifted to stand on his left foot for the remainder of the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1 to 10 seconds:&lt;br /&gt; - foot down x2&lt;br /&gt; - swayed&lt;br /&gt; - arms&lt;br /&gt; - hopping&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 10 to 20 seconds&lt;br /&gt; - foot down x1&lt;br /&gt; - swayed&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 20 to 30 seconds&lt;br /&gt; - foot down x2&lt;br /&gt; - swayed&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;4 of 4&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The PBT was not offered.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;ACTION TAKEN/ADDITONAL INVESTIGATION:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Based on the test results the driver was arrested on November 2, 2023, at approximately 0210 hours for driving under the influence. &amp;nbsp;Upon running Dudley, he was wanted (D230119223) and was advised of this during the arrest. &amp;nbsp;The driver was transported to the MSP - Cumberland Barrack for further processing and was issued the warrant prior to be transported to the Allegany County Detention Center in order to be seen by a Commissioner pertaining to the warrant.&amp;nbsp; The driver&amp;rsquo;s identity did come into question, and the driver was asked direct questions pertaining to how old he was and his date of birth.&amp;nbsp; However, based on his level of impairment and his statement &amp;ldquo;I do smoke a lot&amp;rdquo; it was difficult to ascertain if he was lying or severely impaired.&amp;nbsp; The photo of Dudley did give a resemblance to the person in custody and again was difficult to verify.&amp;nbsp; The driver was advised of his DR-15 right and REFUSED the intoximeter test at approximately 0247 hours. &amp;nbsp;Throughout the early morning hours, the driver signed multiple documents (DR-15, DR-15A, &amp;amp; Advice of Rights of Counsel x2) as, Jaden Dudley and maintained that he was in fact Dudley. &amp;nbsp;On November 6, 2023, I was contacted by the MSP - Cumberland Barrack that an individual claiming to be Dudley who advised that he believed somebody was using his identification card that was stolen in order to commit crime. &amp;nbsp;Upon further investigation it was determined that Dudley was not in Allegany County at the time of the incidents.&amp;nbsp; In order to ascertain identity, I investigated the video footage captured on the body camera from the night of the arrest.&amp;nbsp; On initial approach, I identified a distinct tattoo, resembling a skull that I was able to match using prior photos I located.&amp;nbsp; To my knowledge, Jaden Dudley does not have any tattoos on either side of his neck.&amp;nbsp; Further investigation determined that the driver&amp;#39;s true identity is Christopher Leon Love Jr., B/M, DOB 04/11/2002. It was later discovered that Love has unique tattoos on the left and right sides of his neck that matched those observed on the video footage and while in my custody.&amp;nbsp; The mother of the child, identified as Jasmine Rideout was verified to have had a relationship with Love, and they are the parents of Chyna.&amp;nbsp; Per the driver&amp;rsquo;s request, Rideout arrived at the Maryland State Police &amp;ndash; Cumberland Barrack in order to pick up the child.&amp;nbsp; The vehicle that Love was operating was later located at 137 Virginia Avenue where a known relative resides based on previous police involved incidents with Love. Love is currently wanted in multiple counties for felony and misdemeanor crimes.&amp;nbsp; Love has been known in the past to assume other&amp;rsquo;s identities in order to avoid prosecution.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;It is believed that Love is also the perpetrator for the other crime related to warrant (D230119223) that I served.&amp;nbsp; That case, 23-MSP-027509 has since been expunged against Dudley.&amp;nbsp; That case has been re-opened and Love is considered a suspect at this time. &amp;nbsp;Dudley&amp;#39;s identification was confiscated as a result of Love refusing the intoximeter test. &amp;nbsp;I contacted Dudley and advised that I will request the Allegany County States Attorney&amp;#39;s Office to nolle prosequi all the pending traffic violations resulting from this incident.&amp;nbsp; Those citation numbers are 4D70JF9, 4D80JF9, 4D90JF9, 4DB0JF9, 4DC0JF9, 4DD0JF9, 4DF0JF9.&amp;nbsp; Per Dudley&amp;rsquo;s request, the driver&amp;rsquo;s license was destroyed according to the proper policies and procedures after being photographed and scanned.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;A DR-15, DR-15A and citations were issued to Love, however they were at that time completed using Dudley&amp;rsquo;s information.&amp;nbsp; These forms were not sent to the Maryland Motor Vehicle Administration.&amp;nbsp; The forms are in the case files as evidence, however another DR-15A was completed and sent using Love&amp;rsquo;s information.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As a result of the traffic arrest against Love JR., I issued the following citations: 4DG0JF9, 4DH0JF9, 4DJ0JF9, 4DK0JF9, 4DL0JF9, 4DM0JF9, 4DN0JF9, 4DP0JF9, 4DQ0JF9, 4DR0JF9, 4DS0JF9, 4DT0JF9, 4DV0JF9.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On November 9, 2023, I filed an application of charges against Love for the following criminal charge:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;CR 8-301(c) (1) **FRAUD-PER. IDENT. AVOID PROS** **1_1364**&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A warrant, D220305525 has been issued for the immediate arrest of Christopher Leon Love Jr., B/M, DOB 04/11/2002 pertaining to this incident.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Based on the above stated facts, I respectfully request this case remain open pending the suspects arrest.&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Allegany County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 23:09:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/17/2023 23:10:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Diehl</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dwight</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5745</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bennett</LastName>
            <FirstName>Darwin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5492</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528054</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>15</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1364</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/02/2023 01:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1364</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:18:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/17/2023 17:19:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528054</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3187</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/02/2023 01:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3187</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:18:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/17/2023 17:21:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528054</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/02/2023 01:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:18:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/17/2023 17:21:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528054</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/02/2023 01:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:18:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/17/2023 17:21:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528054</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14588</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/02/2023 01:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14588</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:18:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/17/2023 17:21:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:18:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/17/2023 17:23:57</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392962</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Love</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leon</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/11/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>11/14/2023 09:12:12</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Love</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leon</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/11/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>L100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/14/2023 09:12:12</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>137</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Virginia</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>B</SubNumber>
               <City>Cumberland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21502</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3952</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-78.762904</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.636595</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:23:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:23:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:23:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:23:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>23</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:18:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/17/2023 17:22:01</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>384286</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dudley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jaden</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alexander</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/31/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/05/2023 03:19:11</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D340</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J350</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dudley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jaden</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alexander</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/31/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D340</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J350</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/05/2023 03:19:11</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1032</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Concord</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hagerstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21740</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>727</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3575</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:22:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:18:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/17/2023 17:18:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159023</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:18:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/17/2023 17:18:05</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1G8AL52F84Z151304</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2004</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>STRN</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ION</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>MAR</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>MAR</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5EL4682</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>7</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 17:31:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/17/2023 17:31:53</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Maryland Provisional Driver's License belonging to Jaden Alexander Dudley, B/M, DOB 07/31/2000 used by suspect (Love Jr) to assume his identity to avoid prosecution and multiple active warrants.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>557</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256650</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>