<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-042543</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/01/2023 22:00:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/01/2023 22:00:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/01/2023 21:29:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/01/2023 21:29:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI / DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/01/2023 22:00:06</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4792</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 11:02:06</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN HWY/ EDEN ALLEN RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>529687</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/01/2023 22:00:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:29:08</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>529687</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Eden</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.650679</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.281474</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EDEN ONE STOP</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>14604-14840 OCEAN HWY / 31708-31724 EDEN ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>14605-14839 OCEAN HWY / 31708-31724 EDEN ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB 13 SO EDEN ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 OCEAN HWY / 0-0 EDEN ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/01/2023 22:00:03</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/01/2023 22:00:03</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 18:28:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/01/2023 22:00:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt; &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Defendant: Conner Jacob Morgan&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 04/07/2005&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 12/01/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 2158 hours&lt;br /&gt; MD SDX:&amp;nbsp;MD10273097096&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;DUI #: 23-95-066&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;Maryland State Police patrol vehicle X-16 is equipped with an in-car camera system and body worn camera.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Case Number: &lt;u&gt;23-MSP-042543&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Attachments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;DR-015&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;DR-015A&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;MSP 033&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;Citations&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;Intoximeter Results (.21)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Certifications / Training:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Test through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*Certified PBT operator.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*Trained in collision investigation by the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*Certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 12/01/2023 at approximately 2142 hours, I, Trooper Wright #7521 was dispatched to the area of S/B US-13 and Eden Allen Road for a possible intoxicated driver in a darker colored Jeep Cherokee. A 9-1-1 caller, who has been identified as Erik Rafael Sanchez (2/M, DOB&amp;nbsp;09/07/1978), was following directly behind the green Jeep Cherokee while providing 9-1-1 with updated location information. Sanchez was able to provide the Maryland registration plate (4FH2690). Sanchez described the Jeep as being driven erratically and unpredictable. Sanchez stated that the operator of the Jeep swerved between lanes 1 and 2 in a reckless manner multiple times. While following the vehicle on S/B US-13 near &amp;quot;How Sweet It Is Produce Market&amp;quot;, Sanchez observed the vehicle exit the roadway into the shoulder/ditch area a total of three times. Sanchez stated that the Jeep exited the roadway numerous times after that, and nearly struck a pick-up truck that was traveling in lane 2. As the vehicle approached Eden Allen Road, Sanchez observed it exit the roadway and nearly strike a guardrail. As Sanchez approached the red light on S/B US-13 at 822 (Royal Farms), he stated that the Jeep entered the turn lane. However, when the light turned green, the Jeep did not turn and instead used the dedicated turn lane to continue straight on S/B on US-13, nearly striking Sanchez in the process. Sanchez also observed the Jeep strike a yellow snow plow marker that was placed in the median grass area. Upon approaching Mt. Vernon Road, the Jeep brake-checked Sanchez multiple times. Sanchez stated that the Jeep drifted off of the road near the McDonalds at Mt. Vernon Road, and once again at Deal Island Road.&amp;nbsp;It should be noted that all of these actions were conducted during rain with unfavorable light conditions. Sanchez later stated that he is an EMT and Firefighter, and he was concerned for the safety of the driver, as well as other vehicles on the roadway.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Just south of Stewart Neck Road, Sanchez stated that the Jeep had come to a complete stop in the left merge lane on S/B US-13. It was at this point that I was able to make contact with Sanchez and the Jeep Cherokee. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on S/B US-13 at Stewart Neck Road.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I made contact with the operator and sole occupant of the green Jeep Cherokee and advised the operator the reason for the stop. When I asked the operator for his driver&amp;#39;s license, I was given a New Jersey driver&amp;#39;s license displaying the name of Connor Morgan (DOB 04/07/2001). It was later revealed that this was a fraudulent driver&amp;#39;s license with a fictitious name and date of birth. The operator&amp;#39;s correct driver&amp;#39;s license was later revealed to be through the state of Maryland, and he was identified as Conner Jacob Morgan (2/M, DOB 04/07/2005). Morgan had a difficult time retrieving his wallet from his pocket, as well as finding his license. I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle, as well as Morgan&amp;#39;s breath as he spoke. Morgan had slurred speech when answering my questions, as well as bloodshot glassy eyes. I asked Morgan to hand me the keys to his vehicle, to which he agreed. When I asked Morgan if he knew that he was stopped in the middle of an active merge lane, Morgan said that he thought it was the shoulder. Morgan stated that he was trying to find his friend. When I asked Morgan where he was coming from, he stated &amp;quot;Maryland&amp;quot;. Morgan went on to tell me that he was from Maryland two more times, before advising that he was traveling from Cecil County. When I asked Morgan if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages prior to driving, Morgan answered with, &amp;quot;no, I was trying to look for my friend.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; Once again, I asked Morgan if he had consumed any alcohol or taken any drugs prior to operating the vehicle, to which he stated, &amp;quot;no, no&amp;quot;. Morgan then admitted to having consumed one or two beers. I asked Morgan what kind of beer he had consumed, to which he answered with either Bud Light or Natural Light. Based on the following, I respectfully requested Morgan to perform standardized field sobriety testing. Morgan agreed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;Slurred speech&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;Bloodshot glassy eyes&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;Odor of alcohol&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;Actions reported by 9-1-1 caller&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;Admission to consuming alcohol&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;As Morgan stepped out of his vehicle, he attempted to take the keys of the ignition, which had already been removed earlier. As Morgan stepped to the front of his vehicle, I immediately noticed poor balance. As I was speaking to Morgan away from his vehicle, I still detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath as he spoke. I asked Morgan if he wore any contacts or glasses, or if he has any medical conditions or brain injuries that would prevent him from completing the test. Morgan responded with &amp;quot;no&amp;quot;. Morgan stated that he could see the tip of my pen, which was used as a stimulus for the horizontal gaze nystagmus test. Standardized field sobriety testing was performed on the left shoulder of S/B US-13, level and free of debris.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test. The tip of my black pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Morgan&amp;#39;s eyes. Morgan was instructed to look straight ahead and keep his head still while following the stimulus with his eyes only. His pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Morgan had a difficult time following directions. Morgan moved his head throughout the test, and had to be reminded to keep his eyes on the stimulus multiple times.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;1.)&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;2.)&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;3.)&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;HGN (6/6 clues observed)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;Vertical Nystagmus - Present&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WALK AND TURN:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Prior to Morgan performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Morgan was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left and have his feet touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Morgan was instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and remain at his side. Morgan was advised to take nine steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on each step. Morgan was advised to keep his hands flat at his side, keeping his eyes focused on his feet, and to count out every step out loud. On the ninth step, Morgan was instructed to keep his ninth-step foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to the left to turn completely around. Morgan was again instructed the second series of nine steps were to be performed identical to the first nine steps. Morgan was informed that once he started the test he was to not stop until he completed the test, keeping his hands down at his side, counting out loud, looking down at his feet. I asked Morgan if he understood the directions of the test, and he stated &amp;ldquo;yes.&amp;rdquo; Morgan could not remain in position during the instructional phase. Morgan began the test during the instructional phase.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;Starts Too Soon (3x)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;Cannot keep balance (1x)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;Walking Stage (1st Nine)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ol dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;li role="presentation" style="text-align: left;"&gt;Incorrect number of steps (took 10 steps instead of 9)&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li role="presentation" style="text-align: left;"&gt;Does not touch heel-to-toe (every step)&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li role="presentation" style="text-align: left;"&gt;Steps off the line (Step 3)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;Walking Stage (2nd Nine)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ol dir="ltr"&gt;  &lt;li role="presentation" style="text-align: left;"&gt;Does not touch heel-to-toe (every step)&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li role="presentation" style="text-align: left;"&gt;Steps off the line (Steps 2, 4 &amp;amp; 5)&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li role="presentation" style="text-align: left;"&gt;Raises arm for balance (Step 5)&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li role="presentation" style="text-align: left;"&gt;Stops (Steps 5 &amp;amp; 6)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;Walk and Turn (7/8 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Prior to Morgan performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Morgan was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his side while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice approximately 6 inches off the ground. While his leg was raised he was to keep the leg straight, watching his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (One thousand one, one thousand two). He was instructed to continue the test until I told him to stop. I asked Morgan if he had any questions regarding the test, to which he stated &amp;quot;no&amp;quot;. Morgan elected to lift his right foot. Morgan lifted his foot for approximately two seconds, lost balance, and put his foot down. Morgan did not raise his foot again. I instructed Morgan that we would start the test over. Morgan elected to lift his right foot a second time.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;Balance and Counting&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;Sways (Throughout the entire test)&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;Raised arms for balance (Between seconds 1-3, 5-6, 10-12, 26-30)&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;Puts foot down (Between seconds 1-3, 5-6, 8-9, 10-14, 15-27)&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="text-align: left;"&gt;Hops (Between seconds 28-30)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;One Leg Stand (4/4 clues observed)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;Following the standardized field sobriety tests, I offered the preliminary breath test (PBT) to Morgan. Morgan agreed to submit a test. The PBT showed a BrAC of .252. Upon seeing the results of the PBT, I asked Morgan if he had consumed more than one or two beers. Morgan stated, &amp;quot;maybe two or three.&amp;quot; Morgan claimed that he has been driving for the last four hours and had not consumed any alcohol while he was driving.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARREST:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At approximately 2158 hours, I placed Morgan under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. Morgan was placed in the front seat of my patrol vehicle and his seat-belt was applied. While securing Morgan&amp;#39;s vehicle, I observed multiple cases of alcohol and open containers through the rear windshield. Upon further inspection, Morgan was found to be in possession of the following cases of alcohol: Miller Lite, Twisted Tea, Busch Light, Natural Light, and a &amp;quot;party bucket&amp;quot; of Fireball Cinnamon Whisky. Every case was opened and partly consumed. After the vehicle was secured, I transported Morgan to the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack for processing.&amp;nbsp;While at the barrack, I was advised that the only available Intoximeter Technician was located at the Somerset County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Office.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Morgan was placed back in my vehicle and transported to SCSO at approximately 2234 hours. While en route to the Somerset County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Office, Morgan claimed that he was not driving the vehicle. When I told Morgan that he was the only occupant in the vehicle, Morgan stated that someone told him to switch to the driver&amp;#39;s seat prior to my arrival. Morgan then stated that there was four other people in the car with him. Morgan then said, &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ll take the DUI. I didn&amp;#39;t drive, but I&amp;#39;ll take it.&amp;quot; While at the Sheriff&amp;#39;s Office, I played the English audio version of the DR-15 Advice of Rights to Morgan from the MVA website. Morgan agreed to submit to the intoximeter test at approximately 2300 hours. Cpl. K. Corbin #7102 from the Somerset County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Office, who is a certified intoximeter operator, administered the test to Morgan at 2310 hours.&lt;strong&gt; Morgan&amp;#39;s results were found to contain an alcohol concentration of .21 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;During the 20-minute observation period, it was determined that nothing entered Morgan&amp;#39;s mouth prior to the test being administered.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Morgan was transported back to the Maryland State Police Barrack at 2332 hours. Morgan was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and traffic citations, and released to his friend.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;All of the above events occurred in Somerset County, Maryland.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Case closed by Arrest.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 17:14:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 10:07:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wright</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7521</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/01/2023 21:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/01/2023 21:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/01/2023 21:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/01/2023 21:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/01/2023 21:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/01/2023 21:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/01/2023 21:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/01/2023 21:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21457</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/01/2023 21:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21457</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16352</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/01/2023 21:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16352</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532016</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16827</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/01/2023 21:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16827</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:36:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:36:26</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>394370</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Morgan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Conner</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jacob</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/07/2005 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.21025965E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>12/02/2023 15:17:35</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C560</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Morgan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Conner</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jacob</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/07/2005 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.21025965E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>M625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C560</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/02/2023 15:17:35</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>107</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Frank Crane</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>North East</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.945287</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.664197</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:36:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:36:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:36:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 17:02:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 17:02:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>226200</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sanchez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Erik</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Rafael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/07/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/30/2019 20:45:27</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S522</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sanchez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Erik</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Rafael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/07/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S522</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/30/2019 20:45:27</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>28719</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Fairmount</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Westover</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.75917622033896</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.11509240100775</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>843</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>303</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1995</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/30/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 17:02:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 17:02:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 16:34:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159480</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 17:03:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/02/2023 17:03:26</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1J4GW48N04C425964</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2004</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CHK</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>DGR</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4FH2690</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>