<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-044059</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/13/2023 10:52:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/13/2023 10:52:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/13/2023 10:18:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/13/2023 10:18:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driving While Under the InfluenceDriving While Impaired</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 10:52:51</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3033</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 08:59:55</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>715868</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 10:52:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 15:20:58</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>715868</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>26</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I270 Sb</StreetName>
         <City>Frederick</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.3544</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.32132</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/13/2023 10:52:46</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/13/2023 10:52:46</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 17:56:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 10:52:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:19</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;strong&gt;CAR- B-11 // Body worn Camera available // In Car Camera available&lt;br /&gt; Assisting Trooper: D/Sgt B. Stein #3033 // Body worn camera available // In car camera unavailable&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; TFC A. Breakall #7145 // Body worn camera available // In car camera available&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *DUI 23-MSP-044059*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TROOPER FIRST CLASS S. PISKOR #6225&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;MARYLAND STATE POLICE-&amp;nbsp;FREDERICK BARRACK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Defendant: Annette Elvira Ortiz&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Date of Birth: 12/19/1975&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Date of Arrest: 12/13/2023&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Time of Arrest: 1013 hours&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Soundex: 0-632-067-224-962 State: Maryland&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TRAINING CERTIFICATES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-NHSTA TRAINED IN ADMINISTERING FIELD SOBRIETY TEST (SFST)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-GRADUATED WITH DISTINCTION OF THE UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND DUI INSTITUTE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST OPERATOR CERTIFIED&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-CERTIFIED RADAR &amp;amp; LIDAR OPERATOR&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-ADVANCED ROADSIDE IMPAIRED DRIVING ENFORCEMENT TRAINING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-ENHANCED DUI ENFORCEMENT: THE COMPLETE ARREST TRAINING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-APPREHENDED MORE 170 DUI OFFENDERS DURING MY TENURE WITH MSP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-NAMED AN EXPERT IN THE HORIZONTALG GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HARRIS VS STATE)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-FIELD SOBRIETY INSTRUCTOR CERTIFIED&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-CERTIFIED INTOXIMTER EC/IR II OPERATOR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Narrative:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PHASE I, (VEHICLE IN MOTION)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;On 12/13/2023, at approximately 1018 hours, I, TFC S. Piskor #6225 of the Maryland State Police Frederick Barrack, Frederick County, Maryland was on duty in full uniform operating unmarked Maryland State Police unit, &amp;quot;B-11.&amp;quot; I was dispatched to the area of southbound I-270 at the 27 mile marker, Frederick, Frederick County, Maryland for a reported disabled vehicle in the roadway. D/Sgt B. Stein #3033 of the Maryland State Police Frederick Barrack arrived on scene prior to my arrival and advised me over the radio the driver was possibly intoxicated. I arrived on scene and observed a silver Pontiac G6 displaying Maryland registration 9FA3949 in lane #2. I observed the driver was sitting in the driver&amp;#39;s seat with the keys on the roof of the vehicle, and the vehicle was off. I made contact with D/Sgt B. Stein.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;D/Sgt B Stein advised me he arrived on scene and observed a witness on scene and identified the witness on scene as the complainant that reported the incident. D/Sgt B.Stein stated the witness on scene observed her driving and described it to be erratic. D/Sgt advised me when he arrived on scene and made contact with her, he also observed the vehicle to be in lane #2, with the driver sitting in the driver&amp;#39;s seat, keys in the ignition, and the vehicle running. D/Sgt B. Stein stated he immediately detected an odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from inside the vehicle. D/Sgt B. Stein stated he had the female driver remove the keys from the ignition, so she could no longer drive, and place them on the roof of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After talking with D/Sgt B. Stein, I made a driver&amp;#39;s side approach to greet the driver.&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE II, (PERSONAL CONTACT)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;I approached the vehicle from the driver&amp;#39;s side, and requested the driver to step out of the vehicle and respond to the front of my vehicle so we could remove the vehicles from the roadway and onto the shoulder. Once all vehicles were on the shoulder, I placed the female driver, later identified as Annette Elvira Ortiz, (H/F, 12/19/1975) in front of my patrol vehicle, so I could further speak with her. I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her person. I observed her eyes were bloodshot and glassy. I also observed her appearance to be disheveled. Her pants were unbuttoned with no belt. I asked Ortiz what was going on today. Ortiz stated she was going to her job. Ortiz stated she was swerving over the roadway. I asked Ortiz where she was coming from today and she stated, &amp;quot;the Comfort Inn.&amp;quot; I again detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath as she spoke. I again observed her eyes to be bloodshot and glassy and her speech was slurred at times while she spoke.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I asked Ortiz if she was drinking alcohol while at the hotel. Ortiz stated, &amp;quot;Uh, yea.&amp;quot; I asked Ortiz what kind of alcohol did she consume. Ortiz stated, &amp;quot;Vodka.&amp;quot; I asked Ortiz how many Vodka&amp;#39;s did she consume and she stated, &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t know.&amp;quot; I asked Ortiz how long ago her last alcoholic beverage was. Ortiz advised she didn&amp;#39;t know, and proceeded to state she has severe anxiety and her heart was beating fast. I asked Ortiz if she consumed any food today and she stated, &amp;quot;no.&amp;quot; Due to the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath, disheveled appearance, admission to consuming alcoholic beverages, and reports from citizens of her erratic driving, (captured below) I began asking Ortiz medical screening questions, captioned below. After conducting the medical screening questions, I asked Ortiz if she would consent to field sobriety tests, and she agreed.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PHASE III, (PRE-ARREST SCREENING)&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;MEDICAL SCREENING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; **I asked Ortiz the following questions;&lt;br /&gt; *Glasses or Contacts: Ortiz stated &amp;quot;contacts.&amp;quot; Ortiz did have contacts in at this time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; *Prescription medications: Ortiz stated, &amp;quot;depression medication.&amp;quot; Ortiz advised she hasn&amp;#39;t taken her medication recently.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; *Injuries: Ortiz advised she recently had a surgery. I asked Ortiz what kind of surgery was it, and she declined to answer. It was later advised she had a breast reduction surgery.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;****Field sobriety tests were conducted on the right shoulder. The scene was illuminated by my sunlight. I observed Ortiz was wearing jeans and shoes that covered the full foot. No noticeable defects or debris was on the sidewalk at the time of the field sobriety tests.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6) CLUES OBSERVED) (VGN NOT PRESENT)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ***This test was instructed to Ortiz. I used my pen as the stimulus and held the stimulus approximately 12-15 inches away and slightly above her eye level. I advised Ortiz to follow the stimulus with her eyes, and her eyes only. Ortiz was instructed to keep her head still and follow the stimulus with her eyes only. During the test, I observed Ortiz&amp;#39;s pupils to both be equal size and both eyes displayed equal tracking. During the test, the following clues were observed,&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Lack of Smooth pursuit present in both eyes (2 Clues)&lt;br /&gt; *Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation present in both eyes (2 Clues)&lt;br /&gt; *Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 Degrees present in both eyes (2 Clues)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **Midway through performing the HGN test, Ortiz stopped the test and stated, &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m fucked up.&amp;quot; I asked Ortiz if she wanted to keep going, and she again stated, &amp;quot;No I fucked up, I&amp;#39;m fucked up.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; .&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;WALK AND TURN (0/8) CLUES OBSERVED&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This test was not conducted. Ortiz refused to attempt the walk and turn test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;INSTRUCTIONAL STAGE&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;WALKING STAGE:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1st Series of Steps:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **Nothing to report.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;2nd Series of Steps:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **Nothing to report.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND (0/4 CLUES OBSERVED.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This test was not conducted. Ortiz refused to attempt the one leg stand test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; **Nothing to report.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;(BALANCE AND COUNTING STAGE)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Counts 1 through 10:&lt;br /&gt; **Nothing to report.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Count 11 through 20:.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; **Nothing to report.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Counts 21 through 30:&lt;br /&gt; **Nothing to report.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ***Ortiz was offered the Preliminary breath test and Ortiz refused.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I was able to determine Ortiz was under the Influence:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Reports from citizens reporting her erratic driving&lt;br /&gt; -Stopping her vehicle in the middle of the roadway&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -Disheveled appearance, unbuttoned pants, no belt.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person&lt;br /&gt; -Bloodshot and glassy eyes&lt;br /&gt; -Admission to consuming alcoholic beverages&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -Clues observed during HGN test&lt;br /&gt; -Freely and voluntarily stating, &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m fucked up.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Due to the number of observations, I concluded Ortiz was driving under the influence and was unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 1038 hours, I placed Vaughan under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol, and she was placed in my front seat of my patrol vehicle per MSP Policy. A mouth check was also done at this time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **After being placed under arrest, Ortiz requested to go to the hospital. Ortiz stated her heart was beating really fast, and she believed she was having an anxiety attack. I immediately requested an ambulance respond to the scene. While waiting for an ambulance to respond to the scene, I placed Ortiz in the front seat of my patrol vehicle with all cameras activated. D/Sgt B. Stein #3033 and TFC A.Breakall #7145 kept an eye on Ortiz while I recovered her phone and keys from her vehicle. I secured the vehicle and Ortiz requested it be left on the shoulder. Ortiz was advised of the 24 hour rule.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Ortiz was transported to Frederick Health Hospital. Due to Ortiz being transported to the hospital, I requested TFC A. Breakall to meet me at the hospital with a DR-15 Advice of rights form, and a blood kit. Due to MSP Policy, my body camera was not activated for any involvement at the hospital.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;*20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The DR-15 Advice of Rights was read to Ortiz. Ortiz became increasingly mad while I was attempting to read the DR-15. Ortiz screamed at me to stop reading the form to her, and that I was pissing her off. Ortiz walked out of the room while I was reading the form numerous times. Frederick Health Hospital security staff responded to her room to attempt to get her to calm down. Ortiz&amp;nbsp; interrupted me numerous times while attempting to read the form. Ortiz did eventually calm down enough for me to finish reading the form. Ortiz did agree to submit to a blood test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;*BLOOD DRAW:&lt;br /&gt; **&lt;/strong&gt;Ortiz submitted and agreed to a blood draw. Ortiz signed and initialed all forms requesting her signature within the blood draw paperwork. Staff at Frederick Health Hospital had a difficult time attempting to draw blood from Ortiz due to Ortiz having small veins. Nurse NIna Funderburk used our blood kit with the given supplies inside, but was unable to successfully draw blood using our blood kit&amp;#39;s needle. Nurse Nina Funderburk had to perform a sonogram of Ortiz&amp;#39;s arm to successfully find a vein to draw the blood. Once that was done, Nina Funderburk used a needle from the hospital to draw blood at approximately 1216 hours. The blood was placed into MSP blood kit&amp;#39;s tubes and I witnessed the draw. Nurse Nina Funderburk signed all requested documents.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Ortiz was provided all prudent paperwork. I obtained all current contact information for Ortiz. Ortiz was advised she would not be charged until blood results came back with her results. Ortiz was advised if any of her contact information changes to let me know. Ortiz agreed. Ortiz was released from the hospital to the care and custody of a sober adult. Ortiz was advised to not drive for 12 hours.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ** I later made contact with the witness who was on scene when I arrived and was the complainant caller of this incident. I contacted him by phone. I identified him on scene by his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license. I identified him as Michael John Miller 2nd, (W/M, 12/8/1971). I asked Miller to tell me what he saw. Miller stated he was traveling south on I-270, when he observed a silver Pontiac G6 with Maryland registration 9FA3949, perfectly describing Ortiz&amp;#39;s vehicle, traveling at what he believed to be way under the posted speed limit in lane #2. Miller advised he passed the Pontiac and continued driving. Miller stated several minutes later, the silver Pontiac immediately sped past his tow truck at a high rate of speed, and cut off a red dump truck. Miller stated the silver Pontiac nearly struck the red dump truck when she cut in front of him. Miller stated the silver Pontiac began swerving all over the roadway and was unable to maintain her lane. Miller stated he and another citizens who did not remain on scene, were able to successfully box her vehicle in, so she came to a stop in the roadway. Miller stated he walked up to her vehicle to make sure the driver, later identified as Ortiz was okay. Miller stated he also immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from inside her vehicle and person. Miller stated several moments later while he was speaking with Ortiz, D/Sgt B. Stein arrived on scene and completed the actions listed above. This concluded Miller&amp;#39;s statement.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Blood results were sent via U.S Mail with all supporting paperwork. Charges will be pending in this case till the results are obtained.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case status: Open pending blood results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;ALL EVENTS DID OCCUR IN FREDERICK COUNTY, MARYLAND.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; CASE CLOSED BY ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 13:18:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6225</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 15:19:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Breakall</LastName>
            <FirstName>Abram</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7145</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Piskor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6225</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1652</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Piskor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6225</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Piskor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6225</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533536</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/13/2023 10:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 15:14:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6225</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 15:21:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533536</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/13/2023 10:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 15:14:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6225</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 15:22:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533536</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/13/2023 15:23:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 15:14:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6225</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 15:23:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>47</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 15:14:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6225</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 15:26:41</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>81649</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Oritz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Annette</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elvira</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/19/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/28/2015 11:44:59</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>O632</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A530</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Oritz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Annette</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elvira</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/19/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>O632</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A530</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/28/2015 11:44:59</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12043</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Veirs Mill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Silver Spring</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20906</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.077711</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.053571</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>817</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Woodland</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Thurmont</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21788</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.400667</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.614304</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>732</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1031</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>755</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4762</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/28/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 15:26:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6225</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 15:26:41</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 15:26:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6225</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 15:26:41</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 15:26:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6225</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 15:26:41</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>52</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 13:02:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 13:02:26</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>395302</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Miller</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>John</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/08/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/14/2023 13:00:22</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Miller</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>John</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/08/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/14/2023 13:00:22</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4410a</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Urbana</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PIKE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Frederick</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21704</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.380415</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.356023</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>476</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3599</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>644</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3373</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 13:02:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6225</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 13:02:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 13:02:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6225</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 13:02:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 13:02:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6225</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 13:02:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/13/2023 15:21:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6225</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 15:21:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159855</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6225</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 13:08:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6225</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 13:08:11</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1G2ZF55B464217974</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2006</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>PONT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>G6</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>2D</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9FA3949</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/18/2023 10:12:16</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/18/2023 10:12:16</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 17:56:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP3033</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 10:12:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:20</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The following was NOT captured on my body-worn camera due to the haste of which I exited my patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On Wednesday, December 13, 2023, at approximately 1018 hours, I was driving on southbound Interstate 270 near the overpass for Park Mills Road, Frederick, Frederick County, Maryland, in unmarked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle, B-2, in lane #1.&amp;nbsp; Once I drove underneath the overpass, I observed traffic stopping and slowing south of my location.&amp;nbsp; I drove for approximately 1/4 mile where I observed a flatbed tow truck stopped in lane #1 and a passenger vehicle stopped in lane #2, which was subsequently blocking a silver Pontiac G6 displaying Maryland registration, 9FA3949.&amp;nbsp; I activated my emergency equipment and drove closer to the stopped cars before parking my vehicle in lane #1, behind the tow truck.&amp;nbsp; Both the driver of the tow truck and the driver of the unidentified passenger car were out of the vehicle and appeared to be attempting to communicate with the driver of the silver Pontiac.&amp;nbsp; Once I stopped my patrol vehicle, I provided MSP dispatch with my observations before exiting my patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp; At first, I believed the driver of the Pontiac was possibly suffering from a medical emergency.&amp;nbsp; As I walked closer to the Pontiac, I observed a hispanic female sitting in the driver&amp;#39;s seat.&amp;nbsp; The engine of the Pontiac was running, and the keys were placed in the ignition.&amp;nbsp; I knocked on driver&amp;#39;s side window of the Pontiac and asked the driver to open the door.&amp;nbsp; She complied.&amp;nbsp; Immediately upon speaking with the driver, I smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from her breath and person.&amp;nbsp; Her speech was very slurred and her eyes were glassy.&amp;nbsp; I asked the driver if she was okay, and she advised she was okay, that she was heading home from work.&amp;nbsp; I asked her if she was experiencing a medical emergency, and she stated she was not.&amp;nbsp; This entire conversation lasted less than 10 seconds.&amp;nbsp; While I was speaking with the hispanic female, the driver of the unidentified passenger vehicle, a male, got back into his vehicle and drove off.&amp;nbsp; The female driver of the Pontiac then appeared to attempt to exit the vehicle and I stopped her.&amp;nbsp; I then ordered her to stay seated in the Pontiac, remove the keys from the ignition, and place the keys onto the dash of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; She complied.&amp;nbsp; I then turned toward the driver of the tow truck, who was later identified John Miller 2nd by his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license.&amp;nbsp; Miller advised that he and the unidentified male driver stopped their respective vehicles in the roadway because the female driver of the Pontiac was driving recklessly and Mr. Miller was concerned for her well-being.&amp;nbsp; As Miller spoke, I realized this incident was not a motor vehicle collision.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I also realized that I was not recording this incident.&amp;nbsp; I turned my attention towards the female driver, ordered her to remain in the vehicle, and advised Mr. Miller to keep his eyes on the hispanic female while I returned to my patrol vehicle to retrieve my body-camera.&amp;nbsp; The time frame from my first approach until I retrieved my body camera lasted between 30 seconds to 1 minute.&amp;nbsp; While retrieving my body-camera, I provided my observations to MSP dispatch, including the female driver appeared intoxicated and asked for back-up units.&amp;nbsp; I also re positioned my patrol vehicle from lane #1 into lane #2, behind the Pontiac.&amp;nbsp; Trooper First Class Piskor advised he was responding from the area of MD 85/I-270.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The following was captured on my body-worn camera:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I re-approached the driver of the Pontiac, who was now speaking to someone on her cellphone.&amp;nbsp; She attempted to exit her vehicle and hand me her phone, advising me that I needed to speak with whoever was on the other end of the call. I declined and advised her to remain seated in the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; I continued to speak with Mr. Miller, who provided me with his observations of the events that occurred prior to him attempting to block and stop the Pontiac.&amp;nbsp; While Mr. Miller was speaking, I continued to monitor the hispanic female who was simultaneously speaking on her phone while rummaging through the interior of the Pontiac.&amp;nbsp; I spoke with Mr. Miller for approximately 2 minutes before retrieving my portable radio from my patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp; Once I retrieved the portable radio, I attempted to power it on, but realized the battery was dead.&amp;nbsp; I returned to my patrol vehicle once again and placed the portable radio back on the driver&amp;#39;s seat. After approximately 3 minutes, I heard the Pontiac&amp;#39;s driver&amp;#39;s side door slam.&amp;nbsp; Believing the driver was attempting to leave, I walked back over to the driver&amp;#39;s side door, opened the door, and removed the keys from the dashboard.&amp;nbsp; I advised the driver that she could &amp;quot;shut the door, but don&amp;#39;t drive off.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I then placed the keys onto the roof of the car.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; For the next 7 minutes, I conducted the following actions:&amp;nbsp; I provided traffic direction to on-coming traffic, continued to update and receive updates from MSP dispatch, and continued to monitor the hispanic female.&amp;nbsp; After approximately 10-12 minutes from the start of this incident, TFC Piskor arrived.&amp;nbsp; I quickly briefed him regarding my observations.&amp;nbsp; TFC Piskor turned his attention towards the driver while I stopped traffic and moved the Pontiac out of lane #2 and onto the shoulder.&amp;nbsp; Mr. Miller moved the tow truck onto the shoulder in front of the Pontiac.&amp;nbsp; TFC Piskor attempted to conduct field sobriety tests with the driver, but she only participated in the horizontal gaze nystagmus test (HGN), declining to participate in the walk and turn and one legged stand.&amp;nbsp; TFC Piskor offered the driver a preliminary breath test, and she declined.&amp;nbsp; After declining the preliminary breath test, TFC Piskor placed the driver under arrest.&amp;nbsp; Once handcuffed, TFC Piskor walked the female towards the passenger side of his patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp; She was then placed into the passenger seat of TFC Piskor&amp;#39;s assigned patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp; TFC Breakall also arrived on-scene and informed me that I could leave.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;This concluded my involvement regarding this incident.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;All events occurred in Frederick County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP3033</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 10:14:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP3033</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 12:56:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cain</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kenneth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0486</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stein</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3033</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>