<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-039311</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/07/2023 12:00:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/07/2023 12:00:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/04/2023 12:30:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/04/2023 12:30:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>11/06/2023 11:30:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>The victim reported his firearm was stolen.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 12:34:14</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1865</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/28/2023 14:07:25</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>STP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>THT</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>712381</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 12:34:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 13:48:45</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>712381</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>26755</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Stone Corner</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Mechanicsville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20659</Zip5>
         <Zip4>5057</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.831721</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.401809</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/07/2023 12:34:10</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/07/2023 12:34:10</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>Y</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 16:56:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 12:34:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 18:52:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BWC utilized.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Scene Processing:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The victim responded to the Maryland State Police Leonardtown Barrack to report his firearm stolen. The victim completed a MSP Form 076, Written Statement and a copy has been attached to this report. An MSP Form 028, Maryland Gun Center Request for Service Form was completed and forwarded to the Maryland Gun Center. A copy of the Maryland Gun Center Request for Service Form and Maryland Gun Center report has been attached to this report. The stolen firearm has been entered in NCIC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Stolen Property:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;One Glock 17 9mm Handgun (Serial #BYTU703) &amp;ndash; Value: $600&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;One black 10 rounds Glock Magazine &amp;ndash; No current value, purchased with firearm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ten rounds of 9mm ammunition &amp;ndash; Value: $2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-bottom:11px; margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;One plastic Glock 17 holster &amp;ndash; Value: No current value, purchased with firearm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Total stolen Value: $602&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Narrative:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On November 7, 2023 at approximately 1200 hours, I, TFC Engleman #7197 responded to the Maryland State Police Leonardtown Barrack, located at 23200 Leonard Hall Drive, Leonardtown, St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland 20650 for a reported stolen firearm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I made contact with the complainant/victim, who was identified as Darius Terrell Redd (B/M DOB: 11/16/1993) by his Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Redd stated on November 4, 2023 at approximately 1230 hours he went to the Maryland International Raceway, located at 27861 Budds Creek Road, Mechanicsville, St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland 20659 with two (2) friends. Redd stated he attended the race with Jalisa Sharnice Hawkins (B/F DOB: 11/16/1993) and her friend known only by the name of &amp;ldquo;Cuzzo.&amp;rdquo; Redd stated they went to the race in &amp;ldquo;Cuzzo&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; green Toyota Corolla and parked in a grass field near the Race-N In gas station, located at 26755 Stone Corner Lane, Mechanicsville, St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland 20659. Once parked, Redd stated he removed his coat and removed his firearm and inside the waist band holster from his belt. Additionally, Redd stated he removed the magazine from the firearm to unload it and put the firearm and magazine in separate pockets of his coat and secured it in the trunk of the &amp;ldquo;Cuzzo&amp;rdquo; subject&amp;rsquo;s vehicle. Redd stated he was carrying one (1) ten (10) round magazine with ten (10) rounds of 9mm ammunition. I asked Redd if he knew &amp;quot;Cuzzo&amp;#39;s&amp;quot; real name and he stated, &amp;quot;No.&amp;quot; I asked Redd if he had met the &amp;quot;Cuzzo&amp;quot; subject before and he stated he could not recall because he has a bad memory.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Redd stated he was then with Hawkins and the &amp;ldquo;Cuzzo&amp;rdquo; subject inside the Maryland International Raceway for approximately one (1) hour when he got into an argument with &amp;ldquo;Cuzzo.&amp;rdquo; I asked Redd what the argument was about and he stated he is a loud person and he believed &amp;ldquo;Cuzzo&amp;rdquo; was upset with the volume of his voice as it pertains to his sexuality. Redd stated he then separated himself and left the area of the raceway where they were sitting so he could call someone to pick him up. Redd stated the argument never got physical.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Redd stated he then proceeded to the raceway parking area in an attempt to call a ride but his cellphone was dead. Redd stated he eventually found a raceway worker that assisted him with charging his cell phone and he was able to call his boyfriend to come and pick him up. Redd stated his boyfriend was at work around the time he called for a ride so he had to wait until approximately 1400-1500 hours before his ride arrived. Redd then left the raceway and went straight to his home address, 10982 Stella Court, Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland 20603. I asked Redd what time he got home and he stated approximately between 1530 and 1600 hours. Redd further explained he did not leave his house after that, and did not leave the house all day November 5, 2023.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I asked Redd when he noticed he did not have the firearm. Redd stated he noticed he did not have his firearm yesterday, November 6, 2023 at approximately 1130 hours when he gathered his things to leave the house. Redd stated he contacted Hawkins via text message asking where his coat and firearm was. Hawkins responded, now possibly identifying the &amp;ldquo;Cuzzo&amp;rdquo; subject as &amp;ldquo;Taylor,&amp;rdquo; stating &amp;ldquo;Taylor has your coat &amp;amp; he threw it out because he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to ride with it in his car.&amp;rdquo; Redd further questioned Hawkins where the firearm was thrown to and Hawkins stated, &amp;ldquo;In the grassy area where he was parked&amp;hellip;behind that store and in front of that house or trailer or whatever.&amp;rdquo; The remainder of the conservation shows Redd sending Hawkins photographs of the area he was at looking to see if he can locate the firearm in relation to where they parked. After review of the messages further, it appears Redd was told they parked in the yard of 26728 Thompsons Corner Road, Mechanicsville, St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland 20659 which is private property. Redd forwarded me screenshots of the text conversation and the images have been attached to this report and uploaded to VeriPic. Redd stated he checked the area and did not locate his firearm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;It should be noted, Redd advised he contacted the Leonardtown Barrack on November 6, 2023 via telephone to report this incident and was advised to come in person to make a report. Redd stated he was provided with an incident number but could not come in until today, November 7, 2023 to file a report.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; While at the barrack, Redd completed a MSP Form 076, Written Statement and a copy has been attached to this report. Redd provided his Maryland Wear and Carry permit ID card and a copy was obtained for this report (ID # 23HGP-133821). Additionally, Redd provided a copy of his U.S Department of Justice, Firearms transaction Record and a copy has been attached to this report. Review of the transaction record revealed the firearm was purchased on March 24, 2023 from Fred&amp;rsquo;s Outdoors, located at 2895 Crain Highway, Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland 20601. Redd stated he purchased the firearm and holster as a bundle for approximately $600. The firearm was identified as a Glock 17 9mm handgun bearing serial #BYTU703. The additional stolen value noted in property is for the ten (10) rounds of 9mm ammunition in the firearm&amp;rsquo;s magazine. Redd stated he did not know what kind of ammunition he was carrying.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I asked Redd if he believed Hawkins would be cooperative if I contacted her in reference to this investigation and he stated he was not sure because she has feelings about the police and even him speaking with me to make this report made him nervous. I advised Redd I would attempt to make contact with Hawkins for this investigation and he provided me with her telephone number.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I provided Redd with a crime/victim&amp;rsquo;s pamphlet, the case number, and my contact information should he have any further information or questions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I conducted a browse through RMS and LinX with Hawkins&amp;rsquo; information looking for known associates with the name of &amp;ldquo;Taylor&amp;rdquo; or an alias &amp;ldquo;Cuzzo&amp;rdquo; which yielded negative results.&lt;br /&gt; Additionally, no known associates were located through Hawkins&amp;rsquo; involvement with the Charles County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On November 7, 2023 at approximately 1305 hours, I completed a MSP Form 028, Maryland Gun Center Request for Service Form and forwarded it to the Maryland Gun Center.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The stolen firearm was placed into NCIC. The initial report was forwarded to Leonardtown Barrack ED Smale to be entered into NCIC, reference NIC #G196088678. A copy of the entry has been attached to this report.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On November 8, 2023 at approximately 0632 hours, I contacted the St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s County Emergency Communications Center (ECC) to check for any history and known associates with Hawkins. ECC currently has no involvements with Hawkins.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On November 8, 2023 at approximately 0710 hours, Tpr. Baden #7152, Tpr. Ruel #7671, and I responded to the RaceN-In, located at 26755 Stone Corner Lane, Mechanicsville, St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland 20659 to follow-up on surveillance and check the area for the firearm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Tpr. Baden, Tpr. Ruel and I checked the area on foot where the firearm was allegedly left and yielded negative results. Tpr. Baden and Tpr. Ruel attempted to make contact with a resident at the 26728 Thompson Corner Road address where Redd&amp;rsquo;s friends stated they had parked and were not able to make contact with a property owner. Additionally, the yard appeared to be freshly mowed, therefore, if a firearm was in the grass it would most likely have been located or damaged by a lawn mower. The 26728 Thompson Corner Road address is also fenced off from the parking lot of the RaceN-In, showed no tire marks in the grass indicating vehicles were recently parked there, and is private property. It is unlikely Redd and his friends parked on that property as reported based on the information above.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We then made contact with Janice Louise Hemsley (B/F DOB: 12/18/1973) who was identified by her MVA photograph. Hemsley resides at 26750 Stone Corner Lane, Mechanicsville, St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland 20659 which shares property with the RaceN-In. Tpr. Ruel asked Hemsley if anyone parks at the 26728 Thompsons Corner Road residence and she stated, &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo; Hemsley further stated an elderly female in an electric wheel chair resides there alone. Hemsley stated all of the parking on the property is handled by the RaceN-In in and she has people knock on her door frequently looking for lost items. Hemsley stated she has not seen any firearms or lost items recently.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I then made contact with employees at the RaceN-In which is equipped with surveillance cameras. I made contact with an employee who advised the rear cameras view the rear parking lot and most of Thompsons Corner Road. I asked the employee how long the cameras record for and she stated she believed it was three (3) days before it records over itself. The employee additionally stated the subject responsible for the camera system is in the hospital currently due to an illness and she was unsure when she would return. I left my contact information should any videos from November 4, 2023 are able to be recovered. I then cleared the scene.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On November 9, 2023 at approximately 0604 hours, I contacted the Maryland Gun Center via email to follow-up on my request sent on November 7, 2023 in reference to this investigation. At 0641 hours, I received a response from the Maryland Gun Center and their report has been attached (Reference MDGC Case Report # 202308264). &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;This case remains open pending further investigation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All of the above events occurred in St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 13:55:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7197</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 11:53:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oles</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5857</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Engleman</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7197</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528777</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0622 23F</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>07</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/04/2023 12:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0622 23F</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 13:49:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7197</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 13:49:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 13:51:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 13:51:35</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>63812</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Redd</LastName>
               <FirstName>Darius</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Terrell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/16/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/22/2015 04:17:18</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Redd</LastName>
               <FirstName>Darius</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Terrell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/16/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/22/2015 04:17:18</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>10982</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Stella</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Waldorf</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20603</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.929661</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.636165</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>819</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8460</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 13:51:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 13:54:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 13:54:03</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392366</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hawkins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jalisa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Sharnice</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/16/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 13:53:55</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J420</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hawkins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jalisa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Sharnice</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/16/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J420</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 13:53:55</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2665</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Husk</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Waldorf</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20602</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.903242</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.599806</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>710</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7755</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 13:54:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>49</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/08/2023 13:54:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/08/2023 13:54:38</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>157076</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hemsley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Janice</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Louise</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/18/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/29/2017 05:47:58</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H524</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hemsley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Janice</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Louise</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/18/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H524</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/29/2017 05:47:58</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>26750</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Stone Corner</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Mechanicsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20659</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.831008</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.401129</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>346</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0955</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/29/2017 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/08/2023 13:54:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>7</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 13:56:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7197</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 13:56:47</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>7</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One Glock 17 9mm Handgun (Serial #BYTU703), One black 10 rounds Glock Magazine, One plastic Glock 17 holster
</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>610</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>600</PropertyValue>
         <Value>600</Value>
         <SerialNumber>BYTU703</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256265</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>Glock</Make>
         <Model>17</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>7</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 13:57:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7197</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 13:57:23</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>7</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Ten (10) rounds of 9mm ammunition</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>424</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>2</PropertyValue>
         <Value>2</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256266</Property_ID>
         <Model>9mm</Model>
         <Quantity>10</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/19/2023 15:05:32</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/19/2023 15:05:32</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 16:56:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/19/2023 15:05:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 18:52:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Narrative:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On November 19, 2023 at approximately 1500 hours, I contacted the victim Redd via telephone. I asked him if he received any additional information about his firearm at this time and he stated, &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo; I asked Hawkins if he had spoken to Jalisa Hawkins since the incident had occurred and he stated, &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo; Redd had no question for me, I then terminated the call.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On November 19, 2023 at approximately 1515 hours, I attempted to contact Hawkins multiple times via telephone. Hawkins did not answer the phone or respond to my voicemail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;This case remains open pending further investigation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All of the above events occurred in St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/19/2023 15:05:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7197</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/27/2023 04:33:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oles</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5857</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Engleman</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7197</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/27/2023 13:43:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/27/2023 13:43:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 16:56:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 13:43:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 18:52:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BWC utilized.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Narrative:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On December 5, 2023 at approximately 1200 hours, I responded to 2129 Briarwood Drive, Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland 20601 to attempt to make contact with Jalisa Hawkins. I made contact with a female subject in the driveway who advised she was Hawkins&amp;rsquo; mother. She stated Hawkins does not reside at this address. She attempted to call Hawkins for me to obtain her new address, however, she did not answer. I was provided with an additional phone number for Hawkins to attempt to contact at a later time. I then cleared the residence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On December 5, 2023 at approximately 1231 hours, I then responded to 2665 Husk Place, St. Charles, Charles County, Maryland 20602 to attempt to make contact with Hawkins at this address located after a browse through LinX. The Husk Place address is an apartment building and a browse through Delta Plus, LinX, and TLO did not indicate a unit number in order to make contact with Hawkins. I attempted to contact Hawkins while on scene multiple times by phone, however, she did not answer. I then cleared the scene.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On December 5, 2023 at approximately 1445 hours, I attempted to contact Hawkins via telephone, however, she did not answer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On December 27, 2023 at approximately 1320 hours, I attempted to contact Hawkins via telephone multiple times, however, she did not answer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On December 27, 2023 I conducted an additional browse through LinX for any additional contact information for Hawkins as multiple attempts have been unsuccessful. No additional contact or address information could be located as Hawkins has had no further police involvements since this report was taken.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On December 27, 2023 at approximately hours, I contacted the victim Redd via telephone and advised him I have not been able to make contact with Hawkins. I advised Redd should he have any further questions or information to contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I request this investigation be suspended due to lack of further investigative leads.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All of the above events occurred in Charles County and St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7197</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 13:44:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7197</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 13:44:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oles</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5857</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Engleman</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7197</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>