<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-040851</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/18/2023 06:58:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/18/2023 06:58:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/18/2023 06:44:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/18/2023 06:44:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI, Single Vehicle Collision</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 06:58:41</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 17:20:41</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>713533</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 10:10:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 10:11:21</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>713533</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>I-95</StreetName>
         <City>Beltsville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.9419133333333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.034675</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/18/2023 06:58:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/18/2023 06:58:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/06/2023 23:33:10</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 06:58:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:14</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>COREA CASTILLO, JULIO CESAR // 23-MSP-040851 // 0Q50Y2X&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Corea Castillo, Julio Cesar&lt;br /&gt; Incident Number: 23-MSP-040851&lt;br /&gt; DUI Folder: 23-282&lt;br /&gt; Date of Offense: 11/18/2023&lt;br /&gt; Arresting Officer: Tpr. Fleming #7439&lt;br /&gt; Breath Technician: Cpl. Kemp #5753&lt;br /&gt; Subsequent Offender: No&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Q-13 IS EQUIPPED WITH AN IN CAR CAMERA&lt;br /&gt; THE EVENT WAS AUDIBLY AND VISUALLY RECORDED&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TRAINING/CERTIFICATES&lt;br /&gt; Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;br /&gt; On November 18th, 2023, at approximately 0644 hours, I, Trooper Fleming #7439 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, was dispatched to the area of southbound 95 at Powder Mill Road, Beltsville, Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland. The call for service was for a report of a black sedan off road. I was in full uniform operating a marked patrol vehicle Q-13. The incident was audibly and visually recorded on my body worn camera and Q-13&amp;rsquo;s in-car camera.&lt;br /&gt; Upon my arrival, I identified a black Toyota Camry bearing Maryland registration &amp;ldquo;2FJ9569&amp;rdquo; with all around damage to the vehicle. The vehicle was completely off road to the right. I exited my patrol vehicle to make contact with the driver involved in the motor vehicle collision.&lt;br /&gt; EMS/Fireboard was on scene prior to my arrival. EMS personnel confirmed that Corea Castillo did not need or want to be transported to hospital.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the driver of the black Toyota who I identified as Corea Castillo, Julio Cesar (5/M, DOB: 10/11/1989) via his Maryland Driver&amp;rsquo;s license.&lt;br /&gt; I observed that there was a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s breath and person. Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s eyes were bloodshot and glassy. Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s speech was slurred and mumbled. Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s movements were slow and lethargic. Corea Castillo would also sway while standing in place.&lt;br /&gt; A Spanish speaking officer was requested due to the language barrier. While waiting for the Spanish speaking officer to arrive, Corea Castillo used google translate to say &amp;ldquo;They are going to revoke my license for being irresponsible.&amp;rdquo; I asked Corea Castillo what he meant by &amp;ldquo;being irresponsible.&amp;rdquo; Corea Castillo used google translate to say &amp;ldquo;for driving drunk.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;br /&gt; An additional police unit arrived on scene. Officer Valdes #3141 of Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County Police Department assisted in translating.&lt;br /&gt; I asked Corea Castillo how the accident happened. Corea Castillo stated that he was driving in the right most lane when another vehicle made him swerve to the right and run off road.&lt;br /&gt; I asked Corea Castillo to perform field sobriety in order to rule out alcohol as a contributing factor. Corea Castillo agreed to perform field sobriety.&lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of southbound 95 at Powder Mill Road. The level and dry. Corea Castillo appeared to be in good physical condition.&lt;br /&gt; I asked Corea Castillo the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; Alcohol &amp;ndash; Corea Castillo stated he had ten beers around 2300 hours last night. Corea Castillo stated he then went to sleep for a couple hours and upon waking up around 0300 hours he had another five beers.&lt;br /&gt; Medication &amp;ndash; Corea Castillo stated he did not take any prescribed medication. Corea Castillo stated he took over the counter pain medication for his back yesterday around 1400 hours.&lt;br /&gt; Physical Condition &amp;ndash; Corea Castillo stated that he did have any physical injuries that would prevent him from walking in a straight line or standing on one foot. Corea Castillo advised that he had struck his left leg during the collision and showed us a bruise on his lower left leg.&lt;br /&gt; Glasses or Contacts &amp;ndash; Corea Castillo stated he did not wear glasses or contacts.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 Clues Observed)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained. The tip of a pen was used as the test&amp;rsquo;s stimulus. The stimulus was held approximately 12-15 inches from Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s eye, slightly above eye level. &amp;nbsp;Corea Castillo was instructed to look straight ahead, keep his head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. &amp;nbsp;Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Before beginning the test, I asked Corea Castillo if he understood my instructions, to which he confirmed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Additional Observations &amp;ndash; Resting gaze nystagmus was not present. Vertical gaze nystagmus was not present.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN TEST (5/8 Clues Observed)&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. Corea Castillo was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Corea Castillo was then instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and remain in that position until told to begin. Corea Castillo was advised to take nine steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line, and take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Corea Castillo was instructed to complete the second series of nine steps in the same heel to toe fashion. Corea Castillo was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, to count every step out loud, and once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Corea Castillo if he understood, and he confirmed that he did.&lt;br /&gt; Instructional Phase &amp;ndash;&lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (First Nine Steps) &amp;ndash;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Stop Walking &amp;ndash; On step nine of his first nine steps, Corea Castillo stops walking.&lt;br /&gt; Improper Turn &amp;ndash; Corea Castillo turned by taking one large step with his rear foot while pivoting around his front foot. Corea Castillo ended his turn with his feet side by side.&lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (Second Nine Steps)&lt;br /&gt; Steps Off Line &amp;ndash; On the third and seventh steps of his second nine steps, Corea Castillo stepped off line by more than one half inch.&lt;br /&gt; Misses Heel-Toe &amp;ndash; On the third and seventh steps of his second nine steps, Corea missed heel to toe by more than one half inch.&lt;br /&gt; Actual Number of Steps &amp;ndash; Corea Castillo stepped ten times.&lt;br /&gt; Additional Observations &amp;ndash; Corea Castillo did not count any steps out loud.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ONE-LEG STAND TEST (0/4 Clues Observed)&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. &amp;nbsp;Corea Castillo was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch the raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two, etc.), and not put his foot down until the end of the test. I asked Corea Castillo if he understood the test, and he confirmed.&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 1-10&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ARREST&lt;br /&gt; Based on the totality of circumstances, I concluded Corea Castillo was driving a motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol.&lt;br /&gt; Corea Castillo was involved in and found to be the at fault driver in a single motor vehicle collision.&lt;br /&gt; The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s eyes were bloodshot and glassy.&lt;br /&gt; Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s slurred and mumbled speech.&lt;br /&gt; Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s slow and lethargic movements.&lt;br /&gt; Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s swaying while standing in place.&lt;br /&gt; Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s admission to consuming alcohol recently.&lt;br /&gt; The presence of an alcoholic beverage with arms reach of the driver in Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; On November 18th, 2023, at approximately 0742 hours, I placed Corea Castillo under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack.&lt;br /&gt; A search incident to arrest of Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s person was conducted. The search of Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s person was negative.&lt;br /&gt; I transported Corea Castillo to the College Park Barrack.&lt;br /&gt; Corea Castillo was played the DR-15 Advice of Rights Spanish recording provided by MVA. Corea Castillo was provided with a copy of the DR-15 to read along as well. At approximately 0758 hours, Corea Castillo agreed to take an alcohol concentration test.&lt;br /&gt; 20 MINUTE OBSERVATION&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Corea Castillo beginning with his arrest. A preliminary search of Corea Castillo was conducted on scene and it was revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. I observed Corea Castillo from the time of arrest until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by Cpl. Kemp #5753 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Corea Castillo had a result of .15 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath on November 18th, 2023 at 0839 hours.&lt;br /&gt; Intoximeter Result: .15 BrAC&lt;br /&gt; Corea Castillo&amp;rsquo;s vehicle was towed by Hannan Towing.&lt;br /&gt; I processed Corea Castillo and released him to Moreno Cruz, Darwin Osman (5/M; DOB: 08/09/1995).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Corea Castillo was issued the following citations.&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-902(a1i) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-902(b1i) DRIVING VEH. WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-902(a1ii) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL PER SE&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-901.1(a) RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OF PERSONS AND PROPERTY&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-901.1(b) NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-201(a1) DRIVER FAILURE TO OBEY PROPERLY PLACED TRAFFIC CONTROL DEVICE INSTRUCTIONS&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-801(b) FAILURE TO CONTROL VEHICLE SPEED ON HIGHWAY TO AVOID COLLISION&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The defendant was issued copies of the following documents:&lt;br /&gt; -Citations (listed above)&lt;br /&gt; -DR-15 Advice of Rights&lt;br /&gt; -DR-15a Order of Suspension&lt;br /&gt; -MSP 33 Notification to Defendant of Result of Test for Alcohol Concentration&lt;br /&gt; All documents were forwarded to the Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County, State Attorney Office.&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 00:11:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 23:17:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Aaron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fleming</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sierra</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7439</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>530321</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/18/2023 06:44:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 10:24:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 10:24:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 10:12:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 10:27:36</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393310</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Corea Castillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Julio</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Cesar</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/11/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/18/2023 09:53:40</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Corea Castillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Julio</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Cesar</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/11/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/18/2023 09:53:40</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>811</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Rambo</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Halethorpe</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21227</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3421</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.65193</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.240459</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>717</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3111</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 10:26:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 10:26:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 10:26:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 10:26:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 10:24:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 10:24:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159039</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 00:06:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 00:06:19</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>4T1G11AK9LU929291</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CAM</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2FJ9569</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>