<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-039970</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/11/2023 21:30:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/11/2023 21:30:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/11/2023 21:13:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/11/2023 21:13:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>4 VEH COLLISION RESULTING IN DUI ARREST WITH CRIMINAL CHARGES</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 21:30:08</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6052</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/24/2023 11:56:58</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>MDOP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>RSA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>N/B 5 N/O WOODYARD RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>714636</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:13:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 08:18:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>714636</AddressId>
         <StreetName>BRANCH</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>CLINTON</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20735</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.8738983333333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.8402</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/11/2023 21:30:05</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/11/2023 21:30:05</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/24/2023 11:57:00</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 21:30:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:01</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;****L-43 EQUIPPED WITH AUDIO/VIDEO EQUIPMENT****&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;****INCIDENT CAPTURED ON MVR &amp;amp; BODYCAM****&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;****TRAINING &amp;amp; CERTIFICATIONS****&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration&lt;br /&gt; - Attended and graduated with distinction, the University of Maryland&amp;rsquo;s DUI Institute&lt;br /&gt; - Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; - Certified SFST Instructor through the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration&lt;br /&gt; - Trained in administering ARIDE tests through the Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;****NARRATIVE****&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On 11/11/2023 at approximately 2114hrs, I was on-duty, in full MSP uniform on Southbound Branch Avenue in the area of Woodyard Road assisting another trooper with a multi-vehicle collision when I observed a yellow Freightliner box truck (VA 97709TA) strike 3 vehicles and continue on Northbound Branch Avenue without stopping. I advised the Trooper on the Northbound side of Branch Avenue and they performed a traffic stop on the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Once I arrived on scene with the box truck I observed the female passenger exit the vehicle while the driver initially did not. Once the driver exited the vehicle I asked him what happened and he ignored me. The driver then walked towards the rear of the truck, squatted down, repeatedly ignored my question of &amp;ldquo;what happened&amp;rdquo; then stated &amp;ldquo;you seen what happened&amp;rdquo; and appeared to nod off and lean forward, face planting into the grass. I asked the driver if he was on anything or if he was hurt as I was unsure if I needed to administer Naloxone as his behavior was abnormal.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked for the driver for his license and he asked &amp;ldquo;are you serious right now?&amp;rdquo; The driver repeatedly ignored my request for his driver&amp;rsquo;s license, became irate, and shouted &amp;ldquo;of course I have a fucking license.&amp;rdquo; I then asked if he was going to give it to me. I requested L-48, Trooper Smalls #7676 respond to the scene to assist as the driver became increasingly uncooperative. The driver started shouting at me about asking if he was hurt despite being notified EMS was already enroute.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the driver&amp;rsquo;s breath and person, I asked how much he had to drink tonight and he said &amp;ldquo;what the fuck, are you fucking crazy bro?&amp;rdquo; and advised he had just hit a car. I advised him that he had actually hit two cars, as at the time I was unaware of the 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; vehicle that was struck. I requested the driver to take a seat as he continually stated he was injured. The driver continued to complain of his injury and ignored my instructions to have a seat. I advised the driver once more that we had an ambulance coming. I advised the driver that moving his arm wasn&amp;rsquo;t helping him if he had a potential injury and he stated &amp;ldquo;I ain&amp;rsquo;t moving it like nothing bro.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I again requested his license. After asking for his license approximately 3 times he stated he couldn&amp;rsquo;t give me his license because he was &amp;ldquo;too fucked up.&amp;rdquo; I asked his passenger if she could get his license for him and he advised I needed to &amp;ldquo;worry about the driver&amp;rdquo; and asked me &amp;ldquo;why you ask her anything&amp;rdquo;. I advised the driver I asked his passenger because he said he wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to get his license. The driver again began to shout about his arm and refuse to give me his license. I asked the driver why he was so angry and he stated &amp;ldquo;fuck you, bottom line.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked the driver if he would be willing to participate in Standardized Field Sobriety Testing and he said &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll do anything you want me to.&amp;rdquo; I then advised I was going to have EMS check him out and I asked if he thought he needed to go to a hospital in which he responded &amp;ldquo;fuck you.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then advised the PCO the driver was potentially 10-55 but I wanted him checked out by EMS before doing anything. The driver then began talking to his passenger. I allowed the driver to speak to the passenger for a while hoping he would calm down. I again asked about his license and he became increasingly irate and aggressive, screaming &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m fucking injured don&amp;rsquo;t worry about my license don&amp;rsquo;t ask me about nothing else.&amp;rdquo; At this point, Trooper Smalls arrived on scene to assist and I deemed it necessary to place the driver in handcuffs for safety reasons as I believed the situation was going to get out of hand, EMS had not yet arrived on scene. As I attempted to place the driver in handcuffs he repeatedly stated his arm was broke and he began to argue that he couldn&amp;rsquo;t put his arms in front of him or behind me. At this time I observed an ambulance drive past our location and it appeared to stop in front of the vehicles. I then discovered that EMS had drove past our location without stopping. I allowed the driver to wait with his hands unrestrained as I believed EMS was on scene and he got in my face and called me a &amp;ldquo;faggot nigger&amp;rdquo;. The driver then appeared to walk towards the travel portion of the roadway and Trooper Smalls pointed him away. Myself and Trooper Smalls advised the driver to take a seat multiple times hoping it would deescalate the situation and keep him from repeatedly trying to walk away. I then asked his passenger if she would be able to assist us with controlling his behavior and she advised he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t listen to her.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I again asked for EMS advising I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to place the driver in handcuffs if his arm truly was broken. At this time I observed as Trooper Smalls appeared to be building a rapport with the driver, I took a step back and allowed Trooper Smalls to continue his dialogue with the driver although I could hear the driver continually swearing at Trooper Smalls. Trooper Smalls was able to convince the driver to hand over his driver&amp;rsquo;s license. At this time the driver was identified via his DC driver&amp;rsquo;s license (DC 3207006) as Derrick Lucas Walls (DOB 10/05/1989). I stepped away from the situation hoping the lack of an overwhelming police presence would calm Walls down as he seemed to prefer dealing with Trooper Smalls. It should be noted, EMS was taking a longer than extended time period to respond. I then asked Trooper Smalls if he wanted to handle the situation as he seemed to have built a rapport with Walls and I thought allowing him to deal with Trooper Smalls rather than myself would help calm the situation.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I again asked for EMS as they still had not arrived on scene. Trooper Smalls then removed a pocket knife off of Walls person for safety reasons. Trooper Smalls advised he would give it back later and that he had taken it to assure he couldn&amp;rsquo;t do anything with it. I then advised Trooper Smalls if Walls got too aggressive we would have to place him in cuffs whether EMS showed up or not. I felt the situation was growing more and more unsafe the longer we waited for EMS. I advised Trooper Smalls that Walls did not need his arms for the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, so to keep Walls occupied while we waited for EMS he could perform SFSTs. Trooper Smalls again asked Walls if he wanted to do SFSTs and Walls stated &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m gonna ACE it and make you feel like a dummy, fuck you, fuck both of y&amp;rsquo;all, all y&amp;rsquo;all some bitches.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As Trooper Smalls began to give instructions, Walls repeatedly stated &amp;ldquo;fuck you&amp;rdquo;. Trooper Smalls asked him again if he wanted to do SFSTs and Walls stated &amp;ldquo;fuck you&amp;rdquo;. I advised over the radio that EMS was taking way too long and that we would have Walls in custody for safety reasons. I attempted to place Walls in handcuffs and as I moved his left arm to the rear he began to shout. In an attempt to avoid exacerbating his existing injury, I then advised Walls to have a seat hoping he would calm down and I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to utilize the handcuffs. Instead of taking a seat, Walls began to shout in my face so I asked if he could move his arms forward and he stated he could not. I observed Walls&amp;rsquo; movements throughout the interaction and noticed several times as he reached forward with no issues. I placed Walls&amp;rsquo; left wrist in handcuffs and attempted to handcuff him to the front. Walls then tensed up and refused to give me his right arm, I advised Walls to relax his arm. Walls was instructed several times to relax his arm. Walls then attempted to yank his right arm out of my grip while stating &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rsquo;re not strong.&amp;rdquo; Myself and Trooper Smalls then pushed Walls arms together and placed him in handcuffs. Walls fell to the ground as we placed him in handcuffs. Walls repeatedly shouted he was in an accident and that he had pulled over. I again requested EMS, which still had not arrived on scene. After another brief wait, EMS finally arrived on scene.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walls asked why he was in handcuffs and I advised him it was because he repeatedly got aggressive. Walls then pulled his legs towards his torso and I advised him not to get up. Walls then got up and Trooper Smalls and myself carefully placed him back on the curb in a seated position. Walls then stated &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m handcuffed, what the fuck can I do?&amp;rdquo; Walls then stated he was in handcuffs for no reason and I advised him it was because he was intoxicated and refused SFSTs. Walls then stated he did not refuse SFSTs and instead of speaking to EMS, he repeatedly shouted he wanted to take Field Sobriety and that his arm was fine. I advised Walls that we were beyond Field Sobriety and he shouted &amp;ldquo;fuck you faggot ass bitch&amp;rdquo;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walls then calmed himself down enough to speak to EMS and repeatedly stated he was &amp;ldquo;good&amp;rdquo;. Walls went back and forth on whether he wanted to go to the hospital and EMS determined he was refusing treatment. I then asked EMS for paperwork showing he refused treatment. Walls continually shouted at Trooper Smalls throughout my interaction with EMS personnel and Walls&amp;rsquo; passenger. I requested a check to see if County had a cage car for transport. Walls again stood up despite being ordered to stay seated. Myself and Trooper Smalls again attempted to place Walls in a seated position to control the situation and he began to thrash around and shout. Walls repeatedly insulted myself and Trooper Smalls and shout in our faces. Myself and Trooper Smalls attempted to deescalate the situation by complying with Walls request to stand and for us to physically let him go. Walls responded by threatening to &amp;ldquo;smack the shit out both of y&amp;rsquo;all&amp;rdquo;. Walls repeatedly stated &amp;ldquo;do it&amp;rdquo; without clarifying what he meant. Walls called me a &amp;ldquo;nigger&amp;rdquo; then a &amp;ldquo;bitch&amp;rdquo; and then a &amp;ldquo;cracker&amp;rdquo;. Walls would move from shouting directly in my face to shouting directly into Trooper Smalls face. Walls then stepped off the curb and attempted to walk away. I stopped Walls and advised him to sit down and he started to scream &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not sitting down, I was in an accident&amp;rdquo; Walls then began to shout at me and I attempted to place him in a seated position as I felt the situation was escalating out of control. I grabbed Walls left arm and Trooper Smalls grabbed Walls right. After a brief struggle, we managed to safely lower Walls to the ground despite his resistance. I was informed county did not have a cage car available. Myself and Trooper Smalls held Walls on the ground. I placed my hands on Walls left shoulder and my knee on his butt. Walls began to shout he could not breath and while it was clear nothing was being done to restrict his airway, myself and Trooper Smalls adjusted to accommodate. I allowed Walls to sit up while I crouched behind him in case he attempted to stand up again. I then attempted to calmly explain the situation to Walls and answer all his questions despite repeatedly asking the same question of &amp;ldquo;why am I in handcuffs&amp;rdquo;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walls advised he wanted to be checked out by EMS so I advised EMS personnel of Walls&amp;rsquo; changed decision. EMS began to question Walls and I retrieved his shoe and handed it to Trooper Smalls. Walls asked how he was supposed to put his shoe on with handcuffs and shouted &amp;ldquo;stop acting like a bitch dog, you&amp;rsquo;s a faggot nigga&amp;rdquo; at Trooper Smalls. I offered to put Walls shoe on to deescalate the situation and he told me not to touch him and stated &amp;ldquo;fuck you&amp;rdquo;. After a brief conversation with EMS, Walls was advised he needed to go to the ambulance for EMS personnel to check him out. Walls advised he couldn&amp;rsquo;t stand up on his own as he needed his shoe on. I put Walls shoe on for him. Walls then proceeded to say he couldn&amp;rsquo;t stand because his left arm was hurt. I asked Walls if I could help him stand up and he advised I could assist from his right arm. I then grabbed Walls under his right arm to assist him to his feet.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walls did not assist in any way so I began to lift him and he hopped up onto his feet and grabbed my face and neck with his hands, I believe in an attempt to choke me. At this time my bodycam was knocked off by Walls and myself and Trooper Smalls grabbed Walls and assisted him to the grassy shoulder utilizing a takedown maneuver. Trooper Smalls&amp;rsquo; bodycam was evidently knocked off by Walls aswell. Myself and Smalls mistakenly grabbed each other&amp;rsquo;s bodycams thinking we had our own. Walls then laid on the ground as if he was being held down despite no outside force was holding him down. Walls stated &amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t put myself in this position&amp;rdquo; and I advised him he could get himself out of it. Walls then, with ease, stood up and began to walk quickly towards the ambulance. I then attempted to keep pace with Walls incase he stepped towards traffic and he stopped and turned around to walk back towards the boxtruck. In an attempt to deescalate the situation, we allowed Walls to speak to his passenger which was revealed to be his wife. Walls would repeatedly walk towards the ambulance and then turn around and walk back to his wife.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Eventually we were able to convince Walls to enter the ambulance with his wife. Trooper Smalls rode in the rear of the ambulance with Walls and EMS personnel. I followed the ambulance to Southern Maryland Hospital where we met up with Cpl York #6327.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Once inside the hospital, Walls repeatedly shouted and threatened hospital security, myself Trooper Smalls, and Cpl York. Walls made death threats to hospital staff, hospital security, myself, Trooper Smalls, and Cpl York. Hospital staff attempted to get Walls to radiology to get X-rays but Walls became argumentative and refused to go to radiology without his wife.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Hospital staff deemed it a refusal, myself, Cpl York, and Trooper Smalls began to escort Walls out of the hospital. Walls attempted to get away from us and began thrashing around. I grabbed Walls right leg, while Cpl York lifted his upper torso, and Trooper Smalls lifted Walls left leg. We carried Walls out of the hospital and placed him in a seated position on the asphalt next to Cpl York&amp;rsquo;s patrol car. I then retrieved my patrol car and brought it to Walls&amp;rsquo; location. Walls was placed in ankle shackles and a waist belt in an attempt to keep his physical outbursts contained. Cpl York and Trooper Smalls attempted to place Walls in the passenger seat of my patrol car and he began to stiffen up and refused to bring his legs into the vehicle. I attempted to push Walls&amp;rsquo; feet into the door of the vehicle and was unsuccessful. After several failed attempts to get Walls to bring his feet into the vehicle, I entered the back seat of the vehicle and leaned the seat back and pulled Walls further into the vehicle causing his feet to fully enter the vehicle. As soon as Walls feet were in the vehicle, he placed them between the door and the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s frame making it impossible to shut the door without crushing his feet. Eventually Walls was convinced to pull his feet into the vehicle so we could shut the door. Trooper Smalls drove my patrol vehicle to Upper Marlboro Department of Corrections while I sat in the rear seat behind Walls. Cpl York followed behind in his own vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walls passed out due to his intoxication while enroute to DOC. Once at DOC Walls woke up and began to threaten myself and Trooper Smalls while refusing to exit the vehicle. Walls exited the vehicle on his own only to shout &amp;ldquo;neither one of y&amp;rsquo;all can control me, nigga fuck you&amp;rdquo; and blow air into my face, simultaneously spitting on my face. Once entering intake at DOC Walls began to blow air and spit at Cpl York and Trooper Smalls aswell. Walls began to scream and shout and began to elbow Trooper Smalls and Cpl York. I then shut off my bodycam as it is DOC policy for all recording devices to be switched off. Once inside the intake center, Walls began to fight with DOC staff who had to force him to the ground and pepper spray him due to his aggressive and uncooperative behavior.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walls was left in Upper Marlboro DOC staff&amp;rsquo;s custody.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walls was not offered an Intoximeter test and the DR15 was never read due to Walls&amp;#39; consistently hostile, uncooperative, and aggressive behavior. Walls&amp;#39; behavior and actions resulted in all tests being deemed a refusal for the safety of all involved.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Walls was cited the appropriate traffic citations and I submitted the proper paperwork for the criminal charges.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All events occurred in Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:43:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7163</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/23/2023 06:35:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smalls</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7676</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Estrin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6052</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>York</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6327</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harr</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeremy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7163</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529438</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 21:13:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:14:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7163</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/23/2023 06:36:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529438</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0600</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 21:13:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0600</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:15:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7163</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/23/2023 06:36:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529438</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0055</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 21:13:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 0055</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:18:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7163</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/23/2023 06:36:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529438</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0050</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 21:13:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 0050</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:18:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7163</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/23/2023 06:36:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529438</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 21:13:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:18:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7163</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/23/2023 06:36:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529438</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3 4025</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 21:13:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>PAINT IN DOOR JAM OF L-43</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3 4025</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:18:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7163</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/23/2023 06:36:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:24:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7163</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 08:24:04</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>394197</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>WALLS</LastName>
               <FirstName>DERRICK</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LUCAS</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/04/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/30/2023 08:22:19</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>WALLS</LastName>
               <FirstName>DERRICK</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LUCAS</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/04/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/30/2023 08:22:19</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1345</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Harvard</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>NW</StreetSuffixCode>
               <City>Washington</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20009</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4903</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.0314869</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.9268604</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:24:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:24:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:24:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:24:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:32:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 08:32:21</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>329590</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Harr</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trooper</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/19/2021 04:15:05</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T616</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Harr</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trooper</FirstName>
               <SLastName>H600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T616</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/19/2021 04:15:05</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3500</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Forestville</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Forestville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20747</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.8736725</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.8403326</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>568</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8101</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/19/2021 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:32:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:32:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:14:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7163</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 08:14:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154733</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:34:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7163</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 08:34:58</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/01/2023 20:31:12</DateOfInfo>
         <DateOfInfo>11/11/2023 08:34:04</DateOfInfo>
         <DateOfInfo>07/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3ALACWDTXEDFJ4172</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FRHT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>M2</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>DS</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>YEL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>YEL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>YEL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>YEL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8EG8938</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicNumber>97709TA</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8EG8938</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2022</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicYear>2022</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehDamageCode>0</VehDamageCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159409</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>VI</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7163</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 08:42:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7163</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 08:42:18</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FM5K8AB4MGC41437</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2021</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>XPL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>L-43</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>ST</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehicleValue>500</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>