<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-039552</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/09/2023 08:15:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/09/2023 08:15:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/09/2023 06:30:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/09/2023 06:30:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Missing Person</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 08:15:42</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5162</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 09:41:10</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>MP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>712565</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 08:15:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 09:09:18</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>712565</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>6124</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>9th</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Chesapeake Beach</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20732</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.537051</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.66303</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/09/2023 08:15:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/09/2023 08:15:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/12/2023 17:59:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 08:15:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On Thursday, November 9, 2023, at approximately 0726 hours, I, Trooper D. Miller, #7666, responded to 6124 9th Street Chesapeake Beach, Calvert County, Maryland, 20732, for the report of a missing person.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Upon my arrival I made contact with the complainant, Robert Steven White Jr (W/M 04/11/1985). White stated he had not seen or heard from his sister, Reina Milagro Andujar (H/F 11/28/1990) in a few days, and he was concerned for her well-being. White stated he last saw Andujar on Tuesday, November 7, at approximately 1400 hours at both of their residence, 6124 9th Street, Chesapeake Beach, Maryland, 20732. White stated that Andujar left the residence while on the way to get her boyfriend, Tyson Wayne Black (W/M 04/11/1988) to take him back to his court-ordered live-in rehab facility located in the Glen Burnie area.&amp;nbsp; Andujar told White that Black had overdosed while at rehab and was taken to a Glen Burnie area hospital. White was unable to provide any additional information on the rehab facility or the hospital. White stated Andujar left the residence driving his vehicle, MD registration, 5FD4341, a gray 2015 GMC Sierra.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;White stated that Andujar never returned home. White stated he had been calling and texting Andujar (667-321-4599) since then trying to get her to respond. White stated that Andujar replied with one message on Wednesday, November 8, 2023, at approximately 0907 hours. White advised Andujar stated her phone&amp;#39;s battery had died, and she was currently on her way to Bank of America in Upper Marlboro. White stated this was the last time he heard from Andujar . White stated he had been calling and texting her however has not gotten a reply. White advised that Andujar had a doctor&amp;#39;s appointment in Glen Burnie on Wednesday, November 7, 2023, to get her suboxone prescription refilled however he is unsure if she went to that appointment. White advised Andujar had used heroin in the past however she has been using suboxone for approximately 10 years to treat her addiction. White stated he is unaware of any relapses in Andujar&amp;#39;s sobriety, and he is confident she would get her suboxone if at all possible.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;White advised this is unusual for Andujar . White stated he is caring for Andujar&amp;#39;s four-year-old daughter and unusual for her to not be around or check in on her. White advised he was concerned for Andujar&amp;#39;s&amp;nbsp; welfare because Black is dangerous. White advised Black was never returned to his rehab facility and currently has multiple warrants for his arrest. White advised if/when Black is apprehended, he has a lot of outstanding jail time, and he is worried about what Black is capable of doing to Andujar . White advised he is furthermore concerned for Andujar&amp;#39;s welfare because Andujar has approximately $16,000.00 in her bank account and that was the last known location Andujar and Black were going. White does not even know if Andujar was infarct the person who texted him from Andujar&amp;#39;s phone, and he is concerned Black could have already done something to harm Andujar . White requested to report Andujar as a missing person.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;White stated Andujar frequently uses Facebook and her profile name is Reina Andujar and her profile picture is a photograph of her two children.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;White confirmed the last time he saw Andujar was on 11/7/2023 at 1400 hours at 6124 9th Street, Chesapeake Beach, Maryland, wearing a gray shirt and gray legging-style pants. White advised Andujar is 5&amp;#39;03&amp;quot; weighs 185 pounds, and is Hispanic with a dark olive skin complexion. White stated that Andujar has a star tattoo on both wrists and &amp;quot;Tyson&amp;quot; tattooed on her left hand between her thumb and pointer finger. White stated that Andujar had been living with him for some time now, and he has custody of Andujar and Black&amp;#39;s child, and it is extremely unlike her to not make contact in any way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Troopers responded to Black&amp;#39;s most recent Calvert County address, 4001 7th Street, Chesapeake Beach, Maryland with negative findings. Troopers checked Andujar&amp;#39;s previous address of 5051 Bayside Drive Huntingtown, Maryland with negative findings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;White advised Andujar recently gained employment with Breezy Point Market located in Chesapeake Beach, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Andujar was entered into NCIC as a missing person&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I contacted the Southern Maryland Information Center (SMIC) and Maryland Coordination and Analysis (MCAC) in reference to obtaining License Plate Reader information on the 2015 GMC Sierra bearing Maryland registration, 5FD4341.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I contacted Calvert County Health Department in reference to obtaining information on Andujar&amp;#39;s where about.&amp;nbsp; I learned Andujar has not been under the care of Calvert County Health Department since 2022.&amp;nbsp; Calvert County Health Department advised Andujar&amp;rsquo;s file was transferred to Dr. Fuller with Brightwell Health.&amp;nbsp; I contacted Brightwell Health and learned Andujar had a tele-appointment scheduled for Novemeber 11.&amp;nbsp; I learned Andujar called Brightwell Health however was never seen for the tele-appontment.&amp;nbsp; Brightwell Health advised they would make contact with me if Andujar contacted them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I contacted Breezy Point Market, 410-535 -3311 and made contact with management.&amp;nbsp; I learned Andujar was not employed with them since 2017.&amp;nbsp; Management was familiar with Andujar however has not seen or heard from her in quite some time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Case open pending locating Andujar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 09:37:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7666</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/13/2023 19:03:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Snyder</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colby</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7588</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dustin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5032</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dylan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7666</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 09:31:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 09:31:41</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392527</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Black</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyson</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/25/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/09/2023 09:31:21</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Black</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyson</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/25/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/09/2023 09:31:21</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 09:31:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158796</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 09:36:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7666</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 09:36:44</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1GTV2UEC0FZ335340</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SRA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5FD4341</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleValue>27000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/10/2023 10:26:30</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/10/2023 10:26:30</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/12/2023 17:59:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6933</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/10/2023 10:26:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Supplemental Narrative/Follow-Up:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On Friday, November 10, 2023, at approximately 1000 hours, I contacted the following hospitals and Emergency Rooms to check if Reina Andujar or Tyson Black had been seen or admitted: &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Arundel Medical Center Luminis Health-Spoke to Chantel in Patient Information&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Capitol Regional Medical Center-Emergency Room&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;University of Maryland Baltimore Washington Medical Center&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;University of Maryland Medical Center Shock Trauma&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Medstar St. Mary&amp;#39;s Hospital&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;University of Maryland Charles Regional Medical Center&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;CalvertHealth Medical Center&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Mercy Medical Center-advised that Tyson Black was seen by them in July of this year for an overdose but is not currently admitted.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; All the following hospitals reported that neither Reina Andujar nor Tyson Black was seen or admitted as of today.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Cpl. Brill #5032 made contact with the complainant and family at approximately 0800 hours to follow-up. Cpl. Brill also spoke to a representative from Maryland Coordination and Analysis Center (MCAC) advising the GMC Sierra truck with Maryland Registration (5FD4341) went through a tag reader on Interstate 695 at approximately 1445 hours yesterday (11/9/2023). There has been no contact with Reina Andujar at this time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Calvert County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6933</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/10/2023 10:27:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6933</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/13/2023 12:11:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dustin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5032</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>DeLeon</LastName>
            <FirstName>Linsay</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6933</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/13/2023 19:27:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/13/2023 19:27:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/12/2023 17:59:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/13/2023 19:27:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On Monday, November 13, 2023, at approximately 1900 hours, I, made contact with complainant, Robert White in reference to a follow-up on the above investigation.&amp;nbsp; Upon making contact with white via telephone I learned White had no additional information to provide. White stated he continues to attempt to make contact with Andujar however has been unable to do so.&amp;nbsp; White stated he does not think Andujar is opening her Facebook.com messages as the unread icon is showing on his sent messages.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I provided White with an updated case synopsis and asked him to make contact with me if any new information is learned.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I attempted to make contact with Andujar at the following telephone number, 667-321-4599 with negative results.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I made contact with Senior Agent Tamara Piper of the Maryland Department of Public Safety and Correctional Services Intelligence and Investigative Division. Senior Agent Piper advised Andujar was on low supervision and her agent, Agent Moyer attempted to make contact with her with negative results.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I received an update from the MCAC in reference to License Plate Reader information.&amp;nbsp; The most recent LPR &amp;quot;hit&amp;quot; on 11/12/2023 at 0459 hours at the area of SE Pulaski Highway and Conkling Street, Baltimore, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; At approximately 2000 hours, I made contact with Baltimore Police Department in reference to checking the area of 3600 Pulaski Highway, the Executive Inn Motel.&amp;nbsp; Baltimore Police Department conducted an attempt to locate the area in an attempt to locate the 2015 GMC Sierra bearing Maryland registration, 5FD4341 with negative results.&amp;nbsp; Baltimore Police Department canvassed the area and checked numerous pay by the day/night hotels/motels for Andujar and the 2015 GMC Sierra bearing Maryland registration, 5FD4341, with negative results.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case open pending locating Andujar.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/13/2023 19:28:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7666</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/13/2023 21:37:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pilkerton</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4319</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dylan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7666</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/14/2023 19:31:54</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/14/2023 19:31:54</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/12/2023 17:59:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 19:31:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On Tuesday, November 14, 2023, at approximately 1705 hours, Andujar&amp;#39;s GMC Sierra, bearing Maryland registration, 5FD4341, license plate was read on a Baltimore Police Department&amp;#39;s mobile vehicle license plate reader in the area of 3436 Wilkens Avenue, Baltimore, Maryland, 21229.&amp;nbsp; Based on the LPR photograph provided by MCAC I believe the truck was parked and occupied based on the fact the trucked was pulled into a parking spot and the brake lights were illuminated.&amp;nbsp; The truck was possibly parked in front of the 7-Eleven convenience store at the above address.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I contacted the Baltimore Police Department in reference to attempting to locate the Andujar and the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; Baltimore Police Department communications advised they had nobody available and were unable to assist at this time.&amp;nbsp; I provided the communications specialist with the LPR number, &amp;quot;BPD SW 199655&amp;quot;, and requested the police officer operating this vehicle contact me at their earliest convenience.&amp;nbsp; As of this writing I have not yet been contacted.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At approximately 1920 hours I contacted Robert White to update him of my recent findings.&amp;nbsp; White advised he has yet to hear from Andujar and had no new information to provide.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case open pending locating Andujar.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 19:33:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7666</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 19:45:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pilkerton</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4319</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dylan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7666</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/15/2023 21:56:05</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/15/2023 21:56:05</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/12/2023 17:59:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 21:56:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #4 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On Wednesday, November 15, 2023, I contacted Jessica White via email.&amp;nbsp; I emailed White a photograph from the license plate reader from a read on November 11, 2023, in the area of the Baltimore Harbor Tunnel Southbound lane. White confirmed in the photograph Black was seen operating the 2015 GMC Sierra bearing Maryland registration, 5FD4341 and Andujar was in the front passenger seat.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I provided White with a 12-hour update on the investigation.&amp;nbsp; White has not had any contact with Andujar.&amp;nbsp; White was unable to provide any additional information.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Investigation open pending locating Andujar.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 21:57:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7666</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/16/2023 18:39:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pilkerton</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4319</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dylan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7666</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>5</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/16/2023 18:40:21</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/16/2023 18:40:21</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/12/2023 17:59:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/16/2023 18:40:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #5 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On Thursday, November 16, 2023, at approximately 1720 hours the Maryland State Police Prince Frederick Barrack was contacted by the Bowie Police Department in reference to missing person Reina Andujar.&amp;nbsp; Bowie Police Department advised they located the 2015 GMC Sierra bearing Maryland registration, 5FD4341 inside their jurisdiction.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I contacted Officer Franks #0114 with the Bowie Police Department.&amp;nbsp; I learned MDaryland registration; 5FD4341 was read on a Mobile License Plate Reader from the Seat Pleasant Police Department.&amp;nbsp; Seat Pleasant, Police Officer observed the operator park the truck in the parking lot of the Bowie Town Center, 15606 Emerald Way, Baltimore, Maryland and exit the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; Bowie Police Officer Franks arrived on scene shortly after.&amp;nbsp; Upon making contact with Officer Franks via cell phone I requested he kept a visual on the truck in an attempt to locate Andujar.&amp;nbsp; A few minutes later Andujar was observed walking back to the truck.&amp;nbsp; Officer Franks observed Andujar to be alone and nobody with her.&amp;nbsp; Officer Franks made contact with Andujar.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Officer Franks learned Andujar had been with Tyson Black for a few days, and recently they had gotten into some type of domestic dispute in the Glen Burnie, Maryland area.&amp;nbsp; Andujar advised she needed to get away which is why she was in Bowie.&amp;nbsp; Franks advised Andujar was in good health and appeared unharmed.&amp;nbsp; Andujar advised she was on her way home to Chesapeake Beach, Maryland and that she would contact her brother, White.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Andujar was removed from NCIC.&amp;nbsp; I contacted White to inform him Andujar was located unharmed.&amp;nbsp; I contacted SMIC and advised Andujar was located, and requested an updated SMIC bulletin be distributed.&amp;nbsp; I contacted MCAC and informed MCAC Andujar and the 2015 GMC Sierra bearing Maryland registration, 5FD4341, had been located and there was no need for any additional LPR reads.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Investigation closed, nothing further.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/16/2023 18:41:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7666</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/16/2023 19:14:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pilkerton</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4319</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dylan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7666</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>6</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/17/2023 19:43:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/17/2023 19:43:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/12/2023 17:59:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 19:43:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #6 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On Thursday, November 9, 2023, at approximately 0726 hours, I, Trooper D. Miller, #7666, responded to 6124 9th Street Chesapeake Beach, Calvert County, Maryland, 20732, for the report of a missing person.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Upon my arrival I made contact with the complainant, Robert Steven White Jr (W/M 04/11/1985). R. White stated he had not seen or heard from his sister, Reina Milagro Andujar (H/F 11/28/1990) in a few days, and he was concerned for her well-being. R. White stated he last saw Andujar on Tuesday, November 7, at approximately 1400 hours at both of their residence, 6124 9th Street, Chesapeake Beach, Maryland, 20732. R. White stated that Andujar left the residence while on the way to get her boyfriend, Tyson Wayne Black (W/M 04/11/1988) to take him back to his court-ordered live-in rehab facility located in the Glen Burnie area. Andujar told R. White that Black had overdosed while at rehab and was taken to a Glen Burnie area hospital. White was unable to provide any additional information on the rehab facility or the hospital. R. White stated Andujar left the residence driving his vehicle, MD registration, 5FD4341, a gray 2015 GMC Sierra. R. White stated that Andujar never returned home. R. White stated he had been calling and texting Andujar (667-321-4599) since then trying to get her to respond with no response. R. White advised he text Andujar instructing her to bring home his truck as she no longer had permission to drive it.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I completed a missing persons report with the Maryland State Police Prince Frederick Barrack. Andujar was entered into NCIC as a missing person. On Thursday, November 16, 2023, at approximately 1720 hours the Maryland State Police Prince Frederick Barrack was contacted by the Bowie Police Department in reference to missing person Reina Andujar. Bowie Police Department advised they located the 2015 GMC Sierra bearing Maryland registration, 5FD4341 inside their jurisdiction. The Bowie Police Department had located Andujar and learned Andujar had been with Tyson Black for a few days, and recently they had gotten into some type of domestic dispute in the Glen Burnie, Maryland area. Andujar advised she needed to get away which is why she was in Bowie. Bowie Police Department advised Andujar was in good health and appeared unharmed. Andujar advised The Bowie Police Department she was on her way home to Chesapeake Beach, Maryland, and that she would contact her brother, R. White, and return his truck.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As of Friday, November 17, 2023, Andujar has not returned home nor has she returned R. White and J. White&amp;#39;s 2015 GMC Sierra bearing Maryland registration, 5FD4341 (VIN- 1GTV2UEC0FZ335340). J. White contacted me and requested charges be filed against Andujar for unlawful use and/or theft of a motor vehicle. At approximately 1610 hours I responded to 6124 9th Street Chesapeake Beach, Maryland, and made contact with Jessica White. J. White provided a written statement. The 2015 GMC Sierra is valued at $27,000. R. White and J. White advised Andujar has not contacted them in any way and was not given permission to drive the truck since November 7, 2023. J. White advised Andujar was only given permission to drive the truck to pick up Black and Andujar was to return the truck the same day. Both R. White and J. White are listed as the owners through the Maryland Motor Vehicle Administration.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I completed an application of charges and respectfully requested Andujar be charged with unlawful removal of motor vehicle and/or motor vehicle unlawful taking, as well as any additional charges the commissioner believes apply.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On November 17, 2023, an arrest warrant was issued for Andujar charging her with&amp;nbsp;unlawful removal of motor vehicle and/or motor vehicle unlawful taking, and theft $25,000 to $100,000.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I respectfully request this investigation status be changed to open, pending follow up until Andujar is located and served with the arrest warrant.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All the above events did occur in Calvert County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 19:44:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7666</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/21/2023 02:58:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pilkerton</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4319</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dylan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7666</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>7</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/25/2023 05:41:32</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/25/2023 05:41:32</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>83</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/12/2023 17:59:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/25/2023 05:41:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #7 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On Friday, November 24, 2023, the Maryland Transportation Authority Police contacted the Maryland State Police Prince Frederick Barrack.&amp;nbsp; The MDTA advised they located the 2015 GMC Sierra bearing Maryland registration, 5FD4341.&amp;nbsp; The vehicle was taken by Taubers Towing located in Lithicum Heights, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; The MDTA later located Andujar and served her with the active warrant.&amp;nbsp; Cpl. Davis made contact with the Whites to inform them of the above events&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed, no further investigation required.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/25/2023 05:51:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7666</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/25/2023 05:54:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pilkerton</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4319</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>83</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dylan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7666</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529020</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1466</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>7</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 06:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1466</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/25/2023 05:48:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7666</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/25/2023 05:48:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 09:29:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7666</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/25/2023 06:15:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392526</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Andujar</LastName>
               <FirstName>Reina</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Milagro</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/24/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14316886E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>11/09/2023 09:29:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Andujar</LastName>
               <FirstName>Reina</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Milagro</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/24/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14316886E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>A532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/09/2023 09:29:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6124</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>9th</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Chesapeake Beach</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20732</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.537051</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.66303</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>667</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>321</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4599</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/25/2023 06:15:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/25/2023 06:15:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 09:33:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/25/2023 06:01:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392528</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>White</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Steven</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/11/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/09/2023 09:33:03</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>White</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Steven</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/11/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/09/2023 09:33:03</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6124</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>9th</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Chesapeake Beach</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20732</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.537051</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.66303</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>512</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7871</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 09:33:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/25/2023 06:01:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158796</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>ST</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7666</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/25/2023 06:01:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7666</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/25/2023 06:01:58</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1GTV2UEC0FZ335340</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SRA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5FD4341</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleValue>27000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>