<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>24-MSP-001143</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/11/2024 10:15:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/11/2024 10:15:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/11/2024 08:52:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/11/2024 08:52:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Firearm violation investigation.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/11/2024 10:15:25</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 09:42:14</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>718579</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>564</SubBeat>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/11/2024 10:15:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/11/2024 19:31:48</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>718579</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>4206</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Hunter</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <StreetSuffixCode>S</StreetSuffixCode>
         <City>Hampstead</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21074</Zip5>
         <Zip4>2104</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.845947</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.619029</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/11/2024 10:15:22</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/11/2024 10:15:22</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>Y</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/17/2024 18:02:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/11/2024 10:15:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6579</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/17/2024 18:03:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>See Supplement #1.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2024 17:58:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/17/2024 18:00:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phelps</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7210</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McCarty</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cade</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6579</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Meekins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4876</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phelps</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7210</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/11/2024 19:30:29</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/11/2024 19:30:29</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>Y</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1201</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/17/2024 18:03:09</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/11/2024 19:30:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6579</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/17/2024 18:03:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Portions of this investigation were captured on body worn and in car camera.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ATTACHMENTS:&lt;br /&gt; Search Warrant (Application and Signed Warrant)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Form 67 &amp;amp; PH &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;METERS printouts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Gun Center documentation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;INTERVIEWED:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Joy Allison Cox&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; W/F&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 10/13/1986&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;4206 S Hunter Rd&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Hampstead, MD&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;717-321-3058&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;INTERVIEWED:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Amanda Gilbart&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; W/F&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 04/24/1977&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;129 Pheasant Ridge Dr&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Hanover, PA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;410-848-1050 (office)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; SUSPECT:&lt;br /&gt; Paul Jacob Cox&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; W/M&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 11/12/1986&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;4206 S Hunter Rd&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Hampstead, MD&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;443-789-2904&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; NARRATIVE:&lt;br /&gt; On 01/10/2024, at approximately 1100 hours, Maryland State Police from the Westminster Barrack received a call from Amanda Gilbart. Amanda stated that she is the principal at the Carroll Lutheran School in Westminster, MD. Amanda was expressing concern over a domestic violence situation her staff member is experiencing and the implications it has for her school. M/Tpr. Meekins spoke at length with Amanda over the phone.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; M/Tpr. Meekins relayed to me the following information:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Amanda is the principal at Carroll Lutheran School located at 1738 Old Taneytown Rd., Westminster, MD. Her employee is Joy Allison Cox. According to Amanda, Joy confided in her that she is planning to leave her husband, Paul Jacob Cox. Joy expressed to Amanda that she was worried about her safety, saying something to the effect that she was scared to be at home. Amanda has had negative interactions previously with Paul which resulted in her contacting his supervisor. Amanda expressed concern for Joy&amp;rsquo;s safety as well as for the safety of her school, staff and students. Amanda explained that Paul is a Carroll County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Deputy. According to Amanda, Paul worked with Carroll Lutheran School to develop an active shooter response plan. He also brought in staff and conducted training for their plan.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Given the circumstances, M/Tpr. Meekins notified Command Staff at the Westminster Barrack and the decision was made to meet with Amanda and Joy the following day at the Westminster Barrack. M/Tpr. Meekins, D/Sgt. John McGee and I conducted an in-depth interview with Amanda and Joy.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; According to Joy, she and Paul live at 4206 S Hunter Rd., Hampstead, MD and have been married for approximately 11 years. She reported that they have had their problems over the years but there was a shift approximately 2.5 years prior. At that time, Joy&amp;rsquo;s and Paul&amp;rsquo;s children were victimized by a family member (reported separately). After that incident, Joy began to notice the way Paul treated her and the children.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Joy explained that since then, things have escalated and their arguments have become more volatile. She explained that eventually Paul began to throw things during arguments. Initially she did not think he was throwing objects &lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;at&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; her, but soon it was clear that he was. She referred to one specific incident on 01/07/2024 when Paul threw a &amp;ldquo;Beanie Baby&amp;rdquo; at her, despite the fact that her daughter, age 3, was on her lap.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; We asked Joy and learned that at no point has Paul physically abused or assaulted her or their children. She also said that he has not specifically threatened to harm her or the children. However, she said that Paul has numerous guns.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; During the course of the conversation about guns, Joy mentioned that Paul does not secure his firearms and leaves them out in common spaces. Joy described that about 2 years ago her youngest child (then age 2) got a hold of one of the guns. She described turning around to see the child holding a handgun and saying something to the effect of &amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m going to shoot you. Joy said that the child was holding the gun oriented in the designed firing manner; the barrel was facing her.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Joy said that she constantly confronts Paul and asks him to lock the guns up but he seems to diminished the issue. Paul regularly says things to the effect that the children do not have the strength to pull the slide back (referring to the action of loading a live round into the chamber) or that he does not leave a magazine in the gun. When asked to clarify, she said that sometimes Paul will leave the magazine separate from, but close by, the gun. Joy said that she has shot guns before and described that when the magazine is kept out of, but close to, the gun, the magazine is loaded with live cartridges.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Despite repeated requests, Paul continues to leave firearms unsecure throughout the house. Joy told me that when she finds the guns out, she puts them away in one of the gun safes that are in their home.&amp;nbsp; Joy said that there are two primary locations where Paul leaves the guns unsecure. One location is on a cabinet in the dining room. The cabinet is approximately 5 feet high. The other location is in the bedroom, usually on a nightstand or a dresser.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Joy provided three photographs. Two pictures capture the image of a black semi-automatic handgun. The photographs appear to be dated. The first image appears to show the date 11/06/2023. The image shows a black handgun laid on its side on the top of a white dresser. There are other items on the dresser, including some pictures and sticks of deodorant. There is a magazine approximately 5 inches to the right. Based on my training, knowledge and experience, the gun is consistent with a &amp;ldquo;Glock&amp;rdquo; brand handgun and the magazine appears consistent with the magazine designed for the gun. There is no magazine in this gun.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The second image, apparently dated 11/25/2023, shows a black semi-automatic handgun in a black leather holster. The gun is laid on its side on top of a white dresser, amidst other items. Based on my training, knowledge, and experience, the gun appears consistent with a &amp;ldquo;Glock&amp;rdquo; brand firearm. The magazine is fully inserted into the magazine well (grip) of the firearm.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The final image, apparently dated 12/21/2023, shows a handgun on the white dresser. The barrel of the gun is black, the frame of the gun is brown and there is a black magazine inserted in the magazine well (grip) of the gun.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the description Joy provided and the angle of the image, the height of the white nightstand appears to be approximately 3 feet tall. Both rooms are accessible to the children. There are 3 children in the house: a boy, age 9; a boy, age 7; and a girl, age 3.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Troopers escorted Joy to the County Commissioner&amp;#39;s office where Joy applied for and obtained a protective order. The order was served a short time after issuance.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the facts and circumstances outlined above, investigators believe that probable cause exists that there may be loaded firearms in a location that is accessible by an unsupervised minor. On 01/11/2024, Troopers drafted and obtained a search warrant at 4206 S Hunter Rd Hampstead, MD. The warrant was signed by the Honorable Judge Danz. Troopers responded to the address to execute the warrant. Upon our arrival, Joy, who was on scene, told Troopers that she had seen Paul&amp;#39;s brother, Ronald, driving down the road a short distance from the house (near the intersection of Business MD30 on Fairmount Rd). Joy described the vehicle Ronald drove, a bright red, lifted Jeep. I saw the vehicle in the same area. Joy told us that Ronald has no reason to be in the area and that the side door to the house should be unlocked. However, at that time it was locked. Joy suspected that Ronald had been at the house.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; D/Sgt. McGee went to try and locate Ronald while Troopers executed the warrant. The warrant was executed at approximately 1644 hours. During the search, one firearm, a Titan .25 cal handgun s/n A61996, was located unsecure and seized.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The handgun seized was located in the room Joy identified as her bedroom. The firearm was located in the closet. Within the closet, a hook was hung on the wall just inside the threshold of the closet. The handgun was hung on the hook such that the hook protruded through the trigger guard. Upon closer look, the handgun had a magazine secured in the magazine well. There were 7 live cartridges loaded in the magazine. There was no live round loaded in the chamber. The hook was approximately 7 feet from the ground. The closet was unsecured; the closet doors were on sliding rails and featured no locks. Additionally, it should be noted that there was a chair against the wall approximately 5 feet from the closet opening. The chair was approximately 18 inches tall from the floor to the top of the seat.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; There were no other firearms seized in violation of the aforementioned crime. However, it should be noted that after consultation with Joy about the guns we located, she indicated that she believed that there were guns that were unaccounted for. Joy gained access to one of the two gun safes stored in the bedroom. The missing guns were not in that gun safe but, at the time, she was not able to access the second safe. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;At the conclusion of the search warrant, S/Tpr. Barry, D/Sgt. McGee and I went and interviewed Ronald. He denied being at the house, said that he did not remember his exact route through the area as we checked on his rental property and overall denied any involvement or role in this investigation and the missing guns. It should be noted that Ronald seemed somewhat uncooperative and agitated.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The seized handgun was transported to the Westminster State Police Barrack where it was submitted into evidence according to procedure.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 01/12/2024, D/Sgt. McGee conducted follow up reference this case, which will be documented in a separate report. At this time, there are guns which are still unaccounted for. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;At this time, the investigation continues and additional investigative action will be documented appropriately.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/12/2024 10:06:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/12/2024 15:12:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McCarty</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cade</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6579</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phelps</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7210</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2024 19:42:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/12/2024 15:16:33</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>397390</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cox</LastName>
               <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jacob</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/12/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/11/2024 19:41:50</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cox</LastName>
               <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jacob</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/12/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/11/2024 19:41:50</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4206</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Hunter</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>S</StreetSuffixCode>
               <City>Hampstead</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21074</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2104</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.845947</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.619029</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>789</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2904</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/12/2024 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/11/2024 19:42:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/11/2024 19:42:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2024 19:44:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/12/2024 15:17:11</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>397391</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cox</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Allison</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/13/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/11/2024 19:44:50</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J000</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cox</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Allison</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/13/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J000</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/11/2024 19:44:50</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4206</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Hunter</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>S</StreetSuffixCode>
               <City>Hampstead</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21074</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2104</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.845947</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.619029</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>717</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>321</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3058</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/12/2024 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/11/2024 19:45:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/11/2024 19:45:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>46</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/12/2024 15:19:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/12/2024 15:19:43</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>397460</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Gilbart</LastName>
               <FirstName>Amanda</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Victoria</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/24/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/12/2024 15:19:30</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A553</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Gilbart</LastName>
               <FirstName>Amanda</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Victoria</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/24/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A553</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/12/2024 15:19:30</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>129</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Pheasant Ridge</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hanover</City>
               <StateCode>PA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>17331</Zip5>
               <Zip4>9844</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.944278</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.750576</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/12/2024 15:19:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/12/2024 15:19:43</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/12/2024 15:19:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/12/2024 15:19:43</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/12/2024 15:22:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/12/2024 15:22:50</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>397461</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cox</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jay</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/25/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>01/12/2024 15:22:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R543</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cox</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jay</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/25/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R543</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/12/2024 15:22:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1335</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Old Manchester</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Westminster</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21157</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3831</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.94916</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.59687</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>846</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2959</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/12/2024 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7210</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/12/2024 15:22:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7210</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/12/2024 15:22:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/12/2024 11:32:14</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/12/2024 11:32:14</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/17/2024 16:51:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP2173</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/12/2024 11:32:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6579</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/17/2024 18:03:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Gun Center ATTACHMENTS Added.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ACTION TAKEN&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; See other reports for detailed events.&amp;nbsp; This report is centered around the coordination between the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack, MSP Gun Unit, and the Carroll County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Department.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On Thursday 1/12/2024, I, Detective Sergeant Jon McGee, became involved in a barrack investigation reported to MSP personnel by Joy Cox.&amp;nbsp; The investigation led to Mrs. Cox completing and obtaining a protective order against her husband Paul Cox. During the investigation information relating to unsecured firearms lying around the house which their children have and could again gain access to was discovered.&amp;nbsp; Paul Cox is a deputy with the Carroll County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Department.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Therefore, my role in this investigation was not as a primary investigator but as the MSP contact Command Staff with the Carroll County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Office.&amp;nbsp; During the investigation, and as Mrs. Cox was in the process of obtaining a Protective Order I made contact with Carroll County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Command Staff, Col. Hart, and briefed him about our current investigation.&amp;nbsp; The reason was that if and when the Protective Order was obtained I knew that sent an alert to the Sheriff&amp;#39;s Department to serve the Protective Order.&amp;nbsp; While this was occurring, MSP troopers were also gathering information and authoring a search warrant for the Cox&amp;#39;s residence centered around the search for unsecured firearms.&amp;nbsp; If the Protective Order and search warrant were granted there would be two different tracks to the investigation.&amp;nbsp; A search for unsecured firearms by MSP and then a secondary recovery/removal of &amp;quot;all&amp;quot; firearms if ordered through the Protective Order.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Both the Protective Order was approved and issued around 1445 hours that afternoon.&amp;nbsp; I do not recall the time, but the search warrant was later approved around 1700 hours.&amp;nbsp; After the approval of the search warrant, myself, M/T Barry (MSP CED), TFC Phelps and S/T Meekins along with Mrs. Cox traveled to the residence.&amp;nbsp; Upon arrival, Mrs. Cox was nervous and stated that she had just seen her brother-in-law&amp;#39;s jeep heading the opposite way on Fairmount Road. The information was relayed to me but as best I can recall she stated she observed the Jeep between the RT 30 and the first stop sign on Fairmount Road.&amp;nbsp; During the execution of the search warrant, I was advised that troopers found one unsecured firearm in the master bedroom closet.&amp;nbsp; The firearm was a Titan .25 cal silver semi-auto with a serial number of A61996 which was seized as part of our investigation for unsecured firearms. The details about the location of that handgun will be in one of the other supplemental reports.&amp;nbsp; During this time I was made aware by the sheriff&amp;#39;s department that they were with Paul Cox at the sheriff&amp;#39;s department where they served the Protective Order and took possession of his agency duty weapon and a long gun (there could have been others long guns).&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;While MSP Troopers were completing the search warrant I traveled to Ronald Cox&amp;#39;s address (brother of Paul Cox and owner of the observed Jeep) at 1335 Old Manchester Road.&amp;nbsp; Ronald Cox was not there, but my information was provided to his roommate.&amp;nbsp; At approximately 1800 hours I received a call from Ronald Cox.&amp;nbsp; I asked if he had been at his brother&amp;#39;s residence today and if he had taken anything out of the residence.&amp;nbsp; He advised no.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Deputy Rex Scott of the CCSO was also on scene waiting for our search warrant phase to end and where the CCSO could seize the other firearms due to the protective order. Mrs. Cox was able to open one of the two gun safes in the master bedroom.&amp;nbsp; If facing the two safes, she was able to open the one on the right.&amp;nbsp; Within that safe I was advised that there was a CCSO shotgun and a Sig Sauer P225 semi-auto handgun.&amp;nbsp; Mrs. Cox could not find the key to the safe on the left.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After our Search Warrant and what information CCSO passed along about the firearms they seized it appeared that we are missing 3 handguns, possibly 4.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ACCORDING to documentation the following handguns are registered to Paul Cox&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1. Sig Sauer P225 9mm Ser# M498457 -- I was told that it was located in the safe on the right.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 2. Gun Make TAS Model 1485 - which should be a Taurus 38 cal revolver&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Ser# CT76638 -- &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;NOT LOCATED&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 3. Titan .25 cal Ser# 170545 -- &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;NOT LOCATED&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 4. Titan .25 cal Ser# - NONE.&amp;nbsp; This could be the handgun MSP seized during the SW.&amp;nbsp; MSP Seized a Titan .25 with a serial number A61996.&amp;nbsp; The absent serial number on the report could be an error when the firearm was entered into the database or this is a missing handgun as well.&amp;nbsp; I contacted Sgt. Meyers from the Gun Center to follow up on. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;NOT SURE YET&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 5. Purchased firearm that has not been entered in the MAIFs system yet.&amp;nbsp; According to MSP Licensing Div.&amp;nbsp; Application # 2023125919.&amp;nbsp; Paul Cox purchased a Beretta APX A1 9mm semi-automatic Ser# AXC119346 from Bass Pro Shop on 11/27/2023 with a received date of 12/05/2023&amp;nbsp; -- &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;NOT LOCATED&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After the search warrant, M/T Barry, TFC Phelps and I went back to Ronald Cox&amp;#39;s residence to see if he was there.&amp;nbsp; M/T Barry and TFC Phelps spoke to him directly.&amp;nbsp; Refer to their report.&amp;nbsp; However, Ronald Cox again stated he had not been at or in his brother&amp;#39;s house and that the last time he was there was sometime around New Year&amp;#39;s because of a sump pump issue he helped his brother.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 1/11/2024 at approximately 2245 hours Capt Debord texted me to advise that Cox has shut down and had not produced the above-listed firearms.&amp;nbsp; According to Capt Debord, Cox advised that he gifted the guns to someone (would not provide name) and does not have them or know where they are located.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 1/12/2024 I reached out to Cpl. Marcus Jackson of our MSP Gun Unit regarding the missing &amp;quot;gifted&amp;quot; firearms.&amp;nbsp; Cpl. Jackson was briefed and will be assisting in the investigation.&amp;nbsp; At approximately 1230 hours I received a call from Cpl. Jackson advising Mrs. Cox located a possible key to the left safe.&amp;nbsp; I contacted CCSO and they had a Sergeant meet me at the residence to secure whatever we found in the safe.&amp;nbsp; Mrs. Joy Cox pointed to the key she found.&amp;nbsp; I took the key and opened the left safe (the one we could not access the evening before).&amp;nbsp; There were only two BB guns located in the safe along with ammunition.&amp;nbsp; According to the Protective Order only firearms were to be seized.&amp;nbsp; Since the two BB guns and the ammo fell outside the scope of the Protective Order they were returned and locked back in the safe.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case remains open.&amp;nbsp; Updates have been provided to all agencies/ units involved.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP2173</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/12/2024 14:27:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/16/2024 10:43:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McCarty</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cade</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6579</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mcgee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2173</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>