<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-039365</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/07/2023 19:22:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/07/2023 19:22:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/07/2023 18:29:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/07/2023 18:29:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Theft / Fraud</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 19:22:39</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4792</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/12/2023 14:41:17</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FRD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>THT</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>470896</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 19:22:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 20:15:16</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>470896</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>28241</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Vesely</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Princess Anne</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21853</Zip5>
         <Zip4>3367</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.773889</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.253889</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/07/2023 19:22:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/07/2023 19:22:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/15/2023 04:30:27</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 19:22:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5794</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/21/2023 13:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; Princess Anne Barrack &amp;quot;X&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; Tpr. Wright #7521&lt;br /&gt; Field Operation Bureau&lt;br /&gt; (11/07/2023)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div&gt;This incident was recorded by body-worn camera.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Case Number: 23-MSP-039365&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Attachments:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;(8) Trailer Photos&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;(2) Copy of title for &amp;quot;Starcraft&amp;quot; RV&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;(1) Copy of bill of sale for $3,500&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Screenshot of Cargo Mate Trailer title&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Type of Report:&lt;/strong&gt; Theft / Fraud&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Suspect:&lt;/strong&gt; George Francis Hilker Jr. (2/M, DOB&amp;nbsp;01/24/1978,&amp;nbsp;28241 Vesely Lane, Princess Anne, MD 21853)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Victim:&lt;/strong&gt; Marco Tulio Lopez-Salgado (5/M, DOB&amp;nbsp;06/03/1990, 321 Naylor Street, Salisbury, MD 21804)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Witnesses / Interviewed:&lt;/strong&gt; Terri Lee Moss (2/F, DOB 10/16/1963, 28225 Vesely Lane, Princess Anne, MD 21853)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Jeremy Lee Classing (2/M, DOB&amp;nbsp;06/28/1995,&amp;nbsp;31008&amp;nbsp;Peggy Neck Road, Princess Anne, MD 21853)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Jeffrey Bruce Serres (2/M, DOB&amp;nbsp;06/23/1977, 31010 Peggy Neck Road, Princess Anne, MD 21853)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Kristen Jeann Serres (2/F, DOB&amp;nbsp;07/01/1980,&amp;nbsp;31010 Peggy Neck Road, Princess Anne, MD 21853)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Certifications / Training:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*Trained&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-5393fba1-7fff-81f5-315f-280129d7c7ea"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Test through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*Certified PBT operator&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; *Trained in collision investigation by the Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*Certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Scene Processing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;A neighborhood check was conducted at 28225 Vesely Lane, Princess Anne, MD 21853. I made contact with the neighbor of the suspect, who was later identified as Terri Lee Moss. Moss provided me with valuable information pertaining to the incident, as well information on Hilker&amp;#39;s business which consists of buying and selling items online through Facebook Marketplace. Moss also confirmed that 28241 Vesely Lane was Hilker&amp;#39;s current address, and provided the names of additional people who live with him at that residence. &lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Narrative:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 11/07/2023 at approximately 1829 hours, I, Tpr. Wright #7521 arrived at the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack &amp;quot;X&amp;quot;. Upon my arrival, I made contact with the victim, who was identified by his Maryland Driver&amp;#39;s License as Marco Tulio Lopez-Salgado (5/M, DOB 06/03/1990). Lopez advised that he had recently purchased an enclosed trailer through Facebook Marketplace, however, when he tried to have it registered through the Department of Motor Vehicles, he was informed that the trailer had a fraudulent title. The enclosed trailer that Lopez had purchases was a &amp;quot;Cargo Mate&amp;quot; trailer. Upon further inspection, it was revealed that both VIN locations on the trailer had been defaced and were illegible. A fraudulent VIN plate was attached to the tongue of the trailer, displaying an RV company by the name of &amp;quot;Starcraft&amp;quot; (VIN#&amp;nbsp;1SAAS01E9S1VK2822). This VIN was associated with a 1995 Starcraft Camping RV.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Lopez advised that he purchased the trailer from 28241 Vesely Lane, Princess Anne, Maryland 21853. Myself, M/Tpr. Price #2599, and Lopez arrived at this address at approximately 1846 hours in attempt to make contact with the seller. Upon arriving at the residence, nobody appeared to be home. We made contact with the neighbor,&amp;nbsp;Terri Lee Moss, at&amp;nbsp;28225 Vesely Lane, Princess Anne, MD 21853. Moss advised that a man by the name of George Hilker resides at the address we previously visited. She stated that Hilker buys and sells items at auctions frequently. When we asked if anyone else lived with Hilker, Moss stated that she believed his girlfriend and her son reside at that address as well. Moss then advised that Hilker&amp;#39;s girlfriend&amp;#39;s son, Kane, usually stays in an RV that is parked behind Hilker&amp;#39;s residence. She did not know the make or model of the RV.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;M/Tpr. Price and I returned to 28241 Vesely Lane to confirm whether the RV matched the VIN plate that was falsely attached to the Cargo Mate trailer that was sold to Lopez. As we entered the rear of the property, we made contact with Hilker&amp;#39;s girlfriend&amp;#39;s son, Kane. We informed Kane as to why we were on the property and requested to see the RV, to which Kane agreed. Upon further inspection, the RV that Kane was staying in was not a 1995 Starcraft Camping RV, but rather a Fleetwood. After speaking to Kane, he was able to provide me with Hilker&amp;#39;s phone number and stated that he was currently coming home from an auction, and that he would be home later in the evening. With that information, I advised Kane that I would contact Hilker and return to the property once he got home. At that time, M/Tpr. Price and I cleared the area and returned to the barrack. Lopez advised that he needed to return home and that he could not wait for Hilker. Lopez was given my contact information and advised to hold onto the trailer until I spoke to Hilker.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Upon arriving at the barrack, I made contact with Hilker over the phone and advised that I needed to speak with him in person. Hilker agreed to meet at his residence. At approximately 2055 hours, I returned to 28241 Vesely Lane. I asked Hilker if he had recently sold an enclosed trailer for $3,500, to which he stated that he did. Hilker advised that he purchased the trailer a month prior to fix and re-sell. Hilker also advised that the person he bought it from provided him with a title, and that was the title that he gave to Lopez when he sold it. I asked Hilker who he had purchased the trailer from, to which he stated that he purchased it off of Facebook Marketplace from Jeremy Classing at 31008 Peggy Neck Road. I requested to see the Facebook messages between himself and Classing to which he agreed. Hilker purchased the Cargo Mate trailer from Classing on 10/18/2023 for $800. Classing stated that there was not a title associated with the trailer. After Hilker had possession of the trailer, he made a few repairs and sold it to Lopez on 10/23/2023 for $3,500.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I asked Hilker if he was still in possession of the photos that he used to list the trailer for sale. Hilker provided me with a photo from 10/23/2023, five days after the trailer was purchased from Classing. Upon examining this photo, it was revealed that the VIN plate for the Starcraft RV had not yet been attached to the tongue of the trailer, which confirmed that it was not there when the trailer was purchased from Classing. After I confronted Hilker about this, Hilker stated that he was unsure about where the fraudulent VIN plate came from. I requested a copy of the photo to which Hilker agreed to share with me. I then cleared from Hilker&amp;#39;s address and started towards Classing&amp;#39;s address at 31008 Peggy Neck Road, Princess Anne, MD 21853.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Upon my arrival at approximately 2139 hours, I made contact with Jeremy Lee Classing (2/M, DOB 06/28/1995). I asked Classing if he had recently sold a trailer, to which he stated that he did. Classing explained that he purchased the 16 ft. Cargo Mate trailer from his neighbor in August 2023, and sold it to Hilker on 10/18/2023. When asked if he added anything to the trailer, Classing stated that he did not make any changes to the trailer and sold it as is. Classing did state, however, that when he sold it to Hilker, he provided a separate title and VIN plate for a Starcraft RV. Classing advised that he did not add the fraudulent VIN plate to the trailer, nor did he encourage Hilker to add it. Classing clarified in the trailer listing that there was no title included, which was what Hilker had already confirmed. Classing also provided me with photos of the trailer prior to selling it to Hilker.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I asked Classing who he had purchased the trailer from, to which he provided me with his neighbor&amp;#39;s name, Jeffrey Serres (2/M, DOB 06/23/1977). Classing stated that Serres was the title owner of the trailer. With the phone number that Classing provided me, I made contact with Serres at approximately 2227 hours. Serres stated that he sold the trailer to Classing, however, he was not the title owner of the trailer. Jeffrey Serres provided me with his wife&amp;#39;s name and contact information, and advised that the trailer was currently registered under her name. I made contact with Kristen Jeann Serres (2/F, DOB 07/01/1980). Kristen Serres confirmed that she was the current title owner of the Cargo Mate trailer, and was able to provide me with a screenshot of the trailer&amp;#39;s title. Kristen advised that they no longer had a use for the trailer, so when the title expired in 2021, she never had it renewed. When the trailer was sold to Classing, Kristen never provided him with the title information. Classing then sold the trailer to Hilker with no title.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Upon learning this information, I informed Hilker and Lopez that I would contact them on 11/11/2023 when I returned for night shift.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I request this case remain open until the trailer has been returned and Lopez has been refunded $3,500.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;All of the above events occurred in Somerset County, Maryland.&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;ul&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 23:33:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 02:44:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3325</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Price</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2599</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Marshall</LastName>
            <FirstName>Randolph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5794</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wright</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7521</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528832</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>NOCHG</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/07/2023 18:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>NOCHG</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/13/2023 04:24:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/13/2023 04:24:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 20:30:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 20:30:17</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392400</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lopez Salgado</LastName>
               <FirstName>Marco</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Tulio</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/03/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 20:29:51</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L122</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lopez Salgado</LastName>
               <FirstName>Marco</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Tulio</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/03/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L122</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 20:29:51</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>321</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Naylor</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21804</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.588867</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.372566</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>406</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5084</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 20:30:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 20:30:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 20:31:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 20:31:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>239909</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>HILKER</LastName>
               <FirstName>GEORGE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>FRANCIS</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/24/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>07/29/2019 00:01:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H426</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>HILKER</LastName>
               <FirstName>GEORGE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>FRANCIS</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/24/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>H426</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/29/2019 00:01:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>28241</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Vesely</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Princess Anne</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21853</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3367</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.773889</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.253889</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>956</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6343</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/29/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 20:31:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>28</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 22:19:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 22:19:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392407</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Classing</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jeremy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/28/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13453722E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 22:18:57</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Classing</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jeremy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/28/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13453722E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>C425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 22:18:57</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>31008</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Peggy Neck</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Princess Anne</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.67726254585078</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.26139550364942</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>880</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7741</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 22:19:22</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>46</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 22:20:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 22:20:15</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>264838</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Serres</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Bruce</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/23/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2020 15:55:18</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J160</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Serres</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Bruce</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/23/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J160</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2020 15:55:18</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4779</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Airport</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21804</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1532</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.530626</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.322804</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>31010</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Peggy Neck</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Princess Anne</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21853</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.676198</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.262267</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 22:20:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>60</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 23:14:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 23:14:06</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>225347</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Moss</LastName>
               <FirstName>Terri</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/16/1963 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/22/2019 20:16:57</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Moss</LastName>
               <FirstName>Terri</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/16/1963 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/22/2019 20:16:57</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>28225</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Vesely</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Princess Anne</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21853</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3367</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.77504</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.254397</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>735</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2076</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/22/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 23:14:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>43</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 23:17:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 23:17:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392410</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Serres</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kristen</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jeann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/01/1980 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16153359E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 23:17:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Serres</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kristen</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jeann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/01/1980 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16153359E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 23:17:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>31010</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Peggy Neck</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Princess Anne</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21853</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.676198</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.262267</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>831</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1589</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 23:17:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/21/2023 11:27:50</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/21/2023 11:27:50</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/21/2023 13:44:40</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/21/2023 11:27:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5794</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/21/2023 13:44:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On Tuesday, 11/21/2023 at approximately 1045 hours, I, Trooper Wright #7521 scheduled a follow-up with Lopez and Hilker to exchange the trailer for the full refunded amount of $3,500. Upon my arrival at 28241 Vesely Lane, Princess Anne, I made contact with Lopez and Hilker. Prior to the trailer being returned to Hilker, an inspection of the interior and exterior of the Cargo Mate trailer was conducted and witnessed by both parties. It was determined that the condition of the trailer was the same as it was when it was originally sold to Lopez. Lopez proceeded to detach the trailer from his truck. Hilker then counted out $3,500 in cash, which I witnessed, as well as captured on my body-worn camera. Lopez confirmed that the amount given was correct. After the exchange, Lopez exited the property.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Lopez provided me with the fraudulent title. I provided Hilker with the correct title and VIN number that was provided to me by the title owner. Hilker is already in possession of the title owner&amp;#39;s contact information, and is in the process of transferring the title.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Due to the victim being fully refunded, I request this case be closed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;All of the above events occurred in Somerset County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7521</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/21/2023 11:32:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7521</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/21/2023 12:16:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Marshall</LastName>
            <FirstName>Randolph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5794</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wright</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7521</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>