<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-001103</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/10/2023 03:03:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/10/2023 03:03:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/10/2023 02:37:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/10/2023 02:37:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI/Accident</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 03:03:09</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0392</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/27/2023 00:09:40</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>679949</AddressId>
      <City>MDC561</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 03:03:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 20:08:29</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>679949</AddressId>
         <StreetName>S/B Capital Beltway @ Branch Ave</StreetName>
         <City>Temple Hills</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20746</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.92714</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.81979</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB 495 @ BRANCH</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/10/2023 03:03:06</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/10/2023 03:03:06</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/26/2023 18:34:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 03:03:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:23:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;This incident was recorded audibly and visually on BWC. L-31 is equipped with MVR.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;Please refer to ACRS report regarding the accident.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Clarks, Lashanda Joy&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 02/16/1984&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 01/10/2023&lt;br /&gt; Times of Arrest: 0336 Hours&lt;br /&gt; DUI # 23-015: (Forestville Barrack)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;*&lt;/strong&gt;Trained and certified to operate the Preliminary Breath Test through the Maryland State Police.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;hr /&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On 01/10/2023 at approximately 0237 hours, I was dispatched to S/B Capital Beltway prior to Branch Ave, Temple Hills, Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland, in reference to a two-vehicle crash.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Upon my arrival at approximately 0242 hours, I observed a Black Nissan Rogue bearing the Maryland Registration (7FC5834) facing Northbound in lane five (5) with all-around damage. I made contact with the driver of a Black Nissan Rogue, who was later identified as Ms. Clarks, Lashanda Joy, DOB: 02/16/1984, by her Maryland Driver&amp;#39;s License. I asked Ms. Clarks if she had any injuries and informed her that the ambulance would arrive soon. At this time, I already detected a strong odor of Alcoholic beverage on her breath and observed her eyes to be glassy and bloodshot. Ms. Clarks stated that she was okay and did not need to get checked out. I asked Ms. Clarks about what had happened. Ms. Clarks stated that she swerved into lane four (4) to avoid traffic in front of her and subsequently struck the middle portion of the tractor-trailer. As Ms. Clarks was speaking with me, it was clear that her speech was slurred. I asked Ms. Clarks to wait in her vehicle and to get a registration card and proof of insurance for me. I then approached a white Tractor-Trailer bearing the Ohio Registration (PWJ2280) and made contact with the driver who was identified as Early, Konn Ford, DOB: 03/19/1973. I asked Mr. Early if he was okay and made sure that there were no injuries. I asked Mr. Early about what happened, and he stated that he was traveling in lane four (4) and observed that Ms. Clarks was speeding, swerved into his lane, and struck the passenger side of his vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At this time, the EMS personnel arrived, and they made sure that everyone was okay. I asked Ms. Clarks where she was coming from, and she stated that she was coming from her friend&amp;#39;s house, Fairfax Village, in the District of Columbia. I asked Ms. Clarks to be honest with me about how many drinks she had because I could smell the alcoholic beverage on her breath, and she stated, &amp;quot;I haven&amp;#39;t had not much.&amp;quot; I asked her again how many, and she stated, &amp;quot;not much.&amp;quot; She then finally admitted that she had two (2) beers about three (3) hours ago. I asked her to be more specific about what she had. Ms. Clarks stated that she had two (2) bottles of Corona Extra with 24 ounces. At this time, Trooper Shai#7463 arrived; Ms. Clarks then just bluntly told us about her personal life story with her boyfriend doing PCP. I then asked Ms. Clarks when was the last time she had PCP, and she stated, &amp;quot;Six (6) months ago&amp;quot;. At this time, I did not detect Ms. Clarks to be on PCP besides being intoxicated. Based on my observation, I asked Ms. Clarks if she would be willing to submit to the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Ms. Clarks agreed to submit to the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on S/B Capital Beltway N/O Branch Ave on the right shoulder. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 30 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and surrounding pole lights. Ms. Clarks appeared to be in good physical condition. (Reference below for further information regarding Ms.Clarks&amp;#39;s injuries and medications.)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Ms. Clarks the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; Injuries - No.&lt;br /&gt; Medication - She takes Prozac for bipolar disorder.&lt;br /&gt; Medical Conditions - Bipolar.&lt;br /&gt; Contact lenses - No.&lt;br /&gt; Glasses - No.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Ms. Clarks&amp;#39;s eyes. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Ms. Clarks&amp;#39;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking, and no resting Nystagmus was observed. I asked Ms. Clarks if she understood the instructions, and she stated, &amp;quot;yes.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 degrees - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*Vertical Gaze Nystagmus - Not observed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Ms. Clarks moved her head a couple of times to the direction of my pen.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;WALK AND TURN (7/8 clues observed)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Ms. Clarks performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Ms. Clarks was instructed to imagine a straight line and place her left foot on the line, place her right foot directly in front of her left foot, and touch heel to toe. After she assumed the instructional position, Ms. Clarks was advised to keep her hands flat at her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Ms. Clarks was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Ms. Clarks was to keep her hands flat at her side, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, she was instructed to keep her lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Ms. Clarks was again explained, and I demonstrated, that the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Ms. Clarks was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her side, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Ms. Clarks if she understood the test, and she stated, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;(Footwear: Brown boots).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1) Unable to maintain balance - Mr. Clarks&amp;#39;s feet broke prior to being told to start walking multiple times.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2) Starts too soon - Observed - Mr. Clarks started walking, and I had to tell her not to start yet more than two (2) occasions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; 1) Stops while walking - Not observed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2) Misses heel-to-toe - Observed - Missed heel-to-toe steps six (6), seven (7), eight (8), and nine (9) during the first series of nine (9) steps.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3) Step off the line - Observed - Stepped off-line on steps six (6), seven (7), eight (8), and nine (9) during the first series of nine (9) steps.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;4) Uses arms to balance - Observed - Raised her arms to gain balance the entire time.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5) Improper turn - Observed - Ms. Clarks kept both feet planted and completely turned around with both feet.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;6) Incorrect amount of steps - Observed - Ms. Clarks took a total of ten (10) steps during the second series of nine (9) steps.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Ms. Clarks was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given during the test. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, one thousand-three), and continue the test until told to stop. Ms. Clarks was asked if she understood the test, and she stated that she understood.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; 1) Putting Foot down - Ms. Clarks put her foot down the first time during the first ten (10) seconds. Ms. Clarks put her foot down one more time, from ten (10) seconds to twenty (20) seconds.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; 2) Swaying - Not observed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; 3) Hopping - Not observed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; 4) Raising Arms - Observed - Ms. Clarks used her arms to balance herself the entire time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After completing the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, I asked Ms. Clarks if she would be willing to take the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT). I informed her that it would not be admissible in court. Ms. Clarks agreed to take PBT and stated, &amp;quot;I wanna know the number too.&amp;quot; Ms. Clarks submitted to a preliminary breath test with a .11 BrAC result&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ARREST/ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Ms. Clarks was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath&lt;br /&gt; *Eyes were glassy and bloodshot&lt;br /&gt; *Admission to consuming alcoholic beverages earlier prior to driving&lt;br /&gt; *My observed signs of impairment as she performed Standardized Field Sobriety Tests&lt;br /&gt; *PBT result of .11&lt;br /&gt; *Causing an accident&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I placed Ms. Clarks under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0336 hours. Ms. Clarks then was transported to the Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack. While at the barrack, I played the English audio DR-15 Advice of Rights form via the MVA&amp;rsquo;s official law enforcement website to Ms. Clarks in its entirety. At the conclusion of the DR-15, Ms. Clarks verbally agreed to submit to the intoximeter test and later (01/10/2023 at 0408 hours) signed the form indicating the same.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I conducted the observation period on Ms. Clarks in its entirety, starting with her time of the arrest. I escorted Ms. Clarks into the arrest processing room and remained in her custody until the time of the test. Ms. Clarks&amp;#39;s mouth was checked and no foreign objects or piercings were observed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;INTOXIMETER RESULT:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The breath test was administered by Sgt. Bolduc #4889. Ms. Clarks was deemed to have refused the test after failing to provide two sufficient samples after three (3) separate attempts.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CHARGES&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Ms. Clarks was charged with the following citations:&lt;br /&gt; 1. DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL (0H90YJK)&lt;br /&gt; 2. DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL (0HB0YJK)&lt;br /&gt; 3. DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE SO FAR IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL CANNOT DRIVE SAFELY (0HC0YJK)&lt;br /&gt; 4. NEGLIGENT DRIVING (0HD0YJK)&lt;br /&gt; 5. DRIVER CHANGING LANES WHEN UNSAFE (0HF0YJK)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms. Clarks was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to a sober driver. Ms. Clarks was polite and cooperative throughout the process.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Prince George&amp;#39;s County, MD.&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 08:39:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/20/2023 16:54:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shai</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7463</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bolduc</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4889</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thienhom</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bryce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7518</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490481</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/10/2023 02:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 15:59:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 19:38:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 19:39:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:09</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365770</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Clarks</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lashanda</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Joy</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/16/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 16:05:37</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C462</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L253</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Clarks</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lashanda</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Joy</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/16/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C462</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L253</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 16:05:37</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mattawoman Way</StreetName>
               <City>Accokeek</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20607</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>873</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1626</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 13:15:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 13:15:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 13:15:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 13:15:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>49</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 20:10:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365795</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Early</LastName>
               <FirstName>Konn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ford</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/19/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 20:09:51</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Early</LastName>
               <FirstName>Konn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ford</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/19/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>E640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 20:09:51</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>210</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5902</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 20:10:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:34</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 20:10:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:34</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 20:10:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:34</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 15:59:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 15:59:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148488</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 16:56:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/20/2023 16:56:05</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5N1BT3BB4NC723285</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>RGE</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7FC5834</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148870</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AC</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 17:02:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/20/2023 17:02:39</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FVACXFC3KHKG5828</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FRHT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>OH</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>PWJ2280</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>