<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-042157</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/28/2023 20:14:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/28/2023 20:14:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/28/2023 19:44:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/28/2023 19:44:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>A vehicle in motion caught on fire. Driver failed to identify herself and requested a fire investigation.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 20:14:32</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 08:30:07</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>VF</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MD-295 / HANOVER RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>714513</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 20:14:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 00:00:12</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>714513</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>295</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>N</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Baltimore-Washington</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PKWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Hanover</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21076</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.7239042</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.1777238</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/28/2023 20:14:29</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/28/2023 20:14:29</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>12/08/2023 02:10:39</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 20:14:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 08:29:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 11/28/2023 at approximately 1944 hours, I, TFC Louderback #6738 of the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack, was dispatched to a vehicle fire on northbound 295 (Baltimore Washington Pkwy) north of Route 100 on the right shoulder. Upon my arrival, I observed a maroon Chevrolet Malibu with its engine compartment fully engulfed in flames. The fire department had not arrived at this time. I observed an adult female who was later identified as Raven Jenell Royal (B/F, DOB: 08/31/1980) on the right shoulder with 3 juveniles. I asked her if there was anyone in the vehicle to which Raven answered &amp;quot;No.&amp;quot; I asked if everyone is ok to which Raven answered &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot; When everyone was at a safe distance, I got the Chevrolet Malibu&amp;#39;s tag information. It had a DC registration GU2643, and it was registered to a Ricky Donnell Royal (B/M, DOB: 08/02/1966). I went back to where Raven and the 3 juveniles were standing, but they were no longer there. I observed them approximately 200 feet south of me, Raven was walking away with her arms waving trying to get a ride from passing vehicles. I caught up to them and asked for her license. Raven stated it was in the car. I asked what her first name was, and she stated &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t have to tell you that.&amp;quot; I asked why not, and she stated &amp;quot;Because you are an officer.&amp;quot; I stated in the State of Maryland she has to identify herself to a uniformed Police Officer, and Raven still refused. I asked if she had any warrants to which she answered &amp;quot;No.&amp;quot; She stated her ex-husband works with law enforcement. I asked what agency, and she stated all law enforcement agencies.I asked if the vehicle in motion when it caught fire, and she stated &amp;quot;Well, he did this on purpose. He has been trying to kill me for years. I have been trying to get away. He just tried to do it with all 3 of my kids in the car. So I really don&amp;#39;t feel comfortable telling you my name because he has friends in law enforcement and every time I tell them, nothing happens. I don&amp;#39;t trust anyone because he has friend in law enforcement. It doesn&amp;#39;t matter where it is at.&amp;quot; I stated I still need her information, but I can put a different address on the report. Raven stated &amp;quot;I need to get my kids home.&amp;quot; I asked if she had anyone she could call to which she answered &amp;quot;No.&amp;quot; Raven asked if I could get her an Uber and I stated I could, but I need her information and her kid&amp;#39;s information first. Raven stated &amp;quot;I cannot tell you that. He has been looking for us, sir. He just tied to kill me and my kids.&amp;quot; The Fire Department and Cpl. Cearfoss #6041 arrived on scene at that time. When I was explaining to Cpl. Cearfoss the situation, Raven walked away heading south. Cpl. Cearfoss caught up to her and asked if she was the driver to which she answered &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot; Cpl. Cearfoss stated to Raven we needed her information so we can do an investigation of the vehicle fire to which she stated &amp;quot;Well, contact Ricky Royal. That is his car.&amp;quot; Ricky Royal was not driving or in the vehicle. Raven&amp;#39;s son, Rico, stated &amp;quot;Oh my fucking god, the car overheated.&amp;quot; Raven and Rico started to argue. After Cpl. Cearfoss and I stopped the argument, Raven walked away, and we informed her she was not allowed to walk on the highway. Rico started to escalate the situation by trying to get into Cpl. Cearfoss&amp;#39; face while yelling, so I placed myself IN front of Rico to attempt to calm him down. Rico stated that we were &amp;quot;asking the wrong questions. It&amp;#39;s a car on fire behind us.&amp;quot; I tried to explain that we need their information so we can do the report for the vehicle fire. Rico asked &amp;quot;What does the highway have to do with the car exploding?&amp;quot; I tried to explain again that they are not allowed to walk on the highway. It is illegal to walk on the highway, to which Rico and Raven stated that I was lying about that. I stated we are trying to make arrangements for all of them to get off the highway. Raven stated &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m not going to go with you all.&amp;quot; Cpl. Cearfoss asked if she had someone to pick her and her kids up, to which Raven answered &amp;quot;No, I don&amp;#39;t. Are you all going to call me an Uber, so I can get my kids home.&amp;quot; Cpl. Cearfoss stated we are not going to pay for her to get an Uber. Raven stated &amp;quot;ok, Then what are you here for then?&amp;quot; Cpl. Cearfoss answered &amp;quot;To get you somewhere safe.&amp;quot; To which Raven stated &amp;quot;No, me and my kids are going to stay right here to wait for someone to come take us.&amp;quot; Cpl. Cearfoss and I tried to give Raven options from taking them to the Royal Farms off of West Nursery Rd. to the train station at BWI Airport. Raven kept telling us no. She then changed the subject by stating that we never asked if she was ok when they just got out of the vehicle fire. I stated to her that I did as soon as I arrived on scene. Raven continued to argue and stated I did not do anything when she told me her husband was trying to kill her. While she was arguing with me, her son Rico walked away heading south on 295 to which Cpl. Cearfoss had stopped him by telling Rico he cannot walk on the highway. Cpl. Cearfoss never touched or got close to him. Raven yelling &amp;quot;Do not touch my son, do not touch my son back the fuck-up.&amp;quot; Cpl. Cearfoss and I tried to make multiple different arrangements for Raven and her kids to get off the highway. Raven would not take any of our suggestions because she stated it was because Cpl. Cearfoss and I volunteered the suggestions. Raven was telling Rico he does not understand how this works, that we, as in The Maryland State Police, have people that work for us. Raven asked how the Police got to the vehicle fire before the Fire Department. I tried to explain the Fire Department got a location further north, and we gave them the correct location. Raven asked where the ambulance was and why wasn&amp;#39;t one there. I asked if she wanted an ambulance, but she ignored my question and continued to try to convince her son Rico that we are not concerned about their safety. Cpl. Cearfoss asked Raven if she wanted EMS to which she stated &amp;quot;Don&amp;#39;t worry about it.&amp;quot;. Raven went back to her not wanting to give us her name. Cpl. Cearfoss had me start on the report because we were getting nowhere with Raven. Raven then stated &amp;quot;Sovereignty law.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I went to the witness in the gray Ford Explorer to get is statement. I decided to keep him anonymous because of how Raven was reacting to the police and fire department. He stated while the Malibu was moving the flames came up from under the vehicle, there was a lot of smoke, and they pulled over. He called 911 to report the fire. I spoke to the Fire Department personnel and told them the situation about Raven was claiming her ex-husband had put a devise on the car to cause it to catch fire. The fire department had the Fire Marshals come to the scene to do an investigation. Miles Towing, towed the Malibu to their lot, so the Fire Marshal could do further investigation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Cpl. Cearfoss made Uber arrangements for Raven and her kids to go to the Royal Farms on West Nursery Rd.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I request this case to be closed and Fire Marshals took over the investigation.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6738</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 23:01:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6738</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/07/2023 01:05:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cearfoss</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6041</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Treleaven</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cearfoss</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6041</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Louderback</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jonathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6738</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>41</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6738</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 23:51:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 00:00:12</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>394083</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Royal</LastName>
               <FirstName>Raven</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jenell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/31/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/28/2023 23:50:25</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Royal</LastName>
               <FirstName>Raven</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jenell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/31/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/28/2023 23:50:25</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2659</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Lafayette</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21216</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4732</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.661349</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.298014</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6738</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 23:51:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6738</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 23:51:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159359</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6738</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/07/2023 01:09:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6738</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/07/2023 01:09:17</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>2</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1G1ZE5E77BF135996</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2011</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MAL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>MAR</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>DC</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>GU2643</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>12</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/28/2023 21:44:55</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/28/2023 21:44:55</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/15/2023 08:29:15</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6041</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 21:44:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 08:29:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On 11/28/23 I, Cpl. Cearfoss #6041, responded to N/B 295 N/O MD 100 in Hanover, Anne Arundel County, MD to assist TFC Louderback #6738 with a vehicle fire. Upon arrival, I made contact with TFC Louderback and the driver, who was later identified as Raven Jenell Royal B/F 8/31/80. Royal was with 3 juveniles. I walked toward Royal, who was walking southbound, away from me on the right lane. I identified myself and notified her that our interaction was being recorded. I asked her for her license so TFC Louderback could conduct his investigation into the vehicle fire. Royal told me that I could contact Ricky Royal, who was not driving or in the vehicle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I informed Royal that she could not walk on the highway, and she insisted that it wasn&amp;#39;t. Throughout our interaction she was extremely agitated and aggressive. Her son &amp;ldquo;Rico&amp;rdquo; was at times as well. She refused to be given a ride off the roadway by law enforcement, tow services, SHA or Fire personnel. She stated she would walk, or asked us to call her an Uber.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Royal made statements that her husband put something on her car to make it explode. Due to those statements, Fire personnel called the Fire Marshall to conduct an investigation into the cause of the fire. TFC Louderback continue for nearly 20-30 minutes to get her and her kids off of the roadway. &amp;ldquo;Rico&amp;rdquo; made attempts to talk her mother into taking a ride or finding a ride off the roadway, but Royal continued to refuse. Royal was extremely anti-police and made several statements that her husband had connections to police. Royal continued to refuse to identify herself. She made a statement about &amp;ldquo;sovereignty&amp;rdquo; leading me to believe she was possibly a sovereign citizen. Royal later made a statement that two of her children had a mental disability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I exhausted every de-escalation tool that I had at my disposal. If I were to arrest Royal, I am confident she would have resisted, and her son Rico would have assisted her in resisting based on our entire interaction. Based on the totality of the circumstance (Royal&amp;#39;s aggressiveness, an aggressive child, two younger children with mental disabilities, being on the side of 295, and traffic passing by), it would be best to not use force, which would escalate the situation over a payable citation for walking on the highway and failure to obey a lawful order. It would create a greater risk if the children were to get involved.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Richard Reeves of the SHA volunteered to call Royal an Uber, and I paid for half. I made the decision to not escalate the situation. The Uber arrived and relayed the Royal and her kids off of the roadway. It was later determined that Royal possibly had open warrants. Once I got back to the Barrack, I contacted Anne Arundel County Child Protective Services and spoke with Dominique Hicks. I explained the situation in an attempt to follow up with the mother and children based on Royal refusing attempted to get her children out of freezing weather and off of the roadway to a safe location and statement she made about her husband. Once the report is completed, it will be forwarded to Hicks. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6041</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 21:46:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6041</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/28/2023 23:44:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Logsdon</LastName>
            <FirstName>Frank</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2064</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cearfoss</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6041</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>