<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009964</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/19/2023 17:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/19/2023 17:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/19/2023 17:02:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/19/2023 17:02:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Warrant arrest resulting in Use of Force</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 17:56:19</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/23/2023 10:52:10</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>683307</AddressId>
      <City>MDC119</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 17:56:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 19:22:05</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>683307</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>612</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Moores</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Cambridge</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21613</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.081987</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.562183</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/19/2023 17:56:18</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/19/2023 17:56:18</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/20/2023 16:18:43</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 17:56:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:20:57</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;On March 19th, 2023 at approximately 1702 hours, I started a card through iMobile for a warrant service at 612 Moores Avenue, Cambridge, Maryland. I advised the barrack of the warrant service and TFC Davis and I proceeded to the address. The warrant service was a bench warrant (Warrant Number: D-035-CR-23-000039-1) for failing to appear on March 13th, 2023. The subject for the warrant was Willie Lamar Tazewell (06/19/1991 B/M). Tazewell is approximately 5 feet 7 inches and 194 pounds. I also knew from Secure Case Search, that Tazewell had two active Show Cause Orders (Case numbers: D-021-CR-21-000720 and D-021-CR-22-000201) for Violation of Probation. The Show Cause Orders were signed on March 13th, 2023. TFC Davis and I arrived at the address at 1707 hours. Upon our arrival, I observed a black male, matching Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s facial description, sitting in a silver Mercedes Benz with Virginia registration ULJ1681. I know from a previous encounter, with Tazewell, as well as looking Tazewell in E-tix, that Tazewell has operated the silver Mercedes Benz previously. I approached the vehicle and greeted the driver asking if he was Tazewell. The male subjected stated that Tazewell was inside the residence and that his name was James. Due to the close resemblance of the male to Tazewell, I asked the male for his identification.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The male stated that he did not have his identification on him and that it was located in the house. I asked the male again if he had his identification on him and the male stated his identification was in his house off of Phillips. The male driver then asked if he could go get his identification real quick. The male driver then asked if he could go get his kids. I did not reply to the males question and the male then exited the vehicle without my direction. The male then walked into the residence of 612 Moores Avenue, and started talking to a second male subject. The first male subject started making comments about how TFC Davis and I were looking for Willie. I called for the male subject by saying Willie, and the male responded back I am not Willie, I am James. The male subject then looked at the second male subject holding the door open and said &amp;ldquo;Can you tell them&amp;rdquo;. The second male subject just stated he was there for his kids. I then called the male subject James and asked him to step back outside. The male subject complied and I explained that he looked like Tazewell and I was just trying to confirm his identification so I could know for sure that he was not Tazewell. The male subject stated he was not Willie, and continued to explain the Willie has hair on his head, and then the male removed his hat to show he had short hair. I asked the male for his last name and he stated it was Jones. I asked the male if he had an identification through Maryland and the male again stated his identification was in a house on Phillips Avenue and that he did not live at this address. I again asked the male if he had an identification and the male stated &amp;ldquo;yes sir&amp;rdquo;. I explained to the male that once I verified his identification he would be good and then I asked the male if he would be able to call Tazewell. I then explained to the male that I needed to serve two (2) Show Cause Orders on Tazewell. I then asked the male for his date of birth and the male stated &amp;ldquo;6/21/19&amp;rdquo;. I asked the male to clarify if he was born in 19 and the male stated 1991. I asked the male for his social security number and the male became agitated stating he did nothing wrong and knew his rights that he did not have to identify himself. I explained to the male that he matched the description of Tazewell and I just wanted the information so I could positively identify him and could verify he was not Tazewell.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I went to my patrol car and utilized my Mobile Data Terminal (MDT) to run James Jones with a date of birth 06/21/1991, through Maryland to obtain a picture of the subject. The driving record of MVA displayed &amp;ldquo;Driver not found&amp;rdquo;. The vehicle record of the MVA displayed a result of a James Jones from Baltimore with a date of birth of 06/21/1970. I also was able to locate the previous booking photo from when I arrest Tazewell in January and took a picture of the arrest photo. I showed the photo to TFC Davis who asked if the male was Tazewell. The male then walked to a neighbor who was outside and asking the neighbor to tell us his name was James. The male stated that he had just talked to Tazewell and that he was at his mom&amp;rsquo;s house and his mom was keeping him there until we arrived, otherwise he was going to run. I asked the male why Tazewell was going to run and the male stated &amp;ldquo;Willie knows he has a Show Cause Order and is going to get arrested&amp;rdquo;. I explained to the male that for a Show Cause Order all that needed to be done was I sign the paperwork and provide a copy to Tazewell. I then advised the male that his name and date of birth was not coming back through Maryland and asked to confirm what state his identification was through. The male stated he did not know why his name was not coming back and I asked the male again what state his identification was through. This time the male advised his identification was through Virginia and I explained that is why the name did not come back. I went back to my vehicle to utilize my MDT to run James Jones with date of birth 06/21/1991, through Virginia. I again received results stating &amp;ldquo;Jones, James &amp;ndash; Customer name was not found in &amp;lsquo;VA&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo;, indicating the male did not have a license/identification through Virginia either. I then ran the name James Jones with date of birth of 06/21/1991, through the Caliber Report Management System (RMS) and had no results within the Maryland State Police system, or Statewide.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;I again re-approached the male and again advised him his name was not coming back through Virginia. The male immediately asked if Willie was going to get locked up today. I explained to the male again he was not going to be locked up for the Show Cause Orders. I explained to the male that I was there to serve Show Cause Orders and just needed to sign the paper and provide a copy to Tazewell. I asked the male if he was going to stop lying and tell me he was Tazewell and the male started to smile, nodded his head down once, and raised his right hand. I asked the male if that was a yes and the male stated that he was Tazewell.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then told Tazewell that he was now being in placed in custody for the Bench Warrant from Talbot County. As I was informing Tazewell he was being placed in custody, I grabbed Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s right wrist with my right hand, and I grabbed Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s right bicep with my left hand. I placed Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s right arm behind his back as TFC Davis grabbed Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s left wrist with his left hand. I then used my left hand to grab Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s left wrist and then used my right hand to grab both Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s thumb, and used my left hand to obtain my handcuffs. I started to place my handcuffs on Tazewell and Tazewell lunged forward to attempt to flee. TFC Davis was able to maintain control of Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s left arm with his left hand and used to right hand to attempt to grab Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s left bicep. Tazewell ran between the silver Mercedes Benz and a white Buick Enclave with Delaware registration 183915, and ran into the roadway. After passing the vehicles, Tazewell stopped and used his right hand on TFC Davis&amp;rsquo; left shoulder to attempt to push TFC Davis off of him. TFC Davis continued to maintain control of Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s left hand and wrist as I was able to grab Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s right bicep with my right hand and used my left hand to grab Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s left side. Tazewell attempted to back up, but, Tazewell tripped and fell onto his back. TFC Davis continued to maintain control of Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s left arm as Tazewell fell while I maintained control of Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s right arm. As Tazewell was falling my body camera came off my shirt and fell face down on the ground. Once Tazewell was on his ground Tazewell stated multiple times, &amp;ldquo;Alright, I&amp;rsquo;m done, I&amp;rsquo;m done&amp;rdquo;. As Tazewell was stating he was done, I started giving Tazewell verbal commands to roll over to his back. I provided a second verbal command for Tazewell to roll over to his back and Tazewell then rolled over onto his stomach. Ultimately I was attempting to provide verbal commands for Tazewell to roll onto his stomach as he was already on his back, but Tazewell seemed to understand what I was asking him to do and showed compliance. TFC Davis then took control of Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s right arm and wrist and held it on Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s lower back. Tazewell then moved his left arm behind his back and TFC Davis gained control of the left hand and wrist. Once TFC Davis had control of both hands I obtained a second pair of handcuffs and was able to place Tazewell in custody. After placing Tazewell in custody, TFC Davis immediately rolled Tazewell onto his right side and I went to retrieve my body camera. I also observed a male subject approaching with Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s phone and I requested the male backup for the time being and the male complied. TFC Davis asked Tazewell if he was injured and Tazewell stated no. TFC Davis and I assisted Tazewell to his feet and escorted Tazewell to my patrol vehicle. While I was putting Tazewell in my patrol vehicle he made a statement that we were being aggressive. I explained to Tazewell we were not being aggressive, we placed him in custody and as soon as he was in custody, we helped him up and we were done. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;I transported Tazewell to the Cambridge Detachment where he was processed and seen by a District Court Commissioner for his initial appearance. I asked Tazewell numerous times at the detachment if he was injured and Tazewell repeatedly answered no. I documented photos of Tazewell to show there were no injuries, bruises, or marks on Tazewell. Tazewell was ultimately held on $1,000 (10%) for the bench warrant and $1,000 (10%) for resisting arrest. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All events occurred in Dorchester County, Maryland&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I request this case be closed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6415</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 19:36:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6415</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 15:59:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colton</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6728</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Chester</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4973</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Del Vecchio</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Glover</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6415</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499364</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0600</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 17:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0600</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6415</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 19:24:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6415</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 19:24:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499364</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1364</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 17:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1364</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6415</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 19:24:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6415</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 19:24:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6415</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 19:26:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:35</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368356</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Tazewell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Willie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lamar</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/15/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.30613858E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>02/07/2023 02:14:10</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Tazewell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Willie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lamar</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/15/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.30613858E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>T240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/07/2023 02:14:10</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>612</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Moores</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Cambridge</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21613</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.081987</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.562183</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6415</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 19:26:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6415</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 19:26:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6415</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 19:44:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>279506</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Glover</LastName>
               <FirstName>TFC</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/12/2020 21:26:22</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T120</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Glover</LastName>
               <FirstName>TFC</FirstName>
               <SLastName>G416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T120</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/12/2020 21:26:22</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7053</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Easton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.06790316318151</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.74250547748684</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6415</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 19:44:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>7</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6415</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 19:40:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6415</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 19:40:28</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>7</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>James Jones DOB 6/21/1991 identification through Virginia
</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>647</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>245664</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/19/2023 18:54:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/19/2023 18:54:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/20/2023 16:18:43</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6728</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 18:54:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:20:57</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On 3/19/2023, I, TFC Davis #6728 of the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack responded to 612 Moores Ave. Cambridge Maryland to assist TFC Glover #6415 in reference to a warrant service. &amp;nbsp;Upon our arrival, a subject later identified as Willie Tazewell (6/15/91) was located in the driver seat of a vehicle. Upon contact he stated Tazewell was inside the residence. Upon contacting the subjects inside the residence, all individuals stated they were not Willie Tazewell. Upon confirming the original subject was Tazewell, TFC Glover went to place him under arrest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I immediately used both my left and right hands to secure Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s left arm. Tazewell responded by lunging forward at which time he began to run. As he did this, my grip went down to Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s left wrist. As Tazewell attempted to flee, I was able to maintain control of Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s left wrist. At that time, I attempted to gain full control of Tazewell. While doing so, Tazewell lost his balance, which resulted in him landing on the pavement on his back. After giving commands, Tazewell was turned to his stomach. I was able to continue to secure Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s right wrist with my right hand and his left wrist with my left hand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;TFC. Glover was able to obtain his handcuffs at which time I assisted in moving both Tazewell&amp;rsquo;s left wrist behind his back as TFC Glover secured it in a handcuff followed by his right wrist. Tazewell was immediately asked if he needed medical attention which he refused.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All events occurred in Dorchester County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6728</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 18:55:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6728</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 19:02:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Chester</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4973</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colton</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6728</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>