<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011226</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/29/2023 12:31:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/29/2023 12:31:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/29/2023 12:22:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/29/2023 12:22:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Death Investigation/House Fire</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 12:31:16</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3572</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 09:19:39</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>688962</AddressId>
      <City>MDC304</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 12:31:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/31/2023 14:40:47</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>688962</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>70</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Upper Green Glade</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Swanton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-79.255414</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.473857</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/29/2023 12:31:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/29/2023 12:31:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>04/03/2023 09:19:38</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 12:31:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3572</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 09:19:39</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;On 3/29/2023 at approximately 1030 hours, Sgt. Ross and I were notified of a house fire located at 70 Upper Green Glade Rd, Swanton, MD 21561. I was advised by Deputy Fire Marshal Rounds that one person from the family was unaccounted for at the time. The possibility for a family member to be located deceased in the fire was very likely.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Ross and I responded to the scene and the two-story home was a total loss burning completely to the ground. I met with family members while Sgt. Ross stayed in contact with fire personnel and the McHenry Barracks. Shortly after our arrival, a body was located inside the home.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; It is believed this body is the remains of Kylo Uber, 19 yr old male living in the home. All other family was accounted for and no one else was in the home other than Kylo Uber. FI Ken Collins and I informed Allen Uber, Father of Kylo, what was discovered.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This investigator met with other family members and it is possible Kylo may have been asleep on the second floor at the time of the fire. His body was discovered in the basement below where his bedroom was located. Kylo was Type I diabetic and a very sound sleeper. He did have braces and some dental work completed by Palaisa Orthodontics in Frostburg, MD. Dental charts may be needed to identify the remains and this information has been passed along to the OCME.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The other family members who also live at the residence are identified as the following:&lt;br /&gt; Allen Uber: Father of Kylo Uber&lt;br /&gt; Sungvien Uber: Mother of Kylo Uber&lt;br /&gt; Wisteria Uber: Sister&lt;br /&gt; Owynn Uber: Brother&lt;br /&gt; Kasera Uber: Sister&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All other family members were not home at the time of the fire. Wisteria received a call from a neighbor who informed her the house was on fire.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Allen Uber stated there were no known adversaries of the family and there have been no threats. He stated the house had older electrical wires due to the age of the home. Allen stated he has been bringing the home&amp;#39;s electrical wires up to date little by little. He has added GFCI outlets where required. He stated the fire in the fireplace was lit the night before, but it had smoldered out by morning and he does not feel this is the start of the fire. Allen did not have any leads to how the fire may have begun.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The cause and origins of the fire are unknown and due to the age of the home, the home engulfed very quickly according to neighbors. Prior to locating this body, the family attempted numerous times to contact Kylo by telephone. The phone went straight to voicemail every time. No foul play is expected at this time.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A neighbor who contacted 911 captured a photograph of the fire on his cell phone at 0855 hours just after contacting 911. At that time the fire could not be contained due to the size of it. This same neighbor took a second photo at 0902 and more than half the home was engulfed prior to fire personnel getting to the scene. I have obtained these photographs for the case file. These have also been forwarded to Deputy Fire Marshal A. Rounds.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Deputy Fire Marshal A. Rounds will conduct the investigation with the fire and will inform me of the findings.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The body was transported by Fredlock Funeral Home to the OCME for an autopsy. I have completed the MSP Form 89B which was also emailed to the OCME.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sgt. Ross contacted the Garrett County State&amp;#39;s Attorney&amp;#39;s Office and informed SA Christian Mash of the body being located.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;This case will remain open pending further investigation and the ruling from the Fire Marshal&amp;#39;s Office.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/31/2023 14:38:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5177</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 09:02:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ross</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3572</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Romanchak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5177</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>19</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 09:08:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373277</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Uber</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kylo</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/26/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 09:07:49</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>U160</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Uber</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kylo</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/26/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>U160</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 09:07:49</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>70</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Upper Green Glade</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Swanton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.255414</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.473857</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 09:08:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>