<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-045897</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/28/2023 14:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/28/2023 14:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/28/2023 14:54:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/28/2023 14:54:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Overdose Death</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/28/2023 16:48:21</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3572</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 14:10:17</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OVD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>656777</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/28/2023 16:48:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/28/2023 20:15:29</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>656777</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>426</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>FINZEL</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>FROSTBURG</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Longitude>-78.966532</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.715109</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/28/2023 16:48:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/28/2023 16:48:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>01/01/2024 01:04:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/28/2023 16:48:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3572</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 14:10:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On 12/28/2023 at 1454 hours, the McHenry Barrack received a call from the Garrett County 911 Center in reference to a deceased person at 426 W. Finzel Rd, Frostburg, Garrett County, Maryland. I arrived on the scene and made contact with Paramedic Krouse. Krouse advised he called the time of death at 1509 hours. Krouse advised that no life saving techniques where performed. The investigation revealed that the victim, Elissa Logsdon, previously suffered from mental illness and drug addiction, specifically heroin usage. Logsdon resided with her mother, Jolissa Lewis and sister, Kasey Logsdon at the listed address. Logsdon was last seen by her mother in the residence at 2200 hours on 12/27/2023. Lewis advised Logsdon&amp;#39;s body was in the basement in her bedroom. Lewis advised that Logsdon has a history of depression and started using CDS when she was 17 years of age.&amp;nbsp; The basement did not have a thermostat in the area, but the temperature felt approximately 60-65 degrees. When I entered the bedroom of Logsdon, I noticed the room to be cluttered and dirty. I noticed Logsdon&amp;#39;s body to be on her bed. She appeared to be sitting on the edge of her bed and slumped over at the waist with her head towards her knee. I noticed there was a small wooden box underneath her right chest.&amp;nbsp; A search of the scene revealed CDS paraphernalia, to include a spoon, a syringe, and two capsules containing suspected heroin/fentenyl.&amp;nbsp; The CDS items and the victim&amp;#39;s cell phone were seized from the scene and stored at the McHenry Barrack. M/Tpr. Romanchak from C.E.D responded to the scene and assisted with the investigation.&amp;nbsp; Forensic Investigator, Greg Skiles was notified at 1555 hours and responded to the scene. Skiles advised that Logsdon was going to be transported the Medical Examiners Office after his investigation. S/T. Peterson from the Garrett County Task Force was notified at 1553 and advised they will not be responding to the scene but requested a copy of the report for further CDS investigation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I spoke with Kasey Logsdon.&amp;nbsp; Kasey stated that Elissa told her and Jolissa that she was going to bed at approximately 2200 hours on 12/27/2023. She advised on 12/28/2023 at approximately 1400 hours she went to give Elissa a slice of pizza and found her unresponsive on her bed. Kasey advised that Elissa had been using fentanyl and heroine for the past four months. Kasey stated that while Jolissa was out bowling, Gavin Halvorsen came to the residence at approximately 2020 hours. Kasey advised that Elissa gave Halvorsen $50 for a fentanyl/cocaine capsule. Kasey advised that Elissa told her what she bought from Halvorsen.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Current Medications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Diclofenac $50mg&lt;br /&gt; Clindamycin 300mg&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The victim was removed from the scene by Newman&amp;#39;s Funeral Home and transported to the Medical Examiner&amp;#39;s Office for an autopsy. The Garrett County Narcotics Task Force was notified and will be following up with the death investigation. The preliminary investigation lists the cause of death as an unintentional drug overdose. The case remains opens pending the results of the autopsy.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I request this case be forwarded to CED for further investigation.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5689</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/28/2023 20:21:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5689</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/29/2023 21:35:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Romanchak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5177</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7189</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barnes</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quinn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7269</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wagoner</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3432</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fitzwater</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5689</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>20</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5689</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/28/2023 20:20:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/28/2023 20:20:01</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371461</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Logsdon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Elissa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/15/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/13/2023 11:17:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L235</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E420</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Logsdon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Elissa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/15/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L235</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E420</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/13/2023 11:17:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>426</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>FINZEL</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>FROSTBURG</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-78.966532</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.715109</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>920</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8967</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>D</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5689</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/28/2023 20:20:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5689</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/28/2023 20:20:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5689</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/28/2023 20:20:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5689</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/28/2023 20:20:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/02/2024 09:22:33</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/02/2024 09:22:33</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40T</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/03/2024 14:10:16</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/02/2024 09:22:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3572</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 14:10:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;On 12/28/2023, at approximately 1500 hours, I was contacted by the McHenry Barrack Duty Officer concerning a twenty-year-old who was found deceased in her home. When I received the call, no troopers were on scene and the details of the death were unknown. I advised I would respond to 426 West Finzel Road to assist.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Upon arrival, troopers had informed me that the deceased female appears to have died from an overdose. Drug paraphernalia was located on the bed, near the body. I viewed the room in the basement where the body was located. The basement temperature felt like it was in the 60&amp;#39;s (Farenheit). The basement was cluttered with items and the bedroom where the deceased was located was a makeshift room with bedsheets used as dividers.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The deceased was located in a position as if she was in a sitting with her right leg hanging off the bed when she was alive. It appears when she slumped over, her face went flat into the bedsheets. This position would make it difficult to breath and receive adequate oxygen. Directly alongside her body was a small box containing drug paraphernalia and capsules of an unknown substance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On this bed was a cell phone. I asked Jolissa Lewis if I could view the contents of this cell phone. Jolissa stated I could take the phone if needed and she provided pass-code of 1119. She stated it was an internet phone which could only receive calls and messages if there was an internet connection. I was able to turn the phone on for a brief minute prior to it shutting down due to low battery power. I observed the phone had no internet connection, so I did not need to put the phone in &amp;quot;airplane mode.&amp;quot; I seized the cell phone and the charger so I could investigate the phone for any potential information which could be passed onto a narcotic investigator.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I remained on-scene until FI Greg Skiles responded. I assisted in collecting the suspected illegal drugs with S/TPR Fitzwater. Once it was evident no foul play was suspected, I exited the scene and S/Tpr Fitzwater remained on-scene until the body was removed by Newman&amp;#39;s Funeral Home.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I was able to view information on the cellphone which belonged to Elissa Logsdon. I have contacted the Garrett County Narcotics Task Force concerning the messages I viewed. Although the information from the phone would be considered circumstantial in the death of Elissa, enough information exists to start an investigation into the person believed to be the one who brought Elissa illegal drugs. This information was discussed with a narcotic investigator. I have forwarded the messages on the phone and a person of interest. The cell phone belonging to Elissa will be returned to Jolissa Lewis in the near future.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; No information was collected showing this death to be a suicide.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 1/2/2024, I sent a request for information to the OCME. The information will be provided when the autopsy of Elissa Logsdon is completed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5177</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2024 09:23:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5177</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 10:11:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ross</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3572</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40T</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Romanchak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5177</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>