<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-040600</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/16/2023 16:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/16/2023 16:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/16/2023 16:26:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/16/2023 16:26:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect was arrested for DUI CDS.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/16/2023 16:56:27</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5824</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 02:32:59</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I70 WB / 56 MM,FREDERICK</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>713359</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/16/2023 16:56:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/03/2023 12:46:30</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>713359</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I70 Wb</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetNumber>56</CrossStreetNumber>
         <Longitude>-77.3690125333333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.4043403</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/16/2023 16:56:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/16/2023 16:56:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/18/2023 02:33:00</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/16/2023 16:56:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:06</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VIDEO/AUDIO RECORDINGS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In-car operational; B-35 recordings available&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BWC available TFC Kaszubski #6859 and TFC Dodson #7103&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUSPECT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Montano Bustamante, Cristian (W/M DOB: 5/23/1991)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; NARRATIVE:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On Thursday, November 16, 2023, at approximately 1626 hours, while on patrol in my marked Ford Explorer, B-35, I was traveling on Westbound I-70 in lane 3, when observed a blue Ford Fusion (MD 7FC1808) traveling in lane 2 with unauthorized window tinting material. The window tinting material was partially covering the front passenger area windows, and front windshield. The window tinting material appeared torn; which, concluded it was placed on the vehicle as an aftermarket modification. I positioned my patrol vehicle behind the Ford Fusion, activated my emergency equipment, and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle stopped on the right shoulder portion of Westbound I-70, just prior to Exit 56, Frederick, Frederick County, MD 21701.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I approached the vehicle on the passenger side, made contact with the driver, and identified myself as a Maryland State Trooper. I identified the driver by his Maryland Driver&amp;rsquo;s License as, Cristian Montano Bustamante (H/M DOB: 5/23/1991). Bustamante advised me that he did not possess a valid letter of approval for the window tinting material from the Maryland State Police Automotive Safety Enforcement Division. Bustamante advised me that he possessed the window tinting material on his windows for privacy reasons &amp;ndash; to prevent thefts of his belongings while working in Baltimore City.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;While speaking to Bustamante I smelled the strong, distinct odor of burnt cannabis emitting from the vehicle, and observed a hand-rolled, partially burnt cigar in the center cup holder area. Bustamante voluntarily provided me with his Maryland Medical Cannabis Card (MMCC #: P05M-E059-6BA6-66FC). I observed Bustamante&amp;rsquo;s eyes to be extremely bloodshot red, and glassy. Bustamante advised me that he, &amp;ldquo;took about five or six hits (puffs) in his car,&amp;rdquo; before operating a motor vehicle. Bustamante estimated his travel time from Baltimore City to the time of the traffic stop to be about 30 to 40 minutes. Bustamante would often laugh while speaking, but advised me that he was nervous around police. Often, Bustamante appeared paranoid, and would look around rapidly, and wipe his face or push his hair back. Bustamante advised me that he was prescribed Cannabis for anxiety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I requested Bustamante to conduct the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) to which he agreed. Bustamante advised me that he was familiar with the process of the SFST. I conducted a browse through Delta Plus, and found Bustamante was previously charged with Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol in February 2023. It should be noted that Bustamante possessed an Ignition Interlock Device in his vehicle at the time of this incident.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder portion of the highway in front of Bustamante&amp;rsquo;s vehicle. The evaluation was conducted during daylight hours, and blocked by multiple police vehicles. The patrol vehicle&amp;#39;s forward facing emergency lights were deactivated prior to the test being conducted. Bustamante was positioned facing away from nearby passing vehicle to prevent the onset of optokinetic nystagmus. Bustamante appeared in good physical condition. Bustamante advised me that he did not consume any illicit substances, alcohol, or medication prior to this incident other than the cannabis cigar. Bustamante did not require eyeglasses to see. Bustamante advised, he had no prior head injuries or serious medical conditions of which would prevent him from walking in a straight line or balancing on one foot. Bustamante advised me that he is only prescribed medications for mental health conditions. Bustamante advised me that he was once prescribed Oxycodone, but is no longer taking it. Bustamante advised me that he was able to perform the tests.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) test (0/6 clues):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test&amp;rsquo;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;rsquo;s eyes.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante advised, he understood. The following observations were made:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; not observed&lt;br /&gt; 2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation &amp;ndash; not observed&lt;br /&gt; 3.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 degrees &amp;ndash; not observed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;No Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was observed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Walk and Turn (4/8 clues):&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Prior to&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;was instructed to take a regular step with his left foot, and place his right foot directly in front of his left foot, touching heel-to-toe.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides, and to remain in the position until told to begin.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel-to-toe on every step.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;was to keep his hands flat by his side, keeping his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step out loud. On the ninth step,&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;was instructed and demonstrated to keep his lead foot planted, and to take a series of small steps in an 180&lt;sup&gt;o&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;semi-circle, around with his rear foot to face the direction he came from.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;was, again, instructed and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps as to be performed identical to the first series.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, maintaining heel-to-toe contact, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante advised he understood the directions. Bustamante was positioned on a center solid white line in the roadway for use of the completion of the test. Bustamante reassured me he understood the directions to remain in the starting position until told to begin. Again, Bustamante was given the option to remove his shoes prior to testing, but chose to keep his shoes on for the remainder of the test.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Walking Phase (1&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;Nine):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante raised his arms from his sides by more than 6 inches on steps 1 &amp;ndash; 3 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Walking Phase (2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;Nine):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante missed heel-to-toe contact by more than 1/2 inch on steps 3, 4, 9, and extra step 10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante raised his arms from his sides by more than 6 inches on steps 3, 4, 9 and extra step 10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante stepped off the line by more than 1/2 inch on step 3, 4, 9, and extra step 10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante took the incorrect number of steps and took 10 steps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante completed the turn satisfactory.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;,One Leg Stand (2/4 clues):&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Prior to&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and while performing the test.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;was explained when the test begins, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, look down at the raised foot, and count out loud, and continue the test until he was told to stop.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;advised, he understood the directions.&amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;chose to lift his left foot, and balance on his right foot.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0 &amp;ndash; 10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;began to sway at seconds 3 &amp;ndash; 10 &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante&amp;nbsp;raised his arms from his sides by more than 6 inches seconds 8 - 10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Seconds 11 &amp;ndash; 20&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante began to sway at second 11 &amp;ndash; 19&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante raised his arms from his sides by more than 6 inches seconds 11 &amp;ndash; 14 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Seconds 21 &amp;ndash; 30&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante began to sway at seconds 23&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ADDITIONAL FIELD SOBRIETY TEST:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I am certified through the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) as well as Standardized Field Sobriety Testing. With the A.R.I.D.E. certification I am able to administer the Modified Romberg and Lack of Convergence tests.&amp;nbsp;Due to the observation I made of Bustamante, and his admission to consuming a controlled dangerous substance (CDS), cannabis &amp;ndash; schedule I, I conducted the A.R.I.D.E. field tests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;LACK OF CONVERGENCE TEST (Negative results)&lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Lack of Convergence test. The tip of a pen was used as the test&amp;rsquo;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Bustamante&amp;#39;s eyes. I informed Bustamante that I will be moving the stimulus around in a circle, and will be moving it toward the bridge of his nose. I also informed Bustamante that I will not actually touch his nose with the stimulus. I instructed Bustamante to keep his head looking straight ahead, and to follow the stimulus with his eyes only. I asked Bustamante if he understood, to which, he advised he did.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Lack of convergence was present; Bustamante&amp;rsquo;s right eye failed to converge both times.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;MODIFIED ROMBERG TEST&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; The second test given was the Modified Romberg test. I instructed Bustamante to stand straight with his feet together and his arms down at his sides. I instructed Bustamante to remain in that position until I was finished giving the instructions. I instructed Bustamante that he will tilt his head back slightly and close his eyes and estimate the passage of 30 seconds. I instructed Bustamante that once he thought 30 seconds has gone by, he was to bring his head forward, open his eyes, and say &amp;quot;stop.&amp;quot; Bustamante advised, he understood the directions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Bustamante&amp;#39;s pupils slightly larger than normal, only slightly exposing his iris&amp;rsquo;. Bustamante would often shiver like he was cold, and laugh throughout the explanation of the instructions. Busamante would look around rapidly, and lick his lips nervously, appearing nervous or paranoid.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Balancing Stage:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante&amp;rsquo;s head would bob up and down throughout the duration of the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante possessed tremors in his eyelids.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:8px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bustamante&amp;rsquo;s legs and hands tremored throughout the duration of the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Based on the observations I made during contact with Bustamante, and the observations made during SFST I had reason to believe Bustamante was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of a controlled dangerous substance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; At approximately 1656 hours, Bustamante was placed under arrest, and a mouth check was conducted at time of arrest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; During a search incident to arrest of Bustamante&amp;rsquo;s vehicle &amp;ndash; various cannabis products were observed with proper prescription labels. Several photographs were taken and digitally uploaded to this report.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Bustamante was seated in the front seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Maryland State Police Frederick Barrack-&amp;quot;B&amp;quot; for further processing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;At approximately 1730 hours, Bustamante was read his DR-15 Advice of Rights. Bustamante submitted to an Intoximeter test resulting in .00 BrAC.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;At approximately 0242 hours, Bustamante was read his Advice of Rights and signed an MSP 180 Advice of Miranda Rights refused to speak further with me, however; Bustamante agreed to submit to a Drug Recognition Expert for further testing and a blood draw. DFC Dykhoff from the Frederick County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office responded to complete the DRE evaluation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; At approximately 1917 hours, Bustamante was transported to the Frederick Health Hospital for a blood draw. At 2020 hours Bustamante submitted to the blood draw, which was obtained by BSRN McLister.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The observed controlled dangerous substances were identified per my Maryland State Police training, knowledge, and experience with prior CDS arrests, and related incidents.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Case remains open pending the blood results, and charges for Bustamante.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;All events occurred in Frederick County, MD.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6859</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/03/2023 12:43:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6859</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/03/2023 13:21:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dodson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Travis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7103</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bonneville</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5824</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kaszubski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Rachel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6859</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>530068</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/16/2023 16:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6859</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/03/2023 13:17:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6859</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/03/2023 13:17:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6859</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/03/2023 13:02:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6859</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/03/2023 13:20:07</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>219556</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Montano Bustamante</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cristian</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/23/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>6.99770091E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>02/12/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M535</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bustamante</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cristian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Montano</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/23/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>6.99770091E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>01/27/2019 04:56:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B235</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Montano Bustamante</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cristian</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/23/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>6.99770091E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>M535</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/12/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bustamante</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cristian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Montano</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/23/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>6.99770091E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>B235</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/27/2019 04:56:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>179</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Poinsett</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Frederick</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21702</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3794</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.4649761</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.4283828</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>8824</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Eureka</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Walkersville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21793</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.35964</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.46548</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>831</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2008</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/27/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>831</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2008</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/27/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6859</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/03/2023 13:20:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6859</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/03/2023 13:20:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6859</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/03/2023 13:20:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6859</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/03/2023 13:20:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6859</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/03/2023 13:17:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6859</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/03/2023 13:17:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159516</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6859</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/03/2023 13:00:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6859</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/03/2023 13:00:12</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3FAHP07109R168883</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2009</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FOC</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4D</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLU</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7FC1808</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>