<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008941</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/11/2023 02:13:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/11/2023 02:13:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/11/2023 02:05:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/11/2023 02:05:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>crash,dui,dwi</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 02:13:16</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 13:29:35</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I695 / CHARLES ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>582316</AddressId>
      <City>MDC103</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 02:13:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/11/2023 05:24:12</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>582316</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I695</StreetName>
         <City>Towson</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.62992</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.41518</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L I695 / 0-0 CHARLES ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 0-0 CHARLES ST  RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 0-0 CHARLES ST LS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IL @ CHARLES RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL PT CHARLES LANE 1</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IL PT CHARLES</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L I-695 PRIOR TO CHARLES ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL @ CHARLES</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL PT CHARLES RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L @ CHARLES ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 0-0 CHARLES ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L @ CHARLES ST  R/SH</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL RAMP TO CHARLES STREET</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IL @ CHARLES</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>INNER LOOP BETWEEN 83S AND CHARLES</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L @ CHARLES ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL BTWN CHARLES/83NB</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 0-0 CHARLES ST RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/11/2023 02:13:13</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/11/2023 02:13:13</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/20/2023 09:33:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 02:13:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP1680</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 16:10:56</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI # 23-144&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;R-41 is equipped with a mobile video recording device, and it was functioning properly. Two segments of this incident are available. The Field Sobriety Testing is recorded utilizing R-41 MVR, as well as body camera footage from myself.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Defendant: Deandre Tyrell Ellis&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Date of Birth: 10/02/1991&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Date of Arrest: 03/11/2023&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Time of Arrest: 0250 hours&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Training Certifications:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;* Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police (MSP) and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;* Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;* Trained operator of Preliminary Breath Test (PBT)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Narrative:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;On Saturday, March 11, 2023, at approximately 0205 hours, I, Trooper Rhoten was dispatched to I/L 695 at Charles St. I arrived on the scene and observed a black Chevy Equinox with Maryland registration 6DX5202 that was disabled in lane 1. The Equinox had heavy front-end damage and airbag deployment. The driver of the Equinox was nowhere to be found.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A witness who I identified through his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license as David McDonald, DOB (06/08/1973) was on the scene and was able to tell me what happened. McDonald stated he was driving home from work and saw the Equinox disabled in lane 1 with heavy front-end damage. As a concerned citizen, McDonald pulls over to make sure nobody is injured. He stated that when he arrived at scene there was a second vehicle with two African American females that seemed to be also checking on the driver of the Equinox welfare. McDonald asked if anybody has called the police, and one of the African American females stated &amp;ldquo;somebody needs to call somebody because this guy is drunk&amp;rdquo;. The driver of the Equinox asked McDonald if he could use his phone and McDonald did not allow him to. McDonald stated that&amp;#39;s when the driver took off on foot on O/L 695. He stated the driver was an African American male wearing a white t-shirt. I relayed this information to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring PCO. I did a routine MVA/METERS check on the Equinox, and it returned that the registered owner is Deandre Tyrell Ellis, DOB (10/02/1991).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At approximately 0230 hours, dispatch puts out a black male pedestrian walking on O/L 695 at Greenspring avenue. TFC Waugh #6930 responds and is successful in locating the pedestrian. Waugh identifies the pedestrian through his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license (MD10272660028) as Deandre Tyrell Ellis, DOB (10/02/1991). I advised Waugh that Ellis is the registered owner of the Chevy Equinox that I am on the scene with. Waugh transports Ellis back onto the scene. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Upon Ellis arrival back on the scene, I was able to positively identify him through his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license as Deandre Tyrell Ellis, DOB (10/02/1991). While speaking with Ellis, I was immediately met with a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his mouth. I asked Ellis if this was his vehicle and he stated &amp;ldquo;yes&amp;rdquo;. I asked Ellis what happened, and he stated that he fell asleep and struck the guardrail. I did a routine check on Ellis, and it revealed he had a valid class C license with no warrants.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I deactivated my front emergency lights and asked Ellis to walk to the front of his vehicle, to which he complied. I asked Ellis if he has had any alcoholic beverages tonight, and he stated &amp;ldquo;a couple of beers&amp;rdquo;. I asked him how long ago did he consume those alcoholic beverages, and he stated &amp;ldquo;2-3 hours ago&amp;rdquo;. I advised Ellis I would like to put him through a series of tests to make sure he wasn&amp;#39;t driving under the influence of alcohol, and Ellis complied. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;The SFST was performed on I/L 695 at Charles St on the left shoulder in front of Ellis&amp;#39;s vehicle. It was dry and approximately 40 degrees with cloudy skies. The road was level and free from any debris. The direct area for testing was illuminated by my flashlight, Ellis&amp;#39;s vehicle lights, and streetlights. Additionally, my patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. I observed Ellis wearing a black sweatshirt, blue jeans, and sneakers. &amp;nbsp;Before administering the SFST, I asked Ellis several preliminary questions:&lt;br /&gt; Glasses or contacts-No&lt;br /&gt; Medical Conditions-No&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Injuries-No&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Ellis&amp;rsquo;s eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. His pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. He was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. Ellis was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;1/2) Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;3/4) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;5/6) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;WALK AND TURN (2/8 clues observed)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Prior to Ellis performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Ellis was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. He was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. He was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. He was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Ellis was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Ellis was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. He was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keeping his hands down by his sides, looking down at his feet, and counting each step out loud. Ellis was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo;.&lt;br /&gt; Instructional stage:&lt;br /&gt; Remained in the right instructed position&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st Nine)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Ellis performed satisfactory during the first nine (9) steps.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Turn:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Ellis failed to keep his front foot planted as instructed.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Ellis took ten (10) steps, rather than the nine (9) he was instructed to.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Prior to Ellis performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. He was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand-two) and continue the test until told to stop. Ellis was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Instructional Stage: Remained as demonstrated.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Balance and Count Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Ellis swayed from side to side for the entire duration of the test.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Ellis raised his arms over the 6-inch minimum to approximately 12 inches away from his body, during the entire duration of the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Ellis hopped during the end of the test to regain balance.&lt;br /&gt; Although not a direct clue, Ellis failed to count out loud during the duration of the test.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;ARREST&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Based on the following, I had reason to believe Ellis was driving a motor vehicle under the influence:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;-Strong odor of alcoholic beverage on breath&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;-Glassy eyes&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;-Admission to consuming alcoholic beverages&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;-Clues observed during Field Sobriety Testing&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Due to the number of observations, I concluded Ellis was driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0250 hours, I placed Ellis under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. Ellis was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy. He was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack for processing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;*** 20-Minute Observation Period***&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;I conducted a 20-minute observation period on Ellis from the time of arrest, where I inspected his mouth and determined there to be no foreign objects of any kind.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;The DR-15 Advice of Rights was audibly read to Ellis in English, and he was also provided a copy to read over at which time he refused to submit to the Intoximeter Test at 0324hrs.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Ellis was very polite and cooperative throughout the process. Ellis was given copies of all pertinent paperwork, including citations for driving under the influence of alcohol, and was released from the Barrack to a sober driver; Victoria Ellis.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;I request this case remain open, pending an approved accident report.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 04:34:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7513</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/15/2023 00:25:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rhoten</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7513</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miranda</LastName>
            <FirstName>Neil</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2271</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rhoten</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7513</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rhoten</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7513</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498340</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3224</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 05:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3224</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 05:23:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7513</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/11/2023 05:27:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498340</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 05:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 05:23:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7513</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/11/2023 05:29:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498340</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 05:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 05:23:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7513</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/11/2023 05:28:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498340</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 05:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 05:23:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7513</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/11/2023 05:28:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498340</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 05:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 05:23:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7513</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/11/2023 05:25:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498340</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 05:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 05:23:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7513</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/11/2023 05:26:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 05:23:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371285</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ellis</LastName>
               <FirstName>Deandre</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Tyrell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/02/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.25634178E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2023 05:05:55</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D536</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ellis</LastName>
               <FirstName>Deandre</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Tyrell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/02/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.25634178E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>E420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D536</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2023 05:05:55</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1600</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Miller </StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Westminster</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21158</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.001994</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.621283</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>381</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8682</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 05:31:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 05:31:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>49</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 23:25:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:59</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371339</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>MCDONOLD</LastName>
               <FirstName>David</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Paul</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/08/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2023 23:25:35</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M235</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>MCDONOLD</LastName>
               <FirstName>David</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Paul</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/08/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M235</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2023 23:25:35</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>703</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9618</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 23:25:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 05:24:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7513</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/11/2023 05:24:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150761</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 05:30:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7513</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/11/2023 05:30:28</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>13</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2GNALFEK0C1203561</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2012</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>EQU</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6DX5202</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/22/2023 09:06:10</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/22/2023 09:06:10</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/23/2023 16:10:56</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/22/2023 09:06:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 16:10:57</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On March 22, 2023, at approximately 0907 hours, I, Trooper Rhoten attached an approved ACRS report.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I request this case closed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All the above events occurred in Baltimore County, MD.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7513</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/22/2023 09:07:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7513</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/22/2023 09:08:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Horton</LastName>
            <FirstName>Arthur</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1680</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rhoten</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7513</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>