<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-001340</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/12/2023 00:04:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/12/2023 00:04:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/11/2023 23:47:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/11/2023 23:47:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic Stop//DUI//DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/12/2023 00:04:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4027</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/18/2023 09:15:25</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>680186</AddressId>
      <City>MDC308</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/12/2023 00:04:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/13/2023 00:21:47</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>680186</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>79</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I95 Nb</StreetName>
         <City>Abingdon</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.271401</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.475721</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/12/2023 00:04:40</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/12/2023 00:04:40</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>62</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/13/2023 23:49:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/12/2023 00:04:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/13/2023 23:49:52</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MSP un-marked patrol vehicle M-51 is equipped with a mobile recording device. This incident was recorded.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Defendant: Anthony Delwayne Robertson&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date of Birth: 09/10/1961&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MD DL: MD-10272920108&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Date of Arrest: 01/12/2023&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Time of Arrest: 0003 (12:03 AM)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUI #: 23-004 (JFK Highway&amp;nbsp;Barrack)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TRAINING/CERTIFICATIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I am trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I am trained and certified to conduct preliminary breath tests by the Maryland State Police.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On January 11, 2023 at approximately 2347 hours, I, Trooper&amp;nbsp;Johnson(#7359) of the Maryland State Police JFK Highway Barrack, was working routine patrol on northbound I-95 in the area of mile marker 79.0, Abingdon, Harford County, Maryland. At that time,&amp;nbsp;I observed a gray Cadillac CTS traveling in lane 3&amp;nbsp;of northbound I-95, traveling at a high rate of speed and failing to maintain its lane. I positioned my unmarked patrol vehicle, M-51, behind the gray Cadillac CTS and began to pace the vehicle. After traveling behind the gray Cadillac CTS for approximately 4/10ths of a mile, keeping equal distance been both vehicles, it was determined the gray Cadillac CTS was traveling at speed of 77 miles per hour. The gray Cadillac CTS was traveling across the solid yellow line dividing lane 3 from the right shoulder by approximately half of the car&amp;#39;s width. I then activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the gray Cadillac CTS. The gray Cadillac CTS was bearing Maryland registration 6CS1547.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I exited my vehicle wearing my full Maryland State Police issued uniform complete with brass breast badge. I approached the vehicle on the passenger side, where I made contact with both the driver and passenger of the vehicle. Once I approached the passenger side window, I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle. I introduced myself to both the driver and passenger of the vehicle, advised the driver the reason for the stop and proceeded to ask who had been consuming alcoholic beverages that night. The passenger immediately stated that she had been out at a bar and that the driver was just giving her a ride back to her residence. I asked the driver if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages, to which he stated that he had not had anything to drink. I observed the driver&amp;#39;s eyes to be bloodshot and glassy while speaking with him from the passenger side of the vehicle. The driver advised me that he was her designated driver home from the bar. The driver was identified by his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license as Anthony Delwayne Robertson (DOB: 09/10/1961, 1/M). I then returned to my patrol vehicle to perform standard METERS/NCIC checks on Robertson and his vehicle. Upon the arrival of Trooper Reid #7459, I approached the gray Cadillac CTS and proceeded to ask Robertson if I could speak with him outside his vehicle. Robertson complied and proceeded to meet me at the front of his vehicle. I advised Robertson that due to the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from&amp;nbsp;the vehicle, his speed and the failure to maintain his lane that I would like to conduct Standard Field Sobriety Testing to make sure that he is okay to continue driving his vehicle. Robertson advised me that he had not been consuming any alcoholic beverages and did not want to perform Standard Field Sobriety Testing. While speaking to Robertson outside his vehicle, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting off of his breath and person. I continued to explain to Robertson that I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting form his breath and that his eyes were glassy. I advised Robertson that due to my observations, both before and during the traffic stop, that I have reason to believe he had consumed alcoholic beverages. Robertson asked what would occur if he did not perform Standard Field Sobriety Testing and I advised Robertson that if he refused the tests that were being offered, that I would then make a decision based off of my observations during the entirety of the traffic stop. I asked Robertson once more if he would be comfortable performing Standard Field Sobriety Testing. Robertson asked if we could travel off of I-95 to a safer location. Robertson advised he did not feel safe performing the tests on the right shoulder of I-95. I explained to Robertson that we would not be leaving our current location. I advised Robertson that there were two patrol vehicles with the rear emergency lights activated behind where we were standing. I explained to Robertson that due to my suspicion of him consuming alcoholic beverages, I wanted to perform the tests at our current location. Robertson then agreed to perform Standard Field Sobriety Testing.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The tests were performed on the right shoulder&amp;nbsp;of northbound I- 95 at mile marker 79.0, Abingdon, Harford County, Maryland. The surface was dry, level, and clear from any debris. Lighting conditions consisted of the headlights from Robertson&amp;#39;s vehicle&amp;nbsp;and my handheld flashlight.&amp;nbsp; Robertson was positioned in a manner to ensure that headlights from passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. Robertson appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any physical injuries. I asked him the following questions:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Do you have any Physical Injuries: None.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Do you have any Medical Conditions: None.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Are you taking any Medications: None,&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Are you wearing any glasses and/or Contacts: Robertson advised that he wore glasses, but did not need them for the testing.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Sanchez had equal pupil size and equal tracking with no resting nystagmus.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Lack of Smooth Pursuit: Present in both eyes.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation: Present in both eyes.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 Degrees: Present in both eyes.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Additionally&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Vertical Gaze Nystagmus: Not present&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Robertson stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Lost his&amp;nbsp;balance and stepped completely offline two (2)&amp;nbsp;separate occasions. Robertson failed to remain in the position that was asked of him until he was told to begin.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Walking Stage (1&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;Nine):&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Stepped completely offline on steps 3 and 6.&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Missed heel to toe by more than 1 inch on steps 7 and 9&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Turn:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Improper turn- Robertson failed to keep his&amp;nbsp;lead foot planted and picked up both feet&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Walking Stage (2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;Nine):&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ol&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Missed heel to toe by more than 1 inch on steps 5 and 7&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Robertson stated he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Robertson raised his foot and put it on the ground on three(3) separate occasions. On the fist attempt to raise his foot, Robertson counted &amp;quot;One-thousand one, one-thousand two, one-thousand three&amp;quot; and put hs foot down. On his second attempt to raise his foot, Robertson counted &amp;quot;One-thousand one, one-thousand two, one-thousand two, one-thousand three&amp;quot;. On his third attempt, Robertson counted &amp;quot;One-thousand one, one-thousand two, one-thousand three&amp;quot; and put hs foot down. Robertson then stopped performing the test and placed his hands in his pockets, prior to me telling him it was over. I asked Robertson if he was done performing the test, to which he stated that there was no way he could do it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Puts foot down on three (3) separate occasions&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li&gt;Uses arms for balance for the entirety of the test&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ARREST:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Due to the clues observed during Standard Field Sobriety Testing, my observations prior to conducting the tragic stop and Robertson to have bloodshot/glassy eyes, I concluded Robertson was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0003 hours, I placed Robertson under arrest for Driving while Under the Influence of Alcohol. He was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and was transported to the Maryland State Police JFK Highway Barrack for processing. While en route to the JFK Highway Barrack, I asked Robertson why he was dishonest about drinking and Robertson stated, &amp;quot;I got CDL&amp;#39;s and shit man&amp;quot;. I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Robertson&amp;#39;s breath and person inside my patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Upon arrival at the barrack, I provided Robertson a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights and read it to him in English. He stated that he understood the form at 0033 hours. Robertson refused to take the intoximeter and said that he would like to speak with his lawyer prior to taking any more tests. After offering the intoximeter test to Robertson, Robertson stated, &amp;quot;I know I&amp;#39;m drunk. I&amp;#39;d probably blow like a 9.9 or something&amp;#39;&amp;#39;. Robertson also advised me while at the barrack that he had been out with his passenger earlier that night at a casino. He explained that they had acquired approximately $2,000 in winnings. Robertson stated, &amp;quot;That&amp;#39;s why we were drinking so much&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;INTOXIMETER RESULT:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;N/A&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Robertson was polite and cooperative during the encounter. He&amp;nbsp;was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to a sober driver from the Maryland State Police JFK Highway Barrack.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 22:00:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2023 23:39:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reid</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7459</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phillips</LastName>
            <FirstName>Billy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4332</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cory</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7359</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490720</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/11/2023 23:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 00:25:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2023 00:30:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490720</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/11/2023 23:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 00:27:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2023 00:30:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490720</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/11/2023 23:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 00:29:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2023 00:30:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490720</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/11/2023 23:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 00:29:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2023 00:30:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490720</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/11/2023 23:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 00:29:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2023 00:30:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490720</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/11/2023 23:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 00:29:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2023 00:30:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>61</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 01:22:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:52</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365890</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>ROBERTSON</LastName>
               <FirstName>ANTHONY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>DELWAYNE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/10/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/12/2023 00:04:47</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R163</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>ROBERTSON</LastName>
               <FirstName>ANTHONY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>DELWAYNE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/10/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R163</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/12/2023 00:04:47</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3543</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Dudley</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21213</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.562267</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.320825</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 01:22:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:39</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 00:29:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2023 00:29:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148532</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/12/2023 00:04:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/12/2023 00:04:46</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/11/2023 23:53:30</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>8</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2011</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CADI</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6CS1547</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>