<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-038023</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/28/2023 21:13:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/28/2023 21:13:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/28/2023 20:17:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/28/2023 20:17:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI/Poss. CDS not marijuana</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 21:13:09</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2864</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 09:56:22</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN HWY/ PEGGY NECK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>585136</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 21:13:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/03/2023 02:40:40</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>585136</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Princess Anne</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.66655</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.260908</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB 13 / JUST NORTH OF PEGGY NECK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13848-14120 OCEAN HWY / 31259-31279 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13647-13844 OCEAN HWY / 31298-31853 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13647-13844 OCEAN HWY / 31280-31297 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13656-13847 OCEAN HWY / 31259-31279 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13845-14111 OCEAN HWY / 31280-31297 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/28/2023 21:13:05</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/28/2023 21:13:05</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/15/2023 09:53:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/28/2023 21:13:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 20:19:43</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&amp;nbsp;Scene Processing:&amp;nbsp; The suspect in this case, Alison P. Rose, was arrested by members of the Princess Anne Police Department and the Somerset County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Office for an active arrest warrant.&amp;nbsp; Once I was able to secure the collision scene, for which Rose was the suspect who had fled the scene, I made contact with her at the Princess Anne Barrack where she was advised of her Miranda Rights and questioned about this case.&amp;nbsp; The interview which was conducted in the Princess Anne Barrack interview room was audibly and visually recorded via my body warn camera.&amp;nbsp; Rose was advised that she was being audibly and visually recorded.&amp;nbsp; Body warn camera video:&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=083ceb11d34c4a13a2948a13f93862f6&amp;amp;partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 10/28/23 at 2113 hrs., I was dispatched to respond to southbound US Rt. 13 at Peggy Neck Rd., Princess Anne, Somerset County, MD in regards to a two vehicle collision. Upon arrival, I met with Officers from Princess Anne Police Department and the Somerset Co. Sheriff&amp;#39;s Office and one of the vehicle operators involved in the collision, Corey Chavell Moore. While speaking with each of these individuals I was able to ascertain the following: Moore was traveling southbound on US Rt. 13 approaching Peggy Neck Rd., in lane 2, operating his 2008 Chevrolet passenger car when his vehicle was violently struck in the left rear by another vehicle. This collision disabled Moore&amp;#39;s vehicle and caused him to spin before coming to final rest in between lanes 1 and 2 of US Rt. 13. The vehicle that collided with Moore fled the scene of the collision, but the vehicle became disabled in lane 1 of US Rt. 13, south of Peggy Neck Rd. where the operator fled the scene on foot. As my investigation continued, I ascertained from Ofc. R. Redding of the Princess Anne Police Department, that the vehicle that caused the collision, a 2018 Mercedes SUV, Maryland registration 4EJ1537, had been reported stolen to them earlier in the day. The suspect in the vehicle theft was the owner&amp;#39;s granddaughter, Alison Paige Rose.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;After a brief K-9 track, Princess Anne PD received information from Rose&amp;#39;s grandmother that Rose had just returned to their joint residence at 30505 Brannigan Dr. Princess Anne. Ofc. T. McGhee of thePrincess Anne PD, along with Dep. Walburt the SCSO responded to this residence where Rose was located. It was learned that Rose had an active arrest warrant issued in Queen Anne&amp;#39;s County, MD for possession of CDS, not cannabis, for which she was placed under arrest and transported to the MSP Princess Anne Barrack for processing.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Near Rose&amp;#39;s person, when she was arrested, were two syringes and two wax folds that were collected and brought to the Barrack with Rose.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;After I was able to secure the crash scene, I responded to the MSP Princess Anne Barrack and made contact with Rose. Rose was taken to the Barrack interview room where she was advised of her Miranda Rights. After being advised of her Rights, which she stated she understood, Rose signed an MSP form 180 acknowledging she understood her Rights and was willing to waive them and be interviewed about the events that had occurred.&amp;nbsp; This interview was audibly and visually recorded via my body warn camera.&amp;nbsp; Rose was advised that the interview was, in fact, being recorded via the body worn camera.&amp;nbsp; In summation of this interview, Rose admitted that she was the operator and sole occupant of the 2018 Mercedes SUV listed above. She admitted that a collision occurred, but her belief was another vehicle &amp;quot;ran into her.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; She made reference to several ailments to include neck and leg pain that had been caused by the collision but refused medical treatment when it was offered. Rose admitted to leaving the scene of the collision, on foot, but was able to &amp;quot;get a ride&amp;quot; to her residence. During the course of the interview, Rose was constantly &amp;quot;on the nod,&amp;quot; her eyes were heavy, her speech was slow and slurred, she often mumbled as she spoke, and her movements were slow and lethargic. Based on these observations, Rose was questioned about her illicit drug use. During these questions, Rose admitted to being a heroin addict and that she had used heroin earlier in the day. She added that the heroin that&amp;nbsp;she had injected earlier in the day may have contained fentanyl as she had a &amp;quot;different feeling&amp;quot; than she usually does after injecting heroin. Rose added, later in the interview, that she had injected heroin, at her residence, just prior to her arrest.&amp;nbsp; She pointed to a red mark on her neck indicating where she had injected heroin stating she &amp;quot;thought she would probably be arrested.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; When asked if she believed she should have been driving based on how she felt from the heroin she had injected at approximately 1100 hrs., prior to her injection before her arrest, Rose stated that she did not believe she should have been driving.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Based on these observations, I asked Rose to submit to standardized field sobriety tests which she stated she would. These tests were conducted in the Princess Anne Barrack interview room and audibly and visually recorded via my body warn camera.&amp;nbsp; Prior to beginning the tests, Rose was asked about any known illnesses or injuries that my affect her taking these tests.&amp;nbsp; Again, Rose stated that she had neck and leg pain caused by the collision, but, again, she advised that she did not want/need medical attention.&amp;nbsp; The results of these standardized field sobriety tests area as follows:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HGN:&amp;nbsp; no nystagmus was noted during the test.&amp;nbsp; It was noted before, during, and after the test, Rose swayed in a circle and would &amp;quot;nod off.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 9 Step walk and turn:&amp;nbsp; During the instructional phase of the test, Rose could not maintain heel to toe contact nor maintain her balance even falling against the interview room wall.&amp;nbsp; During the test, on her first step, Rose lost her balance, stepped off line and used her right hand against the wall to maintain her balance and missed heel/toe contact on each step.&amp;nbsp; After turning, Rose proceeded with the second set of nine steps, losing her balance, stepping off line, and using her left arm against the wall to maintain balance on step 2.&amp;nbsp; On step 4 she again lost her balance, missing heel/toe contact and used her right arm against the table to maintain balance.&amp;nbsp; Rose did not make heel/toe contact on any step.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; One leg stand:&amp;nbsp; During this test, Rose raised her right leg, the one she stated &amp;quot;hurts.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; As she counted to 1003, Rose began to sway in a circle before putting her foot down and asking what number she needed count to.&amp;nbsp; After being advised, again, to continue until told to stop, Rose counted to 1012 where she again began to sway in a circle, lose her balance, and put her foot down when she was advised to &amp;quot;stop&amp;quot; as the 30 second test was ended.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Throughout each test, Rose&amp;#39;s movements where slow and lethargic and she displayed extreme difficulty in maintaining her balance.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;After field sobriety tests were completed,&amp;nbsp; Rose was then advised she was now also under arrest for DUI/DWI and advised of her DR-15 Advise of Rights.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;After being advised of these Rights, Rose submitted to an Intoximeter which was administered by Sgt. Peters, a certified Intoximeter operator in the State of Maryland with the results being .00. Based on my training, knowledge, experience, along with Rose&amp;#39;s admissions of using heroin prior to driving and that she &amp;quot;should not have been driving&amp;quot; it is clear that she was, in fact DUI/DWI during the collision.&amp;nbsp; As such, I attempted to have Rose evaluated by a Drug Recognition Expert but found none available.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;After speaking with Rose, I turned my attention to the syringes and wax folds collected during her arrest. The syringes contained blood and heroin residue while the wax folds contained heroin residue which I was able to recognize as such, again, through my training, knowledge, and experience that includes numerous CDS arrests as a 27 year member of the MSP and by Rose&amp;#39;s own admissions.&amp;nbsp; Based on the nature of the CDS/paraphernalia and it&amp;#39;s danger to those that come in contact with it, the property was photographed and placed in the Barrack sharps container, documented via an MSP form 67, chain of custody.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;After being processed, Rose&amp;#39;s initial appearance was held via telephone.&amp;nbsp; In this case, Rose was charged with CDS, not marijuana, and CDS paraphernalia.&amp;nbsp; The initial appearance also included her hearing for the Centreville warrant and the charges applied for by Ofc. Redding in regards to the vehicle theft.&amp;nbsp; Rose was ordered held without bond.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Upon being transported to the Somerset County Detention Center, against court order, jail personnel refused to take Rose into their custody based on her speaking of injuries she inquired during the collision.&amp;nbsp; Rose was transported to Tidal Health where it was determined that Rose had inquired no noteworthy injuries sustained during the collision but a batter of tests concluded that Rose needed to be medically attended to for illnesses unrelated to the collision and was ultimately admitted into the care of Tidal Health.&amp;nbsp; On 10/30/23 at approximately 1500 hrs., Rose signed herself out of the care of Tidal Health and was transported to the SCDC and released into their custody.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Case closed by arrest.&amp;nbsp; All events occurred in Somerset County, MD</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP2748</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/03/2023 03:03:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP2748</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/10/2023 10:51:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norfolk</LastName>
            <FirstName>Wyatt</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7120</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Meyers</LastName>
            <FirstName>Marlin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2748</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>527485</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/28/2023 20:17:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP2748</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/03/2023 02:59:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP2748</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/03/2023 02:59:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP2748</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/03/2023 02:45:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP2748</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/03/2023 03:02:34</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>228142</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>TATUM</LastName>
               <FirstName>DIANA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MICHELLE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/16/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T350</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Rose</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alison</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Paige</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/17/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/16/2019 13:55:21</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A425</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>TATUM</LastName>
               <FirstName>DIANA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MICHELLE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/16/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T350</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Rose</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alison</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Paige</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/17/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A425</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/16/2019 13:55:21</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>900</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Division</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21804</Zip5>
               <Zip4>6433</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.597043</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.352635</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>30505</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Brannigan</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Princess Anne</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21853</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.694501</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.196613</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>28076</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Venton</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Princess Anne</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21853</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.77957</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.196644</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP2748</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/03/2023 03:02:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP2748</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/03/2023 03:02:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP2748</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/03/2023 02:59:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP2748</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/03/2023 02:59:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>