<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-044406</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/16/2023 01:10:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/16/2023 01:10:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/16/2023 00:43:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/16/2023 00:43:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI Traffic arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/16/2023 01:10:09</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4437</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 09:47:03</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>27 MM CAPITAL BELTWAY EB, HYATTSVILLE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>716151</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/16/2023 01:10:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:17:16</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>716151</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>27</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm Capital Beltway Eb Hyattsville</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.9570766666667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0205198333333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/16/2023 01:10:08</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/16/2023 01:10:08</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 18:44:50</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/16/2023 01:10:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.5pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;MSP unmarked vehicle Q-41 is equipped with a mobile recording device. Body worn camera worn and operational. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:12.5pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;bull; Defendant: Nelson B Hernandez Portillo&lt;br /&gt; &amp;bull; Date of Birth: 06/30/1992&lt;br /&gt; &amp;bull; Date of Arrest: 12/16/2023&lt;br /&gt; &amp;bull; Time of Arrest: 0106 hours&lt;br /&gt; &amp;bull; DUI #: 23-313&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;* Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.5pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:12.5pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;On Saturday, December 16, 2023, at approximately 0043 hours, I, Trooper Webb of the Maryland State Police &amp;ndash; College Park Barrack was on routine patrol in my unmarked MSP vehicle Q-41 in lane 1 of the exit ramp from southbound 95 to outer loop 495.&amp;nbsp; At this time, I observed a red Hyundai Elantra in front of me in lane 1 bearing Maryland registration 8FD7419. I observed the Hyundai go from lane 1 on the exit ramp and off the roadway to the left into the dirt area two times while traveling. As I continued to observe the vehicle now on outer loop 495 prior to Maryland 650 in lane 6, the Hyundai would go from its established lane 6, crossing over the solid white line to the right shoulder by a tire width an additional three times. At this time I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; After turning on my lights, the vehicle pulled off the roadway to the right and onto the shoulder and came to a complete stop.&amp;nbsp; After the vehicle came to a complete stop I made contact with the driver.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the operator via the drivers side window and upon my approach I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; I gave the driver my rank, name, ID number, agency and I informed the driver the reason for the stop. I also advised him the stop was being audibly/visually recorded. I requested his license and registration card.&amp;nbsp; The driver was identified by his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license as Nelson B Hernandez Portillo.&amp;nbsp; I asked Hernandez Portillo how much he had to drink, and he stated, &amp;quot;Four beers.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; As I spoke to Hernandez Portillo, I intentionally observed his eyes to be glassy and bloodshot with a gazed look and noticed his head and body movements were slow and lethargic.&amp;nbsp;I returned to my patrol vehicle and conducted routine checks on Hernandez Portillo.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I approached the vehicle again and requested Hernandez Portillo exit his vehicle and walk to the front of his vehicle, to which he complied.&amp;nbsp; I continued to speak with Hernandez Portillo outside his vehicle and as Hernandez Portillo spoke, I continued to smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.&amp;nbsp;I informed Hernandez Portillo that I wanted him to perform field sobriety tests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.5pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the shoulder of the Beltway. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 30 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlamps, patrol vehicle headlamps, spotlight, and my flashlight. My patrol vehicle&amp;rsquo;s forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Hernandez Portillo appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. Before I continued with Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, I had Trooper Esuma (ID #: 7574) arrive on scene to translate what I said in English into Spanish for Hernandez Portillo.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Hernandez Portillo the following questions:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Injuries &amp;ndash; No&lt;br /&gt; Medication &amp;ndash; No&lt;br /&gt; Medical Conditions &amp;ndash; No&lt;br /&gt; Glasses - No&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pointer finger was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Hernandez Portillo&amp;#39;s eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Hernandez Portillo&amp;#39;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking and no resting Nystagmus was observed. He was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Hernandez Portillo if he understood the instructions, and he stated &amp;quot;yes.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.5pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Hernandez Portillo performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Hernandez Portillo was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Hernandez Portillo was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Hernandez Portillo was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Hernandez Portillo was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Hernandez Portillo was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Hernandez Portillo was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Hernandez Portillo was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Hernandez Portillo if he understood the test and he stated, &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.5pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;1.) Began test before instructed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Nothing to report&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.5pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on step 7.&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Stepped of line by a foots width on step 7.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.5pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Turn:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Improper - turned in one fluid motion to the left.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.5pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND (1/4 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Hernandez Portillo performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Hernandez Portillo was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Hernandez Portillo if he understood the test, and he stated &amp;quot;yes.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Nothing to report.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Hands came up for balance more than 6 inches from her body.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Nothing to report.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Nothing to report.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.5pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Hernandez Portillo submitted to a preliminary breath test with a .085 BrAC result.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;ARREST&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Hernandez Portillo was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Swerving vehicle multiple times.&lt;br /&gt; * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; * Slow and lethargic head and body movements.&lt;br /&gt; * Eyes glassy and bloodshot with a gazed look.&lt;br /&gt; * Admitted to consuming 4 beers.&lt;br /&gt; * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests.&lt;br /&gt; * PBT result of .085.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I arrested Hernandez Portillo for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0106 hours, and he was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Maryland State Police &amp;ndash; College Park Barrack for processing. Once at the barrack, I played the Spanish audio DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Hernandez Portillo in its entirety.&amp;nbsp; At the conclusion of the form, Hernandez Portillo verbally advised that he would not submit to the intoximeter test and signed the form indicating the same.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I conducted the observation period on Hernandez Portillo in its entirety starting with his time of arrest. I escorted Hernandez Portillo into the arrest processing room and remained in his custody until the time of test. Hernandez Portillo&amp;#39;s mouth was checked and no foreign objects or piercings were observed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.5pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Hernandez Portillo was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and later released to his friend. Hernandez Portillo was polite and cooperative throughout the process.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 13:26:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 14:22:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Esuma</LastName>
            <FirstName>Smith</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7574</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dunlap</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6273</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Webb</LastName>
            <FirstName>Noah</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7303</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533883</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 00:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533883</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 00:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533883</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 00:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533883</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 00:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533883</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 00:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533883</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 00:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533883</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 00:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 13:20:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:20:45</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>395430</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hernandez Portillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nelson</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>B</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/30/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/16/2023 04:39:07</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N425</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hernandez Portillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nelson</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>B</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/30/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N425</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/16/2023 04:39:07</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>8704</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Gilbert</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>1</SubNumber>
               <City>Silver Spring</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20912</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.996546</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.998732</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 13:20:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:20:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 13:20:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:20:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 13:20:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:20:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:18:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159892</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 14:21:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 14:21:06</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2008</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HYUN</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ELN</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>RED</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8FD7419</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>