<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-046040</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/30/2023 02:05:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/30/2023 02:05:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/30/2023 01:57:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/30/2023 01:57:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Single vehicle collision resulting in the driver being placed under arrest for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/30/2023 02:05:44</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5781</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 16:46:00</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>S 270 X6 TO X4 HWY/ WOOTTON PKWY</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>717523</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/30/2023 02:05:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/31/2023 05:50:55</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>717523</AddressId>
         <StreetName>S/B I-270</StreetName>
         <City>Potomac</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>2054</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>PKWY</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-77.15787</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.06661</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/30/2023 02:05:40</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/30/2023 02:05:40</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/13/2024 16:46:01</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/30/2023 02:05:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:25</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP unmarked vehicle N-7 is equipped with a mobile recording device&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Darling Matilde Moraga Garcia&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 08/13/1992&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 12/30/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 0242 hours&lt;br /&gt; DUI #: 23-283&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; *Trained in administering advanced standardized field sobriety tests (ARIDE) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; *Attended the DUI Conference held by the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On December 30, 2023, at approximately 0158 hours, I, Trooper Lear (#7154), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating unmarked MSP vehicle N-7 in Rockville, Montgomery County, Maryland. I was dispatched to locate a single vehicle collision in the area of southbound I-270 at Wootton Parkway. I arrived on the scene and observed a blue Ford Fusion with obvious damage to the front passenger side. The blue Ford Fusion was bearing MD registration 8EY9899.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I made contact with the driver and immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I immediately observed the driver&amp;rsquo;s eyes to be bloodshot and glassy with a glazed look. The driver was identified by her MD driver&amp;rsquo;s license as Darling Matilde Moraga Garcia (DOB: 08/13/1992, H/M). I asked Moraga Garcia if she was the one driving the Ford at the time of the collision. Moraga Garcia advised she was the driver and did not remember the sequence of events that led up to the collision. Moraga Garcia advised she was tired and this was her first time &amp;ldquo;going out&amp;rdquo; in a while. Moraga Garcia believed she struck debris in the road. TFC Rowe #5975 checked the area for any debris in the road or shoulders of I-270 and did not locate anything. Moraga Garcia refused medical treatment on scene and advised she was not injured. Moraga Garcia wanted to leave the scene and go to Johns Hopkins Hospital where her daughter was being treated for an unrelated health issue. During our interaction, I would observe Moraga Garcia sway left to right and front to back when she was standing up. Moraga Garcia started to use the concrete traffic barrier to maintain balance. I observed Moraga Garcia&amp;rsquo;s speech and body movements to be slow and lethargic. I advised the Rockville Barrack I would be conducting standardized field sobriety tests on Moraga Garcia. Moraga Garcia obtained a suspended driver&amp;rsquo;s license for numerous court dates she missed. Moraga Garcia had an active warrant out for her arrest for driving on a public highway with a suspended license. Moraga Garcia was unsure if she wanted to submit to the standardized field sobriety tests. Mortgage Garcia advised she didn&amp;rsquo;t have &amp;ldquo;much&amp;rdquo; to drink and didn&amp;rsquo;t drink &amp;ldquo;much&amp;rdquo; before that night. Moraga Garcia admitted to consuming one Tequila shot and one Corona beer at a restaurant in Layhill, MD.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed in front of my patrol vehicle on the right shoulder of southbound I-270 at Wootton Parkway. The surface was dry, level grade, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 30 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of light illuminating from light poles and my patrol vehicle&amp;rsquo;s headlights. Moraga Garcia appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries that would prevent her from walking or standing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Moraga Garcia the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - Injuries &amp;ndash; No&lt;br /&gt; - Medication &amp;ndash; Tylenol&lt;br /&gt; - Medical Conditions &amp;ndash; None&lt;br /&gt; - Glasses/Contacts &amp;ndash; Prescription contact lenses&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from Moraga Garcia&amp;rsquo;s eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Moraga Garcia&amp;rsquo;s pupils were equal in size, showed equal tracking, and no resting Nystagmus was observed. She was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Moraga Garcia if she understood the instructions and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 degrees &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I had to ask Moraga Garcia to follow the stimulus with her eyes on one occasion.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Moraga Garcia performing the test, I properly examined and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Moraga Garcia was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Moraga Garcia was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in the position until told to begin. Moraga Garcia was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Moraga Garcia was to keep her hands flat at her side, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Moraga Garcia was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Moraga Garcia was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Moraga Garcia was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her side, look at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Moraga Garcia if she understood the test and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; Footwear: Crocs.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructional Stage: &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -No clues observed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -Missed heel to toe contact on steps 3 and 9.&lt;br /&gt; -Stepped off line on step 2.&lt;br /&gt; -Took 15 steps.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Turn:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -Completed satisfactorily.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -Stopped walking on step 2.&lt;br /&gt; -Took 14 steps.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Moraga Garcia failed to count the steps out loud during the entire test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Moraga Garcia performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Moraga Garcia was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-one thousand, two-one thousand), and continue the test until told to stop. I asked Moraga Garcia if she understood the test and she stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;#39;&amp;#39; Moraga Garcia chose to raise his right foot. Footwear: Crocs.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructional Stage: &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -No clues observed.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Balance and Count Stage:&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -Swayed throughout the timeframe.&lt;br /&gt; -Raised her arms throughout the timeframe.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Seconds 11-20:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -Swayed throughout the timeframe.&lt;br /&gt; -Raised her arms throughout the timeframe.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Seconds 21-30:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -Swayed throughout the timeframe.&lt;br /&gt; -Raised her arms throughout the timeframe.&lt;br /&gt; -Placed raised foot down on 2 occasions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Moraga Garcia failed to count out loud during the entire test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Moraga Garcia was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -At fault driver of a single vehicle collision.&lt;br /&gt; -The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; -Eyes were glassy and bloodshot with a glazed look.&lt;br /&gt; -Struggled to maintain his balance.&lt;br /&gt; -Struggled to remember the sequence of events that led up to the collision.&lt;br /&gt; -Struggled to follow instructions.&lt;br /&gt; -Admitted &amp;ldquo;going out&amp;rdquo; without me asking her.&lt;br /&gt; -Body movements were slow and lethargic.&lt;br /&gt; -Speech was slow and lethargic.&lt;br /&gt; -Admission to consuming one shot and one beer that night in Layhill, MD.&lt;br /&gt; -Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus &amp;ndash; 6/6 clues observed&lt;br /&gt; -Walk and Turn &amp;ndash; 4/8 clues observed.&lt;br /&gt; -One Leg Stand &amp;ndash; 3/4 clues observed&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I arrested Moraga Garcia for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0242 hours and performed a search incident to arrest. Moraga Garcia was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Rockville Barrack for processing. After arriving at the barrack, I gave Moraga Garcia a copy of the DR-15 form in English to review while I played the entire form in English audio to her in the barrack. The English version audio can be found on mva.maryland.gov. Moraga Garcia signed the DR-15 at approximately 0311 hours, accepting to submit to the intoximeter test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Moraga Garcia beginning with her arrest. A preliminary search of Moraga Garcia was conducted on the scene and it revealed that she had nothing in her mouth. I observed Moraga Garcia from the time of the arrest until the time she submitted to the test and she did not put anything in her mouth. The test was conducted by Sgt. Tribue #5781 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Moraga Garcia&amp;rsquo;s breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of .13 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. Moraga Garcia was transported to the Montgomery County Detention Center to have Moraga Garcia&amp;rsquo;s active warrant served.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; CASE CLOSED BY ARREST.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2024 10:10:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 13:21:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kristopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5975</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lear</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quinn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7154</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tribue</LastName>
            <FirstName>Byron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5781</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lear</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quinn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7154</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lear</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quinn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7154</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535517</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16604</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/30/2023 02:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16604</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:29:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535517</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16624</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/30/2023 02:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16624</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:30:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535517</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16626</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/30/2023 02:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16626</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:30:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535517</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3096</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/30/2023 02:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3096</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:29:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535517</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15561</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/30/2023 02:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15561</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:28:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535517</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/30/2023 02:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:28:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535517</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/30/2023 02:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:27:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535517</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/30/2023 02:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:28:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535517</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/30/2023 02:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:26:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535517</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/30/2023 02:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:27:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535517</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/30/2023 02:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:26:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:31:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>396483</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Moraga Garcia</LastName>
               <FirstName>Darling</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Matilde</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/13/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 05:37:35</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D645</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Moraga Garcia</LastName>
               <FirstName>Darling</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Matilde</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/13/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D645</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 05:37:35</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>13102</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hathaway</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Silver Spring</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.05813429387493</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.070702011798126</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/06/2024 12:31:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:31:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/06/2024 12:31:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:31:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/06/2024 12:31:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:31:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/06/2024 12:31:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 12:31:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:50:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/31/2023 05:50:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>160318</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/31/2023 05:49:46</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3FA6P0CD6LR118472</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FUS</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8EY9899</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>