<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-046128</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/31/2023 01:38:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/31/2023 01:38:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/31/2023 00:48:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/31/2023 00:48:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>When responding to a 911 hang-up call, I identified a vehicle on the shoulder of the road flashing hazard lights. Upon approach, the driver appeared to be under the influence of alcohol. The driver was arrested for DUI. Search incident to arrest revealed a loaded handgun magazine in the driver's pocket. Probable cause search was conducted revealing an unregistered, unloaded, Smith and Wesson handgun in the vehicle.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 01:38:57</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5372</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 13:38:44</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>717502</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 01:39:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/08/2024 13:45:30</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>717502</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>39</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I95 Sb</StreetName>
         <City>Columbia</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.81791</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.16179</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/31/2023 01:38:53</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/31/2023 01:38:53</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>50</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 18:49:46</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 01:38:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:19</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Title: Ramirez, Hector Alexander DUI Investigation&lt;br /&gt; Case Number: 23-MSP-046128&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;This incident was captured on in-car rear facing camera, A-14. This incident was captured on my body-worn camera.&lt;br /&gt; Narrative:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; DUI #: 23-124&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Defendant: Hector Alexander Ramirez (DOB: 12/23/1989)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Preliminary Breath Test Results: 0.167&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Subsequent Offender: No&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Intoximeter Results: Refusal&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Property Hold Number : P-343645&lt;br /&gt; Certification and training:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; - Certified RADAR/LIDAR Operator&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; - Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; - Certified in the administration of Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through NHTSA.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On December 31, 2023, at approximately 0052 hours, I was on duty and dispatched to Southbound I-95 to check the area of MD Rt. 32 for a 911 hang-up call. Upon arrival to the area, I identified a white Chevrolet Express parked, in a canted fashion, on the left shoulder with its hazard lights flashing. I stopped out with the vehicle and identified the registration as TLV6178 (displayed through Virginia). Upon approaching the vehicle, I looked into the driver&amp;#39;s side window and observed the driver asleep at the wheel. I knocked on the window several times with increasing loudness to alert the driver, which was met with no response. The driver woke up after I opened the door, of which he was leaning on, and I made my first contact. The driver was later identified by his Guatemalan ID card as Ramirez, Hector Alexander (DOB: 12/23/1989).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Upon opening the door, I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle and Ramirez&amp;#39;s person. The keys were in the ignition and the vehicle was still running while in park. I asked Ramirez if he was okay and what was going on. Ramirez did not give me a direct answer at the time, and appeared to be confused. I asked Ramirez if he spoke English. Ramirez told me that he did not. Ramirez later told me that he understood some English; however, he had issues writing and speaking it. I again asked Ramirez what he was doing on the side of the road, and asked that he turn off the vehicle. Ramirez complied and turned off the vehicle using slow and labored movements Ramirez proceeded to give me the keys to the vehicle. While Ramirez gave me an explanation as to what he was doing on the side of the road, I noticed his eyes were visibly bloodshot and glassy. I was also able to identify several open and empty containers of alcohol in the vehicle. There was an empty bottle of Corona beer on the floorboard under the seat, as well as a can of Michelob Ultra beer in the center console cup-holder. The Michelob Ultra was later determined to be empty as well. I asked Ramirez about the empty containers of alcohol in the vehicle, to which Ramirez claimed he was not drinking them now. Ramirez later explains that he had been drinking them yesterday. I asked Ramirez for his license, to which Ramirez handed me his Guatemalan identification card. I asked Ramirez if he had a driver&amp;#39;s license, to which Ramirez told me he did not have one.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I again asked Ramirez if he had anything to drink, to which Ramirez told me &amp;ldquo;No, no, nothing.&amp;quot; I asked Ramirez when he had drank last, to which Ramirez explained that it was around 2000 hours on 12/30/2023. Ramirez explained that he was coming from New York. While waiting for the Spanish-speaking officer from Howard County police, Ramirez explained that he was parked for approximately ten minutes, and had parked because he did not want to cause an accident. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; S/Tpr. Morgan #6068, who was also on scene at the time, observed a near empty box of Corona beer on the floorboard of the vehicle, as well as several more empty bottles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Upon arrival of the Spanish-speaking officer, Officer Moon #5511, I requested Ramirez to exit the vehicle, to which Ramirez complied. Officer Moon proceeded to translate for me to Ramirez for the entirety of roadside portion. In front of his van, I again asked Ramirez basic questions. I asked Ramirez when he had last been drinking, his answer changed to 2100 or 2200 hours on 12/30/2023. I again asked if Ramirez was going home, to which he responded &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot; Ramirez explained he was parked for 10 minutes because he didn&amp;#39;t feel he could make it to the rest area. While speaking to Ramirez outside of the vehicle, the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage continued to emanate from his breath. I asked Ramirez if he would be willing to perform field sobriety tests, to which Ramirez complied.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The evaluation was performed roadside on the shoulder of S/B I-95. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of the patrol vehicle headlights, and various flashlights. The front two patrol vehicles forward flashing lights were deactivated; however, the third patrol vehicle in the back still had the forward lights flashing. The test was performed in front of the van and the lights did not have any bearing on the test itself, as the flashing lights were not visible from where the test was performed. I asked Ramirez if he had any medical conditions I needed to know about, as well as anything that would prevent him from balancing/walking in a straight line. Ramirez explained he did not have any injuries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Test #1 Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus: 2 out of 6 clues observed.&lt;br /&gt; The test was properly explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual.&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Ramirez displayed a lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; Notes:&lt;br /&gt; * The test was not able to be completed because Ramirez was unable to focus on the tip of the pen and would continuously look past the pen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Ramirez reiterated several times prior to the tests that there was nothing wrong with his eyes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;* During the HGN test, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Ramirez&amp;#39;s breath.&lt;br /&gt; * Ramirez moves his head several times to follow the tip of the pen.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Test #2 Walk and Turn: 4 out of 8 clues observed.&lt;br /&gt; The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual.&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Ramirez loses his balance during the instructional phase.&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Ramirez takes 11 steps on the first nine steps.&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Ramirez does not complete the turn satisfactorily.&lt;br /&gt; 4.) Ramirez stops during the test.&lt;br /&gt; * Ramirez does not count out loud any of the steps taken.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Test #3 One Leg Stand: 0 out of 4 clues observed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Ramirez starts the test during the instructional phase.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Preliminary Breath Test&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Preliminary breath results were 0.167.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Ramirez did not give a strong breath sample, so the results were likely lower than the actual alcohol breath concentration.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Based on the following totality of the circumstances, I had reason to believe Ramirez was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the drivers breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; * Several empty bottles of beer in the driver&amp;#39;s seat floorboard and cup-holder of the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; * 2/6 Clues on HGN, 4/8 Clues on Walk and Turn, and 0 clues on the OLS.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;* Sleeping on the shoulder of I-95 with delayed reaction time to waking up.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;* Slow and labored movements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Due to my observations, I concluded Ramirez was driving under the influence of alcohol. At 0138 hours, I placed Ramirez under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. A preliminary search of Ramirez was conducted on scene. The search revealed a silver pistol magazine with five loaded 9mm Luger rounds located in the front pocket of Ramirez&amp;#39;s sweatshirt. When asked about the magazine, Ramirez claims that he found it while working. Ramirez further states that he does not have a firearm in the vehicle. After elaborating that I would be searching his vehicle, Ramirez informs us that there is a pistol in a green bag in the vehicle. The search was positive, and the pistol was located in a blue Walmart bag behind the driver&amp;#39;s seat in a holster. The firearm was unloaded at the time of finding it, and was immediately secured in the trunk of my police vehicle. The handgun was identified as a black Smith and Wesson MP9 Shield, 9mm pistol (S/N: HZV2430). Ramirez explained that the firearm was not registered to him. Further investigation revealed the firearm was not registered to anybody. Ramirez was transported to the Maryland State Police Waterloo Barrack for processing.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Ramirez was played his DR-15 Advice of Rights in Spanish via the Maryland MVA audio file in the barrack. After hearing the form read in its entirety, I asked Ramirez if he wished to submit to take the intoximeter test to measure his breath alcohol concentration. Ramirez explained that he spoke a different dialect of Spanish, so some of the words he did not understand. The form was given to Ramirez to read along and was given ample time to read the form after the audio version was played. I explained that I needed an answer or else it would be a refusal. Ramirez would not give me a straight answer and was therefore a marked a refusal. At 0246 hours, Ramirez refused to submit to take an intoximeter test to measure his breath alcohol concentration.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Ramirez was provided all pertinent paperwork and transported to the Howard County Department of Corrections. Ramirez was charged with driving under the influence of alcohol, as well as criminally under CR &amp;ndash; 4-203 for the handgun violation. At 0515 hours, Ramirez was released to the custody of the Howard County Department of Corrections.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The firearm, ammunition, as well as the magazine were processed and placed into the Waterloo temporary storage locker. The Maryland State Police gun unit was contacted and made aware of the situation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Howard County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 00:23:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2024 14:01:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Morgan</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6068</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sheets</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7130</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Krysiak</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1955</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shank</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7587</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535605</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0175</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/31/2023 00:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0175</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 23:23:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/31/2023 23:44:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535605</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/31/2023 00:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 23:25:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/31/2023 23:44:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535605</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/31/2023 00:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 23:25:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/31/2023 23:44:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535605</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/31/2023 00:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 23:25:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/31/2023 23:44:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 23:39:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2024 13:45:29</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>396524</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ramirez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Hector</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alexander</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/23/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 23:38:36</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R562</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H236</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ramirez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Hector</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Alexander</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/23/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R562</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H236</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 23:38:36</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1310</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>fanfield</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Richmond</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>23223</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.423419</Longitude>
               <Latitude>37.548159</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>804</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>806</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1335</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 00:03:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 00:03:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 00:03:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 00:03:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 00:03:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 00:03:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 00:03:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 00:03:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 00:03:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 00:03:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/31/2023 23:23:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/31/2023 23:23:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>160347</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 00:22:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 00:22:28</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1gcfg15xx51115661</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2005</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>EXP</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>TLV6178</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>12</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 00:14:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 00:18:46</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>610</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <SerialNumber>HZV2430</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>258000</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>BLK</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>Smith and Wesson</Make>
         <Model>MP 9 Shield</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
         <BarrelLength>3.1</BarrelLength>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 00:16:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 00:16:05</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Five 9mm luger rounds</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>424</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>258001</Property_ID>
         <Make>Luger</Make>
         <Model>9mm</Model>
         <Quantity>5</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7587</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 00:18:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7587</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 00:18:16</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One silver 7 round magazine.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>611</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>258002</Property_ID>
         <SecondaryColor>SIL</SecondaryColor>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>