<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009740</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/17/2023 23:25:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/17/2023 23:25:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/17/2023 22:56:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/17/2023 22:56:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/ Marijuana less than/ Traffic Collision</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 23:25:50</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4437</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 12:23:50</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>688362</AddressId>
      <City>MDC175</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP7510</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 14:48:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 14:48:32</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>688362</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Capital Beltway</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.890823</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.997803</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/17/2023 23:25:47</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/17/2023 23:25:47</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/06/2023 21:20:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 23:25:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p&gt;Patrol Vehicle Information- Q11 (Marked) is equipped with a mobile recording device. Event captured on Body Camera.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Defendant: Igmar Joshue Hernandez (DOB 02/13/2003, H/M)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Date Of Arrest: 03/17/2023&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Time Of Arrest: 2344 hours&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Witness: Aidan Jamal Gooding (DOB 03/06/2003, B/M)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Officer&amp;rsquo;s Training/Experience&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;*Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Eastern Shore Criminal Justice Academy and the Maryland State Police Academy.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;*Trained and certified to operate Radar through the Maryland State Police.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;*Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE).&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;On March 17, 2023, at approximately 2256 hours, I Trooper Nikodemski #7510 responded to the area of the O/L 495 at Riggs Road for a multi vehicle collision. Upon arrival, I observed three vehicles on location including the following a 2014, Blue and White Suzuki motorcycle (V3) with heavy front end damage, 2021 Dark Blue Toyota Highlander (V2) with damage to its passenger side front fender, as well as a 2022 Silver Audi A3 displaying Maryland registration EZ2650 with damage to its drivers side rear. I observed Tfc. Emerick to be on scene as well. I initially made contact with Aidan Jamal Gooding&amp;nbsp; who was the driver of vehicle 2. Gooding stated that while traveling in lane 1 in this same he observed the Silver Audi (vehicle 1) abruptly change lanes from lane 3 to his lane causing him to swerve to the shoulder to attempt to avoid the collision. Gooding stated that he was unable to avoid the collision and his vehicle struck the rear of the Silver Audi. Gooding stated that the motorcycle which was traveling behind his location could not stop in time and struck the rear of the Silver Audi. As I was speaking with Gooding, I observed the driver and sole occupant later identified by his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license as Igmar Joshue Hernandez of the Silver Audi to be walking near the vehicles and shoulder of the roadway. I observed Hernandez to be stumbling and swaying heavily as he walked. At one point I observed Hernandez to walk toward my location and stumble and fall into me, causing me to have to break his fall by grabbing him with my left hand. At this point Hernandez was told to sit on the front of his vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;It should be noted that the operator of the motorcycle had been transported by EMS prior to my arrival.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;I made contact with Hernandez who standing near the rear of his vehicle. I observed a strong odor of an acholic beverage to be emanating from his breath and person. I asked Hernandez if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages prior to driving. Hernandez stated that he had &amp;quot;one shot of Hennessy 45 minutes ago&amp;quot; prior to driving. I requested Hernandez preform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST&amp;#39;s).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Hernandez was placed in front of his vehicle to preform SFST&amp;#39;s.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A routine check of Hernandez&amp;#39;s license and wanted status revealed that he possessed a valid driver&amp;#39;s license and was not wanted.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;The evaluation was performed on the shoulder of the roadway. The shoulder where the following tests were conducted was level, free and clear of any debris. It was rainy weather during my tests and prior to the collision. Hernandez was asked pre-evaluation screening questions and stated he did have any conditions that would prevent him from preforming my tests. Hernandez stated he did wear glasses but did not need them for the test. Hernandez&amp;#39;s eyes were red, watery, glassy and droopy.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN) (6/6 clues observed)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Hernandez&amp;#39;s eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. His pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. Hernandez was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated yes. At this time I could still observe a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage still emanating from his breath and person.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;I asked Hernandez if he was able to see the tip of my pen to which he stated yes.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;4.)&amp;nbsp; Vertical Nystagmus - Not present&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;WALK AND TURN (5/8 clues observed)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Prior to Hernandez performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Hernandez was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. He was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;1.) Balance- Hernandez swayed and struggled to keep his foot on the line.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;2.) Starts too soon- Hernandez remained as demonstrated.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;3.) Stops walking- Completed as demonstrated.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;4.) Misses to toe- Hernandez missed heal to toe on every step he took.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;5.) Steps off-line- Hernandez stepped off line on every step he took.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;6.) Raises arms- Hernandez raised his arm on every step he took.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;7.) Actual # steps- Hernandez only took 4 steps before being told to stop the test.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;8.) Improper turn -Not applicable&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Hernandez attempted to complete the walk and turn test but had to stop on his first 4 steps due to him repeatedly loosing his balance and nearly falling causing me to have to grab him on his second step to avoid him falling and injuring himself.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;ONE LEG STAND (4/4 clues observed)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Prior to Hernandez performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. He was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Hernandez was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated yes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Hernandez took 4 large steps while counting out loud and did not complete the test at all how I had demonstrated. I observed Hernandez to still be struggling to maintain his balance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;ARREST&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Based on the following, I had reason to believe Hernandez was driving a motor vehicle under the influence:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Involved in a motor vehicle collision,&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Admission to drinking prior to driving.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;-Multiple Clues during Field Sobriety Testing.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;-Hernandez had a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Poor balance and coordination.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Watery, blood shot eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; -Had to be braced several times to avoid falling.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Hernandez was offered a Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) and refused.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Due to the number of observations, I concluded Hernandez was driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 2344 hours, I placed Hernandez under arrest for driving while impaired. A search incident to arrest of Hernandez revealed a small clear plastic baggie containing marijuana within Hernandez&amp;#39;s left front pants pocket.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;I have received a course of instruction in the police academy dealing specifically with the identification and detection of controlled dangerous substances (CDS). Further, I have received subsequent advanced training dealing specifically with interdiction and detection techniques of CDS and related laws. I knew the Marijuana to be Marijuana based on my training knowledge and experience as well as sight, texture and smell&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The CDS was taken to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, photographed and processed in accordance with MSP policy. I packaged the CDS and related items and placed them into evidence. The Marijuana was placed within a sealed K-Pack and submitted with a MSP Form-67. The Marijuana was weighed and found to have a weight of 7.9 grams with packaging which was confirmed by Sgt. Parsons #5657.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The CDS was processed according to MSP policy, and stored at the College Park Barrack. The total weight of the CDS including packaging was 7.9 grams.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Hernandez was placed in my patrol vehicle and read aloud by audio clip the DR-15 Advice of Rights at approximately 2355 hours from the Motor Vehicle&amp;nbsp;Administration website. Hernandez upon being read the Advice of Rights refused to take the test at approximately 0007 hours on 03/18/2023.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;I transported Hernandez to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, in College&amp;nbsp;Park, Maryland where he was released to a sober driver.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;It should be noted that Hernandez&amp;#39;s vehicle was towed from the scene by H and H towing.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;INTOXIMETER RESULT: REFUSED&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;A DR-15A was completed, and a temporary license was issued. Hernandez was issued copies of MVA paperwork to include the DR-15, DR-15A.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Hernandez was issued traffic citations related to DUI and civil citation (0Z46647552) for the Marijuana.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A ACRS report was completed for this vehicle collision and attached with this report.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;All events occurred in Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Case Status-CLOSED by adult arrest.&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7510</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 09:27:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7510</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 20:42:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Emerick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6888</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Houck</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mitchell</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7577</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Parsons</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5657</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>NIKODEMSKI</LastName>
            <FirstName>JONATHAN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7510</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499140</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>CIVIL 5-601</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/17/2023 22:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>CIVIL 5-601</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7510</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/04/2023 12:14:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7510</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/04/2023 12:14:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>20</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7510</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 15:13:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:35</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372443</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hernandez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Igmar</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Joshue</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/19/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 15:12:53</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I256</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hernandez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Igmar</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Joshue</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/19/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I256</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 15:12:53</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7510</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/04/2023 12:16:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7510</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/04/2023 12:16:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>20</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7510</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 11:30:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:21</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373288</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Gooding</LastName>
               <FirstName>Aidan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jamal</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/06/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 11:30:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G352</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A350</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Gooding</LastName>
               <FirstName>Aidan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jamal</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/06/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G352</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A350</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 11:30:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>444</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1218</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7510</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 11:30:39</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7510</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 15:00:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7510</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 15:00:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151233</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7510</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 15:24:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7510</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 15:24:46</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WAUB4CF54NA018078</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>AUDI</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>S5</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5EZ2650</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7510</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 15:27:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7510</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/04/2023 12:17:16</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Marijuana within loose bag</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>245975</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>7.9</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>