<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-044480</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/16/2023 16:05:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/16/2023 16:05:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/16/2023 15:52:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/16/2023 15:52:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Dui</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/16/2023 16:05:09</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/04/2024 07:48:34</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>ARUNDEL,GLEN BURNIE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>716206</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/16/2023 16:05:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 00:41:31</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>716206</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Arundel</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GLN</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.5993891666667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.1511438333333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/16/2023 16:05:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/16/2023 16:05:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 18:48:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/16/2023 16:05:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:19</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;main&gt; &lt;form action="https://rms.public-safety-cloud.com/prod/IncidentNarratives.s?dispatchto=viewNarrative" id="narrative" method="POST" onsubmit="return false"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;DUI #: P-23-187&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; CASE #:23-MSP-044480&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;DEFENDANT: Jake Reid Blanch Maryland Soundex MD10272806468 (W/M DOB 09-21-2005)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *THIS INCIDENT WAS RECORDED ON MY IN-CAR AND BODY WORN CAMERA SYSTEMS*&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;NARRATIVE:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On 12-16-2023 at approximately 1552 hours I, Master Trooper Bartch #5301 of the Maryland State Police was in unmarked MSP unit P-16 and stationary southbound Route 10 @ Route 648 in Anne Arundel County, Maryland. I was inside my patrol vehicle facing northbound, while monitoring the flow of traffic. I observed a vehicle at what appeared to be traveling above the posted speed limit in lane 1. I activated the laser Pro 3 unit PL34656 and received a speed of 77 MPH in a posted 55 MPH zone. While keeping sight of the vehicle I than pursued and positioned my patrol vehicle directly behind the vehicle and activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop. The vehicle pulled to the right shoulder of southbound Route 10 South of Route 648, Anne Arundel County, Maryland. The vehicle was identified&amp;nbsp;as a gray Toyota 4Runner bearing Maryland registration 2FP0571. I exited my patrol vehicle and made contact with the driver, identified myself, advised the traffic stop was being recorded and reason for the traffic stop. The driver was identified by his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license as Jake Reid Blanch (Soundex MD10272806468 W/M DOB 09-21-2005). While speaking to Blanch I observed his eyes to be blood shot and I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. I asked Blanch to exit the vehicle and stand in front of my patrol unit, due to the fact that I detected an odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. I asked Blanch when was his last alcoholic beverage, and he stated &amp;quot;last night&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Based on my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, I suspected Blanch was impaired by alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. Blanch agreed to submit to standardized field sobriety testing. The tests were performed on the right shoulder of southbound Route 10 South of Route 648, Anne Arundel County, Maryland. Test were performed in an area that was level, free of debris and weather was clear.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Instructions: Blanch was told to stand with his feet together and his arms down at his side. A stimulus (ink pen) was held approximately twelve to fifteen inches from Blanch&amp;#39;s face, and he was asked to follow the stimulus with his eyes only and to not move his head. Blanch did confirm he could see the stimulus (ink pen). Prior to beginning the test, I asked Blanch if he understood the instructions, and he answered yes. I initially checked for equal pupil size, resting nystagmus, and equal tracking. I next checked for lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees. Lastly, I checked for vertical gaze nystagmus. Both eyes were checked twice for each clue. 6/6. VGN present. Both pupils were equal in size and equally tracking the stimulus. Resting nystagmus was not present. Nystagmus was observed in each eye during all three observations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;WALK AND TURN&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Instructions: Blanch was told to stand with his right foot in front of his left foot in a heel to toe manner. He was told to stay in that position and keep his arms at his side until being told to begin the test. I asked Blanch if he understood, and he answered yes. I began explaining and demonstrating the test. Blanch was instructed to take nine heel to toe steps on a straight line. On the ninth step, he was instructed to leave his lead foot planted and take a series of small steps to turn 180 degrees. Blanch was told to then take an additional nine heel to toe steps back. He was told to gaze down at his feet, count the steps out loud, keep his hands at his side, touch heel to toe on every step, and to not stop walking until the test is complete. I asked Blanch if he understood the instructions before beginning, and he answered yes. Blanch was told multiple times to stay in the instructional phase. Blanch began to start the test while I was still giving instructions. On the first series of nine steps, Blanch did not complete the turn as instructed. Blanch complete a pivot turn. On the second series of nine steps Blanch missed heel to toe and stepped off-line on step 2.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;ONE LEG STAND&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Instructions: Blanch was instructed to stand with his feet together and his hands at his side while I explained the instructions and demonstrated the test. Blanch was told to raise either foot of his choice approximately six inches off the ground while keeping it parallel to the ground. Blanch was told to begin to count, one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-three&amp;hellip;etc. Blanch was instructed to continue counting until I told him to stop. He was told to gaze down at his feet, to count out loud, to keep his arms at his side, and to not put his foot down. I then asked if Blanch understood the instructions, and he answered yes. Blanch chose to use his right foot. Blanch count one thousand fourteen twice and then put his foot down. I then stopped the test at one thousand eighteen.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ARREST&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Blanch was afforded a PBT and agreed to submit. Blanch results were .15. Based on my observations and my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, Blanch was placed under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol at approximately 1602 time hours. While still on scene inside my patrol vehicle, Blanch was played the audio version of the DR-15 Advice of Rights form in its entirely and Blanch was also given a copy to follow along. Blanch stated he understood the form and agreed to submit to the intoximeter test at 1622 hours. Blanch was then transported to the Annapolis Barracks. At 1703 hours, Maryland State Police Cpl.Engleman a certified intoximeter operator, administered the test. The result of the test were .13 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. Blanch was then&amp;nbsp;provided with all appropriate paperwork and citations. Blanch&amp;#39;s license was confiscated, and he was issued a DR-15A form.&amp;nbsp; Blanch was released to his mother at 1755 hours.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Anne Arundel County&lt;/form&gt; &lt;/main&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/22/2023 00:57:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 01:55:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wiest</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4939</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bartch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5301</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533957</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 15:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/22/2023 00:42:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 00:42:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/22/2023 00:51:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 00:51:01</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>395849</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Blanch</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jake</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Reid</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/21/2005 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/22/2023 00:49:34</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Blanch</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jake</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Reid</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/21/2005 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/22/2023 00:49:34</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>201</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Falcon</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Pasadena</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21122</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5905</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.460308</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.09787</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>784</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1552</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/22/2023 00:51:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 00:51:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/22/2023 00:51:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 00:51:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/22/2023 00:51:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 00:51:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5301</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/22/2023 00:42:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5301</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 00:42:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>