<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011289</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/29/2023 20:11:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/29/2023 20:11:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/29/2023 18:48:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/29/2023 18:48:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Accident/DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 20:11:51</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 12:32:04</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>689022</AddressId>
      <City>MDC405</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 20:11:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/29/2023 23:17:43</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>689022</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2576</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Hoopers Island</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Fishing Creek</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21634</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.229396</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.326684</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/29/2023 20:11:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/29/2023 20:11:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/31/2023 21:36:37</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 20:11:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5204</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/21/2023 07:48:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;main&gt; &lt;form action="https://rms.public-safety-cloud.com/prod/IncidentNarratives.s?dispatchto=viewNarrative" id="narrative" method="POST" onsubmit="return false"&gt;ACRS completed reference same case number.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Alcohol Influence Report Patrol Vehicle Information &amp;ndash; I-26 (Marked) is not equipped with a mobile recording device, however, I am equipped with a BWC (Body Worn Camera), which was operational.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Defendant: Davis, Katherine Savanna&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 05/10/2003 &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 03/29/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 2007&lt;br /&gt; Maryland SDX: D-120-461-758-356&lt;br /&gt; License Status &amp;ndash; Valid&lt;br /&gt; License Restrictions &amp;ndash; Under 21 Alcohol&lt;br /&gt; Registration Violations &amp;ndash; None&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Officer&amp;rsquo;s Training/Experience&lt;br /&gt; * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Anne Arundel County Police Department, Maryland State Police Department, and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Certified Drug Recognition Expert since 2017&lt;br /&gt; * Graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute 2019&lt;br /&gt; *2023 Frederick Police Department &amp;ldquo;Green Lab&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Repeat Offender* - No&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Vehicle not observed in motion.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 03/29/2023, at approximately 1848 hours, I, Trooper Koehler #7524, responded to 2576 Hoopers Island Road, Fishing Creek, Dorchester County Maryland for a report of a single vehicle accident. The caller indicated to our dispatch that they already contacted a tow. Upon my arrival, I located a black Mazda CX-5 displaying Maryland registration 9FE7093. The Mazda was stuck in a ditch with damage to it&amp;#39;s passenger side and driver side. I spoke with the driver of the vehicle, who was later positively identified via her Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license as Katherine Savanna Davis. As I arrived on scene, Davis was curled up in a ball, seated on her rear end, next to the driver side of the vehicle. Davis had a lack of inhibitions on first contact as she was giggling while I first began speaking with her. Davis was informed that I was a Maryland State Trooper and that everything was being recorded with audio and video. Davis explained that she had just had dinner with her friend at Old Satly&amp;#39;s, located at 2560 Hoopers Island Road. Davis explained that she left and began driving north on Hoopers Island Road when some sun had glared in her eyes. Davis explained that she swerved to her right, striking a pole and then back across the roadway to the left, into the ditch. Davis explained that she did not drink any alcohol and she was not texting while driving. Davis explained that the glare got in her eyes around the bend in the road. I questioned her about that, stating that the sun wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be in her eyes, if she were traveling east, with the sun setting behind her. Davis had no explanation, stating she did not know. Davis stated she thought she might have been going 30 or 40 mph.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Davis&amp;#39; friend, Hannah Elizabeth Moore, who was on scene as well, advised that she had just exited Old Salty&amp;#39;s and witnessed the accident. Moore confirmed that they were having dinner prior to the accident. Moore explained that she observed Davis&amp;rsquo; vehicle veer to the right into the telephone pole, and then &amp;ldquo;slingshot&amp;rdquo;. When asked to explain, Moore, stated that it went back to the left and straight into the ditch. Moore stated that they had left dinner around 1811 hours.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I spoke with the owners of the property where the vehicle was stuck in a ditch. They explained that no damage was done on their property.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I went back to Davis and advised her that there was no damage to their property. While speaking with Davis, I could see that her eyes were bloodshot and she had a faint odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath. Davis also appeared to be very nervous, now smoking a cigarette, which is a common masking agent used to cover up the odor of alcohol.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Davis was asked and agreed to conduct standardized field sobriety tests. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed in front of another vehicle in the middle of the roadway. The area where testing took place was level and free of any debris. Prior to any tests being completed, my forward facing flashing lights were deactivated. Davis was wearing blue jeans, gray shoes, a t-shirt with a pink Columbia zipper jacket. Davis stated that she was not sick or injured. Davis stated that she had only taken Tylenol that day and no other medications. Davis stated she was not diabetic or epileptic. Davis was wearing glasses and needed them to see. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (4/6 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Davis&amp;#39;s eyes. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Davis&amp;#39; pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting Nystagmus. Davis indicated that she understood the directions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash; Not Present&lt;br /&gt; Vertical Nystagmus &amp;ndash; Not Present&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;WALK AND TURN (5/8 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to Davis performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Davis was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. She was instructed to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. She was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. She was instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, she was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Davis was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. She was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her sides, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. Davis indicated that she understood the instructions. An imaginary line was utilized for this test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Instructional Stage: - Lost balance and failed to maintain a heel to toe stance, as instructed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st Nine): - Misssed heel to toe on step 5, 6, 7, 8 and 9&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;-Raised arms for balance for all 9 steps&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-Stepped off line on step one&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; - Stopped after nine steps 9 steps asking if she was to turn&lt;br /&gt; Turn : &amp;nbsp;Satisfactory&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (2nd Nine): - Stepped off line on step 2, 7&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;-Raised arms for balance for all 9 steps&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; -Missed heel to toe on steps 4, 5, 6,&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to Davis performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Davis was asked and did not have any questions. Davis shook her head up and down, after the instructions, indicating that she understood.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage: Remained as demonstrated&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage: &amp;nbsp; -swayed while balancing&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;-used arms for balance&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After conducting this test, Davis was asked again, about her consumption of alcohol. Davis now admitted to consuming an orange crush around 2pm, earlier that day.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; PBT was not available to offer. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ARREST&lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Davis was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol&lt;br /&gt; -4/6 HGN&lt;br /&gt; -5/8 WAT&lt;br /&gt; -2/4 OLS&lt;br /&gt; -Bloodshot eyes&lt;br /&gt; -Poor balance and coordination during SFST&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;br /&gt; -Impaired memory&lt;br /&gt; -Lack of inhibitions&lt;br /&gt; -Faint odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from breath&lt;br /&gt; -Admitted to consuming an alcoholic beverage prior to driving&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to the number of observations, I concluded Davis was driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. I placed Davis under arrest at 2007 hours. Davis was placed in handcuffs and seated in the front seat of my patrol vehicle. Davis was then read aloud the DR-15 Advice of Rights form using the MVA audio file in my patrol vehicle. Davis was provided a copy of the same form to read along. After hearing her rights, Davis would agree to complete a test for alcohol of her breath at 2049 hours. Cambridge Police Department&amp;#39;s Sgt. Howard #317 conducted the breath test at 2114 hours, which revealed Davis&amp;#39; breath contained an alcohol concentration of .04 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. A subsequent DR-15A form was not applicable and therefore was not completed. Davis&amp;#39; license status at the time of this incident was valid with an alcohol restriction, due to her age. Davis&amp;#39; driver&amp;#39;s license was provided back to her and she was provided with her copies of the MVA related forms.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Davis was transported the Cambridge Police Department where a sober driver responded and took control of Davis with no further incident.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All event&amp;#39;s occurred in Dorchester County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;INTOXIMETER RESULT: .04&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/form&gt; &lt;/main&gt;  &lt;footer&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/footer&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 23:57:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 16:13:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bringman</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5204</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Koehler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7524</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500692</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/29/2023 18:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 23:18:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/29/2023 23:18:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>19</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 23:25:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372955</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Davis</LastName>
               <FirstName>Katherine</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Savanna</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/10/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/29/2023 23:23:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K365</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Davis</LastName>
               <FirstName>Katherine</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Savanna</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/10/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D120</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K365</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/29/2023 23:23:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>404</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Muir</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Cambridge</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21613</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>205</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2801</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 23:25:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 23:25:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>23</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 00:08:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:19</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372956</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Moore</LastName>
               <FirstName>Hannah</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elizabeth</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/23/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/30/2023 00:08:26</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Moore</LastName>
               <FirstName>Hannah</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elizabeth</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/23/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/30/2023 00:08:26</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2360</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hoopers Island</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Fishing Creek</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21634</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>477</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5520</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 00:08:36</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 23:18:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/29/2023 23:18:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151437</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 23:31:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/29/2023 23:31:05</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JM3KFBBM4K0605233</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MAZD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CX5</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9FE7093</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/06/2023 05:06:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/06/2023 05:06:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/21/2023 07:48:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 05:06:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/21/2023 07:48:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 4/05/2023 at approximately 2300 hours, I, Trooper Koehler #7524, conducted a follow up regarding this case. I issued another related citation for Davis to include : driving motor vehicle with alcohol in blood in violation of restriction. I made contact with Davis via phone call and advised her of the additional charge. Davis indicated that she would stop by the Maryland State Police Barrack and pick up the additional citation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; An additional MVA form, DR 103 was completed as well. A copy of the form was uploaded into this report&amp;#39;s attachments section. The MVA copy of the form was dropped off in the blue envelope, prior to the end of my tour of duty.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case Status : Closed.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 05:07:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 05:15:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bringman</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5204</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Koehler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7524</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>