<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-007016</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/24/2023 00:04:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/24/2023 00:04:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/23/2023 23:41:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 00:04:23</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/04/2023 16:59:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>LIBERTY RD/ ROLLING RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>685293</AddressId>
      <City>MDC519</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 00:04:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:16:39</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>685293</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Liberty</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Windsor Mill</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.76562</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.35637</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>8212-8235 LIBERTY RD / 3600-3601 ROLLING RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/24/2023 00:04:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/24/2023 00:04:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/07/2023 04:24:59</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 00:04:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:13</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>R-24 equipped with in-car camera and body-worn camera.&lt;br /&gt; Case# 23-MSP-007016&lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Montia Lukisha Dunaway&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 04/30/1986&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 02/23/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 2357hours&lt;br /&gt; DUI #: 23-113&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Certificates and Training&lt;br /&gt; *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Certified Emergency Medical Technician by the Maryland Institute of Emergency Medical Services Systems&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Certified RADAR/LIDAR operator by the Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Certified License Plate Reader (LPR) operator by the Maryland State Police&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Vehicle In Motion (Phase 1)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On February 23rd, 2023 at approximately 2341 hours I, Trooper Sigman #7376 and TPR Pezold #7512, currently assigned to the Golden Ring Barrack, were on routine patrol of Liberty Road in the area of Rolling Road. TPR Pezold advised on the radio that he had a traffic stop and requested an additional unit to respond.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Personal Contact (Phase 2)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then arrived with TPR Pezold. I observed that he had stopped a White Acura bearing Maryland registration of 5EG8823 in lane 2 of W/B Liberty Road just west of Rolling Road. TPR Pezold advised me that he observed the Acura driving at night without any lights on, fail to maintain a single lane of travel and drift over the lines separating the lanes, paced the vehicle at 60mph in a posted 35 mph zone, and fail to stop at a red circular signal at W/B Liberty Road and N Rolling Road. He stated that he observed the Acura &amp;ldquo;run&amp;rdquo; the red circular signal at a high rate of speed (See TPR Pezold supplement for additional information). TPR Pezold had already identified the driver of the white Acura as Montia Lukisha Dunaway (04/30/1986) by her Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license. I observed that Dunaway had an ignition interlock restriction on her license.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then made a Passenger side approach of the white Acura bearing Maryland registration of 5EG8823. Upon arrived at the front passenger window I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I then identified myself and requested Dunaway&amp;rsquo;s insurance information. While speaking with Dunaway I observed that she had slurred speech upon conversation, bloodshot glassy eyes, and slow uncoordinated movements while searching for her insurance information. Dunaway was unable to locate any insurance information. I then asked Dunaway where she had been driving from this evening. Dunaway stated that she was driving home from a &amp;ldquo;gathering&amp;rdquo; but was unable to remember where the &amp;ldquo;gathering&amp;rdquo; took place.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked Dunaway if she had an ignition interlock device in her vehicle. Dunaway stated that it was in her &amp;ldquo;other car.&amp;rdquo; I observed that there was no ignition interlock device inside of her Acura. I then requested Dunaway to exit her vehicle and walk to the sidewalk on the right side of the roadway next to her vehicle. Upon stepping out of her vehicle I observed that Dunaway displayed gait ataxia. While standing next to Dunaway I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. I again asked Dunaway where she was coming from. Dunaway was still unable to remember where she had been driving from and stated &amp;ldquo;Baltimore County, that&amp;#39;s what I wanna say.&amp;rdquo; I then asked Dunaway where she lived. Dunaway stated that she lived in &amp;ldquo;Baltimore County&amp;rdquo; but could not elaborate on what area she lived in. I then asked Dunaway how many alcoholic beverages she had consumed. Dunaway denied any alcoholic beverages and stated &amp;ldquo;I sprayed perfume.&amp;rdquo; I then asked Dunaway if she would consent to standardized field sobriety testing. Dunaway agreed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on the sidewalk adjacent to Dunaway&amp;rsquo;s vehicle. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 60 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlights, and overhead lights, and my vehicles takedown lights. My vehicles front facing emergency lights were deactivated for the duration of the field sobriety tests. Dunaway appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries and or defects.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Dunaway the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Injuries- none&lt;br /&gt; Medical conditions- none&lt;br /&gt; Medications- none&lt;br /&gt; Glasses or contacts- none&lt;br /&gt; Alcoholic beverages- denies any alcoholic beverage consumption&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Controlled dangerous substance- none&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The test was properly explained. I then began the test. I did not observe any resting nystagmus. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lack of Smooth Pursuit - present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; *Vertical Gaze Nystagmus - present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; During the test Dunaway had difficulty following directions and had to be reminded multiple times not to move her head while following the stimulus. Dunaway also swayed from side to side during the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walk and Turn (7/8 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to Dunaway performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. I asked Dunaway if she had any questions. Dunaway stated that she understood the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; Steps out of the starting position. After stepping out of the starting position Dunaway had difficulty getting back into the starting position and I had to re-explain the starting position.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Steps off line&lt;br /&gt; Misses heel to toe&lt;br /&gt; Takes 12 steps&lt;br /&gt; Stops walking and looks at me and says &amp;ldquo;turn?&amp;rdquo; as she had forgotten how to complete the test. I advised Dunaway to complete the test as I had demonstrated&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Steps off line&lt;br /&gt; Misses heel to toe&lt;br /&gt; Raises arms for balance&lt;br /&gt; Takes 10 steps (on the 10th step Dunaway began to walk off of the left side of the sidewalk forcing me to intervene to prevent her from falling)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Turn:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Incorrect, uses both feel to walk in a counterclockwise direction&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; One Leg Stand (3/4)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to Dunaway performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Dunaway advised that she understood the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; Sways from side to side&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10:&lt;br /&gt; Sways from side to side&lt;br /&gt; Raises arms for balance&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20:&lt;br /&gt; Sways from side to side&lt;br /&gt; Raises arms for balance&lt;br /&gt; Puts foot down&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30:&lt;br /&gt; Sways from side to side&lt;br /&gt; Puts foot down&lt;br /&gt; Raises arms for balance&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then offered my PBT to Dunaway . Dunaway agreed and the results were .15 on serial #1205990. Dunaway then advised me that she works at &amp;ldquo;Women&amp;#39;s corrections.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Arrest&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had probable cause to believe Dunaway was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Unable to maintain a single lane of travel&lt;br /&gt; *Driving without any lights on a dark street at night&lt;br /&gt; *Failure to stop at a red circular signal&lt;br /&gt; *Traveling 25mph over the posted speed limit&lt;br /&gt; *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle&lt;br /&gt; *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on her breath and person&lt;br /&gt; *Glassy eyes&lt;br /&gt; *slurred speech&lt;br /&gt; *Gait ataxia&lt;br /&gt; *Poor SFST&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At this time Dunaway was placed under arrest for DUI. Dunaway was then handcuffed, searched, and placed in the front seat of R-24 and seat belted inside. Dunaway was then mirandized. Dunaway was then transported to the Golden Ring Barrack. While in my vehicle Dunaway became rude and discourteous yelling that I was &amp;ldquo;racist&amp;rdquo; and that I was &amp;ldquo;going to kill her.&amp;rdquo; Dunaway then stated &amp;ldquo;I really didn&amp;rsquo;t have any drinks, my lent started yesterday.&amp;rdquo; Dunaway then stated that she gave up &amp;ldquo;liquor&amp;rdquo; for lent.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Dunaway&amp;rsquo;s vehicle was towed from the scene due to being stopped in lane 2 of Liberty Road.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Once at the Golden Ring Barrack Dunaway was walked inside and placed in the intoximeter room. A physical copy of the DR15 was placed in front of her and the audio version was played aloud. At the conclusion of the audio Dunaway stated that she &amp;nbsp;did not wish to take the intoximeter test. The time of the refusal was 0046 hours.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 20-Minute Observation Period:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; N/A&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Intoximeter Result:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; N/A&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Dunaway was then issued a DR15A. Dunaway was then released to her sober and responsible friend in the front parking lot of the Golden Ring Barrack.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The original citations were voided, and the correct citations were sent to Dunaway through certified mail.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All above events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:58:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:58:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>PEZOLD</LastName>
            <FirstName>JONATHAN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7512</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Twardowski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sigman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7376</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17578</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15640</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15529</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16827</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>12</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15647</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>12</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496413</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>13</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>13</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 23:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>36</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:21:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369964</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dunaway</LastName>
               <FirstName>Montia</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lukisha</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/30/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.18110391E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 00:57:24</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M530</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dunaway</LastName>
               <FirstName>Montia</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lukisha</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/30/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.18110391E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>D500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M530</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 00:57:24</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1628</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Appleton</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21217</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1114</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.6490888</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.3072208</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>759</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1511</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:21:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:21:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:21:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:21:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:21:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150174</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:22:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:22:57</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2HNYD28609H521931</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2009</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>ACUR</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MDX</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5EG8823</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>