<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-004145</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/02/2023 10:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/02/2023 10:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/02/2023 10:29:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/02/2023 10:29:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic Stop / Recovery of Stolen Registration Plate / Theft Less Than $500</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/02/2023 10:54:07</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4913</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/04/2023 11:08:26</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>THMV</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>US-50 EB TO DAVIDSONVILLE NB / DAVIDSONVILLE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>684143</AddressId>
      <City>MDC383</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/02/2023 10:54:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 16:51:58</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>684143</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>16</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Westbound U.S. Route 50</StreetName>
         <City>Davidsonville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.64702129332612</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.962226453144105</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/02/2023 10:54:04</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/02/2023 10:54:04</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>Y</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/02/2023 22:19:36</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/02/2023 10:54:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:43</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;strong&gt;This stop was audibly and visually recorded on the Axon Body Worn Camera and on the Axon Digital Video Camera System installed in unmarked Maryland State Police unit, J15.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;This investigation is related to Anne Arundel County Police, Report #2023-701295.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;SCENE PROCESSING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I recovered one (1) stolen front Maryland registration plate, &amp;quot;4CY6302&amp;quot;, from the rear of a white BMW 320I, VIN #WBA8E1G3XHNU16935, operated by Shannon Bree Behling.&amp;nbsp; I took eleven digital photographs at the scene of the vehicle and the registration plate.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PHYSICAL EVIDENCE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;-One (1) front Maryland registration plate, &amp;quot;4CY6302&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;-Eleven (11) digital photographs.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;NARRATIVE&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;On 02/03/2023, at approximately 1022 hours, I, S/Tpr. S. Matthews #5973, was stationary on the right shoulder at westbound U.S. Route 50, in the area of Mile Marker 19, Davidsonville, Anne Arundel County, Maryland, in unmarked Maryland State Police unit, J15.&amp;nbsp; I observed a white BMW 320 I, bearing Maryland registration, &amp;quot;4CY6302&amp;quot;, pass me in Lane 3.&amp;nbsp; The License Plate Recognition sytem alerted on the registration for a stolen registration plate.&amp;nbsp; I verified the registration and conducted an MVA query of the registration.&amp;nbsp; I observed the registration was reported stolen through METERS/NCIC, NIC #P238110101.&amp;nbsp; The registration plate was reported stolen on 01/11/2023 at 0904 hours.&amp;nbsp; The registration plate belonged on a 2018 Honda CRV, VIN #2HKRW2H83HH650970 registered to Evan Morris Johnson, W/M, DOB: 03/24/1982.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I got behind the BMW and initiated a traffic stop with it in the area of westbound U.S. Route 50 at Exit 16, Davidsonville, Anne Arundel County, Maryland. I made a passenger&amp;#39;s side approach and made contact with the driver.&amp;nbsp; I identified myself and advised the driver the reason for the traffic stop.&amp;nbsp; I advised her that she had a stolen registration on the BMW.&amp;nbsp; The driver was identified by her Virginia Driver&amp;#39;s License as Shannon Bree Behling, W/F, DOB: 02/19/1977.&amp;nbsp; As I was speaking with Behling at the passenger&amp;#39;s side window, I observed she was holding a Maryland temporary registration and a Maryland temporary registration placard, &amp;quot;T1017171&amp;quot;, which showed an expiration of 10/2022.&amp;nbsp; Behling handed the items to me.&amp;nbsp; She stated the BMW was her vehicle.&amp;nbsp; I asked her where did she get the Maryland registration plate from.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;She stated, &amp;quot;That&amp;#39;s my tag.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked what tag was on the BMW before the hard metal tag.&amp;nbsp; She stated it was the temporary Maryland placard that I had in my hand.&amp;nbsp; I asked her if she transferred the Maryland hard plate from another vehicle.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;No.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; She stated the only other tag that she had was a vanity tag.&amp;nbsp; I asked Behling for her Driver&amp;#39;s License.&amp;nbsp; She handed me her Virginia Driver&amp;#39;s License.&amp;nbsp; I verified Behling&amp;#39;s address, which was in Annapolis, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; I asked Behling if she had a front registration on the BMW. She stated she did not.&amp;nbsp; I asked her where she got the registration stickers from.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;The stickers...I mean, they came from the DMV.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I advised her they appeared written on.&amp;nbsp; Behling appeared confused and asked to get out of the vehicle and look at the registration plate.&amp;nbsp; I met Behling at the rear of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I observed a fake month sticker in the upper left-hand corner of the registration plate.&amp;nbsp; It was a white 7 sticker on a red square sticker.&amp;nbsp; I observed a fake year sticker on the upper right-hand corner, with a black 2 and black 3 stickers on a white square sticker background.&amp;nbsp; The fraudulent month and year stickers appeared to have been made in a careful fashion, using vinyl stickers.&amp;nbsp; The red and white square backgrounds appeared to be carefully cut into squares.&amp;nbsp; The registration plate had two screws in the top screw holes.&amp;nbsp; I observed a black plate cover over the registration plate, attached with two screws on the bottom screw holes and through the Maryland plate.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The registration plate was confirmed stolen through Anne Arundel County Police Department.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I asked Behling if she saw the tag and advised her the stickers were fake.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;This isn&amp;#39;t my tag though.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked her again where she got the tag from.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;This has been sitting...I don&amp;#39;t know...I mean I had my own plates, and&amp;nbsp; I actually had to go through Drive Time.&amp;nbsp; I&amp;#39;ve been battling this...this car sat...actually for the last 24 hours in a parking lot.&amp;nbsp; I helped my boyfriend move.&amp;nbsp; This isn&amp;#39;t my...this isn&amp;#39;t my plate.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked Behling what was her plate then.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;I mean don&amp;#39;t know my license plate by heart, I&amp;#39;m sorry.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked Behling where her BMW was parked.&amp;nbsp; She stated it was parked at a parking lot off of West Street, in Annapolis.&amp;nbsp; She stated she could pull it up for me on her phone because she just paid for parking to pull the vehicle out.&amp;nbsp; Behling quickly stood up and walked back to the driver&amp;#39;s side of the BMW and got in.&amp;nbsp; Behling stated she was on her way to Washington, D.C.&amp;nbsp; She showed me on her cell phone that she was parked at the Larkin Street Lot in Annapolis.&amp;nbsp; I asked her again if she had another set of hard registration plates on her BMW.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked her if she had a front registration plate and a rear plate.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;No, I didn&amp;#39;t have a front tag.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked her where the front registration plate that she was supposed to have.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m guessing it&amp;#39;s in a box from moving.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked her what state the registration plate was through.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;It was through Virginia, because when they had kept...when they did this it was a complete cluster, excuse the terminology...when they registered the car they registered it to...they gave me 30-day tags in Maryland, but set it up to go through Virginia, because I was still living in Virginia at the time, in the midst of moving.&amp;nbsp; So they were Virginia plates.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I asked her if the Virginia plates expired or not.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;The Virginia plates shouldn&amp;#39;t be expired at all.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I asked her directly again, &amp;quot;So how did that tag get on the back of this vehicle.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; She replied, &amp;quot;Well that&amp;#39;s what I am saying right now...is that...I don&amp;#39;t know.&amp;nbsp; Those aren&amp;#39;t my tags.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked Behling what tag did she have on the BMW when she left it parked in Annapolis.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;My Virginia tag.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I verified that she had a Virginia metal plate on the back of the vehicle when she parked it in the Larkin Street parking lot.&amp;nbsp; She said yes.&amp;nbsp; She stated she did not know the tag number.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I advised her that I was going to write down the vehicle VIN number.&amp;nbsp; I advised her it appeared that someone had put a stolen Maryland tag on her BMW and maybe stole her Virginia tag from the rear of the BMW.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked if one of her Virginia registration plates was stolen then.&amp;nbsp; She looked confused and stated, &amp;quot;Okay.&amp;quot; I asked her how many Virginia tags did she have.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;For me...well I mean there has been some confusion because I had an Audi prior, um...&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I stopped Behling because I noticed that her answers were elusive.&amp;nbsp; She did not answer my direct questions with simple answers and she gave me complex excuses and details about her circumstances and registering her BMW.&amp;nbsp; I felt that Behling was not being truthful with me.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I obtained Behling&amp;#39;s phone number and current address.&amp;nbsp; She lived in Annapolis currently.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;That&amp;#39;s the issue, I was in the midst of moving, so I got the car from Drive Time.&amp;nbsp; My credit was not awesome at the time, so I got the car from there..got it.&amp;nbsp; They put 30-day tags on it from Maryland...which was going to work long term but I realized...&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I confirmed we were talking about the Maryland temporary placard that I was holding.&amp;nbsp; She confirmed it was.&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;It was longer than 30 days.&amp;nbsp; I ended up doing for like...60 days or something like that.&amp;nbsp; You can look at it...um...the issue came in with the fact that they screwed everything up in the process, uh then making it for my permanent plates to go through Virginia, when I wanted it through Maryland, and then it took forever for me to get the title from them.&amp;nbsp; Obviously it&amp;#39;s not a straight-up organization.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked her directly again, &amp;quot;You don&amp;#39;t know anything about that tag on the back of your car?&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; She stated, &amp;quot;No, I don&amp;#39;t.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; She confirmed again that she had a Virginia plate on the rear of the BMW.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I verified the VIN of the BMW with the Maryland temporary registration card.&amp;nbsp; I returned to my patrol car and examined the Maryland temporary registration card.&amp;nbsp; I observed Behling purchased the vehicle on or about 08/03/2022 and the Maryland temporary registration was valid for 60 days.&amp;nbsp; The registration card was legitimate and matched what was in the MVA data through METERS.&amp;nbsp; The registration card showed the BMW was going to be titled in Virginia.&amp;nbsp; The vehicle was sold by DriveTime Car Sales Company.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;A check through ETix showed that Behling had been stopped numerous times.&amp;nbsp; I observed the following dates:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;*06/22/2022 at 1034 hours, Behling was stopped in a black 2018 Audi Q5, bearing VA registration, &amp;quot;USV1842,&amp;quot; and issued two Warnings for expired registration, in Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;*07/16/2022 at 2329 hours, Behling was stopped in a black 2018 Audi Q5, bearing no registration plates in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; Behling was issued citations for operating unregistered vehicle on highway, driving uninsured vehicle, and driving without current registration.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;*11/23/2022 at 1555 hours, Behling was stopped in the white 2017 BMW 320, bearing Maryland temporary registration T1017171&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp; Behling was issued warnings for displaying expired registration plates.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I took eleven digital photographs of the BMW, and the vehicle registration plates.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;CPL O&amp;#39;Connor #4385 removed the Maryland registration plate from the rear of the BMW, and put the expired temporary registration placard on.&amp;nbsp; I gave the registration card back to Behling. She showed me a screenshot of the payment for parking, on Parking.com.&amp;nbsp; The screenshot showed a parking time between 02/01/2022 at 11:41 A.M. and 02/02/2022 at 10:08 A.M.&amp;nbsp; I took a digital photograph of Behling&amp;#39;s screenshot, on her cell phone.&amp;nbsp; I took possession of the stolen Maryland registration plate.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I advised Behling to come to the Barrack in the next few days so that I could take a theft report for her stolen Virginia registration.&amp;nbsp; I suspected that Behling was not going to come to the Barrack because she was not truthful.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;At approximately 1151 hours, I responded to the Evan Johnson&amp;#39;s address in Crofton, Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; I observed E. Johnson&amp;#39;s blue Honda CRV parked in the driveway of the residence.&amp;nbsp; The Honda was bearing a new Maryland registration, &amp;quot;1FG4809&amp;quot;.&amp;nbsp; I made contact with E. Johnson&amp;#39;s wife, Camille Elizabeth Johnson, W/F, DOB: 10/02/1978.&amp;nbsp; C. Johnson stated that she drove the Honda and the vehicle was registered in her husband&amp;#39;s name.&amp;nbsp; C. Johnson stated she came out of her residence on 01/11/2023 at approximately 0800 hours, and observed the front registration plate was missing from the Honda.&amp;nbsp; She stated she called Anne Arundel County Police and reported the registration plate as stolen.&amp;nbsp; C. Johnson stated her neighbor, at 2586 Windy Oak Court, has a Ring camera.&amp;nbsp; She stated the neighbor checked the camera and did not note any suspicious on the night of 01/10/2023.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;C. Johnson stated she works in Annapolis, Maryland, at 833 Bestgate Road.&amp;nbsp; She stated she did not notice if the front registration plate was missing when she left work on 01/10/2023.&amp;nbsp; C. Johnson emailed a picture she took of the Honda CRV in her driveway on 01/10/2023.&amp;nbsp; I asked C. Johnson if she knew Behling.&amp;nbsp; She stated she did not know her.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;At approximately 1257 hours, I responded to C. Johnson&amp;#39;s place of employment, located at 888 Bestgate Road, Annapolis, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; I observed external cameras around the building.&amp;nbsp; I went inside the building and made contact with th building engineer, Peter Figueroa.&amp;nbsp; He advised the external cameras were not functional.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;At approximately 1321 hours, I responded to the Larkin Street Parking Lot and observed there were numerous cameras around the ticket box.&amp;nbsp; I contacted Annapolis Parking by phone and spoke with Breyanna Benton.&amp;nbsp; She advised me that the camera system was not functional.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Due to the fact that there was no camera footage at the Larkin Street Parking Lot, nor at 888 Bestgate Road, there are no additional leads to pursue.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;This case is suspended.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 09:15:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5973</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/02/2023 17:17:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>O'Connor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4785</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Allen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5509</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Matthews</LastName>
            <FirstName>Shawn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5973</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493527</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>04</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 3090</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/02/2023 17:17:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 3090</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 16:52:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5973</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/02/2023 17:17:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493527</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>04</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0621 23G</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/02/2023 17:17:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0621 23G</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 16:53:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5973</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/02/2023 17:17:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 17:03:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368965</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Behling</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shannon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Bree</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/19/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.88601796E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 17:02:44</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S550</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Behling</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shannon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Bree</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/19/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.88601796E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>B452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S550</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 17:02:44</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>316</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Burnside</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Annapolis</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21403</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.486913</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.971164</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>330</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>940</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9696</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>330</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>940</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9696</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 17:03:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 17:14:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368966</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Evan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Morris</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/24/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>J525238609237</LastName>
               <FirstName>EVAN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MORRIS</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/24/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 17:07:51</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Evan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Morris</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/24/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>J525238609237</LastName>
               <FirstName>EVAN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MORRIS</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/24/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 17:07:51</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2588</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>WINDY OAK</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Crofton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21114</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>254</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2056</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/02/2023 17:15:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/02/2023 17:15:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149794</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>VI</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 17:15:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5973</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 17:15:19</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2HKRW2H83HH650970</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CR-V</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4CY6302</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149793</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 17:16:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5973</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 17:16:03</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WBA8E1G3XHNU16935</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>BMW</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>320</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>T1017171</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2022</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>10</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>7</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 17:18:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5973</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 17:18:08</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>5</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One Maryland registration plate, "4CY6302", valued at $135.00.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>996</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>135</PropertyValue>
         <Value>135</Value>
         <SerialNumber>4CY6302</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243526</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>WHI</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>WHI</SecondaryColor>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5973</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 17:37:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5973</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 17:37:56</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Eleven digital photographs.  </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>30</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243527</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>11</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>