<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012850</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>64</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/11/2023 14:32:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/11/2023 14:32:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/11/2023 13:33:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/11/2023 13:33:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Accident/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 14:33:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5459</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 23:57:57</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>690335</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 14:33:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/11/2023 16:57:26</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>690335</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>78</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I68 Eb</StreetName>
         <City>Hancock</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-78.23004</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.71278</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/11/2023 14:32:59</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/11/2023 14:32:59</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>64</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/14/2023 23:57:58</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 14:33:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:33</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-5a0f19a4-7fff-9d3c-f5e8-bd94ce0a4b41"&gt;THIS INCIDENT WAS CAPTURED ON BWC WITH FUNCTIONING AUDIO AND VIDEO&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Brian Keith Pattie&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth 03/24/1984&lt;br /&gt; Date of arrest: 04/11/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of arrest: 1427 hours.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; DUI #&amp;nbsp; 23-039&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-5a0f19a4-7fff-9d3c-f5e8-bd94ce0a4b41"&gt;*Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *Trained in the use of RADAR/LIDAR speed detection equipment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On April 11, 2023, at approximately 1333 hours, I responded to Eastbound Interstate 68 at the 78 mile marker for the report of a two vehicle property damage collision. I did not observe either vehicle in motion for this incident.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Upon arrival, I observed a red International truck, pulling a trailer containing guard rail on the right hand shoulder of the roadway. I contacted the driver of the truck, who I identified by his Pennsylvania driver&amp;#39;s license as, Mark Alan Richey (1/11/1969) Richey advised he was sitting stationary on the right shoulder of the roadway with his amber lights activated when he was struck from behind by a gray SUV. I observed damage to the drivers side of the Truck. In front of the truck I observed a gray Ford SUV bearing Maryland registration 5FG2386. The ford was stuck to the guardrail on the right shoulder, with the front of the vehicle facing lane #2. I contacted the driver, and sole occupant of the ford, who I identified by his Maryland driver&amp;#39;s license as, Brian Keith Pettie (B/M 03/24/1984). I asked Pettie what happened, to which he responded &amp;quot;no comment&amp;quot; As I spoke with Pettie I observed his eyes were bloodshot and glassy. While speaking with Pettie I also observed he swayed back and forth as he stood still. I asked Pettie to submit to the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Pettie the following:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Injuries: NO&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Medication: NO&lt;br /&gt; Glasses: NO&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Pre-arrest screening (PHASE 3)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; The SFSTs were performed on the right Shoulder of Interstate 68.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-5a0f19a4-7fff-9d3c-f5e8-bd94ce0a4b41"&gt;The surface was dry free from any obvious debris. All forward facing emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Pettie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible signs of injury.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (0 Of 6 CLUES OBSERVED)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. My pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Pettie&amp;#39;s eyes. Pettie was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. I observed Pettie to have equal pupil size, and equal tracking. Pettie verbally advised he understood the directions for the test. Pettie had to be reminded to follow the stimulus with his eyes, and his eyes only, and to not move his head. Pettie swayed from side to side during the HGN test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lack of smooth pursuit - not present&lt;br /&gt; Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation-not present&lt;br /&gt; Onset Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees-not present&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Vertical Gaze Nystagmus-not present&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walk and turn (3 of 8 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Prior to Pettie performing the test I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Pettie was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Pettie was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until instructed to begin. Pettie was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Pettie was instructed to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Pettie was explained and I demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and planted, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around to his left. Pettie was again explained and I demonstrated a second series of nine (9) steps were to be completed identically to the first series. Pettie was instructed that once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed. Keep his hands down by her&amp;nbsp;side, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. Pettie verbally advised she understood the directions for the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Instructional Phase&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Pettie started too soon two (2) separate times before being advised to begin the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; First set of nine steps:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Pettie came to a complete stop after the first set of nine steps.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Second set of nine steps:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Pettie missed heel to toe contact on step 1.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; One leg stand (2 of 4 clues observed)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-5a0f19a4-7fff-9d3c-f5e8-bd94ce0a4b41"&gt;Prior to Pettie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be completed. Pettie was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down at his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Pettie verbally stated he understood the directions for the test. Pettie raised his right foot for the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 1-10&lt;br /&gt; Pettie swayed side to side while balancing&lt;br /&gt; Pettie raised his arms more than 6&amp;#39;&amp;#39; away from his body in order to maintain balance&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; swayed side to side while balancing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Seconds 21-30&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;swayed side to side while balancing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lack of Covergance:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Pettie was advised to stand with his feet together, and his arms straight down at his side. Pettie was advised to keep his head straight and to follow my stimulus with his eyes, and his eyes only.&amp;nbsp; I used a black pen as a stimulus. Pettie verbally advised he understood the instructions for the test. LOC was observed in Petties right eye.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Modified Rhomberg Balance:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Pettie was advised to stand with his heels together, and his arms straight down at his sides. Pettie was advised to tilt his head backward, close his eyes, and estimate the passage of thirty (30) seconds. Pettie was advised after he felt thirty seconds had elapsed, to open his eyes, tilt his head back forward and advised me he was done. Pettie estimated the passage of thirty seconds in approximately twenty-five (25) seconds. During the test, I observed Pettie sway from side to side while balancing, and I observed Petties. eyelids to tremor&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-5a0f19a4-7fff-9d3c-f5e8-bd94ce0a4b41"&gt;ARREST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-5a0f19a4-7fff-9d3c-f5e8-bd94ce0a4b41"&gt;Based on the following, I had reason to believe Pettie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;was driving a motor vehicle while impaired by a controlled dangerous substance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &amp;nbsp;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-5a0f19a4-7fff-9d3c-f5e8-bd94ce0a4b41"&gt;*At fault vehicle in property damage accident, striking a parked vehicle with lights activated.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-5a0f19a4-7fff-9d3c-f5e8-bd94ce0a4b41"&gt;*My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety testing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-5a0f19a4-7fff-9d3c-f5e8-bd94ce0a4b41"&gt;*Bloodshot eyes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Pettie was placed under arrest at approximately 1427 hours. Prior to placing&amp;nbsp;Hunt in my patrol vehicle, I conducted a search of his person which revealed no contraband. I also checked Pettie&amp;#39;s mouth and found it was free of any foreign substances.&amp;nbsp; A cursory check of the area within Petties reach within the vehicle he was operating was checked, revealing no contraband. Pettie was transported to the Maryland State Police Hagerstown Barrack. Once at the Hagerstown Barrack, Pettie was read and given to read a copy of the DR-15 advice of rights while seated directly to my right. Pettie refused to submit to the intoximeter test, and refused to submit to any more testing, or speak with a DRE at approximately 1534 hours. Pettie was issued the appropriate traffic citations, and given all appropriate copies of his paperwork, which he declined to sign.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Pettie was released from the barrack to a sober driver.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; CASE STATUS:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I respectfully, respect this case be closed by arrest.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; All events occurred in Washington County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 17:01:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6783</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/11/2023 22:25:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CVED</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Blubaugh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0241</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>64</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shilling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kenneth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5459</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>64</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derek</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6783</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502254</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/11/2023 14:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 16:58:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6783</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/11/2023 16:58:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 16:58:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374010</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Pettie</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Keith</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/24/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/11/2023 16:51:06</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Pettie</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Keith</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/24/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/11/2023 16:51:06</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>211</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Maryland</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Cumberland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21502</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-78.756022</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.650677</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 17:00:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 17:00:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 16:58:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6783</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/11/2023 16:58:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>