<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-005078</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/09/2023 13:41:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/09/2023 13:41:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/09/2023 13:15:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/09/2023 13:15:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>PWID Fentanyl / Cocaine</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/09/2023 13:41:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3267</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/17/2023 19:52:33</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>Advanced Auto Parts</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>683663</AddressId>
      <City>MDC136</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/09/2023 13:41:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 09:44:39</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>683663</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>25</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Industrial</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Cumberland</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-78.764039</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.632761</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/09/2023 13:41:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/09/2023 13:41:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40J</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/17/2023 13:48:16</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/09/2023 13:41:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On February 9, 2023, at approximately 1315 hours, I, S/Tpr Whorton was operating my unmarked MSP vehicle CE-144 in the area of Industrial Blvd at Virginia Ave, Cumberland, Allegany County, MD. It should be noted, M/Tpr Talbert was riding in my front passenger seat and Sgt Smith was riding in the rear passenger side seat.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;At this time, myself, M/Tpr Talbert and Sgt Smith observed a blue Honda passenger car traveling from Virginia Ave to Industrial Blvd, a known area for CDS activity, with no front plate and heavy window tinting material. A registration plate could be seen on the passenger side on the dash behind the windshield. As the Honda traveled from W/B Industrial Blvd to E/B Industrial it stopped at the Virginia Ave traffic light. Once through the light, the Honda turned into Advanced Auto, located at 25 E. Industrial Blvd, Cumberland without signaling.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As the Honda entered the Advanced Auto parking lot, I activated the emergency equipment on CE-144 and stopped behind the Honda in a parking spot adjacent to the advanced Auto building. Once the Honda stopped, I made contact with the driver, identified as Curtis Eugene Evans (06/09/1994) through the driver&amp;#39;s window and M/Tpr Talbert made contact with the passenger identified as Justin Terrell Lewis (08/16/1991). While speaking with Evans, he was nervously looking around and did not want to place his window down completely. As Evans handed me his license, he attempted to place the window back up, however I told him not to, and he did not seem sure of where his registration and insurance information was. As I was speaking with Evans, I could see a bottle of alcohol on the passenger seat and could smell the odor of alcohol emanating from within the vehicle. During this time, M/Tpr Talbert was speaking with Lewis and made a gesture to his nose indicating that he could detect an odor coming from within the vehicle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Based on the circumstances, I asked Evans to exit the vehicle to speak. Evans was reluctant, however did exit the vehicle. Once Evans exited the vehicle, he began nervously pacing back and forth while blading himself off. Based on the way Evans was pacing and balding himself off, I felt as if he may have been considering striking me. Evans was asked several times to relax and I asked if I could pat him down for weapons and search him. Based on Evans behavior, I suspected he may have been concealing a weapon and/or contraband. I then attempted to pat Evans down for weapons as he stepped back and continued to step around trying to create distance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;At this time, I attempted to pat Evans down once again based on his behavior and he took flight on foot, fleeing E/B on the sidewalk of Industrial Blvd toward Grand Ave. As Evans began fleeing, myself and S/Tpr Peterson began to pursue, while ordering Evans to stop several times. Evans disobeyed the orders to stop and continued fleeing approximately 250-300 yards before turning right onto the end of Grand Ave. As Evans was about to turn onto Grand Ave, I could see him reaching into the right front pocket of his sweatpants with his right hand and appeared to remove an item. Once Evans rounded the corner, S/Tpr Peterson could see that Evans removed a clear plastic bag from his right front sweatpants pocket containing a white and blue substance.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;It should be noted, I, M/Tpr Talbert and Sgt Smith was wearing tactical police gear displaying &amp;quot;Police&amp;quot; and/or &amp;quot;Trooper&amp;quot;. S/Tpr Peterson was wearing the MSP winter Uniform of the Day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As S/Tpr Peterson could see the bag of suspected CDS substance, he could see Evans attempt to throw the bag twice. On the second attempt to throw the bag, Evans was able to throw the bag up in the air off to his right as he continued to flee. As Evans was able to discard the bag, S/Tpr Peterson was able to catch Evans and take him to the ground.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As S/Tpr Peterson was attempting to apprehend Evans, I rounded the corner and could see the bag in mid-air before it landed on the sidewalk. As the bag landed on the sidewalk, I could see it contained a white substance of suspected CDS. As I saw the bag land on the ground, I passed by to assist S/Tpr Peterson, as I continued running to where S/Tpr Peterson was, Evans was activity trying to get up. S/Tpr Peterson had hold of Evans shirt as Evans was trying to stand up. Based on Evans fleeing, disregarding orders and pulling away from S/Tpr Peterson, I assisted S/Tpr Peterson with keeping Evans on the ground and take Evans into custody without further incident.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As Evans was taken into custody, the bag Evans discarded was recovered from the sidewalk and contained suspected cocaine (29.5grams) and blue round pills (34) stamped &amp;quot;M&amp;quot;, disguised as Prescription Oxycodone of suspected fentanyl (11.5 grams).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Once Evans was walked back to the scene of the traffic stop, M/Tpr Talbert advised that he could smell the odor alcohol and marijuana emanating from within the Honda. Based on the odor of marijuana and bag containing suspected Cocaine and Fentanyl that Evans discarded from his person a probable cause search of the vehicle was conducted. During search of the Honda the following suspected CDS was located:&lt;br /&gt; 1-One small bag containing suspected marijuana (9.5 grams) (Located inside the front passenger door pocket by S/Tpr Deaner)&lt;br /&gt; 2-One large heat seal type bag containing suspected marijuana (204 grams) (Located on rear passenger seat by S/Tpr Whorton)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I know based on my training, knowledge and experience as a Maryland State Trooper that Cocaine has been identified by the DEA as Schedule II narcotic. I also know the amount of suspected cocaine Evans was possessed and in the manner he possessed it was in sufficient quantity to indicate Evans possessed the cocaine with the intent to distribute the same. Further; I know the amount of suspected cocaine Evans possessed and the manner in which he possessed it was indicative of street level sales.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I also know based on my training, knowledge and experience that the blue pills stamped &amp;quot;M&amp;quot; are consistent with fraudulent prescription Oxycodone pills based on the inconsistent and off color of blue coloring of the pills. I also know based on past arrests and current trends CDS distributors have been recently disguising Fentanyl to appear as prescription Oxycodone pills. Further; I have seized kilo amounts of these same Fentanyl pills disguised as prescription Oxycodone stamped &amp;quot;M&amp;quot;. I also know that Fentanyl has been identified by the DEA as a schedule II narcotic. I also know the amount of suspected fentanyl Evans was possessed and in the manner he possessed it was in sufficient quantity to indicate Evans possessed the suspected fentanyl with the intent to distribute the same. Further; I know the amount of suspected fentanyl Evans possessed and the manner in which he possessed it was indicative of street level sales.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I also know based on my training, knowledge and experience that Evans possessed a large amount of fentanyl, more than 5 grams as described in the Maryland Commissioners Manual under CJIS 1-0881 CR 5-612 Poss-Large Amount.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;After the vehicle was searched, Evans was transported to the Allegany County Detention Center, located at 14300 McMullen Highway, Cumberland, MD where he was held without bond.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The suspected CDS was processed into evidence at the MSP Cumberland Barracks, which was documented on MSP Form 67 (Chain of Custody) and Property Record (P-342972). Once processed the CDS property was stored at the MSP Cumberland Barrack evidence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All the above events occurred in Allegany County, MD.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 11:23:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 10:54:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Talbert</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4777</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Peterson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5308</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeremy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4780</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wilson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ersel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6100</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeremy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4780</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Whorton</LastName>
            <FirstName>Charles</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6096</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494464</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/09/2023 13:15:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 09:46:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 09:46:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>28</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 09:53:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>19558</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Evans</LastName>
               <FirstName>Curtis</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Eugene</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/09/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/23/2014 03:28:48</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E152</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C632</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Evans</LastName>
               <FirstName>Curtis</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Eugene</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/09/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>E152</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C632</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/23/2014 03:28:48</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>916</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Lanvale</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hagerstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21740</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.737822</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.645747</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6096</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 09:53:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6096</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 09:53:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 09:46:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 09:46:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 10:01:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 10:01:30</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One bag containing suspected cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243509</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>29.5</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 10:01:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 10:01:30</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One bag containing 34 round blue pills of suspected Fentanyl</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243510</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>H</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>11.5</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 10:01:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 10:01:31</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One bag containing suspected marijuana</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243511</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>9.5</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 10:01:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 10:01:31</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One bag containing suspected marijuana</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243512</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>204</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>