<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013452</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/16/2023 00:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/16/2023 00:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/15/2023 23:26:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/15/2023 23:26:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driving under the influence of alcohol</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 00:08:30</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4993</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/15/2023 15:39:38</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>TWILLEYS BRIDGE RD/ WANGO RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>690845</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 00:08:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 00:08:55</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>690845</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Twilleys Bridge</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Salisbury</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.45559</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.32088</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>32950-33400 TWILLEYS BRIDGE RD / 33410-33559 WANGO RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/16/2023 00:08:27</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/16/2023 00:08:27</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/10/2023 09:41:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 00:08:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 09:41:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subsequent offender:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&amp;nbsp;No&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This stop was recorded on body worn camera.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=560868312f174211bfab03636b90299c&amp;amp;partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=976cea77cb274772b10d47a92a3c2250&amp;amp;partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=09494df650ad442b9b6a1527edb0f4af&amp;amp;partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vehicle in motion:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On 4/16/2023 at 2326 hours, I, M/Tpr. A. Edwards, was traveling on north on Wango Road south of Twilleys Bridge Road, Salisbury, Wicomico County when I observed a green and black utility terrain vehicle (UTV) traveling directly in front of my patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp; As the vehicle continued north, I observed the vehicle cross the double yellow line by approximately one foot with both driver side tires on two separate occasions.&amp;nbsp; While I was behind the vehicle, I did not observe any registration plates on the rear of the vehicle. The vehicle, which was later identified as a 2016 Can Am UTV, made a right turn onto Twilleys Bridge Road and I activated the emergency equipment in my assigned marked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle E-28 and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; The vehicle was traveling with several other vehicles and one additional vehicle, a black Razor side by side UTV, stopped when I activated my emergency equipment.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personal contact:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I approached both of the vehicles and stood between them as they stopped next to each other. I identified myself and explained the reason for the stop to the drivers.&amp;nbsp; I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from both vehicles.&amp;nbsp; I asked the drivers if they consumed anything to drink and the driver of the green and black UTV advised that he had had a &amp;quot;couple.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; I asked both of the drivers for their licenses and registrations and neither driver had any registration information for the vehicles because neither vehicle was registered through the motor vehicle administration.&amp;nbsp; The driver of the black and green vehicle was able to provide his license to me.&amp;nbsp; The driver was identified as the above listed defendant, Boyd Richard Cox.&amp;nbsp; I asked each driver to exit the vehicle in order to perform field sobriety. The driver of the Razor completed field sobriety successfully and I did not believe he was driving while impaired by alcohol.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I asked the defendant to exit the vehicle to perform field sobriety tests and he agreed to do so.&amp;nbsp; I instructed the defendant to walk towards the front of my patrol vehicle and when he did I observed him to walk with an ataxic gait.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pre-arrest screening:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Once the defendant was away from the vehicle and the other driver, I was able to smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from the defendant&amp;#39;s breath when he spoke. The defendant spoke with slow and slurred speech and his movements were slow and sluggish. I asked the defendant if he had any major medical problems and he advised that he suffered from vertigo and poor circulation in his legs. He has suffered from problems with vertigo for approximately the last eight years.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I asked the defendant if he took any medication and he stated that he takes medication for anxiety, depression, and high blood pressure.&amp;nbsp; The defendant advised he takes a generic version for Paxil for his anxiety and depression but could not recall the name of it as well as Gabapentin for his nerve pain.&amp;nbsp; He advised he routinely takes all of his medication at the same time and took them at approximately 1730 hours.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I asked the defendant how much he had to drink and he advised that he had three beers (12 ounces) at his house in Willards.&amp;nbsp; He advised he also had one beer on the farm prior to driving. He believed his last drink was only a few minutes prior to stop before leaving the farm. I asked the defendant what time he thought it was and he stated, &amp;quot;1130&amp;quot; and it was 2332 hours.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; At the time of the stop the defendant was wearing glasses. I asked the defendant what he wore glasses for and he stated that he wears them for every day and cannot see anything without them.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; While I was speaking with the defendant he put his hand on the front of my police car for balance and even leaned against it with his buttock and lower back.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; The tests were performed in the area of Twilleys Bridge Road that was blocked by my patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp; The roadway was flat and was constructed on light gravel and hand packed sand.&amp;nbsp; There were not any large hole or large rocks that would affect the test.&amp;nbsp; At the time of testing, the defendant was wearing a t-shirt, jeans, and slip on shoes that he said he was comfortable wearing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Test one - Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-I explained the test to the defendant and he stated that he understood all the directions and did not have any questions.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1. The defendant displayed the lack of smooth pursuit and equal tracking in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2.&amp;nbsp;The defendant displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3. The defendant displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;4. The defendant displayed vertical nystagmus in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-The defendant swayed from side to side by approximately two inches during the entire test.&lt;br /&gt; Total clues: 6 out of 6.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Test two - Walk and Turn:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; -I explained the test to the defendant and he stated that he understood all the directions however he stated that he was unable to do the test because of his medical issues and his poor balance. The defendant did not perform the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Test three - One Leg Stand:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-I explained and demonstrated the test to the defendant and he stated that he understood all the directions however he stated that he was unable to do the test because of his medical issues and his poor balance.&amp;nbsp; The defendant picked his foot up of the ground and immediately lost his balance and staggered backwards.The defendant did not perform the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I asked the defendant if he could read and write the English language and knew his numbers and he stated that he did. I asked the defendant what his highest level of education was and he advised that he failed out of the tenth grade.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Test four - Number:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; -I asked the defendant to count backwards from the number 57 and ending at the number 42.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; -The defendant stated counting at 56 and counted backwards to 47 and stated, &amp;quot;where&amp;#39;d you tell me to stop?&amp;quot; The defendant resumed counting and stopped at 45.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; -During the test, the defendant counted extremely slow.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; -I asked the defendant if he was done and he stated that he could not recall what number I asked him to stop at.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Test five - Alphabet:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; -I asked the defendant to say the alphabet from the letter G to the letter T without signing it.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; -After telling the defendant to begin the test he paused for several seconds before he stated.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; -The defendant completed the test in the following manner, &amp;quot;H, I, J, K L, M, N, O, P, Q, R, S, T.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I offered the defendant a preliminary breath test, however he refused to submit a sample.&amp;nbsp; Based on the defendant&amp;#39;s poor performance on field sobriety tests he was placed under arrest at 2354 hours. The defendant was seated&amp;nbsp;in my patrol vehicle while I contacted the other driver and passenger. When I returned to my vehicle and entered it, I was able to smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage that was not present prior to the defendant being seated in it. The defendant was&amp;nbsp;transported to the Salisbury Barrack for processing.&amp;nbsp; While at the barrack, the defendant was read and allowed to read his DR-15 Advice of rights. After completing the DR-15, the defendant agreed to submit to the intoximeter at 0054 hours.&amp;nbsp; The defendant submitted a sample of .10 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 0104 hours. The defendant was issued six citations for DUI, negligent driving, failing to drive right of center and operating an unregistered motor vehicle. The defendant was to his son from the barrack.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Based on all the above facts, I request that the case be closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; CASE&amp;nbsp;CLOSED.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 00:56:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 03:51:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norfolk</LastName>
            <FirstName>Wyatt</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7120</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tykeshia</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6883</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bruce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6083</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Edwards</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alexander</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5096</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502859</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 00:14:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 00:14:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502859</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 00:14:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 00:14:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502859</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 00:14:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 00:26:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502859</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 00:14:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 00:26:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502859</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 00:14:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 00:26:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502859</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>18599</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 23:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>18599</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 00:14:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 00:26:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>68</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 00:21:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:16</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375037</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cox</LastName>
               <FirstName>Boyd</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Richard</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/22/1955 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/23/2023 00:19:31</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cox</LastName>
               <FirstName>Boyd</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Richard</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/22/1955 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/23/2023 00:19:31</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7659</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Old Mill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Willards</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21874</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.359079</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.400005</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>513</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0537</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 00:28:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 00:28:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 00:14:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 00:14:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152252</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5096</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/23/2023 00:30:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5096</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 00:30:51</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>UNKNOWN</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2016</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CANA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>XX</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRN</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>N/A</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>