<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-010918</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/27/2023 01:14:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/27/2023 01:14:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/27/2023 00:35:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/27/2023 00:35:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop leading to DUI/DWI arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 01:14:28</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5364</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 11:30:03</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>688648</AddressId>
      <City>MDC275</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 01:14:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 03:58:07</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>688648</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>5</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I270 Sb</StreetName>
         <City>Potomac</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.15789</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.06689</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB ML AT WOOTTON</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/27/2023 01:14:26</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/27/2023 01:14:26</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/29/2023 04:09:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 01:14:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/29/2023 04:09:31</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;MSP marked vehicle N-36 is equipped with a mobile recording device&lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Andy Eliand Paz&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 01/17/2005&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 03/27/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 0111 hours&lt;br /&gt; DUI #: 23-073&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; *Trained in administering advanced standardized field sobriety tests (ARIDE) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; *Trained in detection and administering advanced standardized field sobriety tests for Cannabis Intoxication through the Montgomery County Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On March 27, 2023, at approximately 0035 hours, I, Trooper Lear (#7154), was on duty in an official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating marked MSP vehicle N-36 in Rockville, Montgomery County, Maryland. I was traveling southbound on I-270 at Shady Grove Road when I observed a white BMW 320i pass me at a high rate of speed. I was able to pace the BMW by maintaining an equal distance and equal speed with the vehicle on southbound I-270 at Maryland Route 28 for approximately three tenths of a mile. The speed of the BMW reached 120 miles per hour in a 55 miles per hour zone. I identified the vehicle as a white BMW 320i bearing MD registration 7CL1948. I activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I approached the vehicle and made contact with the occupants, the vehicle was occupied with four people. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I immediately observed the driver&amp;rsquo;s eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. The driver was identified by his MD driver&amp;rsquo;s license permit as Andy Eliand Paz (DOB: 01/17/2005, H/M). Paz&amp;rsquo;s mother, Aricel Bolanos Torres (DOB: 10/10/1979, H/F), was the front-seat passenger who did not possess a driver&amp;rsquo;s license. Andy Paz advised he was on the way home after dropping off his friend in Gaithersburg. I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Andy Paz. I advised the Rockville Barrack that I would need a backup unit for field sobriety. A check through the Motor Vehicle Administration revealed Andy Paz had no open warrants. I asked Andy Paz to exit the vehicle, to which he complied. Andy Paz pleaded by asking if he could receive a ticket for speeding on three occasions. Andy Paz claimed he was sober while the other three passengers consumed alcoholic beverages. Andy Paz advised he was traveling the same speed limit as the other motorists on the road. Andy Paz also advised that since he is new to driving, he does not understand the speed limits. Andy Paz advised the speed limit went from 65 miles per hour to 55 miles per hour. On southbound I-270 from Shady Grove Road to Wootton Parkway, there are no 65 mile per hour zones or posted signs. Before submitting to field sobriety, Andy Paz claimed he could refuse the test because he did not consume any alcoholic beverages. Andy Paz asked if he submitted to the tests, could his mother or sister drive home, after explaining to me that he was sober and all three passengers consumed alcoholic beverages earlier in the night. Andy Paz finally admitted to consuming 2 to 3 beers on scene. Later at the barrack, Andy Paz advised he consumed 3 Blue Moon beers at approximately 2400 hours at his friend&amp;#39;s house. While talking to Andy Paz on scene and at the barrack, Andy Paz&amp;rsquo;s body movements were slow and lethargic as well as his speech being mumbled and slurred.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed in front of the BMW 320i on the left shoulder of southbound I-270 at Wootton Parkway, Rockville, Maryland. The surface was dry, slight downhill grade, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 60 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of light illuminating from light poles and my patrol vehicle&amp;rsquo;s headlights. Andy Paz advised he sustained a gunshot wound to his right knee. Andy Paz advised it would not affect him from walking or standing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Paz the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; - Injuries &amp;ndash; Right knee&lt;br /&gt; - Medication &amp;ndash; No&lt;br /&gt; - Medical Conditions &amp;ndash; No&lt;br /&gt; - Glasses/Contacts &amp;ndash; None observed&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from Andy Paz&amp;rsquo;s eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Andy Paz&amp;rsquo;s pupils were equal in size, showed equal tracking, and no resting Nystagmus was observed. He was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Andy Paz if he understood the instructions and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 degrees &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;WALK AND TURN (2/8 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Andy Paz performing the test, I properly examined and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Andy Paz was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Andy Paz was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in the position until told to begin. Andy Paz was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Andy Paz was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Andy Paz was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Andy Paz was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Andy Paz was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Andy Paz if he understood the test and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo;. Footwear: sneakers.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -No clues were observed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -Raised his arms on step 1.&lt;br /&gt; -Took ten (10) steps.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Turn:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -No clues were observed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -Took ten (10) steps.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Prior to Andy Paz performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Andy Paz was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two), and continue the test until told to stop. I asked Andy Paz if he understood the test and he stated, &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo;. Andy Paz chose to raise his left foot. Footwear: sneakers.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -No clues were observed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Balance and Count Stage:&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -No clues were observed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Seconds 11-20:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -No clues were observed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Seconds 21-30:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -Put foot down throughout the time frame.&lt;br /&gt; -Swayed throughout the time frame.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Andy Paz was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; -Traveling 120 miles per hour in a 55 miles per hour zone.&lt;br /&gt; -The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; -Eyes were glassy and bloodshot with a glazed look.&lt;br /&gt; -Body movements were slow and lethargic.&lt;br /&gt; -Mumbled and slurred speech.&lt;br /&gt; -Admitted to consuming three Blue Moon beers approximately one hour prior to the traffic stop.&lt;br /&gt; -Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus &amp;ndash; 6/6 clues observed&lt;br /&gt; -Walk and Turn &amp;ndash; 2/8 clues observed&lt;br /&gt; -One Leg Stand &amp;ndash; 2/4 clues observed&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; At approximately 0111 hours, I placed Andy Paz under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. Andy Paz was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Rockville Barrack for processing. After arriving at the barrack, I gave Paz a copy of the DR-15 form in English to review while I played the entire form in English audio to him in the barrack. Paz signed the DR-15 at approximately 0141 hours, agreeing to submit to the intoximeter test.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Andy Paz beginning with his arrest. A preliminary search of Andy Paz was conducted on the scene and it revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. I observed Andy Paz from the time of the arrest until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by Sgt. Tribue #5781 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Andy Paz&amp;rsquo;s breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of .11 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. Andy Paz was released to the custody of his father, from the barrack.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; CASE CLOSED BY ARREST.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 05:01:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/29/2023 03:58:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barnes</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quinn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7269</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tribue</LastName>
            <FirstName>Byron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5781</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lear</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quinn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7154</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500321</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 00:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:04:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 04:04:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500321</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 00:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:05:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 04:05:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500321</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 00:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:05:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 04:05:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500321</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 00:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:06:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 04:06:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500321</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 00:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:07:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 04:07:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500321</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 00:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:07:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 04:07:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500321</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 00:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>120 mph in 55 mph zone</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:08:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 04:08:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500321</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16827</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 00:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>Alcohol Restriction </Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16827</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:09:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 04:09:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500321</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15420</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/27/2023 00:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15420</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:10:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 04:10:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:14:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:30</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372652</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Paz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Andy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Eliand</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/17/2005 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 04:13:46</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A530</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Paz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Andy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Eliand</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/17/2005 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A530</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 04:13:46</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1810</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Crosby</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hyattsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20783</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:14:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:14:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:04:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 04:04:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151330</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:14:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 04:14:54</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>BMW</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>320</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7CL1948</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>