<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-010474</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/23/2023 20:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/23/2023 20:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/23/2023 19:22:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/23/2023 19:22:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 20:08:57</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/28/2023 16:29:21</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>672</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>564</SubBeat>
      <City>MDC305</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 20:08:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 00:38:39</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>672</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>3137</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>BALTIMORE</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>FINKSBURG</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>564</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-76.88366468224739</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.49104791550077</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>JIFFY MART</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>JIFFYMART</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MD - SPPCS - WIRELESS CALLER</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>JIFFYMART    F/U</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/23/2023 20:08:55</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/23/2023 20:08:55</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/10/2023 12:00:34</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 20:08:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:20:56</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;INCIDENT CAPTURED BY BWC AND MVR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;23-MSP-010474&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUI#: 23-048&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ATTACHMENTS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Copy of DR-15&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Copy of DR-15A&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Copy of MSP Form 33&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Copy of Citations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Copy of Criminal Citation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Copy of DR-023&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Copy of Notice to Appear Form&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Copy of License Return&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Copy of Registration Return&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WITNESSES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dustin Michael Mahle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;7867 Twin Ridge DR&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Glen Burnie, MD 21061&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;W/M DOB: 2/04/2001&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;443-848-0483&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jessica Marie Miller&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2847 Baltimore Blvd&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Finksburg, MD 21048&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;W/F DOB: 0/24/1977&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;443-536-5267&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ACCUSED:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kevin Michael Sweeney&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;297 E Main Street&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Westminster, MD 21157&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;W/M DOB: 1/27/1990&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NARRATIVE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On 3/23/2023, I was on duty in full uniform operating marked MSP vehicle G-19.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On 3/23/2023 at approximately 1922 hours, the MSP Westminster Barrack received a 911 call in reference to a possible impaired driver in the Jiffy Mart parking lot located at 3137 Baltimore Blvd Finksburg, MD 21048. The caller advised that there was a male subject passed out behind the wheel of a tan Volkswagen sedan. The caller also stated that the vehicle was in drive and slowly drifting towards Baltimore Blvd.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On 3/23/2023 at 1929 hours, I arrived at the Jiffy Mart and made contact with the complainant who I identified as Dustin Michael Mahle (W/M DOB: 2/04/2001). Mahle stated that he observed the vehicle near Baltimore Blvd and advised that the male subject &amp;ldquo;completely asleep&amp;rdquo; behind the wheel of the vehicle. Mahle informed me that his girlfriend&amp;rsquo;s mother approached the subject and got him out of the vehicle while Mahle moved the vehicle into a parking spot for safety purposes. Mahle stated that they did not administer NARCAN nor any other substance to the male subject. Mahle then pointed out the vehicle and driver in question. I identified it as a tan Volkswagen Jetta bearing MD Registration 3FG3605.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 1 &amp;ndash; VEHICLE IN MOTION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I did not observe the vehicle in motion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 2 &amp;ndash; PERSONAL CONTACT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I made contact with the driver of the vehicle and questioned him about what was happening. The driver advised that he was going to rehab. The driver also advised that he did not recall being approached by the complainants and almost being in the lane of travel. I then asked the driver for his license and identified him as Kevin Michael Sweeney (W/M DOB: 1/27/1990) by his MD Driver&amp;rsquo;s License. When questioned further about going to rehab, Sweeney stated, &amp;ldquo;This time it&amp;rsquo;s for Cocaine but my whole life has been opioids.&amp;rdquo; While speaking with Sweeney, I observed him to be constantly moving and fidgeting with his keys. Sweeney dropped his keys several times while speaking with me. Sweeney advised that he was at the Towson Mall before coming up to the Jiffy Mart in Finksburg. Sweeney stated that he was familiar with the area which is why he came up to Finksburg. Sweeney advised that the rehab facility he was intending on going to was in southern MD. Sweeney stated that he is prescribed Gabapentin for anxiety and that he last took it earlier today. Sweeney then said, &amp;ldquo;It can kinda bring you up, and it beings you down. Makes you tired and sleepy.&amp;rdquo; Sweeney stated that he takes the Gabapentin three times daily and last took a dose approximately one hour prior to this incident. Sweeney advised that he currently felt a little nervous and a little cloudy when asked how he was feeling.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Due to the statements made to me by Mahle and my observations thus far including: Sweeney being unconscious behind a moving vehicle, Sweeney not remembering being approached by the complainants, Sweeney admitting to taking Gabapentin approximately one hour prior to the incident, and Sweeney&amp;rsquo;s constant moving and fidgeting, I suspected Sweeney was impaired by the presence of CDS/Prescription medications in his blood.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PHASE 3- PRE ARREST SCREENING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I am certified by the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) to administer standardized field sobriety tests (SFSTs).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; SFSTs were conducted in the parking lot of the Jiffy Mart. The testing area was level, was hard, and was free of any debris that would inhibit testing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Sweeney was not wearing glasses. Sweeney denied having glasses or contacts. Sweeney advised that he is only prescribed the Gabapentin three times daily. Sweeney denied taking any over the counter vitamins or supplements. Sweeney denied having any physical ailments that would inhibit testing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (4/6):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The first test that was conducted was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) test. I used a pen as the stimulus. The stimulus was passed horizontally at a distance of 12-15 inches and slightly above eye level in front of Sweeney&amp;rsquo;s eyes. I instructed him to follow the stimulus with his eyes only. Sweeney stated that he understood the instructions to keep his head still.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Sweeney&amp;rsquo;s pupils were equal in size and both eyes tracked equally prior to the test. Sweeney displayed a lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes, and distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes. Sweeney&amp;rsquo;s eye lids were droopy during testing where they would partially close while conducting the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Sweeney displayed four of six validated clues of HGN (4/6). I did observe the presence of vertical nystagmus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WALK AND TURN (3/8):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I explained and demonstrated the instructional phase in which Sweeney was instructed to put his right foot in front of his left foot in a heel to toe manner and to keep both arms at his side and to remain in that position until told otherwise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Once Sweeney assumed the instructional position, I explained and demonstrated the walking phase in which Sweeney was instructed to take nine steps in a heel to toe manner while counting out loud, keeping his arms down at his sides, while looking down at his feet the entire time. Upon his ninth step, Sweeney was instructed to turn while keeping his lead foot planted by taking a series of small steps around his lead foot, and to take nine heel to toe steps in the same manner back in the opposite direction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Sweeney was instructed to complete the test. Sweeney used his arms for balance for the entire nine steps of the first set of steps. Sweeney completed the turn unsatisfactorily by swinging his follow foot in the air in order to gain momentum to turn himself around. Sweeney stopped walking after completing the turn portion of the test. Sweeney then used his arms for balance for the entire nine steps of the second set of steps.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Sweeney displayed three of the eight validated clues for the Walk and Turn Test (3/8).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ONE LEG STAND (2/4):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The test was explained and demonstrated prior to Sweeney attempting the test. Sweeney was instructed to lift either foot approximately six inches off of the ground while keeping the base of his foot parallel to the ground, keeping his arms down at his sides, while counting out loud by thousands until told to stop.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Sweeney. began the test by lifting his left foot. Sweeney used his arms for balance during the entirety of the test. Sweeney also swayed during the entirety of the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Sweeney displayed two of four validated clues of the One Leg Stand test (2/4), and in thirty seconds Sweeney only counted to twenty-six.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ADVANCED ROADSIDE IMPAIRED DRIVING ENFORCEMENT (A.R.I.D.E.):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I am certified by the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) to administer Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E) Tests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of Convergence Test&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prior to attempting this test, Sweeney indicated that he did not have any medical problem that would prevent him from performing the test. It was determined that he was not wearing contacts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The test was performed at 1920 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sweeney was first informed that a stimulus would be moved around in a circle and will be moved toward the bridge of his nose. In addition, he was also informed that the stimulus would not touch his nose.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sweeney was then instructed to keep his head steady and follow the stimulus with his eyes only. After stating that he understood the instructions, the test started.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The stimulus was placed 12 to 15 inches from the bridge of his nose and then 2 inches away without touching the nose.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The results of this test showed that the lack of convergence was present on both of his eyes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Modified Romberg Test&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prior to attempting this test, Sweeney indicated he did not have any medical problems that would have prevented him from performing the test. Sweeney was instructed to stand with his feet together and keep his arms at his sides during the test. When instructed to start, he was to tilt his head back slightly and close his eyes. Sweeney was instructed to estimate when 30 seconds had passed and say &amp;ldquo;stop&amp;rdquo; when he thought it had been that long, after which he could open his eyes. He was further instructed to keep his eyes closed during the test. After the test was demonstrated Sweeney stated that he understood the instructions and was asked to begin the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sweeney completed the task and stopped after 50 seconds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finger To Nose Test&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prior to attempting this test, Sweeney indicated he did not have any medical problems that would have prevented him from performing the test. Sweeney was instructed to stand with his feet together during the test and start by placing his arms at his sides. Sweeney was told that he will have to tilt his head back slightly and close his eyes. He will then have to touch the tip of his nose with the index finger (left or right as indicated) and return to start position. He was further instructed to keep his eyes closed during the entire duration of the test. After the test was demonstrated Sweeney stated that he understood the instructions and was asked to begin the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;During the test, Sweeney was asked to touch his nose 6 times in the following order: right, left, right, left, left, right.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The third time, Sweeney missed touching his nose with the finger.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Sweeney was offered a preliminary breath test (Alco Sensor III SN: 00014040). The preliminary breath test indicated a result of 0.00 grams of alcohol. Note: the Alco Sensor&amp;rsquo;s calibration was tested after the stop and found to be within acceptable limits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Based on my training knowledge and experience in the field of DUI/DWI enforcement and the evidence gathered thus far, I determined that Sweeney was impaired. Due to my observations, I placed Sweeney under arrest for driving under the influence of Drugs/CDS at 2007 hours. Sweeney was then transported to the MSP Westminster Barrack. I confirmed that Sweeney was able to read and write English. I read Sweeney a DR-15 Advice of Rights. Sweeney advised that he would agree to submit to the alcohol concentration test at 2058 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Sweeney was then transported to the Westminster City Police Department where Sgt. Ecker # 137 administered the test. The official test results indicated an alcohol concentration of 0.00 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 2126 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; After receiving the results of the breath test, I determined that those results were not consistent with the level of impairment that was observed.&amp;nbsp; I requested that a Drug Recognition Expert (DRE) respond to the Westminster Barrack to perform a Drug Influence Evaluation.&amp;nbsp; TFC White #6932, a certified Drug Recognition Expert, responded to the Westminster Barrack and offered to conduct a 12-Step IACP/NHTSA approved Drug Influence Evaluation of the Sweeney. Sweeney refused to complete the evaluation. I consulted with TFC White as to my observations thus far and he found Sweeney to be impaired, and unable to operate a vehicle safely.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sweeney was issued a DR-15A temporary license and issued the following citations:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;21-902(c1i): Driving vehicle while so far impaired by (drugs/drugs and alcohol) cannot drive safely&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;21-902(d1i): Driving vehicle while impaired by controlled dangerous substance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;21-901.1(b): Negligent Driving&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;21-901.1(a): Reckless Driving&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Sweeney was given a Notice to Appear Form and was released to John Poutre.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Case Closed Via Must Appear Citations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All events occurred in Carroll County, MD.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CASE CLOSED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt; </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6611</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 07:31:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6611</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 10:24:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Meekins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4876</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phelps</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7210</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Iman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6696</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McCarty</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cade</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6579</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Woodworth</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kurt</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6611</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499874</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/23/2023 19:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6611</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:39:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6611</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 00:40:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499874</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/23/2023 19:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6611</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:39:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6611</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 00:41:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499874</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/23/2023 19:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6611</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:39:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6611</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 00:40:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499874</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/23/2023 19:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6611</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:39:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6611</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 00:40:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6611</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:39:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:45</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372407</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sweeney</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/27/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 00:33:27</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sweeney</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/27/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 00:33:27</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>297</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Main</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Westminster</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21157</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5527</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.9871617</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.5667083</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>485</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7828</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6611</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:46:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6611</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:46:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6611</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:46:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6611</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:46:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6611</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:39:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6611</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 00:39:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151213</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6611</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 01:13:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6611</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 01:13:28</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3VWDP7AJ8DM204106</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>VOLK</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>JET</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GLD</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3FG3605</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>