<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-006388</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/18/2023 21:28:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/18/2023 21:28:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/18/2023 21:08:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/18/2023 21:08:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was stopped for expired registration plates and found to be under the influence and in possession of CDS.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 21:28:04</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4425</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/27/2023 11:59:43</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>684764</AddressId>
      <City>MDC136</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 21:28:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 04:16:45</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>684764</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Dogwood</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <StreetSuffixCode>SW</StreetSuffixCode>
         <City>Cumberland</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-78.80534</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.6234</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11654-11711</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/18/2023 21:28:00</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/18/2023 21:28:00</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>52</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/27/2023 04:44:27</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 21:28:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:52:56</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Attachments:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DR-15&lt;br /&gt; MSP-33&lt;br /&gt; Traffic Citations&lt;br /&gt; Criminal Citation #222001030764&lt;br /&gt; Current front mugshot&lt;br /&gt; License photocopy&lt;br /&gt; Registration plate photocopy&lt;br /&gt; Insurance card photocopy&lt;br /&gt; MSP 67&lt;br /&gt; MSP 63 P-342990&lt;br /&gt; Six (6) Digital Images (CDS &amp;amp; Container)&lt;br /&gt; MVA PRINT OUT&lt;br /&gt; Intoximeter Worksheet&lt;br /&gt; Detention log&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The DUI Number for the following incident is 23MSP006388/23-020.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;C-19 is equipped with an in-car camera and was operational at the time of the incident.&lt;br /&gt; TFC T. Michael is issued a body camera (00017189) and was operational at the time of the incident.&lt;br /&gt; C-19 is equipped with an in-car radar system, which was functioning and calibrated per MSP policies and standards.&lt;br /&gt; C-19 is a marked police unit.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Suspect:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Michael James Fletcher, W/M, DOB 01/01/1981&lt;br /&gt; 12507 Wright Avenue&lt;br /&gt; Cumberland, Maryland 21502&lt;br /&gt; 240-572-8357&lt;br /&gt; F432603367002/MD&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Vehicle Information:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 2002 Chevrolet Silverado (gray)&lt;br /&gt; 3EP4116 MD&lt;br /&gt; Expired: 05/07/2021&lt;br /&gt; DMV Insurance Lapse: 09/26/2021&lt;br /&gt; Progressive Insurance Card Expiration: 04/11/2022&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Violation:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On Saturday, February 18, 2023 at approximately 2108 hours, I was on patrol in the area southbound US-220/McMullen Hwy and N Cresap Street in Allegany County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; I observed a gray 2002 Chevrolet Silverado bearing Maryland registration 3EP4116.&amp;nbsp; Upon conducting a registration check of the vehicle, the Maryland State Police &amp;ndash; Cumberland Barrack advised the expiration was 5/7/2021 and had a noted insurance lapse dating 9/26/2021.&amp;nbsp; The Chevrolet Silverado made a left turn onto Dogwood Avenue, right onto Bowling Street and a left onto Olive Avenue.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I activated my emergency equipment and the vehicle pulled to the right shoulder of Olive Avenue.&amp;nbsp; I exited my patrol vehicle, performed a driver side approach, and made contact with the driver of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; The driver was identified by his Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license as Michael James Fletcher, W/M, DOB 01/01/1981.&amp;nbsp; I identified myself; I was audibly and visually recording and my identification number. I advised him for the reason of the traffic stop.&amp;nbsp; While speaking to the driver, I detected the moderate odor of alcohol emanating from his breath and person.&amp;nbsp; I observed his eyes were red, glassy and his speech was soft and slurred.&amp;nbsp; I advised Fletcher that his gas gauge appeared to be near empty and Fletcher advised that he be on his way to the Pit &amp;amp; Go to get gasoline.&amp;nbsp; I was confused as to why he turned off US-220 onto Dogwood Avenue and when asked, Fletcher provided an eluding statement that he was coming from his house on Wright Avenue.&amp;nbsp; I asked Fletcher if he had anything to drink and he advised that he had one &amp;ldquo;Bootlegger&amp;rdquo; approximately 1.5 hours prior.&amp;nbsp; Note that Johny Bootlegger is only available in 6.8 oz. bottles and is 12% alcohol by volume.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I returned to my patrol vehicle to advise the Maryland State Police &amp;ndash; Cumberland Barrack of the driver and that I would have him out on standardized field sobriety testing.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I approached the vehicle and asked Fletcher to exit the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; Prior to exiting, I asked Fletcher if he had a jacket and if he wanted to wear it.&amp;nbsp; Fletcher advised he had one but declined, advising it was not that cold.&amp;nbsp; Once Fletcher was at the rear of the vehicle, I asked him to zip up &amp;ldquo;the fly&amp;rdquo; of his jeans.&amp;nbsp; I proceeded to ask him if he wished to consent to the Standardized Field Sobriety Test and he advised that he would.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I am trained and certified to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. The tests were performed on the paved surface of Olive Avenue.&amp;nbsp; In that area, surface was flat and free from debris. Note that the area was illuminated.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Defendants Attire:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Fletcher was wearing jeans, t-shirt, jacket, and bandana.&amp;nbsp; Fletcher was wearing leather boots at the time of the stop.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Physical injuries:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Fletcher advised that he did not have any physical injuries that would prevent him from walking in a straight line or standing on one leg.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Medication:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Fletcher advised that he is not currently taking any prescription or non-prescription medications.&amp;nbsp; ((After the HGN test, Fletcher advised that he be prescribed and currently taking Suboxone.))&amp;nbsp; Fletcher advised that he administered a dose at 9 o&amp;rsquo;clock.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;CDS: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Search incident to arrest located one prescription bottle on the passenger side floorboard of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; Inside the bottle, was one clear plastic baggie containing five orange oval shaped pills, suspected Alprazolam (Xanax).&amp;nbsp; Upon being asked about the pills, Fletcher advised that he be not prescribed those pills.&amp;nbsp; Fletcher also advised that he does smoke marijuana now and then.&amp;nbsp; Fletcher advised that he is not currently prescribed a medical marijuana card and he last smoked four to five days prior. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eyesight:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Fletcher advised he did not need corrective lenses or contacts to function or operate a motor vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Illnesses: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Fletcher advised that he is diagnosed with Meniere&amp;rsquo;s disease and is prescribed medication for it, but does not take it because he has not suffered effects of the illness in a long time.&amp;nbsp; Fletcher also advised he had Tinnitus.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #1 Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Fletcher stated that he could see the stimulus.&amp;nbsp; I advised Fletcher that I needed to follow the stimulus with his eyes and eyes only.&amp;nbsp; I advised Fletcher that his head was to remain stationary. &amp;nbsp;The stimulus was held 12-15 inches from Fletcher and just above eye level. &amp;nbsp;Fletcher was able to track the stimulus with his eyes only. &amp;nbsp;Fletcher had equal pupil size and tracking ability. Fletcher displayed lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;6 out of 6&lt;br /&gt; Stimulus: Tip of a ballpoint pen&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Prior to the Walk and Turn test, Fletcher requested his jacket and it was provided.&amp;nbsp; It was at this time that Fletcher advised he is prescribed and currently taking Suboxone.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #2: Walk and Turn&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Fletcher was placed in the instructional stage, which was demonstrated to Fletcher as standing with his right foot in front of the left foot, touching heel-to-toe and arms placed at his sides. Fletcher was advised not to deviate from the instructional position, and was advised not to begin the test until told do so.&amp;nbsp; I then proceeded to demonstrate the test by taking three heel to toe steps on line, turn around keeping one foot on line, and return three heel to toe steps.&amp;nbsp; I explained to Fletcher that he would have to take nine heel to toe steps and return taking another nine heel to toe steps. I explained that the three steps I took were for demonstration purposes only.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - While demonstrating the test, Fletcher leaned to the left, causing him to go off balance.&amp;nbsp; Fletcher took one-step to the left in order to maintain balance.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - On the first series of nine steps, Fletcher missed heel to toe and stepped offline on step 7.&amp;nbsp; Fletcher performed a noticeable stop during walking prior to continuing.&amp;nbsp; On step 9, Fletcher again missed heel to toe.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - On the second series of nine steps, Fletcher again stop on step one and asked, &amp;ldquo;Does that count as one&amp;rdquo;.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;4 out of 8&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #3 One Leg Stand&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Fletcher was told to stand with his heels together and arms placed at his sides and instructed not to begin the test until told to do so. The test was explained and demonstrated to Fletcher by explaining that I wanted him to raise one leg, whichever he felt most comfortable with, approximately six inches off the ground, foot pointed out.&amp;nbsp; Fletcher was also instructed to keep both legs straight and to keep his eyes on the elevated foot. While holding that position, count aloud, one thousand and one, one thousand and two, one thousand and three, and so forth until told to stop.&amp;nbsp; Fletcher stated that he understood the instructions and agreed to perform the test. Fletcher raised his right leg and began to count aloud.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - Immediately beginning the test, Fletcher raised his right hand in order to maintain balance for the first 17 seconds of the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - Fletcher began to sway on count 27 and 28 seconds.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - Fletcher lost balance and placed his foot down on 29 seconds prior to the conclusion of the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **Note:&amp;nbsp; Fletcher had only counted to 18 seconds at the time 30 seconds had concluded. **&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;3 out of 4&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At the end of demonstrating each standardized field sobriety test, I asked Fletcher if he understood the test.&amp;nbsp; Fletcher advised that he understood all the tests prior to him performing them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Fletcher if he wished to consent to taking the preliminary breath test.&amp;nbsp; I advised Fletcher in detail that the PBT was a voluntary test and would not be used against him in the court of law; however, it is an additional instrument I use during the course of my duties.&amp;nbsp; I advised Fletcher that he could refuse the test and I would not use his refusal against him.&amp;nbsp; I advised Fletcher that the PBT is used in addition to the results of the SFST&amp;rsquo;s.&amp;nbsp; Fletcher consented to taking the PBT.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PBT results:&amp;nbsp; .08 BAC&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;em&gt;ACTION TAKEN:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Fletcher was placed under arrest on February 18, 2023 at approximately 2128 hours.&amp;nbsp; Search incident to arrest resulted in the discovery of several glass 6.8 oz. bottles of Johny Bootlegger liquor on the front passenger seat.&amp;nbsp; One of the bottle&amp;rsquo;s seal was broken and liquor was noticeably absent.&amp;nbsp; One prescription bottle was located on the passenger side floorboard of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The prescription was addressed to Fletcher for Suboxone.&amp;nbsp; Inside the bottle, I located one clear plastic baggie containing five orange oval shaped pills, suspected Alprazolam (Xanax).&amp;nbsp; Upon being asked about the pills, Fletcher advised that he be not prescribed those pills.&amp;nbsp; Fletcher was transported to the Maryland State Police &amp;quot;C&amp;quot; Barrack, his DR-15 rights were advised, and he accepted the intoximeter test at 2203 hours.&amp;nbsp; At approximately 2210 hours, Fletcher had an alcoholic concentration of .04 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&amp;nbsp; A DR-15A was not issued and his driver&amp;rsquo;s license was not seized.&amp;nbsp; A DR-15, MSP 33, MSP 225 and citations, were issued.&amp;nbsp; Criminal citation #222001030764 was completed and issued.&amp;nbsp; Fletcher was released to the custody of his wife from the Maryland State Police &amp;ndash; Cumberland Barrack.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The CDS was processed at the MSP &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;C&amp;rdquo; Barrack according to the policies and procedures of the Maryland State Police.&amp;nbsp; A MSP 67 and MSP 63 forms were completed and filed.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Based on the above stated facts, I respectfully request this case be closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Allegany County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:43:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/27/2023 03:09:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wilson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ersel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6100</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McCue</LastName>
            <FirstName>Hunter</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6631</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Barry</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495784</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4 3550</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4 3550</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:32:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 04:33:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495784</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:32:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 04:34:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495784</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:32:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 04:34:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495784</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:32:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 04:35:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495784</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:32:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 04:35:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>42</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:20:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:35</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>270801</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Fletcher</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>James</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/01/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/26/2020 19:28:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F432</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Fletcher</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>James</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/01/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F432</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/26/2020 19:28:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12507</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Wright</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Cumberland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21502</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5250</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-78.8070044</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.6244429</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>920</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7604</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/26/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>572</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8357</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:36:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:48</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:36:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:48</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:36:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:48</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:36:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:48</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:36:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:48</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:32:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 04:32:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>44763</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:32:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 04:32:19</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/08/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <DateOfInfo>02/25/2023 04:30:16</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1GCEK14T32Z246548</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2002</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SLV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>PK</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>53L825</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3EP4116</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2021</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>5</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehicleValue>1000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 04:39:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 04:39:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>ONE CLEAR PLASTIC BAGGIE CONTAINING 5 ORANGE OVAL SHAPED PILLS, SUSPECTED ALPRAXOLAM ("XANAX")</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244320</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>O</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>5</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>