<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013483</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/16/2023 03:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/16/2023 03:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/16/2023 03:41:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/16/2023 03:41:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was stopped for a traffic violation and found to be driving under the influence of alcohol.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 03:54:56</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4425</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/04/2023 11:36:08</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>39 MM I68 WB, CUMBERLAND</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>690862</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 03:54:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 00:20:14</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>690862</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>39</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I68 Wb Cumberland</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-78.8312715</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.635242</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/16/2023 03:54:55</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/16/2023 03:54:55</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>52</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/18/2023 03:13:41</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 03:54:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Attachments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DR-15&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; DR-15A&lt;br /&gt; MSP 33&lt;br /&gt; TRAFFIC CITATIONS&lt;br /&gt; DRIVING RECORD/METERS&lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE REGISTRATION/METERS&lt;br /&gt; PHOTOCOPY OF DRIVERS LICENSE/REGISTRATION&lt;br /&gt; FRONT PHOTO OF SUBJECT ON MORNING OF ARREST&lt;br /&gt; DETENTION LOG&lt;br /&gt; INTOXIMETER WORKSHEET&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - The DUI Number for the following incident is 23MSP013483/23-049.&lt;br /&gt; - C-19 is equipped with an in-car camera (outward facing) and was &lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;/strong&gt; operational at the time of the incident.&amp;nbsp; The non-functionality was documented at the beginning of the work shift at approximately 2300 hours on 4/15/2023.&lt;br /&gt; - C-19 is equipped with an in-car (inward facing) camera and was operational at the time of the incident.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; - TFC T. Michael is issued a body camera (00017189) and was operational at the time of the incident.&lt;br /&gt; - C-19 is equipped with an in-car radar system, which was functioning and calibrated per MSP policies and standards.&lt;br /&gt; - C-19 is a marked police unit.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;VIOLATION:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On Saturday, April 16, 2023 at approximately 0341 hours, I was on routine patrol traveling westbound on I-68 in the area east of the 40 mile marker in Allegany County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; I observed a black 2017 Kia Sportage bearing Maryland registration 4ES5710 traveling in lane two.&amp;nbsp; I observed the Kia swaying within lane two, touching the white dotted line separating lane two from lane one and three.&amp;nbsp; The Kia repeated this behavior on three separate occasions as we continued west on I-68.&amp;nbsp; At the top of Haystack Mountain, there is a long left sweeping turn after the I-68 goes from three into two lanes of travel.&amp;nbsp; I observed the Kia while still in lane two, fail to navigate the left sweeping turn by crossing over the solid white line by over half the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s width for approximately 600 feet.&amp;nbsp; I continued to observe the vehicle until there was a safer shoulder to initiate a traffic stop.&amp;nbsp; While continuing to follow the Kia in lane two, I observed the vehicle continue to swaying between the dotted white line and solid white fog line in lane two.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;At the base of Haystack Mountain, prior to exit 40 (Vocke Road) I initiated a traffic stop by activating my emergency lights.&amp;nbsp; The Kia applied brakes and moved to the right shoulder of the roadway west of exit 40.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I conducted a driver side approach and made contact with the driver.&amp;nbsp; I identified myself; I was audibly and visually recording and my identification number. I advised her for the reason of the traffic stop.&amp;nbsp; The driver was identified as Haley Michelle Dawson, W/F, DOB 01/27/1997 by her Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; **Please note that the driver&amp;rsquo;s license that was displayed referenced the driver&amp;rsquo;s maiden name of &lt;strong&gt;DAWSON&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp; Dawson&amp;rsquo;s married name was changed to Young and was cross referenced to be accurate via NCIC/METERS and was verified to come back to the same Soundex as the license that was displayed.&amp;nbsp; The driver advised that she had lost her most recent driver&amp;rsquo;s license, however was using the one displayed because it had not expired.&amp;nbsp; All paperwork contained &lt;strong&gt;DAWSON&lt;/strong&gt;. **&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While speaking to Dawson, I detected the strong odor of alcohol emanating from her breath and person. &amp;nbsp;I observed her eyes were red and glassy.&amp;nbsp; Dawson advised that she and her friend had just left another friend&amp;rsquo;s house and justified the driving behavior because they were discussing personal matters.&amp;nbsp; Upon asking Dawson how much she had to drink, Dawson advised that she had nothing to drink.&amp;nbsp; I returned to my patrol vehicle to advise the Maryland State Police &amp;ndash; Cumberland Barrack of the details of the traffic stop.&amp;nbsp; TFC Williams #7133 advised that he would be in route to back me on the traffic stop.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Dawson to turn the vehicle off (almost out of gas) and exit the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; At the rear of her vehicle, I advised that based on my observations I was asking her to voluntarily submit to the Standardized Field Sobriety Test.&amp;nbsp; Dawson consented to take the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I am trained and certified to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. &amp;nbsp;The tests were performed on the right shoulder of westbound I-68 in the area of Exit 40.&amp;nbsp; The surface of the roadway area was flat and free from debris. Note that the area was illuminated by my patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp; Forward flashing emergency lights were deactivated.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Defendants Attire:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Dawson was wearing jeans and t-shirt.&amp;nbsp; Dawson was wearing sandals at the time of the stop.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Physical injuries:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Dawson advised that she did not have any current physical injuries that would prevent her from walking in a straight line or standing on one line.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Medication:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Dawson advised that she is currently taking a prescription medication for hyperthyroidism and to her knowledge there are no warning labels indicating caution when operating machinery, dizziness or drowsiness.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eyesight:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Dawson advised she did not need corrective lenses or contacts to operate a motor vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Medical Conditions: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Dawson advised that she has hyperthyroidism.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #1 Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Dawson stated that she could see the stimulus.&amp;nbsp; I advised Dawson that I needed her to follow the stimulus with her eyes and eyes only.&amp;nbsp; I advised Dawson that her head was to remain stationary. &amp;nbsp;The stimulus was held 12-15 inches from Dawson and just above eye level.&amp;nbsp; Dawson did have difficulty following the stimulus with her eyes only and had to be reminded twice. &amp;nbsp;Eventually, Dawson was able to track the stimulus with her eyes only. &amp;nbsp;Dawson had equal pupil size and tracking ability.&amp;nbsp; Dawson displayed lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;6 out of 6&lt;br /&gt; Stimulus: Tip of a ball point pen&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #2: Walk and Turn&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Dawson was placed in the instructional stage, which was demonstrated to Dawson as standing with her right foot in front of the left foot, touching heel-to-toe and arms placed at her sides. Dawson was advised not to deviate from the instructional position, and was advised not to begin the test until told do so.&amp;nbsp; Dawson did not understand the position and I had to demonstrate and walk her through the steps.&amp;nbsp; I then proceeded to demonstrate the test by taking three heel to toe steps on line, turn around keeping one foot on line, and return three heel to toe steps.&amp;nbsp; I explained to Dawson that she would have to take nine heel to toe steps and return taking another nine heel to toe steps. I explained that the three steps I took were for demonstration purposes only.&amp;nbsp; Dawson had to keep her right foot offline in order to maintain balance while I demonstrate the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On the first series of nine steps, the following clues were observed.&amp;nbsp; On step two, Dawson stepped offline and missed heel to toe with the left foot.&amp;nbsp; Step four, missed heel to toe/offline.&amp;nbsp; On step eight, Dawson missed heel to toe/offline.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On the first series of nine steps, Dawson only took eight steps.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The turn was completed unsatisfactory by Dawson not keeping the lead foot planted, pivoting off the rear foot while turning.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On the second series of nine steps, the following clues were observed.&amp;nbsp; On step three, Dawson missed heel to toe/offline.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;5 out of 8&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #3 One Leg Stand&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Dawson was told to stand with her heels together and arms placed at her sides and instructed not to begin the test until told to do so. The test was explained and demonstrated to Dawson by explaining that I wanted her to raise one leg, whichever she felt most comfortable with, approximately six inches off the ground, foot pointed out.&amp;nbsp; Dawson was also instructed to keep both legs straight and to keep her eyes on the elevated foot. While holding that position, count aloud, one thousand and one, one thousand and two, one thousand and three, and so forth until told to stop. &amp;nbsp;Dawson stated that she understood the instructions and agreed to perform the test. Dawson raised her left leg and began to count aloud.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Dawson placed her foot down on counts three, eight and twelve.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Dawson noticeably swayed for the entirety of the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;2 out of 4&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; At the end of demonstrating each standardized field sobriety test, I asked Dawson if she understood the test.&amp;nbsp; I did demonstrate the walk and turn test two times based on Dawson advising that she was unclear.&amp;nbsp; Dawson advised that she understood all the tests prior to execution.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Dawson if she wished to consent to taking the preliminary breath test.&amp;nbsp; I advised Dawson in detail that the PBT was a voluntary test and would not be used against her in the court of law; however, it is an additional instrument I use during the course of my duties.&amp;nbsp; I advised Dawson that she could refuse the test and I would not use the refusal against her.&amp;nbsp; I advised Dawson that the PBT is used in addition to the results of the SFST&amp;rsquo;s.&amp;nbsp; Dawson refused the PBT.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;ACTION TAKEN:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Dawson was placed under arrest on April 16, 2023 at approximately 0354 hours.&amp;nbsp; Dawson was transported to the Maryland State Police &amp;quot;C&amp;quot; Barrack, her DR-15 rights were advised, and she accepted the intoximeter test at 0418 hours. At 0430 hours, Dawson&amp;rsquo;s test resulted in a .16 BAC.&amp;nbsp; Based on the results, Dawson&amp;rsquo;s license was seized and a DR-15A was issued.&amp;nbsp; A DR-15, DR-15A and MSP 33, citations, and MSP 225 were issued.&amp;nbsp; Dawson was released to the custody of a sober driver from the Maryland State Police &amp;ndash; Cumberland Barrack.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the above stated facts, I respectfully request this case be closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Allegany County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 01:58:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 03:01:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Barry</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502890</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 03:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 00:33:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 00:35:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502890</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 03:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 00:33:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 00:35:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502890</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 03:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 00:33:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 00:35:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 00:33:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:27</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374489</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dawson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Haley</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/27/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Young</LastName>
               <FirstName>Haley</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/27/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 00:26:15</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>Y520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>M</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dawson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Haley</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/27/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Young</LastName>
               <FirstName>Haley</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/27/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>Y520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 00:26:15</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11910</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Aster</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Cumberland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-78.80896751113437</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.61586083414882</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 00:36:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 00:36:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 00:36:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 00:36:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 00:33:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 00:33:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152043</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 00:33:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 00:33:32</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>KNDPM3AC5H7299288</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4ES5710</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>