<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-001959</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/17/2023 02:30:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/17/2023 02:30:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/17/2023 02:13:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/17/2023 02:13:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>01/17/2023 04:00:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>Traffic stop / DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 02:30:07</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/15/2023 17:35:52</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>10303 BALTIMORE,BELTSVILLE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>680737</AddressId>
      <City>MDC132</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 02:30:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/17/2023 20:53:34</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>680737</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>10303</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Baltimore Beltsville</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.9232222166667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0237726666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/17/2023 02:30:06</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/17/2023 02:30:06</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/22/2023 14:17:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 02:30:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 14:17:49</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;MSP marked vehicle Q-17 is not equipped with a mobile recording device, but is equipped with a body-worn camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUI #&lt;/strong&gt; 23-005&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defendant&lt;/strong&gt;: Dennis Maurice Robinson&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date of Birth&lt;/strong&gt;: 08/05/1957&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date of Arrest&lt;/strong&gt;: 01/17/2023&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time of Arrest&lt;/strong&gt;: 0227 hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;District of Columbia Driver&amp;rsquo;s License&lt;/strong&gt;: 2159703&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Training Certificates&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:56px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Baltimore County Police and Maryland State Police.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;li style="margin-left:56px; margin-bottom:11px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:list .5in"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;NHSTA certified to conduct field sobriety tests (SFST)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Vehicle in Motion (Phase 1)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On 01/17/2023 at approximately 0213 hours, I, Trooper Jones #7445 of the Maryland State Police &amp;ndash; College Park Barrack was on duty and conducting traffic enforcement at the intersection of Rt. 1 and Ikea Way, College Park, Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County, MD 20740. At this intersection, there is a &amp;ldquo;No Turn On Red&amp;rdquo; sign at the traffic light once vehicles exit from north bound I-495 to north bound Rt. 1. During the time I was conducting the traffic enforcement, I observed a silver, 2007 Nissan Altima bearing District of Columbia registration, FX5645 exit from I-495 and fail to stop at the red light to turn onto north bound Rt. 1. I observed the Nissan then make the right turn onto Rt. 1 and begin heading north. I then activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the vehicle. As I was behind the vehicle with my emergency equipment on, I observed the Nissan for approximately 5-10 seconds swerving left and right from lane 2 which it was in originally, to lane 1 in a jerking motion. The vehicle then swerved back into lane 2 of Rt. 1 and was driving at a very slow rate while now weaving in and out of lane 2 and the right shoulder, ultimately coming to a stop in lane 2 of Rt. 1 just prior to South Dr. It is noted, the vehicle had more than enough room to the right where the driver could have pulled over.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Personal Contact (Phase 2)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I then exited my patrol car and approached the vehicle on the right passengers side. Upon walking up to the vehicle, I could see the male driver moving around so I decided to stand back at the &amp;ldquo;B&amp;rdquo; pillar of the vehicle and watched the driver&amp;rsquo;s actions for a few seconds since he did not know I was at his window. I then took a step forward and was standing at the center of the passenger door which the male driver still did not notice me doing. After approximately 40 seconds of standing at the window, I acknowledged the driver and began introducing myself and explaining why he was being pulled over. Prior to even getting my name out, the male quickly handed me his registration as if he was in a rush. I asked the male if he knew why he was being pulled over, and he began listing different traffic violations which were not the actual reason for the traffic stop. I advised the male he ran the red light coming off I-495 which he stated he did not realize he did. While I was standing at the window of the Nissan, I immediately detected a strong odor of alcoholic beverages emanating from within the vehicle. I asked the male how much he had to drink that evening, and he replied &amp;ldquo;I aint drinking nothing man, I&amp;rsquo;m trying to get to work.&amp;rdquo; I then asked the male why he parked his vehicle in the center of Rt.1 and not the shoulder. He did not have an answer which prompted me to ask again if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages that night. The male again stated he did not have anything to drink at which time I asked if he would then feel confident in stepping out of his vehicle and performing field sobriety tests. The male immediately responded stating, &amp;ldquo;I ain&amp;rsquo;t gonna do all that&amp;rdquo;. The male then attempted to explain how he had not consumed any alcoholic beverages that night. The male advised me he was not drinking anything at the moment and I stated to him that I did not say he was drinking at the moment, I asked how much he had consumed that night. The male driver replied &amp;ldquo;really nothing man&amp;rdquo;. I again asked the male if he would feel confident in performing field sobriety tests, and he replied &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not doing all that&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At that time, I called for Tpr. Webb #7303 to respond to my location while I continued speaking with the male. He then provided me with his District of Columbia Drivers License identifying himself as Dennis Maurice Robinson (B/M, DOB: 08/05/1957). Throughout the short period of time I was speaking with Robinson, not only did I detect the strong odor of alcoholic beverages from within the vehicle, but his speech was also slurred, eyes were blood shot and watery, and I observed there to be an empty 750 ML bottle of Ready to Drink Margarita Wine Cocktail sitting on the front passenger seat. I then asked Robinson for a final time if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages that night, and he replied again, no. Due to my training, knowledge, and experience I have received from the Baltimore County Police Training Academy, Cecil County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office, and the Maryland State Police I knew Robinson was not telling the truth based on the observations made thus far and asked him again if he would be willing to step out and perform the field sobriety tests? Robinson then became agitated, turned off his vehicle, and stated he was going to step out.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Robinson exited his vehicle and stood in front of it with Tpr. Webb and then began to yell and use curse words towards me. I informed Robinson I was not going to be cursed at and asked if he would like to take the field sobriety tests or not. Robinson; still agitated, continued to avoid the question by attempting to justify himself and why he shouldn&amp;#39;t have been pulled over. When asked if Robinson remembered why he was pulled over he stated he did not. I then explained the reason for the stop again while Robinson continued to plead his case and avoid the question of performing field sobriety tests. At one point during Robinson&amp;#39;s explanations, he stated &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m a marine like you guys. You&amp;rsquo;re not a marine, your a Navy SEAL. Whatever you wanna do.&amp;rdquo; Robinson continued making numerous comments like these throughout the night that did not make sense as well as being argumentative when asked if he would like to take the field sobriety tests while on the traffic stop.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ARREST:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;After numerous attempts to get an answer from Robinson, I advised him he needed to make a decision. At that time, Robinson yelled &amp;ldquo;Lock me up then if that&amp;#39;s what you wanna do&amp;rdquo;. At approximately 0227 hours, I advised Robinson to turn around and placed him under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. &lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Based on my training, knowledge, and experience, Robinson&amp;rsquo;s eyes being bloodshot, glassy, watery, the strong odor of alcoholic beverages coming from within the vehicle as well as off Robinson&amp;rsquo;s breath and person, the empty bottle of alcohol in the front seat of his vehicle, and Robinson being unable to make complete sentences, I believe&amp;nbsp;that he was driving under the influence of alcohol. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Once Robinson was placed in handcuffs, I proceeded to conduct a search incident to arrest of his person. During this time, Robinson continued to be argumentative and uncooperative. At one point, I went to remove a pocket knife from his right pants pocket when Robinson yelled that it was his and attempted to push up against me with his body. Robinson was then placed up against my patrol car by Tpr. Webb and myself until he calmed down. I explained to Robinson that he was in handcuffs and nothing was going to happen. Robinson continued to argue while I completed the search of his person. After the search was completed, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I then placed Robinson in my patrol car and transported him to the barrack&lt;br /&gt; . &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Upon arrival to the barrack, &lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;a secondary search was completed by Corporal Dunlap #6273 with no contraband located. Robinson was still extremely upset and argumentative while speaking with Cpl. Dunlap.&amp;nbsp;At approximately 0250&amp;nbsp;hours, I provided Robinson with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and then played the online recording of the form for Robinson as well. At the completion of the DR-15 being read, I asked Robinson if he had any questions. Robinson was still attempting to argue and ask irrelevant questions. It took several times of Robinson being asked before he finally advised that he would submit breath samples for the intoximeter test, but would not sign the form indicating the same. At approximately 0302 hours, I signed the DR-15 indicating that Robinson refused to sign and checked the box indicating he did wish to submit breath samples based on the verbal confirmation he made. During the time of trying to get an answer from Robinson, he was not only argumentative and uncooperative with myself, but for Cpl. Dunlap as well.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Robinson was then walked into the testing area with Cpl. Dunlap where he was given the opportunity to submit to the test. Cpl. Dunlap accurately and properly explained the intoximeter breath test to Robinson. Robinson was asked if he understood the instructions on how to blow into the machine, and he advised he did. Robinson then failed to provide adequate breath samples on all three attempts that the test allows and was noted as a refusal on all documents.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;INTOXIMETER RESULT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;***REFUSAL ***&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Robinson was issued a series of traffic citations released.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;All events occurred in Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 19:06:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/19/2023 04:32:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Webb</LastName>
            <FirstName>Noah</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7303</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dunlap</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6273</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jones</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7445</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491342</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/17/2023 02:13:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 18:46:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/17/2023 18:46:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>65</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 19:01:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>265274</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Robinson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dennis</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Maurice</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/05/1957 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.78841284E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>03/16/2020 04:42:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R152</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Robinson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dennis</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Maurice</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/05/1957 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.78841284E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>R152</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/16/2020 04:42:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>154</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Chesapeake</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>SW</StreetSuffixCode>
               <City>Washington</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20032</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1321</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.0107224</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.8284481</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>621</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3997</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/16/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 19:01:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:39</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 19:01:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:39</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 19:01:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:39</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 18:46:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/17/2023 18:46:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>108810</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7445</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/17/2023 19:05:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7445</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/17/2023 19:05:03</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/16/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1N4AL21E07C124365</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2007</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ALT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>DC</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>FX5645</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2020</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>