<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008260</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/06/2023 02:55:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/06/2023 02:55:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/06/2023 01:49:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/06/2023 01:49:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI, Traffic Stop</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 02:56:00</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/04/2023 21:51:25</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>25 MM CAPITAL BELTWAY NB, COLLEGE PARK</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>686418</AddressId>
      <City>MDC132</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 02:56:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 09:09:11</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>686418</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>25</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm Capital Beltway Nb College</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PARK</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.917948</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0186954166667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/06/2023 02:55:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/06/2023 02:55:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/16/2023 07:47:27</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/06/2023 02:56:00</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Q-25 IS EQUIPPED WITH AN IN CAR CAMERA&lt;br /&gt; THE EVENT WAS AUDIBLY AND VISUALLY RECORDED&lt;br /&gt; Defendant: &amp;nbsp;Matute Carrillo, Obed&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 09/19/1987&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 0252 hours&lt;br /&gt; DUI#: 23-053&lt;br /&gt; TRAINING/CERTIFICATES&lt;br /&gt; Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;br /&gt; On March 6th, 2023, at approximately 0255 hours, I, Trooper Fleming #7439 and Trooper Stallings #7589 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, were on routine uniform patrol in the area of the outer loop of 495 south of Baltimore Avenue, College Park, Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland. I was in full uniform operating a marked patrol vehicle Q-25. The incident was audibly and visually recorded on my body worn camera and Q-25&amp;rsquo;s in-car camera.&lt;br /&gt; I observed a brown Ford F150 bearing the Maryland temporary registration &amp;ldquo;8EL9069&amp;rdquo; swerving and jerking within lane two in the distance. I moved to lane two approximately two car lengths behind the vehicle to better observe the driver&amp;rsquo;s actions. The vehicle was weaving within the lane and the left side wheels of the vehicle fully weaved over the white dotted line into lane one. The vehicle then increased his speed from approximately 60 MPH to 75 MPH. Once again, the left side wheels of the vehicle fully weaved over the white dotted line into lane one. The vehicle then slowly changed lanes from lane two to lane three without the use of its right turn signal. I moved to lane three approximately two car lengths behind the vehicle to better observe the driver&amp;rsquo;s actions. The vehicle then activated its left turn signal for approximately three seconds for no apparent reason. The vehicle then drifted towards the left side of lane three. The left side wheels of the vehicle touched the white dotted line separating lanes two and three for approximately five seconds.&lt;br /&gt; I then activated my emergency lights to signal the vehicle to the shoulder. The barrack was notified of my location and the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s information. The left side wheels of the vehicle fully weaved over the white dotted line into lane two. The vehicle weaved fully back into lane three and then slowly changed lanes from lane three to lane two. The left side wheels of the vehicle fully weaved over the white dotted line into lane one on two separate occasions. I attempted to signal the vehicle to the left shoulder; the vehicle instead pulled to the right shoulder. The vehicle took approximately 1 minute 20 seconds to pull over from the time I activated my emergency lights. The vehicle came to a stop on the right shoulder of the outer loop of 495 at the Triple Bridges, College Park, Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland. I exited my patrol vehicle to make contact with the driver.&lt;br /&gt; PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; The driver was identified as Matute Carrillo, Obed (5/M, DOB: 09/19/1987) via his Maryland Driver&amp;rsquo;s License. I approached the passenger&amp;rsquo;s side of the vehicle in order to make contact with the driver. Upon making contact with the driver, I observed that his eyes were bloodshot and glassy. There was a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from within the vehicle. Matute Carrillo&amp;rsquo;s speech and movements were slow and lethargic. I asked the driver and passengers where they were driving from and where they were driving to; they stated that they were driving from a passenger&amp;rsquo;s brother&amp;rsquo;s residence in Lanham to a passenger&amp;rsquo;s residences in Hyattsville.&lt;br /&gt; I requested Spanish speaking officer in order to perform field sobriety. Corporal Cervantes #3891 of Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County Police arrived on scene. Matute Carrillo was asked to exit the vehicle. When Matute Carrillo opened the driver&amp;rsquo;s side door, I observed an empty glass Heineken bottle located in the driver&amp;rsquo;s side door panel.&lt;br /&gt; PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;br /&gt; Corporal Cervantes #3891 assisted in translating the Standard Field Sobriety Tests.&lt;br /&gt; I asked Matute Carrillo to perform field sobriety in order to rule out alcohol as a contributing factor to his swerving. I asked Matute Carrillo where he was coming from, Matute Carrillo stated that he was coming from dropping some friends off after playing soccer. I asked Matute Carrillo if he had anything to drink, Matute Carrillo stated that he hadn&amp;rsquo;t had alcohol in a while. I asked when was the last time Matute Carillo had something to drink. Matute Carrillo stated that had something to drink at 1700 hours on March 5th, 2023.&lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed on right shoulder of the outer loop of 495 at the Triple Bridges, College Park, Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland. The shoulder area was level and dry. Matute Carrillo did not display any visible injuries. Matute Carrillo limped with his left leg.&lt;br /&gt; Medication &amp;ndash; Matute Carrillo informed me that he does not take any kind of medication.&lt;br /&gt; Physical Injuries &amp;ndash; Matute Carrillo informed me that he had an injury to his left knee.&lt;br /&gt; Glasses or Contacts &amp;ndash; Matute Carrillo stated he did not wear glasses or contacts.&lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 Clues Observed)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained. The tip of a pen was used as the test&amp;rsquo;s stimulus. The stimulus was held approximately 12-15 inches from Matute Carrillo&amp;rsquo;s eye, slightly above eye level. &amp;nbsp;Matute Carrillo was instructed to look straight ahead, keep his head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. &amp;nbsp;Matute Carrillo&amp;rsquo;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Before beginning the test, I asked Matute Carrillo if he understood my instructions, to which he confirmed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; Additional Observations &amp;ndash; Resting gaze nystagmus was not present. Vertical gaze nystagmus was present. I had to remind Matute Carrillo to continue to follow the stimulus with eyes on four separate occasions. I had to remind Bunch to follow the stimulus with only his eyes and to not move his head on one occasions.&lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN TEST (4/8 Clues Observed)&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. Matute Carrillo was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Matute Carrillo was then instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and remain in that position until told to begin. Matute Carrillo was advised to take nine steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line, and take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Matute Carrillo was instructed to complete the second series of nine steps in the same heel to toe fashion. &amp;nbsp;Matute Carrillo was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, to count every step out loud, and once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Matute Carrillo if he understood, and he confirmed that he did.&lt;br /&gt; Instructional Phase &amp;ndash;&lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (First Nine Steps) &amp;ndash;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Misses Heel-Toe &amp;ndash; On steps eight through ten of his first nine steps, Matute Carrillo missed his heel to toe by more than one half inch.&lt;br /&gt; Steps Off Line &amp;ndash; On steps eight through ten of his first nine steps, Matute Carrillo stepped off line by more than one half inch.&lt;br /&gt; Actual Number of Steps &amp;ndash; Matute Carrillo stepped ten times and counted the first nine steps out loud.&lt;br /&gt; Improper Turn &amp;ndash; Matute Carrillo turned counter clockwise when his left foot was behind his right foot which resulted in an unnatural turn. Matute Carrillo pivoted with both feet instead of stepping around with his rear foot.&lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (Second Nine Steps)&lt;br /&gt; Misses Heel-Toe &amp;ndash; On steps three through nine of his second nine steps, Matute Carrillo missed his heel to toe by more than one half inch.&lt;br /&gt; ONE-LEG STAND TEST (3/4 Clues Observed)&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. &amp;nbsp;Matute Carrillo was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch the raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two, etc.), and not put his foot down until the end of the test. I asked Matute Carrillo if he understood the test, and he confirmed.&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 1-10&lt;br /&gt; Raises Arms &amp;ndash; Matute Carrillo would keep his right arm raised greater than six inches from his body throughout the first ten seconds.&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20&lt;br /&gt; Puts foot down &amp;ndash; Matute Carrillo lowered his foot to the ground, touching the ground with his entire foot once during this period.&lt;br /&gt; Raises Arms &amp;ndash; Matute Carrillo would raise his arms greater than six inches from his body on one occasion during the second ten seconds.&lt;br /&gt; Hopping &amp;ndash; Matute Carrillo would hop on his right foot in attempt to maintain his balance during the second ten seconds.&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30&lt;br /&gt; Additional Observations &amp;ndash; Matute Carrillo did not start counting until the third ten seconds.&lt;br /&gt; ARREST&lt;br /&gt; Based on the totality of circumstances, I concluded Matute Carrillo was driving a motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol.&lt;br /&gt; Matute Carrillo&amp;rsquo;s failure to maintain designated lane directions.&lt;br /&gt; Matute Carrillo took approximately 1 minute 20 seconds to pull over from the time I activated my emergency lights&lt;br /&gt; The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Matute Carrillo&amp;rsquo;s breath and person.&lt;br /&gt; Matute Carrillo&amp;rsquo;s eyes were bloodshot and glassy.&lt;br /&gt; Matute Carrillo&amp;rsquo;s slow movement and speech.&lt;br /&gt; An open alcoholic beverage was inside the vehicle and within arm&amp;rsquo;s reach of the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat.&lt;br /&gt; Matute Carrillo was dropping friends off after playing soccer at approximately 0200 hours.&lt;br /&gt; Clues during Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (6/6), WAT (4/8), OLS (3/4)&lt;br /&gt; On March 6th, 2023 at approximately 0252 hours, I placed Matute Carrillo under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack. A search incident to arrest of Matute Carrillo&amp;rsquo;s person was conducted. The search of Matute Carrillo&amp;rsquo;s person was negative. I transported Matute Carrillo to the College Park Barrack.&lt;br /&gt; Matute Carrillo was played the DR-15 Advice of Rights Spanish recording provided by MVA. &amp;nbsp;Matute Carrillo was provided with a copy of the DR-15 to read along as well. At approximately 0318 hours, Matute Carrillo agreed to take an alcohol concentration test.&lt;br /&gt; 20 MINUTE OBSERVATION&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Matute Carrillo beginning with his arrest. A preliminary search of Matute Carrillo was conducted on scene and it was revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. I observed Matute Carrillo from the time of arrest until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by Tpr. Peris #7511 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Matute Carrillo had a result of .16 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 0404 hours.&lt;br /&gt; Intoximeter Result: .16 BrAC&lt;br /&gt; Matute Carrillo&amp;rsquo;s vehicle was left on the right shoulder of the outer loop of 495 at the Triple Bridges, College Park, Prince George&amp;#39;s County. Matute Carrillo&amp;rsquo;s vehicle was entered in CAD&amp;rsquo;s unattended/disabled vehicle log and an MSP Form 23A was attached to the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; I processed Matute Carrillo and released him to Hernandez Nicolas, Marvin N (5/M, DOB: 07/18/1985).&lt;br /&gt; Matute Carrillo was issued the following citations.&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-902(a1i) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-902(a1ii) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL PER SE&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-902(b1i) DRIVING VEH. WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-901.1(a) RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OF PERSONS AND PROPERTY&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-901.1(b) NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON&lt;br /&gt; TA - 21-201(a1) DRIVER FAILURE TO OBEY PROPERLY PLACED TRAFFIC CONTROL DEVICE INSTRUCTIONS&lt;br /&gt; The defendant was issued copies of the following documents:&lt;br /&gt; -Citations (listed above)&lt;br /&gt; -DR-15 Advice of Rights&lt;br /&gt; -DR-15a Order of Suspension&lt;br /&gt; -MSP 33 Notification to Defendant of Result of Test for Alcohol Concentration&lt;br /&gt; All documents were forwarded to the Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County, State Attorney Office.&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 09:47:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 09:47:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stallings</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7589</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Aaron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fleming</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sierra</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7439</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497659</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/06/2023 01:49:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:10:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 09:10:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:12:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:34</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370848</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Matute Carrillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Obed</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/19/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/06/2023 04:57:22</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M332</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>O130</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Matute Carrillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Obed</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/19/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M332</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>O130</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/06/2023 04:57:22</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11439</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Cherry Hill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>304</SubNumber>
               <City>Beltsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20705</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.949769</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.044639</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>481</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4056</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:13:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:13:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:13:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:13:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:10:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 09:10:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150569</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 09:14:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 09:14:38</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FTFW1ET8BFB30173</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2011</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>F15</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BRO</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8EL9068</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>12</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>