<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-007018</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/24/2023 00:33:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/24/2023 00:33:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/24/2023 00:06:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/24/2023 00:06:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop leads to DUI arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 00:33:21</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5364</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 11:02:39</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>S 495 TO E 190 RAMP / RIVER RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>685317</AddressId>
      <City>MDC275</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 00:33:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 17:08:22</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>685317</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>I-495</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Potomac</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20854</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-77.1543116</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0050573</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/24/2023 00:33:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/24/2023 00:33:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/13/2023 22:02:23</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 00:33:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:10</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;N-36 is equipped with a mobile recording device, and body worn camera operational.&lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Rene David Alvarez Castillo 5/M&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 10/24/1991&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 02/24/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 0033 hours&lt;br /&gt; DUI #: 23-053&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:18px"&gt;CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;* Successfully completed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;six month Maryland State Police Academy (6/2020).&lt;br /&gt; *Trained and certified in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; * Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (4/2022).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:18px"&gt;AUDIO VISUAL RECORDING:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;MSP marked patrol vehicle N-36 is equipped with audio visual recording equipment. Body worn camera also equipped.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:18px"&gt;VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On February 24, 2023 at approximately 0003 hours I, Trooper First Class Emerick #6888, was sitting stationary on the right shoulder of southbound I-270 south of Montrose Road. I observed a green Subaru Forester that had an inoperative driver&amp;#39;s side tail lamp. I pulled out and caught up to the Subaru on southbound I-270 prior to the Split. I observed the Subaru to be bearing Virginia registration &amp;quot;TZU3102&amp;quot;. The Subaru was traveling in lane 2 approaching Democracy Boulevard, the Subaru then drifted from lane 2 over the solid white line into the HOV lane by more than one tire width. The Subaru then drifted back into lane 2. The Subaru then changed lanes to lane 3. As the Subaru was negotiating a curve to the right the vehicle went onto the right shoulder by more than half a car, and drifted back into lane 3. Once out of the turn and in a straight, the Subaru again drifted from lane 3 over the solid white fog line, and onto the shoulder by approximately on quarter of a car width and then back into lane 3. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the Subaru on the Outer Loop of I-495 prior to River Road. Once I activated my emergency equipment the Subaru made an abrupt lane change from lane 3, across lane 4 and lane 5 to the right shoulder.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:18px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;I made contact with the driver of the Subaru Forester, who was the sole occupant of the vehicle. I advised the driver my name, ID number, agency I work for, that the stop was being audibly and visual recorded, and the reasons for the stop (left tail lamp inoperative, left brake light inoperative, improperly showing white light to the rear, and failing to maintain his lane). I asked the driver if there was any reason that he was all over the road, and he stated that there was no reason for his vehicle to be all over the road, but he was unaware the light was out. I immediately observed the driver&amp;#39;s eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the driver&amp;#39;s breath as he spoke to me. I then requested his driver&amp;#39;s license and vehicle registration, at this time he advised me that he does not have a license.&amp;nbsp; I asked the driver where he was coming from, and he stated &amp;quot;my cousins house, I am going to my house in Virginia.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; The driver advised me that he did not currently have the registration card for the vehicle either. The driver was identified by his El Salvador ID card as Rene David Alvarez Castillo (5/M DOB 08/08/1985).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I then returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct an MVA check. The check revealed that Alvarez Castillo did not have a valid license in the United States.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Another unit arrived on scene for Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. I deactivated my patrol vehicles forward facing emergency lights.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I asked Alvarez Castillo to step to the front of his vehicle, as&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo went to step out of his vehicle it was not in park.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo&amp;#39;s vehicle then began to go forward. Alvarez Castillo then placed his car in park and stepped to the front of his vehicle. I then advised him that I wanted him to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, to which he consented.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:18px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of the Outer Loop I-495 prior to River Road. The surface was dry and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear, lighting conditions were dark, there were some streetlights in the area. I observed Alvarez Castillo to be in decent physical condition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;I asked&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Glasses or Contacts - Neither.&lt;br /&gt; Medication - None.&lt;br /&gt; Medical Conditions - None.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Alvarez Castillo how much alcohol he had to drink. He said that he had about 5 beers, approximately 15 minutes ago.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:18px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my index finger was used as the stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo&amp;#39;s eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo&amp;#39;s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking and no resting nystagmus was observed.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; While performing HGN&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;Alvarez Castillo was swaying.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:18px"&gt;WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Prior to&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo was instructed to place his left foot on an imaginary line out in front of him with his right foot directly in front and touching heel to toe.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in that position until told to begin.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo was advised to take a series of nine (9) steps in a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo was instructed to keep his hands down at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count each step out loud.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo was explained and demonstrated on the ninth step to keep his lead foot planted on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to the left to turn completely around.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo was instructed that once the test began he was to keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, count each step out loud, and to not stop until the test is complete.&lt;br /&gt; Alvarez Castillo was extremely argumentative during the instructional phase.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo elected to take his sandles off and do the test in just ankle socks. As&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo kept arguing, I asked if he wanted to complete the test or not, and he stated &amp;quot;I mean I&amp;#39;ll do the test, it&amp;#39;s okay.&amp;nbsp; I know what is going to happen at the end.&amp;quot; I then gave&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo the directions again, and demonstrated the steps and turn again.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Broke from starting position.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking stage (1st Nine):&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Stepped off-line on step 1.&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Stopped walking on steps 1, and 9.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;Turn:&lt;br /&gt; Completed unsatisfactorily.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Stepped off-line on steps 2, 7.&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Stopped walking on step 4.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:18px"&gt;ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Prior to Alvarez Castillo performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, and so on) and to continue the test until told to stop.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo elected to raise his left foot.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage:&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 0-10:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 11-20:&lt;br /&gt; 1.) Left foot hit the ground.&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Used arms for balance.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:18px"&gt;Preliminary Breath Test (PBT):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;While on scene,&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo submitted to a preliminary breath test. The results of the PBT were .16 BrAC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:18px"&gt;ARREST:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;Based on the following, I had reason to believe&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol.&lt;br /&gt; * Driving behaviors.&lt;br /&gt; * Bloodshot and glassy eyes.&lt;br /&gt; * Odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath.&lt;br /&gt; * Admission of drinking.&lt;br /&gt; * Clues during SFST&amp;#39;s.&lt;br /&gt; * .16 BrAC PBT result.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Alvarez Castillo was placed under arrest at approximately 0033 hours. A preliminary search of&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo was conducted on scene. Upon arrival at the barrack, I provided&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights in Spanish (at his request to be in Spanish).&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo was also played the MVA recording of the DR-15 Advice of Rights in Spanish.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo elected to submit to an evidentiary breath test. The results of the Intoximeter test were .15 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.&amp;nbsp;Alvarez Castillo was charged with DUI and released to his wife.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 19:02:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 21:37:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Capezuto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Travis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6694</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>John</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7358</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Emerick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6888</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Butler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andre</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0452</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Emerick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6888</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Emerick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6888</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496415</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16615</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/24/2023 00:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16615</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 17:06:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 17:17:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496415</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15408</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/24/2023 00:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15408</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 17:06:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 17:17:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496415</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/24/2023 00:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 17:06:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 17:18:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496415</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/24/2023 00:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 17:06:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 17:19:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496415</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/24/2023 00:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 17:06:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 18:54:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496415</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/24/2023 00:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 17:06:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 17:14:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496415</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/24/2023 00:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 17:06:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 17:15:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496415</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/24/2023 00:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 17:06:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 17:16:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 17:06:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369983</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Alvarez Castillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Rene</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>David</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/24/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 04:23:25</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Alvarez Castillo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Rene</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>David</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/24/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>A416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 04:23:25</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>834</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Frederick</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>302</SubNumber>
               <City>Arlington</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>22204</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.116943</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.856274</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>559</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7100</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 18:58:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 18:58:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 18:58:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 18:58:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 17:06:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 17:06:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240010642</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName> State Of Maryland</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 18:55:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 18:55:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150187</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 17:06:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 17:06:42</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JF1SF6359YH703956</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2000</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>SUBA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FOR</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRN</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>TZU3102</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>11</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>