<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-007288</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/26/2023 02:20:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/26/2023 02:20:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/26/2023 01:28:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/26/2023 01:28:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Assist Other agency, CCSO</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/26/2023 02:20:16</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5562</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/26/2023 23:46:33</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>LIBERTY RD/ OKLAHOMA RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>538350</AddressId>
      <City>MDC236</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/26/2023 02:20:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/26/2023 03:03:07</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>538350</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Liberty</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Sykesville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.932421</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.39897</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1702-1729 LIBERTY RD / 6341-6351 OKLAHOMA RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1702-1716 LIBERTY RD / 6341-6351 OKLAHOMA RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1730-1733 LIBERTY RD / 6341-6351 OKLAHOMA RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1700-1799 LIBERTY RD / 0-0 OKLAHOMA RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/26/2023 02:20:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/26/2023 02:20:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>02/26/2023 23:46:33</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/26/2023 02:20:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5562</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/26/2023 23:46:33</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was captured on BWC with functioning audio and video.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; THIS REPORT WAS TAKEN IN REFERENCE TO CCSO REPORT 23000863&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; A MSP Blueteam use of force was also completed, and submitted for this incident.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Narrative:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On February 26, 2023, at approximately 0128 hours, I responded to Maryland Route 26 at Oklahoma Road to assist Carroll County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Deputy Sherman on a traffic stop.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Upon arrival, Deputy Sherman was conducting the Standardized Field Sobriety test (SFSTs) on the suspect, Richard Kesick Brunson (B/M 10/31/1991). As Brunson spoke, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy, and his speech to be slurred. Brunson was cooperative for the duration of the SFSTs. As Deputy Sherman placed Brunson under arrest, and secured him in handcuffs, Brunson began to cry and repeatedly apologize. Brunson was led to Deputy Sherman&amp;#39;s patrol vehicle, where he continuously cried and said he did not want to be in trouble, at this time Brunson began to tense his entire body, and lean backwards, so that he had to be physically supported so he could remain standing, and moan out loud. Brunson advised he did not physically have control over this happening Brunson was repeatedly advised to relax, and refrain from tensing up. Brunson was advised to sit in the front seat of Deputy Sherman&amp;#39;s patrol vehicle, Brunson sat down, and repeatedly ignored verbal commands to put his feet in the vehicle. Brunson then attempted to stand up, and began to flail his entire body out of the vehicle. Deputy Sherman, and I placed Brunson in a seated position on the ground outside the patrol vehicle. Brunson continued to Tense his entire body, and moan out loud. Brunson repeatedly kicked his feet, nearly striking Deputy Sherman and I. Despite several attempts, and verbal commands, Brunson refused to sit up, or stand up, and comply. Brunson repeatedly tensed and flailed his entire body while screaming. Brunson repeatedly stated he did not do anything wrong. Brunson requested an ambulance. I requested EMS start to our location. Due to Brunson repeatedly flailing and kicking his legs, after ignoring verbal commands to stop doing so, Deputy Sherman placed leg restraints on Brunson. Deputy Sherman and I attempted to keep Brunson maintained in the recovery position, repeatedly giving verbal commands to stop tensing, and flailing his body. At one point, Brunson began to strike the back of his head against the ground. Deputy Sherman was able to stabilize, and control Brunson&amp;#39;s head. Brunson continued to tense his entire body, scream, and advise he was stressed, and could not control what he was doing. Brunson repeatedly attempted to strike me with his legs, and grab my hands. During the course of the incident, no strikes were administered to Brunson whatsoever. I utilized muscling techniques in order to maintain control of Brunson. EMS arrived, along with other units, and Brunson was able to be secured to a stretcher, and transported to Carroll Hospital Center.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/26/2023 03:04:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6783</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/26/2023 04:55:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Horner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jonathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5895</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Karas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5562</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derek</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6783</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>