<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-028577</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/13/2023 02:51:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/13/2023 02:51:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/12/2023 22:24:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/12/2023 22:24:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Warrant arrest/ subject punched cell wall.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 02:51:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4794</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 09:57:14</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WFC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>45562</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 02:51:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 03:35:50</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>45562</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>12848</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21842</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.102992</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.335413</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WEST OCEAN CITY PARK AND RIDE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>West Ocean City Park &amp; Ride</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/13/2023 02:51:40</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/13/2023 02:51:40</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/19/2023 09:57:13</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 02:51:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4794</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 09:57:14</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:85.5pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This incident was captured on the in-car camera and the body warn camera &lt;/strong&gt;(&lt;strong&gt;BBC)&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Warrant Service #:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;D-023-CR-22-001244-3&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Wicomico County Sheriff Department (WCSD)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Run #:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;23005178&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Self Inflicted Injury:&lt;/strong&gt; Boxer&amp;#39;s Fracture&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Photographs:&lt;/strong&gt; Five(5)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On 08/12/2023 at approximately 2230 hours, I, Trooper Gibbons # 7441 was dispatched to respond to the Park and Ride in West Ocean City for a possible wanted person out of Wicomico County Sheriff Department. Upon my arrival I made contact with TFC Bradley # 7100, who then advised that the subject Robert Lee Hayes Junior (DOB: 10/03/1992 W/M) may have a warrant. Hayes was positively identified through NCIC/ Meters. Hayes was wearing a black hat, gray short sleeve shirt, beige khaki shorts, white socks, and black shoes. Hayes upon my first initial contact was verbal and coherent. Hayes did have minor scraps, and scars on both his legs, and cuts on his left and right arms prior to the arrest.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:85.5pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At 2244 hours, the Berlin Barrack received confirmation that Hayes did have a warrant for Violation of Probation through Wicomico County Sheriff Department (WCSD). At 2249 hours, I then placed Hayes under arrest for the warrant.&amp;nbsp; Hayes after being searched was placed in the front seat of my patrol vehicle per MSP policy. Hayes was informed that everything in the vehicle was being audibly, visually recorded. While traveling to the barrack, Hayes then began to fall asleep. I asked Hayes if he was ok, but he did not respond. Hayes then sat up once he heard the sound of the in-car radio, then again fell asleep.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:85.5pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At approximately 2315 I then arrived with Hayes at the Berlin Barrack. While approaching the back entrance Hayes responded saying &amp;ldquo;Take me to jail&amp;rdquo;. I informed Hayes that he needed to speak with the Commissioner first. Hayes replied saying, &amp;quot;I already know what&amp;#39;s up&amp;quot;. &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t need no Commissioner to tell me that I have a violation of probation&amp;rdquo;. I then informed Hayes that we still had to go through the process. We then entered into the Barrack through the rear entrance, and I then conducted a second search on Hayes in front of Cpl. Ruiz # per MSP policy. Hayes was then escorted to cell # 2. While in the entrance of the cell Hayes began to cry as I removed his necklace. He then became upset as I continued to remove the necklace telling me to rip it the fuck off. I informed him that I was not going to do that. He then replied saying &amp;ldquo;Well then give them to me, and I&amp;#39;ll rip them the fuck off&amp;rdquo;. I then asked him to relax and be cooperative.&amp;nbsp;Hayes then saw the metal frame in the cell, and asked if he had to sit on the metal. I informed him that he could sit on it or on the floor. He then replied saying &amp;ldquo;Yeah we will see how that works&amp;rdquo;. Then he stated that he was going to do something else with the metal frame since there was no bed. I then asked him a second time if he was going to be cooperative, and he said yes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="tab-stops:85.5pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cpl. Ruiz then advised him that as soon as the Commissioner sees him, then he would be able to roll out. Hayes then replied saying, &amp;ldquo;Yeah, and I know how long that takes&amp;quot;. He then stated that he did not know why we wouldn&amp;#39;t just take him to jail. Before Hayes entered the Barrack, and the cell he did not have any injuries to his hands at all.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At approximately 0050 hours, I then advised Hayes that the Commissioner was on the phone, and ready to speak with him. At that time Hayes was seated with his back towards me on the metal bunk. He than seemed to be very lethargic. I asked Hayes if he was ok, but he did not reply I then asked him multiple times to put his shoes on so that he could speak with the Commissioner. He then began to utter words that I was not able to make out. He sat After a few minutes passed I asked which hand he wrote with, and he stated his right hand, but he was not able to use his hand. I asked if he thought his hand was not working, and he did not reply. After six minutes passed, I was able to place the handcuffs on him. While placing the handcuffs on him, he stated that he punched the wall. I asked him why would he punch the wall, but he did not respond. While in the Troopers room, as Commissioner Ward was on the telephone, Hayes stated that he did not want to speak with her. I informed Commissioner Ward of Hayes&amp;#39;s statement. I then asked Hayes if he was going to participate in the hearing, and he stated that he did not want to participate. Hayes as I was placing the handcuffs on him stated that he did not have any feeling in his right hand. I asked him if he needed EMS. I asked him a second time if he needed EMS. Furthermore, I then informed the -Duty Officer at the time, Cpl. Ruiz. EMS then was en-route to the Barrack. There were technical difficulties with the speakerphone on the telephone in the Troopers&amp;#39; Room, so we then moved into the Intoximeter Room to attempt to use the telephone there. Unfortunately the telephones were not functioning properly, so I then used my cellular phone so that Hayes would be able to have his hearing. While Commissioner Ward began informing Hayes of his charges, and the warrant, he stated that he knew what the warrant was for. Commissioner Ward then informed him that he was going to end up with the same results. While she was speaking he interrupted her and replied saying,&amp;quot; Yeah so why don&amp;#39;t you just fucking do it then&amp;quot;. He then made a statement saying that he told me that he did not want to talk to her. She then informed him that he does not get that option. He then made a comment to her saying,&amp;quot; Well apparently I do&amp;quot;. Commissioner Ward then advised Hayes since he was being argumentative with her that he would just go to the jail, and then wait on till the upcoming Monday to see the judge for his bail review. Hayes then stated that he told me to take him to the jail. Hayes continued to become argumentative with Commissioner Ward. She then advised Hayes that we have to wait until she tells us to take him to jail first. She then advised him that it&amp;#39;s not an option for him. He then replied saying,&amp;quot; We shall see what an option is then&amp;quot;. He stated this three times. Commissioner Ward asked Hayes what he ment by that statement twice. Hayes did not reply. Commissioner Ward then advised me of the commitment form that she would be sending to me for Hayes, and that he would have his bail review with the judge since he was not willing to cooperate.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; At approximately 0115 hours EMS arrived on scene at the Barrack to see Hayes for his injury. While being seen by EMS, Hayes was asked if he could move his fingers. The paramedic advised me that he was going to have X-rays done at the hospital. He was only able to me three of the five. He then agreed to get checked at the hospital. He was only able to put one shoe on due to his injury. Hayes stated that he only had the one hand injured. I then escorted Hayes into my marked patrol vehicle, and transported him to Atlantic General Hospital (AGH) in Berlin Maryland. At 0133 hours, I then arrived with Hayes at AGH. Hayes was then placed in a wheelchair, and was then escorted to the front entrance to register in. Hayes then was seen my the nurse, and was asked multiple times what his injury was, and his medical history. The nurse then advised that if he is not willing to respond to questions being asked then he will be marked as a refusal for treatment. Hayes finally responded after a few minutes responded to the nurse, and answered her questions. Hayes then had to have three (3) X-rays of his right hand done. After the X-rays the Doctor arrived, to informed him that he had sustained a Boxer&amp;#39;s Fracture to his right hand, and that he needed to have it wrapped with a compression bandage, and a splint. The doctor advised that he did write a non-narcotic pain reliever that the jail would have to administer to him. After receiving the discharge at approximately 0250 hours, I then was en-route to Snowhill Detention Center with Hayes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; At approximately 0310 hours, I arrived at the Snowhill Detention Center. At 0328 Hayes was released into the care of the Snowhill Detention Center staff without any further incidents. Five (5) photographs of the injury were taken and attached to this report. The return of service was faxed to Wicomico County Sheriff Department (WCSD).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed.&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7441</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 22:08:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7441</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 21:31:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7100</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jenkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7357</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jonischek</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4794</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibbons</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7441</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>30</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7441</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 05:46:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7441</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 21:36:04</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>185993</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hayes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/03/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/01/2018 19:43:28</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hayes</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/03/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/01/2018 19:43:28</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>10433</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Georgetown</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Berlin</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21811</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.200683</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.352196</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7441</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 05:46:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7441</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 05:46:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>