<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-020333</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/06/2023 20:17:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/06/2023 20:17:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/06/2023 19:25:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/06/2023 19:25:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was stopped for a traffic violation and was later arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 20:17:42</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4913</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 18:36:15</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>US-301,ANNAPOLIS</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>696831</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 20:17:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 22:30:30</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>696831</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>22</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>US-301</StreetName>
         <City>Annapolis</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21401</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.568059</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.983828</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/06/2023 20:17:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/06/2023 20:17:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/13/2023 02:44:58</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 20:17:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;J-16 equipped with a mobile recording device and BWC, this stop was recorded.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Chelsea Dawn Hicks&lt;br /&gt; Date of Birth: 3/18/1984&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 6/6/2023&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 1947 hours&lt;br /&gt; DE SDX: 1496081&lt;br /&gt; DUI #: J-23-102&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;br /&gt; * Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; * Apprehended more than 210 impaired drivers during my career with the Maryland State Police to date.&lt;br /&gt; * Attended the 2016 DUI Conference&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Completed the 2017 DUI Institute at the University of Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Received the Smooth Operator Award&lt;br /&gt; * Received the Aggressive Drivers are Public Threats (ADAPT) Award.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;* Completed the Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Course (ARIDE).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Narrative:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Vehicle in Motion (Phase 1)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On June 6, 2023, at approximately 1925 hours, I (TFC Jeans #6483) was in the uniform of the day and operating unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle J-16. At that time, I was on routine patrol eastbound Rt. 50 in the area of I97 in lane three, Annapolis, Anne Arundel County, Maryland. At that time, I was in lane three when I looked in my rear-view mirror and observed a silver Toyota in lane one switching to lane two. The Toyota appeared to be exceeding the posted speed limit of 65 MPH and was passing other vehicles. I activated the rear antenna of my Golden Eagle II RADAR unit in the same direction moving mode and obtained a speed of 86 MPH in a 65 MPH zone. Once I captured the speed, the silver Toyota, bearing Maryland Registration T1366085, passed my patrol vehicle before braking and slowing down once in front of me in lane two. I then moved from lane three to lane two, activated my emergency equipment, and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle came to a stop eastbound Rt. 50 at the 22-mile marker.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I made contact with the operator of the vehicle by making a passenger side approach. As I made my approach, I observed the driver light a fresh cigarette and observed she was wearing sunglasses. I stated to the female driver the stop was being audibly and visibly recorded. Before I even began talking, I was able to tell the driver appeared to be irritated and mad that she was being stopped by making aggressive hand gestures (throwing hands up) and body movements. I stated to the female driver the reason for the stop and requested her Driver&amp;#39;s License and Registration card. After stating the reason for the stop, the driver stated she was not speeding and was not passing other vehicles. I asked the female driver if there was any reason for her attitude and she stated she was frustrated that she was stopped because she believed everyone was going the same speed, which was not the case. When I asked the driver if she had not passed any other vehicles, how she passed me. She responded by saying I drove past you. She continued and stated she was going the same speed as everyone else.&amp;nbsp; The driver handed me her Maryland Driver&amp;#39;s License and registration. The driver was identified as Chelsea Dawn Hicks, B/F, DOB: 3/18/1984. Once I received Hicks&amp;rsquo; information, I went back to my cruiser and conducted a license and wanted check. The license check revealed Hicks was driving on a suspended license, and she was not wanted. When I went into a Law Enforcement Database to see if Hicks had been stopped for anything else recently, that check revealed she had been stopped the day prior, June 5, 2023, in Queen Anne&amp;rsquo;s County for several traffic violations, including driving while suspended. There was another stop from just a few days before that stop where Hicks was also issued driving while suspended citations. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;After finding this information out, I requested another unit to respond. When another unit arrived, I made my second approach and asked Hicks to step out of the vehicle. Hicks initially did not obey this order and did not exit her vehicle. I asked Hicks several more times to exit the vehicle, and she was being passive aggressive by not exiting the vehicle. After asking several times, Hicks eventually exited the vehicle and she was placed under arrest for driving on a suspended license. I walked Hicks to the front bumper of my patrol car and Cpl. Anderson #6354 watched her so I could clear off my front seat of the patrol car. As Cpl. Anderson was listening to Hicks talk and ramble, he detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Hicks&amp;rsquo; breath. I then got Hicks in my front passenger seat and walked around my vehicle and entered it. When I entered my vehicle, I too detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Hicks&amp;rsquo; breath. Hicks was advised that I was able to detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and I asked her if I transported her to the Annapolis Barrack if she would perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Hicks replied by stated she did not think it was necessary. Hicks then later stated she was drinking at Happy Hour and was having one drink an hour. Hicks stated she had to use the restroom so I transported Hicks to the Annapolis Barrack to accommodate her. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Upon arrival to the Annapolis Barrack, I walked Hicks downstairs into the Trooper&amp;rsquo;s Room where a female officer from Annapolis City Police Department searched Hicks. I then let Hicks use the restroom. After using the restroom, I walked Hicks back to the Troopers Room and asked her if she wanted to do Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. At that point, Hicks agreed to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Hicks&amp;rsquo; sunglasses were removed at this point and it was clear Hicks had bloodshot and glassy eyes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed in the Trooper&amp;rsquo;s Room at the Annapolis Barrack. The floor was level and free from any debris. Hicks appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any major visible injuries when walking from the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Hicks the following questions:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Medical Conditions &amp;ndash; None&lt;br /&gt; Injuries &amp;ndash; Spinal fusion one year ago&lt;br /&gt; Medication &amp;ndash; Suboxone (takes it in the morning) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Had not fallen or hit their head.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Hicks was not wearing glasses at the time of the stop&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Hicks&amp;rsquo; eyes. Hicks was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Hicks&amp;rsquo; pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. Hicks was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. Hicks was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&lt;br /&gt; 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Hicks did show signs of vertical nystagmus, indicating a possibly high amount of alcohol in Hicks&amp;rsquo; system.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The walk and turn test was properly explained and demonstrated per the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. At the conclusion of the demonstration and explanation, Hicks was asked if she understood the test, to which she stated &amp;ldquo;yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Hicks was unable to keep her right foot in front of her left foot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Walking Stage (1st Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 2, 3, and 6-9.&lt;br /&gt; 2.) Stepped off line on step 4.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Turn: Completed unsatisfactorily. Did not take a series of small steps in a circle like she was instructed to do.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Walking Stage (2nd Nine):&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1.) Hicks missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 2, 3 and 5.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;2.) Stepped off line on step 4.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ONE LEG STAND (3 out of 4 clues observed, right foot raised)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The one leg stand test was properly explained and demonstrated per the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. At the conclusion of the demonstration and explanation, Hicks was asked if she understood the test, to which she stated &amp;ldquo;yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&lt;br /&gt; I had to repeat how to put her foot out in front of her. Hicks asked &amp;ldquo;like this&amp;rdquo; and then picked her foot up and raised it, moving it behind her and bending her knee.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Balance and Count Stage:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1) Raised arms by more than 6 inches from her sides for balance throughout the entire test.&lt;br /&gt; 2) Swayed to maintain her balance on counts 1013 and 1021.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;A preliminary breath test was offered to Hicks, which she refused.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; ARREST&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the following, I had reason to believe Hicks was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; * Odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from breath and engulfing my vehicle once in it.&lt;br /&gt; * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.&lt;br /&gt; * Admitting to consuming alcoholic beverages.&lt;br /&gt; * Clues during standardized field sobriety testing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to the number of observations, I concluded Hicks had been driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 2017 hours, Hicks was advised she was also being charged with DUI/DWI. The DR-15 Advice of Rights was then read to Hicks on 6/6/2023 at 2025 hours. Hicks was also provided a copy to read over at which time she refused to submit to an intoximeter test. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="background-color:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:12.65pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;INTOXIMETER RESULT:&lt;br /&gt; Refusal&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Hicks was given copies of all pertinent paperwork and was transported to the Jennifer Road Detention Center to go before a District Court Commissioner.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case closed by arrest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:57:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 23:26:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jeans</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6483</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509768</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/06/2023 19:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:31:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 22:31:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509768</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3099</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/06/2023 19:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3099</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:32:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 22:32:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509768</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/06/2023 19:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19731</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:32:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 22:32:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509768</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21199</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/06/2023 19:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21199</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:33:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 22:33:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509768</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/06/2023 19:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:34:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 22:34:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509768</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/06/2023 19:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:35:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 22:35:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509768</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/06/2023 19:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:35:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 22:35:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509768</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/06/2023 19:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:38:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 22:38:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:51:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>379165</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hicks</LastName>
               <FirstName>Chelsea</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dawn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/18/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.12234518E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 22:49:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C420</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hicks</LastName>
               <FirstName>Chelsea</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dawn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/18/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.12234518E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>H200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C420</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 22:49:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>69</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Foxtrail</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Smyrna</City>
               <StateCode>DE</StateCode>
               <Zip5>19977</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3978</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.598734</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.273088</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>440</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1318</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:56:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:56:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:56:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 16:11:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 16:11:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153866</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:57:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 22:57:18</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>4T1C11AK5LU317510</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CAM</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>T1366085</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/07/2023 14:09:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/07/2023 14:09:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/13/2023 02:44:58</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6354</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/07/2023 14:09:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On June 6, 2023, at approximately 1947 hours, I, Cpl Anderson #6354 was in uniform of the day and operating marked MSP patrol vehicle J-28.&amp;nbsp; At that time, I responded to the right shoulder on E/B Rt 50 prior to West St to assist TFC Jeans who was on a traffic stop.&amp;nbsp; TFC Jeans eventually placed the driver under arrest and placed her in handcuffs.&amp;nbsp; Because the shoulder was narrow TFC Jeans had to move his patrol vehicle, J-16 in order for the driver to be placed into the passenger seat per department policy.&amp;nbsp; While TFC Jeans was moving his patrol vehicle, I had a conversation with the driver.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While speaking with the driver, I detected a strong odor of an acholic beverage emitting from her person/breath.&amp;nbsp; Once TFC Jeans moved his patrol vehicle, the driver was placed into the passenger seat of J-16.&amp;nbsp; I then let TFC Jeans know of my observations, and he conducted his investigation.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6354</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/07/2023 14:11:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6354</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/07/2023 14:38:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jones</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mujaihid</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1788</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>