<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-020608</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/08/2023 22:22:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/08/2023 22:22:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/08/2023 20:04:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/08/2023 20:04:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Subject called 911 stating he was assaulted and bleeding from the head. Investigation showed that the subject was the primary aggressor in a domestic assault and was ultimately arrested.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/08/2023 22:22:18</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1773</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/19/2023 09:09:20</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>697083</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/08/2023 22:22:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 20:48:16</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>697083</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>12433</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Torquay</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.123334</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.35296</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/08/2023 22:22:16</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/08/2023 22:22:16</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/17/2023 05:06:59</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/08/2023 22:22:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-485debec-7fff-f93b-3f6b-00ce05edbe9a"&gt;&amp;nbsp;***NO PHOTOS LOADED TO VERIPIC***&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Photos attached to report.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-485debec-7fff-f93b-3f6b-00ce05edbe9a"&gt;CASE NUMBER:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;23-MSP-020608&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-485debec-7fff-f93b-3f6b-00ce05edbe9a"&gt;DATE OF OFFENSE:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Thursday, June 8th, 2023.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-485debec-7fff-f93b-3f6b-00ce05edbe9a"&gt;OFFICER:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;S/TPR. J. Woo #5911. Maryland State Police, Berlin Barrack, Road Patrol.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-485debec-7fff-f93b-3f6b-00ce05edbe9a"&gt;REASON FOR CONTACT/CRIME:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Subject called 911 stating he was assaulted and bleeding from the head. Upon investigation, Subject showed signs of deceit and was determined to be the primary aggressor. He was arrested for domestic related assault 2nd degree.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-485debec-7fff-f93b-3f6b-00ce05edbe9a"&gt;SUSPECT:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Bryant, Jeffrey Daniel. 10/04/1986 W/M.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 12433 W. Torquay Rd,&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Ocean City, MD 21842.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 302-236-6705&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-485debec-7fff-f93b-3f6b-00ce05edbe9a"&gt;VICTIM:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-485debec-7fff-f93b-3f6b-00ce05edbe9a"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Sidleck, Isabella Anne 07/31/1997 W/F&lt;br /&gt; 12433 W. Torquay Rd,&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Ocean City, MD 2182&lt;br /&gt; 717-419-8987&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-485debec-7fff-f93b-3f6b-00ce05edbe9a"&gt;SCENE PROCESSING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; -Photos Taken and attached to report.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -Ring Camera footage.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-485debec-7fff-f93b-3f6b-00ce05edbe9a"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong id="docs-internal-guid-485debec-7fff-f93b-3f6b-00ce05edbe9a"&gt;NARRATIVE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; On Thursday, June 8th, at approximately 8:04 PM (2004 hours) I, S/Tpr. J. Woo #5911, was dispatched to the address of 12433 W. Torquay Rd, Ocean City, MD 21842 in reference to an assault where a subject was struck and bleeding from the head. While en route, I was advised that it was unknown if the suspect was still on scene, and what weapons were involved.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Upon my arrival, I observed a pick up truck with DE tags parked in the driveway, with a black mustang parked in front of it. The mustang had the driver&amp;#39;s side door open. I was then met in the driveway by a female, later identified as Isabella Anne Sidleck 07/31/1997.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick appeared frustrated but calm. As I spoke with her, I observed a subject laying down on the porch, lifting his head up and waiving. Sidleck was stating that the relationship had been over for two to three weeks. She stated that she had an abortion two weeks ago, and that every time she tries to talk to the male subject, he &amp;quot;Flips out&amp;quot; on her. She stated that he has also been drinking.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; TFC. Brader then arrived on scene. I had TFC. Brader talk with Sidleck while I spoke with the male subject, later identified as Jeffrey Daniel Bryant 10/04/1986. I observed Bryant to have blood running down his face from his head and several drops of blood around Bryant on the porch. At this time, the fire chief arrived on scene.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As I looked at Bryant, it appeared as though the wound was healing and the bleeding was slowing. There was a decent amount that had dripped down Bryant&amp;#39;s face and shirt, but the drips on the deck were small. The blood on Bryant&amp;#39;s face appeared to be drying up already as well.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bryant&amp;#39;s demeanor and reactions appeared disingenuous. Bryant appeared to be attempting to give the impression that he had lost consciousness, or was extremely weak from losing a large amount of blood. However, based on what I had observed, there did not appear to be so much blood loss, that it would cause weakness.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Bryant what happened. Bryant spoke softly and stated that she (Sidleck) hit him in the head with something, but he did not know what. Bryant stated that Sidleck is in the process of moving out. He stated that he has it all on video, that Sidleck hit him several times in the bedroom. He stated that Sidleck had some belongings sitting by the front door, he stated that he tried to carry it outside.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; He stated Sidleck held onto the bag and that he tried to pull it out of her hands. He stated that as he did this, Sidleck fell. He then stated that Sidleck went into the bedroom and then came back out. He stated that when she came back out, she hit him in the head with something, but he wasn&amp;#39;t sure what it was.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bryant stated that he did not know what he got hit with. He stated that Sidleck stated that a mirror hit him in the head, but that is not what happened. He stated it was a full sized mirror, which is still standing up in the room. He stated that he was standing in the doorway when he was struck, but he does not know what he was struck with.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As EMS began tending to Bryant, they asked if he lost consciousness at all. Bryant stated that he &amp;quot;Faded out for a few seconds&amp;quot; and that&amp;nbsp; he was &amp;quot;a little bit concussed.&amp;quot; EMS personnel asked what he meant by this. Bryant stated that when the lady (dispatcher) was asking him questions, he could not remember the answers to them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; EMS continued to try and clean the wound. As they did, Bryant stated that he took some tylenol, which may have thinned his blood. The EMS provider stated that Tylenol was not a blood thinner, but Ibuprofen and Asprin were. Bryant then stated that he meant Advil, not Tylenol.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bryant continued to state that he did not know what he was hit with, but it definitely was not the mirror, and that he was standing in the doorway when he was struck. As the EMS provider continued to clean Bryant&amp;#39;s wound, I was able to see that it was a very small laceration, about 1/4 inch in length, and very shallow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As the Ambulance crew arrived, and continued to clean Bryant&amp;#39;s wound, I overheard them recommend that he go to the hospital to get checked out, because they would be able to better diagnose and treat Bryant. Bryant stated he did not want to go to the hospital. I also heard them recommend getting the would glued. As they worked on Bryant, they asked if he knew what day of the week it was.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bryant responded stating, to be fair, he did not know what day it was before the incident and laughed. This gave the impression that he had been drinking, and drinking enough to forget what day it was. Bryant continued to joke with EMS as they continued to clean the blood.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As one of the paramedics cleaned Bryant&amp;#39;s left arm, Bryant stated that the blood there was not from tonight. I then asked what it was from. Bryant stated that it was from a separate incident that had occurred the night prior. Because of the way Bryant was talking, I was unsure what he meant. I asked if this was a consensual incident. Bryant stated it was not. Bryant did not explain any further or wish to talk more about this previous incident.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As I spoke with Bryant, he gave the impression he was afraid of Sidleck. He stated that she was moving out, and he was just trying to lie low until she was gone. Bryant stated that he had video proof of what happened. This lead me to believe he was talking about this incident that occurred tonight. Bryant later stated he did not have any video evidence of what happened tonight, and that the only videos he did have, were of them arguing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As I spoke with Bryant, I observed several indications of that he was not being completely truthful with his statements. I recognized these clues based on my training, knowledge, experience and observations. I have completed Law-Tech&amp;#39;s Interviews and Statement Analysis training. In this training, I was taught signs and indications to determine the truthfulness of an individual&amp;#39;s statements.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Some indications of lack of truthfulness displayed by Bryant were that details of his story changed several times. The level of pain displayed by Bryant was not consistent with the injury. Bryant claimed to have almost passed out from loss of blood, but the amount of blood throughout the scene appeared relatively minor. Bryant gave the impression that he was weak and could not move one moment, but was walking around, talking and laughing at other times. Bryant appeared to be telling a story and trying to convince us of what happened, rather than explaining the events that unfolded.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Another indication was that the actions described did not match with the emotions described. Bryant later described how he was hit, he indicated that it caused him to be fed up with Sidleck&amp;#39;s actions, and got up to move her bag outside. He indicated that he was doing this calmly, and to help her with moving out, and not in a malicious manner. His next action was a violent pulling on the bag to yank it away from Sidleck as she attempted to taker property away from him.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As EMS finished up cleaning Bryant&amp;#39;s wound, he refused transportation to the hospital and advised he would go to his own doctor later. Bryant stated he did not have insurance and could not afford an ambulance ride, but also indicated he felt it was not an urgent matter and would go at a later time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then went inside the house and observed the bedroom. Inside the bedroom, I did observe a reclining chair in the reclined position, with a large full sized mirror leaning against the chair.&amp;nbsp; There was a full sized bed on a box spring on the floor, on the wall opposite of the closet. The room was messy, but appeared to be from general untidiness, rather than an altercation. There were old dishes, an unmade bed, and food items that appeared to have been there for some time. Things appeared to be intentionally placed or left throughout the room, rather than thrown or tossed. The bed was unmade. The only thing out of place was that the mirror was leaning on the recliner and there was a drink that had spilled on the floor near the mirror.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Due to the mess of the room, I was unable to locate anything that may have been used to strike Bryant in the head.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I did observe some blood on the bedsheets, floor, and recliner. Bryant was standing in the bedroom doorway and stated that was where he was standing when she came up and hit him from behind. He stated that he fell forward onto the bed, leaving the blood marks on the bed. He stated that he did not realize he was bleeding at first, that he collapsed as soon as she hit him, indicating it was a very hard hit.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Bryant to explain what happened again. Bryant stated that he was sitting in the recliner when Sidleck physically pulled the mirror off the wall. He indicated that this made him angry, so he got up to take one of her bags outside. As Bryant explained the situation, he gave the impression that he was acting calmly. He stated that as he walked to the porch, Sidleck grabbed the bag. He stated that he tried to pull the bag away from her, and she &amp;quot;tripped and fell.&amp;quot; He stated that after she fell, he went back to the room, and that is when she came up behind him and hit him in the head.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This was odd to me because, Bryant made it sound like it was a complete accident that Sidleck fell, however, he did not try to help her up, see if she was OK, or apologize for any accident that may have occurred.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked him why he pulled the bag away from her. He stated that he was trying to get the bag out of her hand. He stated he was just trying to help her get her stuff out of the house, that she was already in the process of moving out, and he was just trying to help. This appeared to me, to be an over explanation, in order to convince me of what happened, rather than just stating the facts.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As Bryant explained the situation again, he continued to make sure to state that Sedlick did hit him with the mirror, but it was not what hit him in the head. He wanted to make it clear that the side of his head where the injury was, was on the opposite side of where the mirror hit him when he was sitting in the chair. Bryant continued to explain the events again. He stated that after Sedlick fell, he let go of the bag and walked back to the room.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bryant then stated &amp;quot;As far as pushing her down...&amp;quot; he explained that he pulled the bag, he did not push Sedlick.&amp;nbsp; Up to this point, no one had made any claims to me that Sedlick was pushed down, or that Bryant pushed her down, so this statement stuck out to me. I asked Bryant what he meant by that. He stated that there was no pushing. I asked he said &amp;quot;as far as pushing her down&amp;quot; then. Bryant then argued that he did not say that he pushed her, that he pulled her. Bryant again continued to explain the incident stating that he pulled the bag. This appeared to me, again to be an over explanation, as well as an attempt to show that he did nothing wrong, or combat any statements she may make later.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I again asked Bryant why he made the comment about pushing her down, when no one had said he pushed her down, and I had not suspected him of pushing her down. Bryant then stated that Sedlick told the dispatcher that he had pushed her down.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked Bryant what happened to his arm. Bryant gave a long pause and looked away towards the right. Bryant then stated that the incident happened two nights ago, rather than last night. He stated that he had rolled over and was trying to sleep when &amp;quot;Next thing I know&amp;quot; Sedlick was standing over top of him. He stated that she balled her fist up, and punched him in the ear, and then two more times in the head. She then yanked his shirt collar up until it ripped off of him, causing the injuries to his neck and arm.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I did not investigate these claims further because Bryant did not wish for this incident to be investigated. However, based on my training, knowledge, experience, and observations, Bryant&amp;#39;s story did not appear to be truthful. Looking to the right is an indication of constructing a thought, rather than remembering. Statements along the lines of &amp;quot;Next thing I knew,&amp;quot; are an indication of leaving out details. Bryant appeared to be elaborating to the story as well, stating she balled her fist up. If he was asleep, eyes closed in a dark room, facing away from her, he would not have seen this. Further sings of attempting to convince through story telling, rather than stating facts.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; After looking through the room several times, I was unable to locate or determine what may have struck Bryant in the head, that would have caused that injury.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then spoke with Sedlick inside the house. Sedlick explained that Bryant was sitting in his recliner in his room talking with his mother. Sedlick stated that there was a show that she and Bryant were supposed to go to the following day, and that Bryant&amp;#39;s parents were possibly coming too. Sedlick stated that they had been breaking up, but she liked Bryant&amp;#39;s parents so she was happy that they were coming to the show. They then began talking about the show and who&amp;#39;s car they would be taking to the show. Bryant then began to argue, which angered Sedlick. She stated that she then walked out of the room and slammed the door behind her.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sidleck then began looking for the bag in question. She stated it was a Marshall&amp;#39;s reusable shopping bag with a blanket inside. She then remembered that she had put the bag in her car. She then explained that she came out of the room and sat at the kitchen table. She stated that Bryant then came flying out of the room, grabbed her bag, and began running towards the door. She stated that she then grabbed the bag. Sedlick stated that instead of letting her have the bag, he threw her against the front door, causing her to fall to the ground.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick stated that Bryant then teased her stating &amp;quot;ooo, ooo.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp; She stated that she told him no, she was not doing this right now. She stated that Bryant was trying to egg her on, stating come on, lets go, but she continued to state that she was not doing this. She stated that she then went into he bedroom and shut the door. She stated that Bryant then pushed the door open, so she went towards the closet.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The way the room is set up, the recliner is blocking the closet. The mirror was leaning against the wall next to the closet entrance, and next to the recliner. Sedlick stated that she pushed the recliner, to get into the closet, causing the mirror to fall. She stated that as this happened, Bryant went the opposite way around the recliner to try to go into the closet, which is when she believed the mirror hit him. Sedlick did clarify that she did not see the mirror hit him. She then stated that as soon as she came out of the closet, he jumped on top of her and put his hands around her neck.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick stated that she was laying there, when he saw the blood drip down onto her. She stated that he stated this was all he needed and he got up off of her. I did observe what appeared to be two small drips of blood on Sedlick&amp;#39;s left shoulder, which had run down her arm about two inches each.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick stated that Bryant then called 911. She state that she did not intend for him to get hurt and she did not try to hurt him. She stated that when she realized he was bleeding, she then tried to help him and make sure he was OK.&amp;nbsp;Sidleck stated that she went outside and Bryant followed her outside and called 911. She stated that she then tried to make sure Bryant was OK, but that Bryant was telling 911 that she was trying to attack him. She stated that Bryant was also stating that he felt like he was going to pass out.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick stated that she believed Bryant had been drinking all day, and had not eaten. She stated that she also believes he took medication. Sedlick explained that she works in the medical field. She stated she believed that he may be feeling like he was going to pass out because of the lack of food, alcohol, and mixing of medications, rather than the head injury, but she wanted to take a look at him to make sure.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick again stated that she was not trying to hurt him, she just did not want her belongings thrown outside.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick stated that she has been working on moving out. She stated she has a text from Bryant stating she has 30 days to move out. She stated that they have been having relationship issues for the last 8 months. She stated that she has lived there for over a year. She stated that in March, Bryant had asked her to move out. She stated that she loves him and begged him to try to work things out. She stated that Bryant agreed to try to work things out until July, and then they would talk about it again.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick stated that in April, she found out she was pregnant. She stated that she got an abortion because Bryant was so verbally abusive to her. She stated that Bryant told her on a daily basis that he did not want anything to do with her, that she was the last person he wanted to have a child with, that she was mentally unstable, and horrible. Sedlick stated she just had the abortion two weeks ago and is just trying to survive right now.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked Sedlick what happened to Bryant&amp;#39;s neck and arm. She stated it was from the other night. She stated she was trying to get in bed, and every time she tried to adjust the sheets, he would mess it up. She stated that she would try to fix the sheets, and Braynt would jump on the bed and push her off. She stated that she grabbed his shirt because he would not let her get in bed and fix the sheets.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick started that she has bruises on her arm from the other night as well. She stated that Bryant grabbed her. Sedlick showed me her right bicep area and I observed several small bruises consistent with fingertips. Sedlick went on to say that Bryant also has a bruise on his thigh/groin area.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick stated that she was trying to apologize to him, and he was recording her. Sedlick stated that she asked him to stop recording her because she did not want to be recorded while she was apologizing. She stated that she did grab his phone and he then pushed her down onto the bed. Sedlick stated that she then used her foot to push Bryant off of her, which is why he has a bruise.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then questioned Sedlick further about being choked by Bryant. I did not understand how she went from standing to being on the ground. Sedlick clarified that as she came out of the closet and back towards the bedroom door, past Bryant, he pushed her down. She was then sitting on the floor with her back leaning against the bed. She stated that Bryant was over her with his hands around her neck. I asked if he was squeezing and choking her. Sedlick stated that she did not feel that he was trying to kill her, but it was enough to scare her.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As I spoke with Sedlick, I did observe light red marks around her neck and chest area that faded over time. I did observe Sedlick&amp;#39;s left upper arm to be red and have a bruise forming in the middle. She stated that it was from being thrown against the front door.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on my interaction with Sedlick, She appeared to be truthful. Sedlick was willing to share deeply personal information, and admit to her own wrongdoing. Her story was consistent and appeared to be facts rather than containing additional details to convince me that an event occurred.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As I went to speak with Bryant again, Sedlick asked if she could talk with Bryant. She stated that she did not want to press charges. She just wanted to go their separate ways and let it be in the past.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then spoke with Bryant. Bryant also stated that he did not want to press charges, and just wanted things to end. I did ask Bryant how much he had to drink. Bryant stated he had 1 drink. He stated he had just poured the second drink when the argument happened and it was now spilled on the floor.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I explained to Bryant that domestic violence related assault investigations are tricky. I explained that based on my conversation with him, his story was not adding up. I went on to explain that he stated he was hit while standing in the doorway, but Sedlick stated he was hit by the mirror. Bryant then interrupted my and stated that her statement doesn&amp;#39;t add up, because he has an injury to the left side of his head, but if he was sitting in the chair when the mirror hit him, it would have hit him on the right side. Bryant pointed this out numerous times throughout the investigation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bryant stated several times that he has video evidence of being assaulted by Sedlick, but does not have any video of tonight events. During the investigation, Bryant showed me his Ring Doorbell video footage which showed Sedlick walking out the front door very angry. Sedlick can be heard yelling that Bryant just threw her across the room. I asked Bryant if he would be able to share the video with me. Bryant screen recorded the video and forwarded it to me voluntarily.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Bryant if he had any security cameras inside. Bryant stated he did not. At a later time, it was discovered that Bryant does have a security camera inside, however it may not have been recording at the time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on my conversations with both subjects, the layout and condition of the room, and lack of evidence, I believe that Bryant was struck in the head with the sharp corner of the mirror as he went around the left side of the chair towards the closet, making Bryant&amp;#39;s injury accidental and possibly self-inflicted.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; There are drops of blood in the chair and closet. Bryant indicated he did not go near either of those after being struck in the head.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; There was no weapon or any other object found, consistent with the wound to Braynt&amp;#39;s head. Braynt stated that he believes a charging plug, observed in the middle of the floor is what struck him. The plug had two prongs and a rounded body with rounded corners and appeared to be thinner plastic and lightweight. Bryant argued that if Sedlick grabbed the cord and swung it hard enough, it would have cause bleeding. Bryant&amp;#39;s wound was on small, shallow gash in his head. If the prongs struck him, there should have been two wounds. If he was struck hard enough with the body of the charger to cause bleeding, I believe the charger would have broken into pieces.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Both parties stated that the injury to Bryant occurred after the injury to Sedlick occurred.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the above, I determined that Bryant was the aggressor. I then went back inside to talk with Bryant.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bryant was in his room with the door shut, talking to his brother on the phone. I knocked on the door and then went in. At this time, Bryant was standing up and then knelt back down stating he felt dizzy. I asked why he was feeling dizzy. Bryant stated that he just got dizzy when he stood up.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Bryant if I could get some photos of his injuries. Bryant then walked out into the kitchen and stood with no issues, moving and showing off his scars.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then placed Bryant under arrest. At this time, Bryant&amp;#39;s brother began speaking to us through a hidden camera inside the home. Bryant&amp;#39;s brother stated that he believed Bryant was concussed and needed medical attention. I explained that Bryant had been seen by EMS and refused treatment. Bryant&amp;#39;s brother stated he believed Bryant was confused because he &amp;quot;sounded concussed&amp;quot; and could not remember things like the date. Bryant had joked with EMS personnel earlier about not remembering the date.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bryant himself did not request EMS, and did not appear in any different condition then he had throughout the evening. Based on this, and because he had already been seen by and refused EMS, I did not believe Bryant required any further medical attention.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then conducted a search of Bryant&amp;#39;s person prior to transporting him. During this time, I located three loose pills in Bryant&amp;#39;s back pocket. Bryant stated that they were Adderall. I asked Bryant if he had a prescription for the medication. He stated that he did and so did Sedlick. Bryant stated he was not sure where his prescription bottle was and indicated that they shared prescriptions. Eventually, Bryant stated that because he does not have insurance, he was unable to refill his prescription when it ran out and that these pills were from Sedlick&amp;#39;s prescription bottle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then spoke to Sedlick about this. Sedlick stated confirmed that this was correct. She stated that he does have a valid prescription for the medication, but does not have the money to purchase it at the time. I then handed the medication over to Sedlick.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bryant was transported to the MSP Berlin barrack where he was charged and processed. While at the barrack, Bryant requested to make a phone call and wished to contact his attorney. I allowed Bryant to make a phone call. He then called his brother and asked him to find him an attorney. He later stated he did not need an attorney for the initial appearance. During Bryant&amp;#39;s phone call with his brother, I learned that Bryant&amp;#39;s brother was out of town at a wedding and highly intoxicated. Bryant&amp;#39;s brother apologized for not being able to come back to help him out. He stated that he was too drunk to drive.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; During this time, Bryant read through the statement of probable cause. Bryant argued that he was hit with the mirror before Sedlick fell into the door. Bryant was angry and argumentative and stated numerous times throughout the night that this was not right, that he should not have been arrested.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The following day, I was advised to contact Sedlick because she had further information. I was later advised to respond to the residence at Torquay Rd because Sedlick had to get a few more belongings out of the house, and that she had more to tell me. Sedlick&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;After Sedlick had removed the rest of her property from the house, I had her sit in my patrol car and share her additional information with me. This interview was recorded on body camera and in-car camera.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick stated that she had realized that with everything going on, she knew she did not mention that she pushed the chair, causing the mirror to fall. Sedlick then stated that Bryant told her that if she had said this before, he would not have been arrested. As I talked with Sedlick, it appeared that Bryant was coercing Sedlick into changing her story.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As I spoke with Sedlick, she stated that Bryant called her when he got released. She stated that Bryant had originally stated he was going to get a protective order against her. She stated that they talked in the morning and went over everything and both decided not to file charges or protective orders.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick stated that she wanted to put it on the record that she did push the chair prior to Bryant picking up her bags. Sedlick stated that she pushed the chair to try to get into the closet, which knocked the mirror down. There was no intent to touch or harm Bryant. This was not an act of aggression and I would not consider Sedlick to have been the primary aggressor based on this act.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As I spoke with Sedlick in my car, in front of Bryant&amp;#39;s house, Bryant returned home with his friend and roommate, and two pit bull dogs. Bryant and the roommate had gone on a walk with the dogs in order to leave the house while Sedlick retrieved her belongings. I observed Bryant to be walking with no issues and to be holding the leashes of both dogs. I also observed him to be holding back as the dogs pulled on the leashes while the roommate ran towards the house.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Through this conversation with Sedlick, she continued to appear to care for Bryant. She also appeared to be manipulated by Bryant. Sedlick stated that Bryant wanted her to let us know that he felt like he was treated unfairly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick stated that Bryant told her he did want to go to the hospital, he just did not want to take the ambulance. Sedlick stated that Bryant was talking about litigation, and that he was treated poorly. She stated that he also stated he did not know what would happen to her. Sedlick stated that she did not know what that meant for her, if Bryant did go forward with something.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This gave me the impression that Bryant was threatening Sedlick in an attempt to get charges dropped.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; As I spoke with Sedlick, she stated that Bryant told her he does not remember anything from that night until he was at the barrack, and that he was concussed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I explained that this did not make sense to me for several reasons, one being that he did not lose that much blood. Sedlick stated that she agreed. She stated that working in the medical field she has seen people go unconscious from losing too much blood. She stated that they don&amp;#39;t usual talk much, but Bryant was sitting up and talking quite a bit. Sedlick stated she had trouble knowing what to believe because Bryant&amp;#39;s statements were not matching with the actions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick stated that she could not tell if Bryant was lying and wished he would have gone to get medical attention to know for sure. I then asked if Bryant had gone to get medical attention after being released last night or if he had gone at all yet today. Sedlick stated that he had not gone to get any medical attention. I pointed out that if he was that concerned, he should have gone as soon as he got out. I also explained that if he felt he needed medical attention, and asked for it, we would have gotten him additional medical attention. Bryant never did request any further medical attention, and never made any statements to me that he felt ill.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick then stated that she was afraid that Bryant would try to ruin her life now. She stated she is just trying to move on with her life. She stated that she is already getting professional help, but that after this, she knows she will need more professional help.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I then asked Sedlick if she had considered a protective order. Sedlick stated that she did not want to because they both go to the same gym, and she did not want to prevent him from being able to go to the gym, or cause him to lose his job of working at the gym.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Sedlick continued to state that she was afraid of what Bryant would do, and how it would affect her life. I referred Sedlick to the commissioner&amp;#39;s office to file for a protective order. Sedlick was given additional brochures for domestic violence resources.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 21:04:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5911</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 04:58:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brader</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6714</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Woo</LastName>
            <FirstName>Johnathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5911</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shockley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4814</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Woo</LastName>
            <FirstName>Johnathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5911</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Woo</LastName>
            <FirstName>Johnathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5911</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510043</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/08/2023 22:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 20:50:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5911</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 20:56:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>36</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>C</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 20:50:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:54</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>1076</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bryant</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Daniel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/04/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/07/2013 05:04:18</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B653</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J160</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bryant</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Daniel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/04/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B653</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J160</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/07/2013 05:04:18</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>309</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Park</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>10</SubNumber>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21801</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.600989</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.369306</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12433</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>West Torquay</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Ocean City</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21842</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.12268</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.353114</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>302</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>236</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6705</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/21/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 21:02:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 21:02:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 21:02:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>25</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 20:50:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:54</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>363388</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sidleck</LastName>
               <FirstName>Isabella</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/31/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/12/2022 00:54:59</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S342</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I214</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sidleck</LastName>
               <FirstName>Isabella</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/31/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S342</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I214</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/12/2022 00:54:59</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12433</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>West Torquay</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Ocean City</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21842</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.12268</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.353114</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>717</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>419</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8987</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/12/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>D</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 21:03:24</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 21:03:24</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5911</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 21:03:24</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>