<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-026953</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/30/2023 01:35:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/30/2023 01:35:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/30/2023 00:55:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/30/2023 00:55:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>MVC with injuries, DUI, Departmental</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 01:35:31</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4437</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/06/2023 23:40:05</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>27 MM CAPITAL BELTWAY EB, HYATTSVILLE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>705569</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 01:35:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 20:11:14</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>705569</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I-95</StreetName>
         <City>College Park</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20740</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.94035</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.021595</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/30/2023 01:35:29</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/30/2023 01:35:29</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/01/2023 07:14:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 01:35:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:04:54</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;DUI ARREST&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Incident was audibly and visually captured on Q-41&amp;rsquo;s equipped MVR, as well as body worn camera.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Defendant: Carlos Alberto Lasso Estrada&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Date of Birth: 09/23/1981&lt;br /&gt; Date of Arrest: 07/30/2023&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Time of Arrest: 0200 hrs.&lt;br /&gt; MD License #: L-223-108-041-736&lt;br /&gt; DUI #: 23-161&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;TRAINING/CERTIFICATES&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Baltimore County Police Department, Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, December 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) Trained, November 2017.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -Drug Recognition Expert (DRE) Training, July 2018.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -University of Maryland Institute for Advanced Law Enforcement Studies DUI Institute, Distinct Graduate, June 2019.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)&amp;nbsp;and PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; On July 30, 2023 at approximately 0102 hours, I, Tpr. Ryan Stewart #7590, currently assigned to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack &amp;ldquo;Q&amp;rdquo; was on patrol when Tpr. Javier Gonzales #7442 requested EMS to his location during a traffic stop. At that time, hearing the distress in his radio transmission requested his location. Tpr. Gonzales advised he was I/L Capital Beltway (I-495) prior to Baltimore Ave. (Rt. 1). I immediately began responding to his location from I/L I-495 south of Rt. 1. While enroute Tpr. Gonzales advised his vehicle was struck while he was on a traffic stop. Fire Board was enroute.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Upon arrival at approximately 0104 hrs. I observed a marron Honda Odyssey Van partially in lane 5, along with Tpr. Gonzales unmarked patrol vehicle (Q-8) on the I/L I-495 at Cherry Hill Rd. in the main/through lanes. At that time, I utilized my patrol vehicle to block lane 5 and approached the scene. I first made contact with Tpr. Gonzales and immediately observed his left arm/elbow to be bleeding. I then made contact with the occupants of the Honda Odyssey, three of which were juveniles (Ages 16, 12 and 12). The juveniles were complaining of injuries from the crash. The driver of the vehicle exited the vehicle when I briefly made contact with him, at which time I detected an odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person, and requested he enter his vehicle. The driver continued to exit the vehicle multiple times into oncoming traffic and was ordered back into the vehicle for his safety until fire board arrived on scene, both in English and Spanish by Tpr. Gonzales. While speaking with the daughter of the driver (second row passenger side occupant) she stated &amp;ldquo;He&amp;rsquo;s drunk&amp;rdquo;, referring to her father the operator of the vehicle. After speaking with the juvenile occupants and getting the driver back into the vehicle, I opened the passenger door of the vehicle to speak with the driver. When I opened the passenger door I again detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the passenger compartment of the vehicle and his breath and person. I requested his drivers license, which he provided and was identified as Carlos Alberto Lasso Estrada (H/M 9/23/81). Lasso Estrada later refused any medical attention. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;While I was handling the scene Tpr. Murry was on scene and remained with Lasso Estrada.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The mother of the three juveniles, America Yeset Flores De Zamora (H/M 1/1/79). Flores was visibly upset when she arrived but Fire Department personnel were able to speak with her in spanish and calm her down. Flores, as the mother of the children, elected to refuse further treatment/transport of the children stating she would take them to be further evaluated on her own. After obtaining information from the children and Flores I again made contact with Lasso Estrada who was leaning/seated on the concrete barrier.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I again introduced myself and advised Lasso Estrada everything was being audibly and visually recorded. I observed Lasso Estrada eyes to be glassy and I continued to detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I asked Lasso Estrada where he was coming from and he advised Manassas Park, in Virginia. I asked Lasso Estrada how much he had to drink and he seemed to no understand. I attempted to communicate with him in Spanish and asked &amp;ldquo;cuantas cervezas&amp;rdquo; which translates roughly to &amp;ldquo;how many beers?&amp;rdquo; Lasso Estrada seemed to understand and responded &amp;ldquo;three cervezas&amp;rdquo;. Lasso Estrada advised his last drink was 45 minutes ago in Virginia. Lasso Estrada continued to advise he was driving to his residence in Greenbelt (MD).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I asked Lasso Estrada how much English he understood and he stated 20% but was able to mostly communicate with me. Sgt. Camilo Melnyk with Branchville Volunteer Fire Company was on scene and assisted with translation as needed. Through Sgt. Melnyk translating Lasso Estrada stated his last drink with 40 minutes prior in Manassas. At that time, I had arrived on scene approximately 35 minutes prior. Lasso Estrada then changed his time frame of his last drink to an hour and a half ago.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I asked Lasso Estrada to perform standardized field sobriety tests, to confirm that he was okay to drive and he agreed and advised he understood.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; The evaluation was performed right shoulder of the main lanes of S/B I-495 just prior to Cherry Hill Rd. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight, and the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s headlights. Lasso Estrada appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. Prior to beginning the test my vehicle&amp;rsquo;s forward facing emergency lights were deactivated.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I asked (NAME) the following questions:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Glasses or Contacts &amp;ndash; None&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Medical Conditions &amp;ndash; None&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Injuries &amp;ndash; None&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;After asking the above questions, Lasso Estrada began speaking in Spanish, to which I did not understand. Sgt. Melnyk stated that Lasso Estrada advised that as he was driving the police car stopped very suddenly which is why he struck the police car. Lasso Estrada then stated he did not see the police car and that he was traveling approximately 65 mph.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (2/6 clues observed)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of a pen was used as the test&amp;#39;s stimulus. Lasso Estrada was instructed to look straight ahead, keep his head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus (pen) with his eyes only. Lasso Estrada was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. Lasso Estrada pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking.&amp;nbsp;Lasso Estrada advised he understood the directions and he did not have any questions. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Lack of Smooth Pursuit &amp;ndash; Present in both eyes&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation &amp;ndash; Unable to complete &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees &amp;ndash; Test stopped prior. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Vertical Gaze Nystagmus &amp;ndash; Test stopped prior&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;While administering this test, Lasso Estrada had trouble following the directions. I was able to complete the Lack of Smooth Pursuit portion after stopping and explaining it a second time. While attempting the Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation Lasso Estrada failed to continue to watch the stimulus and was looking short of it and/or would following it out to maximum deviation then look straight ahead at me. Due to his inability to follow the directions the test was stopped after completing the lack of smooth pursuit part of the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; WALK AND TURN (7/8 clues observed)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. Lasso Estrada was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Lasso Estrada was then instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and remain in that position until told to begin, he advised he understood. After providing the instructions and demonstration, I asked Lasso Estrada if he understood the test and he confirmed that he did.&amp;nbsp;The instructions of this test were provide using Sgt. Melnyk as a translator.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Lasso Estrada performed this test wearing white lace up shoes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Instructional Stage:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; -Unable to maintain the starting position&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;-Started before being instructed to start &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (1st Nine)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; - Stepped off line&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;- Missed heel to toe&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Turn:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Stopped and spun on lead foot did not take a series of small steps as instructed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Walking Stage (2nd Nine)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; - Stopped after turn before second set of steps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;- Missed heel to toe&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;- Improper number of steps (11)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;During the instructional phase, Lasso Estrada step from the starting position multiple times and when attempting to get back into the starting position he would place is left foot in front of his right and had to be corrected.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; The test was explained and demonstrated. Lasso Estrada was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. I asked Lasso Estrada if he understood the test and he confirmed that he did.&amp;nbsp;Lasso Estrada stated he had no questions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Balance and Count Stage:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Seconds 0-10:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Puts foot down.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sways&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Raises arms 6 inches or greater&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Seconds 11-20:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Puts foot down.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sways&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Raises arms 6 inches or greater&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Seconds 21-30:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Puts foot down&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lasso Estrada failed to count throughout the duration of the test, failed to point his toe on his elevated foot, failed to keep his eyes on his elevated foot and failed to keep both legs straight. Lasso Estrada also alternated the foot he raised multiple times throughout the test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;While on scene, I informed Lasso Estrada of his Preliminary Breath Test Rights. Lasso Estrada was offered a PBT, to which he consented. &amp;nbsp;I administered the PBT, S/N# 1405833. Lasso Estrada was unable to follow PBT instructions and was not providing a sufficient breath sample. After two failed attempts I retrieved a new straw for the PBT and again explained how to blow for the PBT. Lasso Estrada was able to provide a sufficient sample with a result of 0.189 BrAC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; ARREST&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; Based on the totality of circumstances, I had reason to believe Lasso Estrada was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Striking parked police car with lights activiated, causing crash and injuries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle/breath/person.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Glassy eyes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Clues during Standardized Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (2/6), WAT (7/8), OLS (3/4).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Inconsistent / inaccurate account of events&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Inability to follow directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Driver admitting to consuming &amp;ldquo;three beers&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;PBT result of 0.189 BrAC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Due to the number of observations, I concluded Lasso Estrada was driving under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a vehicle safely.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;At approximately 0200 hours, I placed Lasso Estrada under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. I notified the barrack, and searched his person for weapons and contraband, both with negative results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lasso Estrada was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy. A mouth check was completed at 0209 hours. I transported Lasso Estrada to the College Park Barrack and while enroute to the College Park Barrack I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person in my patrol vehicle.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Upon arrival at the College Park Barrack I asked Lasso Estrada if he preferred English or Spanish, and he advised Spanish. I asked Lasso Estrada if he could read and write the Spanish language, he stated he could. Lasso Estrada was advised of his Advice of Rights using the Spanish audio recording from the MVA&amp;rsquo;s website. The recording was stopped after the first paragraph and I asked Lasso Estrada if he could hear and understand the recording, he confirmed that he could.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; 20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Lasso Estrada beginning with his arrest. A preliminary search of Lasso Estrada was conducted on scene and it revealed that he had nothing in his mouth at 0209 hours.The test was conducted by Cpl. McGee of the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack on a certified instrument. Lasso Estrada had a result of 0.14 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 0253 hours.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; I processed Lasso Estrada and transported him to Capital Regional Hospital for a Medical Clearance prior to transporting him to Prince Georges County Department of Corrections (PG DOC). After receiving a medical clearance with discharge paperwork, I transported Lasso Estrada to PG DOC where custody of him was transferred to DOC staff while he awaited his initial appearance in front of a District Court Commissioner.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; The defendant was issued copies of the following documents:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; - All applicable citations&lt;br /&gt; - DR-15 Advice of Rights.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; - DR-15a Order of Suspension.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;- MSP 033 State of Maryland Notification to Defendant of Result of Test for Alcohol Concentration.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; All documents were forwarded to the Prince George&amp;#39;s County, State&amp;#39;s Attorney Office.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; The vehicle was towed from the scene by Alley Cat Towing.&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Prince George&amp;#39;s County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:02:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/01/2023 06:57:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gonzales</LastName>
            <FirstName>Javier</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7442</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>19</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ngoushema</LastName>
            <FirstName>Penyinema</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7453</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McGee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stewart</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7590</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516398</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/30/2023 00:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516398</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/30/2023 00:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516398</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/30/2023 00:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516398</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/30/2023 00:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516398</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/30/2023 00:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516398</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/30/2023 00:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516398</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/30/2023 00:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516398</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>20970</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/30/2023 00:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>20970</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516398</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19740</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/30/2023 00:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19740</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516398</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14584</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/30/2023 00:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14584</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>41</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:16:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 20:16:37</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386643</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>LASSO ESTRADA</LastName>
               <FirstName>CARLOS</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ALBERTO</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/23/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/31/2023 20:15:35</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L223</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>LASSO ESTRADA</LastName>
               <FirstName>CARLOS</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ALBERTO</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/23/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L223</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/31/2023 20:15:35</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9206</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>SPRINGHILL</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>201</SubNumber>
               <City>Greenbelt</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20770</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:16:36</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:16:36</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:16:36</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 20:10:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/31/2023 07:40:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/31/2023 07:40:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/01/2023 07:14:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 07:40:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:04:54</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="text-autospace:none"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;On July 30, 2023 at approximately 0055 hours I, Trooper Gonzales #7442 currently assigned to the College Park Barrack was operating unmarked police patrol vehicle Q-8. I was conducting a traffic stop in the area of southbound I-495 main lanes north of Route 1 on the right shoulder. I conducted a traffic stop on a white Mazda 3 bearing Massachusetts registration &amp;ldquo;1CBF79&amp;rdquo; for a speeding violation in a 55 mile per hour zone. I made contact with the driver identified as Khaalis Raymon Coppock-Bey (B/M DOB: 5/24/1990) via his Maryland Drivers license (MD-10273786918) I was about to conclude the traffic stop, outside my patrol vehicle and approached the front passenger window to provide Coppock-Bey his paperwork for the traffic stop. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="text-autospace:none"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;At approximately 0100 hours as I was approximately five feet from the passenger window I heard the sound of screeching tires and the sound of a collision; before I had a chance to look behind to see what occurred I was pushed forward. I was pushed forward by my patrol vehicle on my lower back region as I managed to turn myself around, tuck in my chin to protect my head from striking the road and braced for the fall with the left side of my body. Upon getting up after being shoved to the ground, I examined myself quickly for any immediate, visible, serious injuries and observed a laceration on my elbow bleeding. I notified over the air for emergency medical services to respond to my location and then clarified that my patrol vehicle has been struck. I immediately checked on the well-being of Coppeck-Bey who advised he was okay as I advised him EMS was enroute and to remain inside the vehicle. I observed the front end of my patrol vehicle has struck the rear end of Coppeck-Bey&amp;rsquo;s Mazda.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="text-autospace:none"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;I attempted to get to the rear of my patrol vehicle to examine the other vehicle and the well-being of any/all occupants inside said vehicle. I observed that my patrol vehicle was against the jersey wall preventing me from walking directly to the rear to examine the other vehicle and occupants(s). I hopped over the jersey wall to the local lane side, moved towards the rear of my vehicle, and hopped over the jersey wall again to the main lane side and observed a maroon minivan occupied four times. I observed the occupants to be the driver later identified as Carlos Alberto Lasso Estrada (H/M DOB: 9/23/1981) via his Maryland Drivers License (L-223-108-041-736) and three children in the passenger seats behind Lasso Estrada. The children were later identified as Carlos, Daniela, and Ricardo Flores. I observed the Minivan&amp;rsquo;s front end has struck the rear left fender area of my patrol vehicle as the minivan was still in the roadway. The children were hysterical and visibly scared as they were asking for help and what happened. I immediately shifted all my attention towards consoling the children and advised them that they were involved in a collision and EMS was enroute. I opened the passenger door to establish contact with Lasso Estrada to ask him what happened as he didn&amp;#39;t provide an answer and my attention was shifted towards the children again as they had their mother on the phone asking what happened. The mother was greatly concerned as I spoke to her in Spanish and advised her that the occupants of the minivan were involved in a collision, are okay, provided her their location, and that EMS was enroute to tend to the children. The mother advised she was on her way as Trooper Stewart #7590 and Trooper Ngoushema #7453 arrived shortly after the collision to assume responsibility of the scene. I checked on Coppeck-Bey again and continued to provide assistance on scene however I could as EMS arrived shortly after; I requested for EMS to tend to the children occupants first and Coppeck-Bey as I was then advised to get treated as well for any other visible/non-visible injuries I might have as a result of the collision. I was transported to Holy Cross hospital in Silver Spring by ambulance PA811 run number: 016 at approximately 0139 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="text-autospace:none"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;I arrived at Holy Cross at approximately 0200 hours when I was under the care of the staff from 0200 hours until 1000 hours when I was released. Results of my injuries were a laceration to my left elbow, a bruise on my leg hip from landing on my MEB, a scrape on the back of my head, and tense soreness in my back and neck area. I was released from Holy Cross at 1000 hours and returned to the College Park Barrack to retrieve items from my now disabled patrol vehicle that had significant damage to its rear left fender, damage on it&amp;#39;s rear right fender, and damage to it&amp;#39;s front bumper.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="text-autospace:none"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;I was advised to see another physician who documented the same injuries and advised I be off-duty until August 23, 2023.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="text-autospace:none"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;All events occurred in Prince George&amp;rsquo;s County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 07:42:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7442</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/01/2023 07:03:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McGee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gonzales</LastName>
            <FirstName>Javier</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7442</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>