<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-029096</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/17/2023 15:22:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/17/2023 15:22:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/17/2023 15:21:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/17/2023 15:21:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Case Information Transferred from Tamp Police Department, Tampa Florida.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 15:22:40</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/10/2024 08:54:00</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>CAC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>13303 Harrison Ave, Fort Washington, MD 20744</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>704134</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 15:22:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 15:30:40</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>704134</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Hanover Ccu</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/17/2023 15:22:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/17/2023 15:22:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>08/23/2023 11:09:52</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 15:22:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/10/2024 08:53:39</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Attachments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Tampa PD Report (Including Subpoenas and Returns)&lt;br /&gt; - Signed Google Search Warrant&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Narrative&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 05/26/2023, TFC Zachary Crowe #6726 Maryland State Police / Maryland Internet Crimes Against Children Task Force, was transferred investigative case data from the Tampa Police Department in Tampa, Florida related to &amp;ldquo;Operation Justice Torch,&amp;rdquo; an operation designed to identify suspects responsible for seeking and/or buying child pornography via Instagram.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In January of 2023, Detective Gregory Van Heyst of the Tampa Police Department conducted an undercover chat with Instagram account delilahxox3, who appeared to be selling self-produced child pornography images and videos. This led to a search warrant being issued for Instagram accounts delilahxox3 and delilahxox4. Hundreds of images/videos constituting child pornography were recovered from the both accounts and with help from the Colorado Springs Police Department, the minor female (DOB: 03-23-2009) featured in the Instagram accounts was identified.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; In April of 2023, Det. Van Heyst conducted a review of the data acquired from Instagram and observed Instant Message conversations between delilahxox3 and johnnymakesitrain. This conversations began on 12/11/2022 at 08:32:36AM (UTC) and ended on 12/14/2022 at 02:30:27AM (UTC). Significant details related to this conversation are set forth below: &lt;div style="margin-left:40px"&gt;- Johnnymakesitrain opened the conversation stating, &amp;ldquo;Hey I&amp;rsquo;m interested&amp;rdquo; (Likely responding to a &amp;quot;Story&amp;quot; posted by delilahxox3 on Instagram)&lt;br /&gt; - Delilahxox3 provided a menu of &amp;ldquo;4 videos for 50$ and 30 pics for 50$ :3&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; - Johnnymakesitrain sent Delilahxox3 a Roblox code for $50 requesting &amp;ldquo;half n half for $50 so like 2 vids n 15 pics&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; - Delilahxox3 sent johnnymakesitrain two videos and 15 pictures featuring the identified minor nude, semi-nude, or in sexually themed poses.&lt;br /&gt; - Johnnymakesitrain acknowledged receiving the material and state &amp;ldquo;Wow&amp;rdquo; followed by &amp;ldquo;If you ever do custom please lmk.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; - Delilahxox3 sent a message apparently in response to being asked her age &amp;ldquo;13!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt; On 04/24/23, Det. Van Heyst transmitted a subpoena to Meta Platforms requesting subscriber information related to numerous accounts suspected of purchasing child pornography from delilahxox3, including johnnymakesitrain. Meta Platforms provided the following information:  &lt;div style="margin-left:40px"&gt;- Service: Instagram&lt;br /&gt; - Internal Ticket Number: 7765354&lt;br /&gt; - Target: 1447990015&lt;br /&gt; - Account Identifier: johnnymakesitrain&lt;br /&gt; - Name: [blank]&lt;br /&gt; - First: JMR&lt;br /&gt; - Registered Email Address: omgitsmetheg123@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt; - Vanity Name: johnnymakesitrain&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt; On 07/26/2023, Det. Van Heyst transmitted a subpoena to Google requesting subscriber information related to the Google account, omgitsmetheg123@gmail.com. Google provided the follow information, set forth below in relevant part:  &lt;div style="margin-left:40px"&gt;- Name: Alex G&lt;br /&gt; - Given Name: Alex&lt;br /&gt; - Family Name: G&lt;br /&gt; - E-Mail: omgitsmetheg123@gmail.com (&amp;quot;TARGET GOOGLE ACCOUNT&amp;quot;)&lt;/div&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Det. Van Heyst observed numerous IP addresses utilized to access the TARGET GOOGLE ACCOUNT and determined them to be a mixture of residential Verizon Fios IP addresses, mobile IPV6 addresses, and possible VPN providers.&amp;nbsp; Det. Van Heyst transmitted a subpoena to Verizon requesting subscriber and service address information pertaining to two residential IP addresses, 96.255.104.101 and 96.255.181.24, which were used to access the TARGET GOOGLE ACCOUNT.&amp;nbsp; Verizon provided the following customer information, set forth below in relevant part: &lt;div style="margin-left:40px"&gt;- Customer Name: OSCAR AVILA&lt;br /&gt; - Account Address: 13303 HARRISON AV FORT WASHINGTON, MD 20744&lt;br /&gt; - Email Address: avilaoscar1973@gmail.com&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt; TFC Crowe reviewed the materials purchased by the Instagram user, johnnymakesitrain.&amp;nbsp; TFC Crowe observed there to be numerous files constituting child pornography.&amp;nbsp; Three of the files are described below:&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div style="margin-left:40px"&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;File Name&lt;/u&gt;: linked_media/unified_message_472938901623871.mp4&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Description&lt;/u&gt;: This is a 26 second color video depicting a fully nude juvenile female exposing her bare vagina, breasts, and buttocks. The juvenile in this video has been identified by law enforcement and determined to be 13 years of age at the time this video was created.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;File Name&lt;/u&gt;: linked_media/unified_message_3454040801588356.mp4&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Description&lt;/u&gt;: This is a 34 second color video depicting a fully nude juvenile female exposing her vagina, breasts, and buttocks. The video appears to be self produced by the juvenile female.&amp;nbsp; The juvenile female has been identified by law enforcement and determined to be 13 years of age at the time this video was created.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;File Name&lt;/u&gt;: linked_media/unified_message_872289283797543.jpg&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Description&lt;/u&gt;: This is a color image depicting a juvenile female nude from the waist down.&amp;nbsp; The juvenile female is hugging her left leg and her bare vagina and anus are the focus of the image. This juvenile female has been identified by law enforcement and determined to be 13 years of age at the time this video was created.&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt; After completing a full analysis of the materials provided by Tampa Police Department, TFC Crowe authored an application for a search and seizure warrant requesting all stored electronic content associated with the TARGET GOOGLE ACCOUNT in order to obtain potential attribution to a single person frequenting or residing within 13303 Harrison Ave, Fort Washington, MD 20744. The warrant was signed by the Honorable Cathy H. Serrette, Judge of the Circuit Court for Prince George&amp;#39;s County on 08/14/2023.&amp;nbsp; TFC Crowe transmitted the signed search warrant to Google via their secure law enforcement portal on 08/17/2023.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Case Status&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Open / Pending&lt;/div&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/17/2023 15:31:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6726</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 18:32:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Crowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6726</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/09/2024 07:34:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/09/2024 07:34:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/10/2024 08:53:38</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/09/2024 07:34:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/10/2024 08:53:39</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Attachments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Google Records Certification&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Narrative&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Since the last update, TFC Crowe received production from Google.&amp;nbsp; During review, TFC Crowe located several photos that appear to depict the owner of the account, but no specific information providing an identity to the subject.&amp;nbsp; Based on the email address, and numerous emails addressed to &amp;quot;Alex,&amp;quot; TFC Crowe reasonably believes the suspect to be a juvenile male named Alex, likely the son of Oscar Avila Garcia, who has a registered address of 13303 Harrison Ave, Fort Washington, MD according to MVA records.&amp;nbsp; This address matches the service address obtained by Tampa Police Department via subpoena. No other individuals registered to the house have last names that start with &amp;quot;G.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; On 01/08/2024, TFC Crowe and TFC Mueller responded to 13303 Harrison Avenue in Fort Washington.&amp;nbsp; Troopers knocked at two entrances to the residence, but neither door was answered.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Because this is likely a juvenile suspect, and with special consideration to escalating caseload numbers, TFC Crowe is requesting this case be suspended pending additional CyberTips related to the suspect or address.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Case Status&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; SUSPENDED</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2024 07:36:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6726</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 07:50:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Crowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6726</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>