<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-029266</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/19/2023 02:06:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/19/2023 02:06:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/19/2023 01:39:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/19/2023 01:39:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was stopped for multiple traffic violations and was found to be driving under the influence of alcohol.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 02:06:12</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4816</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/29/2023 13:17:09</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>704282</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 02:06:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 08:58:41</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>704282</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>199</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Main</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Frostburg</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-78.921676</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.654497</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/19/2023 02:06:08</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/19/2023 02:06:08</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>52</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/27/2023 08:03:29</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 02:06:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:02:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Attachments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DR-15&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; DR-15A&lt;br /&gt; MSP-33&lt;br /&gt; TRAFFIC CITATIONS&lt;br /&gt; DRIVING RECORD/METERS&lt;br /&gt; VEHICLE REGISTRATION/METERS&lt;br /&gt; PHOTOCOPY OF DRIVERS LICENSE/REGISTRATION&lt;br /&gt; FRONT PHOTO OF SUBJECT ON NIGHT OF ARREST&lt;br /&gt; DETENTION LOG&lt;br /&gt; INTOXIMETER WORKHEET&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The DUI Number for the following incident is 23MSP029266/23-083.&lt;br /&gt; C-19 is equipped with an in-car camera and was operational at the time of the incident.&lt;br /&gt; TFC T. Michael is issued a body camera (00017189) and was operational at the time of the incident.&lt;br /&gt; C-19 is equipped with an in-car radar system, which was functioning and calibrated per MSP policies and standards.&lt;br /&gt; C-19 is a marked police unit.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;VIOLATION (Vehicle in Motion):&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; On Saturday, August 19, 2023 at approximately 0139 hours, I was located in a stationary position conducting traffic enforcement in the area of US-40 Alt and Tisdale Street NW in Frostburg, Maryland, Allegany County, Maryland.&amp;nbsp; I observed what appeared to be a red pick-up truck make a right turn onto eastbound US-40 ALT (Main Street) from Lashbaugh&amp;rsquo;s West.&amp;nbsp; I observed the red pick-up truck accelerate rapidly, spinning tires and crossing the double yellow centerline.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I caught up to the red pick-up truck in the area of South Water Street.&amp;nbsp; I was operating the radar in accordance with the manufactures recommendations and specifications.&amp;nbsp; The radar was checked before and after the stop and was working correctly.&amp;nbsp; The radar is a certified speed measuring device.&amp;nbsp; The records are kept at the Maryland State Police Cumberland Barrack.&amp;nbsp; I am a certified RADAR operator certified by the Maryland State Police and the State of Maryland.&amp;nbsp; I observed the red Dodge Ram 2500 bearing Maryland registration 7EC8652 traveling eastbound on US-40 Alt, west of Maple Street.&amp;nbsp; The vehicle appeared to be traveling in access of the posted 25 mph speed limit.&amp;nbsp; The vehicle entered the radar with a speed displayed of 39 mph east of my location.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; While traveling eastbound on US-40 Alt west of Maple Street, I observed the red Dodge Ram 2500 again cross the double yellow centerline and swerve back into the eastbound lane.&amp;nbsp; I activated my emergency lights and stopped the red Dodge Ram 2500, on the right shoulder of eastbound US-40 Alt west of South Grant Street.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Personal Contact)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I exited my vehicle and conducted a driver side approach.&amp;nbsp; I advised the driver that I was a Maryland State Trooper, my name, that the traffic stop was being audibly and visually recorded and my identification number.&amp;nbsp; I advised the driver of the reasons for the traffic stop.&amp;nbsp; The driver handed me his driver&amp;rsquo;s license and continued to attempt to locate his registration.&amp;nbsp; While speaking to the driver, I observed the driver&amp;rsquo;s eyes were red and glassy.&amp;nbsp; While I continued to speak to the driver, I detected the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.&amp;nbsp; I asked the driver if he had anything to drink and he advised that he had a couple beers at Lashbaugh&amp;rsquo;s West.&amp;nbsp; I asked the driver how long prior to the traffic stop his last beer was consumed and he advised a half hour prior to the traffic stop.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The driver was positively identified by his Maryland driver&amp;rsquo;s license as James Leo Michaels 3rd, W/M, DOB 01/07/1979.&amp;nbsp; I verified his address was accurate and returned to my patrol vehicle.&amp;nbsp; Upon a Frostburg City Police Officer arriving on scene to assist with the traffic stop, I conducted a secondary approach to the driver side of the vehicle.&amp;nbsp; I proceeded to ask Michaels to exit the vehicle in order to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Test.&amp;nbsp; Michaels agreed to the Standardized Field Sobriety Test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Pre-Arrest Screening)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I am trained and certified to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. &amp;nbsp;The tests were performed on the right shoulder of US-40 Alt (Main Street), Frostburg, Maryland. &amp;nbsp; The surface of the entrance area was flat and free from debris. Note that the area was illuminated by my vehicle&amp;rsquo;s headlight and spotlight.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Defendants Attire:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Michaels was wearing jeans, and t-shirt. Michaels was wearing tennis shoes at the time of the stop that he deemed to be not comfortable, but better than his work boots he usually wears.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Physical injuries:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Michaels did not advise me of any recent injuries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eyesight:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Michaels advised that he does wear prescription contact lenses and he had them properly in place at the time of testing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Medical Conditions: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Michaels advised that he had issues with both of his knees and when asked for specifics, Michaels advised that he torn his left meniscus.&amp;nbsp; Michaels advised that he broke his back in the past and had herniated discs in his spine.&amp;nbsp; When asked to elaborate, Michaels advised that his L1 to L5 and S1 were herniated.&amp;nbsp; When asked if this issues would prevent him from walking, he advised yes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I advised Michaels that I would take his medical issues into consideration throughout the investigation during the traffic stop.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #1 Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Michaels stated that he could see the stimulus.&amp;nbsp; I advised Michaels that I needed him to follow the stimulus with his eyes and eyes only.&amp;nbsp; I advised Michaels that his head was to remain stationary. &amp;nbsp;The stimulus was held 12-15 inches from Michaels and just above eye level.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;-&amp;nbsp;Michaels had equal pupil size and tracking ability. Michaels displayed lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;6 out of 6&lt;br /&gt; Stimulus: Illuminated tip of finger&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #2: Walk and Turn&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Michaels was placed in the instructional stage, which was demonstrated to Michaels as standing with his right foot in front of the left foot, touching heel-to-toe and arms placed at his sides. Michaels was advised not to deviate from the instructional position, and was advised not to begin the test until told do so.&amp;nbsp; I then proceeded to demonstrate the test by taking three heel to toe steps on line, turn around keeping one foot on line, and return three heel to toe steps.&amp;nbsp; I explained to Michaels that he would have to take nine heel to toe steps and return taking another nine heel to toe steps. I explained that the three steps I took were for demonstration purposes only.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Michaels was not able to maintain the instructional position.&amp;nbsp; On the first attempt, Michaels lost balance, taking a side-step in order to prevent him from falling.&amp;nbsp; On the second attempt, Michaels had to take a step to maintain balance.&amp;nbsp; On the third attempt, he again stumbled and needed to side step in order to maintain balance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; First series of nine steps:&lt;br /&gt; 1. Heel/Toe, Offline, raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 2. Raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 3. Heel/Toe, raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 4. Raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 5. Raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 6. Raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 7. Raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 8. Raised arms&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - Michaels took a total of 8 steps&lt;br /&gt; - After the turn, Michaels took a step and stopped.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Second series of nine steps:&lt;br /&gt; 1. Stopped, raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 2. Raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 3. Heel/Toe, and raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 4. Raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 5. Raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 6. Raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 7. Raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 8. Raised arms&lt;br /&gt; 9. Raised arms&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;6 out of 8&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TEST #3 One Leg Stand&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Michaels was told to stand with his heels together and arms placed at his sides and instructed not to begin the test until told to do so. The test was explained and demonstrated to Michaels by explaining that I wanted him to raise one leg, whichever he felt most comfortable with, approximately six inches off the ground, foot pointed out.&amp;nbsp; Michaels was also instructed to keep both legs straight and to keep his eyes on the elevated foot. While holding that position, count aloud, one thousand and one, one thousand and two, one thousand and three, and so forth until told to stop. &amp;nbsp;Michaels stated that he understood the instructions and agreed to perform the test.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; - Michaels stood on his left foot.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 1 to 10 seconds:&lt;br /&gt; - foot down at approx. 9 seconds&lt;br /&gt; -raised arms&lt;br /&gt; -sway&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 10 to 20 seconds&lt;br /&gt; - foot down at approx. 13 and 18 seconds&lt;br /&gt; - raised arms&lt;br /&gt; -sway&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 20 to 30 seconds&lt;br /&gt; - sway&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;TOTAL CLUES:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;3 of 4&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I asked Michaels if he wished to consent to taking the preliminary breath test.&amp;nbsp; I advised Michaels in detail that the PBT was a voluntary test and would not be used against him in the court of law; however, it is an additional instrument I use during the course of my duties.&amp;nbsp; I advised Michaels that he could refuse the test and I would not use his refusal against him.&amp;nbsp; I advised Michaels that the PBT is used in addition to the results of the SFST&amp;rsquo;s.&amp;nbsp; I advised Michaels that I was offering the PBT in order to better distinguish if his medical issues were effecting his ability to perform the tests correctly.&amp;nbsp; Michaels AGREED to take the PBT.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;PBT results:&amp;nbsp; .10 BAC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;ACTION TAKEN:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Michaels was placed under arrest on August 19, 2023 at approximately 0205 hours.&amp;nbsp; Michaels&amp;rsquo;s mouth observation time began at approximately 0215 hours.&amp;nbsp; Michaels was transported to the Maryland State Police &amp;ndash; Cumberland Barrack, his DR-15 rights were advised, and he AGREED the intoximeter test at 0225 hours.&amp;nbsp; At 0234 hours, Michaels test resulted in .09 BAC.&amp;nbsp; Based on the results, Michaels&amp;rsquo;s license was seized and a DR-15A was issued with a temporary 45 day driver&amp;rsquo;s privilege.&amp;nbsp; A DR-15, DR-15A, citations, MSP 33 and MSP 225 were issued.&amp;nbsp; Michaels was transported home safely by the Maryland State Police.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Based on the above stated facts, I respectfully request this case be closed by arrest.&lt;br /&gt; All events occurred in Allegany County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 09:35:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 07:34:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Barry</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Michael</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6292</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518714</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 02:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 09:21:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 09:23:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518714</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 02:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 09:21:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 09:23:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518714</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 02:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 09:21:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 09:24:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>44</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 09:21:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 09:25:33</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>179255</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Michaels</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leo</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/07/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>02/06/2018 14:04:18</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M242</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Michaels</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leo</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/07/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>M242</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/06/2018 14:04:18</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>216</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Shaw</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>19</SubNumber>
               <City>Frostburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21532</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12006</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Upper Georges Creek</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>SW</StreetSuffixCode>
               <City>Frostburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21532</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-78.935843</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.628829</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>707</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8557</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/06/2018 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 09:25:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 09:25:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 09:25:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 09:25:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 09:21:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 09:21:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156475</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6292</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/26/2023 09:29:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6292</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 09:29:22</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3D7KS28D66G102466</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2006</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>R25</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>RED</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>RED</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7EC8652</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>