<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-022962</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/26/2023 09:30:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/26/2023 09:30:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/26/2023 09:30:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/26/2023 09:30:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Fatal Overdose</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/26/2023 14:40:36</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2436</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 12:59:56</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DSM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>577957</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/26/2023 14:40:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 13:20:19</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>577957</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>9350</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Double Hills</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Denton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.822298</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.863814</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>CAROLINE SHERIFFS DEPARTMENT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/26/2023 14:40:33</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/26/2023 14:40:33</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40F</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:19:56</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/26/2023 14:40:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;On June 26, 2023, at approximately 0900 hours, I, Dfc. Hampton #0223 responded to the area of 920 Market Street, Denton, Caroline County Maryland, to assist Denton Police Dept. on a fatal overdose. Upon arrival, I observed the subject later identified as James Michael Ray Alton Jr. deceased in the parking lot with a hypodermic syringe located in his left hand. It is noted no other CDS items were located on his person at that time. A black cell phone was located on Alton&amp;#39;s person and was seized as evidence for download to be completed by Cpl. Hafer of CCSO. Alton was further observed to have an ankle tracking monitor on his left leg. A subpoena was submitted by Lt. Secrist of Denton Police Dept. in reference Alton&amp;#39;s locations for the 48 hours prior to the fatal overdose.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I received the content download of Alton&amp;#39;s cell phone from Cpl. Hafer on July 12, 2023, and observed multiple cash app transaction, phone calls and text messages to the name &amp;quot;Lady&amp;quot; in Alton&amp;#39;s contact list with the number of 410-829-2582.&amp;nbsp; A search of law enforcement databases revealed that 410-829-2582 is an active Verizon wireless account and subscribed to be Patrina Monique Brandford. The Caroline County Drug Task Force (CCDTF) is familiar with Bradford and has obtained several CDS related tips pertaining to her distributing CDS in the Denton, Caroline County, Maryland area. Based on this information I submitted a preservation request for the content related to the number believed to be utilized by Patrina.&amp;nbsp;At this time I request this case remain open for further investigation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case Status: OPEN&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 13:21:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 14:15:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nichols, II</LastName>
            <FirstName>Leonard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2436</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hampton</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>TF0223</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/16/2023 11:58:47</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/16/2023 11:58:47</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40F</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:19:56</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/16/2023 11:58:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On June 26, 2023, I, Dfc. Hampton #0223 assisted Denton Police Department with a fatal overdose of James Michael Ray Alton Jr. I obtained Alton&amp;rsquo;s cell phone (240-615-0767) during this investigation and observed multiple phone calls, cash app transactions and text messages to 410-829-2582 listed as &amp;ldquo;Lady&amp;rdquo; in Alton&amp;rsquo;s phone. The following messages to 410- 829-2582 from Alton&amp;rsquo;s cell phone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strand # 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;June 25, 2023&amp;nbsp; 8:51 PM&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 240-615-0767&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;I got 9 bags of boy you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t trade me&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;June 25, 2023&amp;nbsp; 8:52 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo; Naw don&amp;rsquo;t fuck with it&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; June 25, 2023&amp;nbsp; 8:52 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp; 240-615-0767&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo; Oh alright&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I know through training, knowledge and experience, as a law enforcement officer and drug investigator that the term &amp;ldquo;boy&amp;rdquo; is a street terminology for CDS.&amp;nbsp; Specifically, boy is used for heroin. The term &amp;ldquo;bags&amp;rdquo; is street terminology for wax folds, commonly used to store approximately 0.1 grams of heroin/fentanyl. I&amp;nbsp;further observed on Alton&amp;rsquo;s Cash App account, multiple payments to Patrina Brandford ($nazandnunu) of different denominations that are common amounts for street level sales of CDS. The account transactions are as follows.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;In 2022, while investigating an unrelated CDS distribution case in the Caroline Apartments, Denton, Caroline County Maryland, Cpl. McInerney also of the CCDTF observed vehicle and foot traffic going to and from apartment 208. Cpl. McInerney further observed a black female, later identified as Patrina Brandford coming and going from the apartment and operating a red Mazda SUV with MD registration 7ER3602. At that time, Cpl. McInerney was not aware of any tips or information regarding CDS distribution coming from that apartment, but the traffic and movement at Brandford&amp;rsquo;s apartment was consistent with the distribution of CDS based on his training, knowledge and experience.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;During the week of June 18, 2023, a concerned anonymous citizen wished to provide information to the Caroline County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Office in reference to heroin and crack cocaine distribution. The Concerned citizen advised a black female by the name &amp;ldquo;Angel&amp;rdquo; known to investigators to be Brandford, was selling heroin and crack cocaine out of Caroline Apartments, Denton, Caroline County Maryland. The Concerned citizen provided &amp;ldquo;Angel&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; cell phone number of 410-829-2582. I conducted a search through law enforcement databases and confirmed the cell phone number subscriber to be Patrina Monique Brandford of 208 Caroline Apartments, Denton, Caroline County Maryland. Anonymous sources, concerned citizens and confidential sources, often wish to provide information regarding illegal activity occurring in their community. These sources wish to remain anonymous to prevent possible detection and retaliation from those they are providing the information about. Remaining anonymous does not deem the information any less reliable than that of someone that is identified.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;During the week of June 18, 2023, Cpl. McInerney was contacted by a confidential source of information (CSOI#1) who advised he/she knew that Brandford is distributing heroin and crack cocaine from apartment 208 Caroline Apartments. CSOI#1 believed that Brandford was working with or being supplied the CDS by her son, Carlos Austin. CSOI#1 has provided information in the past that has been found to be factual. Information provided by the CSOI#1 has been corroborated through investigative means and found to be true. The CSOI#1 has never provided information found to be false or misleading.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; During the week of July 9, 2023, I, conducted a search through multiple law enforcement databases of the Mazda CX7, displaying Maryland registration 7ER3602, registered to Patrina Brandford. The above listed vehicle can be observed by license plate reader digital date and time stamped photographs, traveling west across the Chesapeake Bay Bridge and into Baltimore City, specifically in the areas of Brooklyn Park and Monroe Street. The vehicle is then observed in digital date and time stamped photographs leaving Baltimore City and east across the Chesapeake Bay Bridge within a one to two-hour time frame. Although most westbound and eastbound travel was captured by license plate reader digital photograph, not all can be captured based on traffic condition and travel patterns. The vehicle can be observed between the dates of January 8,&amp;nbsp;2023, to July 10,&amp;nbsp;2023, approximately 10 times. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; I know through training, knowledge, and experience, Baltimore City, specifically the areas of Brooklyn Park and Monroe Street are known to be high drug trafficking area. The CCDTF in prior unrelated investigations has conducted traffic stops on vehicles returning to Caroline County from Baltimore City. As a result of these investigations the CCDTF recovered large amounts of CDS purchased in Baltimore City that was intended to be distributed in Caroline County. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On July 14, 2023, I, conducted surveillance in the area of 208 Caroline Apartments, Denton, Caroline County Maryland. I observed a red Mazda SUV displaying Maryland Registration 7ER3602 entering the apartment complex and parking in front of the 200 building. I further observed the driver and sole occupant to be a black female identified as Patrina Monique Brandford.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On July 19, 2023, Cpl. Stivers conducted a search of numerous law enforcement databases in reference to phone number 410-829-2582. Cpl. Stivers observed on October 14, 2022, Patrina Brandford contacted Denton Police Department to file a complaint of two children playing in the street from the 410-829-2582, further corroborating its use by Brandford.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On July 21, 2023, I, authored a search warrant for SMS/MMS (Text Message) Database/Records Storage System for cellular phone number 410-829-2582, believed to be utilized by Patrina Monique Brandford. The Honorable Judge Heather Price of the Caroline County Circuit Court reviewed and ultimately signed the SMS search warrant. That warrant was submitted to Verizon on July 21, 2023. On July 24, 2023, I obtained those results and found the following messages showing the phone is used by Brandford and for the purpose of distributing CDS.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strand #1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Hello Patrina next week can you work at Vanreuth on Thurs, Fri, and Sun &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot; I&amp;#39;m scheduled already to &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;You wasn&amp;#39;t on there Thursday I want to change take you off Monday and give you thursday&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;So your days next week will be Thurs, Fri and sunday&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Thanks&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Ok whatever works for you!!! Thank you &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;You so sweet thanks for all you do &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Patrina Brandford p.brandford1973@gmail.com \n4108292582 Brandford&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Trina you sent that to me&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The above strand further corroborates that Brandford is utilizing the phone number 410-829- 2582.&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strand #2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt; July 18, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Just seen u called me earlier &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Oh lol my bad probably breast dialed you &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023,Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;I got ya. I need some where r ya&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;About to leave work &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Where u at I head to u&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m on Kent island &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;When are u leaving work. I meet u somewhere &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;2:30&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Ok I&amp;#39;m leaving easton heading that way. Call me when u leaving &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;U got me or no&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;July 18, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;quot;Me too&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;July 18, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;What!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;July 18, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m leaving &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Wanna meet me at uncle marvins?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;ldquo;Ok&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; July 18, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;What u want&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Through my training, knowledge, and experience, I know text message conversations referring to CDS and CDS transactions are vague or written in code to avoid detection by law enforcement. The above strand shows though it is unknown what type of CDS is being purchased the &amp;ldquo;I got ya. I need some where r ya&amp;rdquo; is the CDS user requesting to meet Brandford to purchase CDS. Your affiant knows, typically CDS transactions are pre-determined locations that both parties have completed successful transactions prior and feel it is a safe area to meet. I believe &amp;ldquo;Wanna meet at uncle marvins&amp;rdquo; is that pre-determined location. I further know, CDS users typically purchase different amounts of CDS each transaction based on how much they can purchase at that time and the &amp;ldquo;what u want&amp;rdquo; is Brandford requesting how much CDS they want at this transaction.&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strand #3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:16px"&gt; July 21, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Good morning tell me something good!!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 21, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Who dat&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 21, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Angel&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 21, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;What up&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 21, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Everything Everything??&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 21, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Wwya wyd ??&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 21, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m home and what the prices on them shoes for size 7 and 10.5&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 21, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;150 &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 21, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Ball&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 21, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;4 for 3&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 21, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;Ok she right? &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; July 21, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582 &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ll grab it&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I know based on training, knowledge and experience, in the strand above the terms &amp;ldquo;Ball&amp;rdquo; is a common CDS terminology for an (8) eight ball, or an amount of cocaine that is approximately 3.5 grams in weight. I further know, an (8) eight-ball is sold in Caroline County for approximately $150.00. Typically, larger CDS distributors will lower the selling price if a larger amount is purchased in bulk. I believe Brandford is purchasing a large amount of cocaine for distribution.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; On 8/8/23, I, authored a second search warrant for SMS/MMS (Text Message) Database/Records Storage System for cellular phone number 410-829-2582 that was ultimately reviewed and signed by the Honorable Judge Heather Price of Caroline County Circuit Court. The signed search warrant was sent to Verizon Wireless and is currently pending content.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I request this case remain open pending further investigation.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case Status: Open.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/16/2023 11:59:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/30/2023 13:19:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nichols, II</LastName>
            <FirstName>Leonard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2436</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hampton</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>TF0223</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/29/2023 09:20:40</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/29/2023 09:20:40</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40F</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:19:56</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 09:20:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On August 8, 2023, I, Dfc. Hampton #0223, authored a second search warrant for SMS/MMS (Text Message) Database/Records Storage System for cellular phone number 410-829-2582, believed to be utilized by Patrina Monique Brandford. The Honorable Judge Heather Price of the Caroline County Circuit Court reviewed and ultimately signed the SMS search warrant. That warrant was submitted to Verizon on August 8, 2023.&amp;nbsp; On September 11, 2023, I, obtained those results and found the following messages showing the phone is used by Brandford and for the purpose of distributing CDS.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strand #1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo; Hey&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo; Yo&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;\0C\0a\0n \0t\0 \0t\0a\0l\0k\0 &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Why u text me then&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;I know what I want to eat&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;See where are &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Don&amp;#39;t talk shit white boy lol&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;Now wtf u at a C bitch hungry&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Lol sorry I&amp;#39;m hot and out of smokes.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I&amp;#39;m getting ready to leave Cordova &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Don&amp;#39;t be giving me light bag today either.&amp;nbsp; Lol&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Lmk when u passing college&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Ok&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;I want el Jeffers&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Ok &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Send me address to u&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;204 shopping creek drive &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Shopping? &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Shipping &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 28, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Okay&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I know based on training, knowledge and experience in the above strand, the term &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;#39;t be giving me light bag today either.&amp;nbsp; Lol&amp;quot; is CDS terminology for amount of CDS that is less than the CDS user requested and purchased from the CDS distributor. It further corroborates the CDS user has conducted prior transactions with Brandford and has received less CDS than expected. I know CDS distributors will state to the CDS user they are receiving a certain amount of CDS however; will provide them with a lesser amount while still charging the same price to further their product.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strand #2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Hey&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;Who this&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;Can I come&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;200 &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;No r u sending her te money then I&amp;#39;ll tell u where it is&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Sent it&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;It&amp;#39;s whatever she made earlier &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;OkY where am I going&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Hold up lemme get her up&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Imma cook more so she can rest and put under mat in car give b m e a few to cook&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Can he leave now and just wait?&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Yes &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Whose he&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Incoming 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;My husband&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Tell him don&amp;#39;t go over by office stop in front of her car and grab under mat and dont lock door please &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;July 29, 2023, Outgoing 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;\nPassengers side&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I know based on training, knowledge and experience, the above strand, specifically &amp;ldquo;200 &amp;quot; and &amp;quot;No r u sending her te money then I&amp;#39;ll tell u where it is&amp;quot; is requesting $200.00 payment through a third-party payment application before telling the CDS user where they can pick up the CDS. I know, the strand &amp;quot;Imma cook more so she can rest and put under mat in car give b m e a few to cook&amp;quot; is advising the CDS user the CDS must be cooked before they can come to pick up the cooked product under the floor mat of her vehicle. I further know that powder cocaine is cooked into crack cocaine and based off prior confidential sources of information, crack cocaine is said to be distributed by Brandford.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strand #3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;Hey&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &amp;ldquo; What&amp;rsquo;s up&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &amp;ldquo;Not much how was your day. U work tomorrow&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &amp;ldquo;Yup In Baltimore 6am to 8pm putting gas in my car now then bed I go&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &amp;ldquo;What time u going through by royal farms in queen anne &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;4:30&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;God damn it.&amp;nbsp; I meet you there if u give me specific time in morning &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;No&amp;nbsp; not meeting anyone tomorrow&amp;nbsp; gotta a coworker riding so Come now or wait until tomorrow night&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;You meet at royal farms now?&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;How much &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;100&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;Goose Creek&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;I can&amp;#39;t come that far hun&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot; bring it or no&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Ok well my girl about to leave here maybe she will meet you bc I&amp;#39;m not coming that far nooo !! I&amp;#39;m about to stop anyway delivering altogether so want her&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;If she coming now yes&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;Ok&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;Yes leaving here in 10&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;I will just meet with you tomorrow hun.&amp;nbsp; Thank you anyway.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I got to work tomorrow anyway &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Ok so why take me through all that now she got my snit &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;Bye can&amp;#39;t do games!!&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;I will be there if she not long &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;August 4, 2023, Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;U meet me at royal farms for 150?&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I know based on training, knowledge, and experience, typically text message conversations referring to CDS and CDS transactions are vague or written in code to avoid detection by law enforcement. The above strand shows though it is unknown what type of CDS is being purchased the &amp;quot;How much &amp;quot; and &amp;ldquo;100&amp;rdquo; is Brandford requesting how much CDS the CDS user wants to purchase. I know the &amp;quot;Ok well my girl about to leave here maybe she will meet you bc I&amp;#39;m not coming that far nooo !! I&amp;#39;m about to stop anyway delivering altogether so want her&amp;quot; further corroborates that Brandford has been and still is utilizing her red Mazda SUV displaying Maryland Registration 7ER3602 and cell phone number 410-829-2582 to complete CDS transactions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; During the week of September 23, 2023, I conducted surveillance on Brandford&amp;rsquo;s red Mazda SUV displaying Maryland Registration 7ER3602. I observed Brandford as the driver and the sole occupant in the vehicle, leave her residence of 208 Caroline Apartments, Denton Maryland and travel to multiple residence and travel to the Goose Creek Convenience store, in Denton Maryland. It is noted, I observed Brandford stay briefly at each of these locations before exiting and traveling to the next. I observed Brandford stay for a brief period and left the area traveling west bound on Shore Highway. I then observed Brandford exit Shore highway and park in the side parking lot of Royal Farms located in Queen Anne Maryland. I observed a white female approach Brandford&amp;rsquo;s driver side window and exchange an unknown amount of U.S. currency to Brandford through the driver side window. I then observed Branford exit the Royal farms parking lot and continue west on Shore Highway. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I know based on training, knowledge, and experience, as a law enforcement officer and a narcotics investigator that the Goose Creek convenience store located in Denton, Maryland and the Royal Farms store located in Queen Anne, Maryland are known areas where CDS transactions are conducted. I know that CDS transactions take place in public areas such as convenience stores, gas stations and public parking lots due to the high volume of vehicle and foot traffic, for both the CDS distributor and CDS consumer to hide in plain sight to avoid detection from law enforcement. I know CDS transactions are conducted in public areas by hand-to-hand exchanges of U.S. currency and CDS. I further know that Brandford&amp;rsquo;s travel patterns are indicative of conducting CDS transactions in multiple sales in multiple locations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; During the week of September 23, 2023, I conducted surveillance on Brandford&amp;rsquo;s red Mazda SUV displaying Maryland Registration 7ER3602. I observed the vehicle being operated by Lamonte Jackson and Tamera Bordley as the front seat passenger, leave 103 Riverview Gardens and travel to 111 Liberty Road, Federalsburg, Caroline County Maryland. I observed both Lamonte and Tamera only stay at the above address for a brief period before leaving and traveling to the Royal Farms store located at the corner of Shore Highway and Harmony Road. While conducting surveillance I observed the red Mazda SUV displaying Maryland registration 7ER3602 parked in a parking space, on the north side of the Royal Farms store. I observed Lamonte seated in the driver seat and Tamera standing near the front entrance of the store. I observed Tamera continuously look throughout the parking lot and check the area while standing in front of the store. I did not observe Tamera enter the store at any time and Tamera appeared to be waiting for someone. I observed Tamera walk to and enter the passenger side of the Mazda at which time Lamonte reversed out of the parking space on the side of the store and moved the vehicle to the front of the store and back into a parking space. I then observed a silver in color Dodge Durango quickly pull into the parking spot next to the red Mazda SUV with Lomonte and Tamera seated in it. Its noted the brake lights were illuminated on the dodge Durango at this time and it did not appear the vehicle was placed into park. I observed Tamera exit the passenger side of the Red SUV and approach the Dodge Durango, a brief hand to hand interaction between Tamera and the driver of the Dodge took place and Tamera left the driver window and reentered the passenger side of the Mazda SUV. I then observed both vehicles quickly leave the parking lot in opposite directions. I further observed Lamonte and Tamera return to 103 Riverview Gardens Apartment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;big&gt; On September 9, 2023&lt;/big&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I, authored a second search warrant for SMS/MMS (Text Message) Database/Records Storage System for cellular phone number 410-829-2582.The Honorable Judge Heather Price of the Caroline County Circuit Court reviewed and ultimately signed the SMS search warrant and was submitted to Verizon on September 26, 2023.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; I request this case remain open pending results of SMS/MMS search warrant.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case Status: OPEN.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 09:21:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 12:56:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nichols, II</LastName>
            <FirstName>Leonard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2436</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hampton</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>TF0223</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/14/2023 09:46:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/14/2023 09:46:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40F</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:19:56</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 09:46:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident&lt;/strong&gt;: Residential/ Person/ Vehicle Search Warrant Execution&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date/Time&lt;/strong&gt;: 11/09/2023, 0715 hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Locations&lt;/strong&gt;: 208 Caroline Apartments, Denton, Caroline County MD.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 103 Riverview Gardens, Denton, Caroline County MD.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suspect 1&lt;/strong&gt;: Patrina Monique Brandford&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; B/F 10/03/1973&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suspect 2&lt;/strong&gt;: Tamera Monique Bordley&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; B/F 02/16/1999&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suspect 3&lt;/strong&gt;: Lamonte Damar Jackson&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; B/M 03/01/1997&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Evidence Seized from 208 Caroline Apartments:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Evidence Bag #1:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ITEM A: One (1) clear plastic bag containing suspect Cocaine;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Weight: 3.0 grams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Location: Bed side table of Brandford&amp;rsquo;s bedroom&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Evidence Bag #2:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ITEM B: Two (2) $1.00 bill U.S. currency and clear-cut straw containing suspected Cocaine;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Weight: 0.1 grams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Location: Bed side table of Brandford&amp;rsquo;s bedroom&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Evidence Bag #3:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ITEM C: One (1) operational digital scale (black in color) containing suspected Cocaine;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Weight: Trace&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Location: Bed side table of Brandford&amp;rsquo;s bedroom inside a Kleenex tissue box&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Evidence Bag #4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ITEM D: $727.00 U.S. dollars in a stack, in multiple denominations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Location: Bed side table of Brandford&amp;rsquo;s bedroom.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ITEM E: One (1) Prescription pill bottle without prescription label containing Four (4) Tramadol pills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Location: Inside of handbag, next to Brandford&amp;rsquo;s bed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ITEM F: One (1) white and gold in color Apple IPhone belonging to Brandford.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Location: On bed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Evidence Seized from 103 Riverview Gardens:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Evidence Bag #1:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Item A: One (1) operational digital scale (black in color);&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Location: Entertainment stand in Tamera&amp;rsquo;s bedroom&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;NON CDS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ITEM #B: One (1) blue Motorola smart phone claimed by Tamera, (Serial#: Unknown, Model: Unknown)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Located on Tamera&amp;rsquo;s bed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Incident captured on body worn cameras&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Entry teams- MSP S.T.A.T.E. Teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;208 Caroline Apts. Search Team-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Dfc. Hampton (seizing, CCSO/CCDTF)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cpl. McInerney (MSP/CCDTF)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lt. Paugh (CCSO/CID)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cpl. Hafer (CCSO/CID)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;103 Riverview Gardens Apts. Search Team-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;M/Tpr. Vansant (seizing, MSP/CCDTF)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sgt. Flamma (MSP/TCNTF)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cpl. Royer (TCSO/TCNTF)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dfc. Beck (CCSO/CID)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On November 9, 2023, at approximately 0715 hours, I, Dfc. Hampton and members of the CCDTF assisted by the Caroline County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office Criminal Investigation Division, Uniformed Denton Police Department, and Maryland S.T.A.T.E Team simultaneously, executed the search and seizure warrants on 208 Caroline Apartments, Denton, Caroline County, Maryland, Patrina Monique Brandford and 2014 Mazda CX5 red in color, displaying Maryland registration number 7ER3602, 103 Riverview Gardens, Denton, Caroline County, Maryland. The warrants stemmed from numerous citizen complaints from 2022 to current date. The citizens complaints advised heavy vehicle and foot traffic consistent with drug trafficking. During surveillance operations Dfc. Hampton of the CCDTF observed numerous individuals whom he was familiar with as drug users coming from and going to the apartment. Dfc. Hampton further observed Brandford&amp;rsquo;s vehicle movements during the surveillance operations in the red Mazda CX5 to multiple public locations, residences, and convenience stores and conducting hand-to-hand transactions with individuals from the vehicle to be indicative of CDS sales and delivery. Throughout multiple surveillance operations, Dfc. Hampton observed Brandford frequent 103 Riverview Gardens, Denton, Caroline County Maryland and conduct hand to hand transactions from the vehicle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Dfc. Hampton further observed the red Mazda CX5 was being shared with a male and female subject that resided at 103 Riverview Gardens, who were later identified as Tamera Monique Bordley and Lamonte Damar Jackson and learned Bordley to be Brandford&amp;rsquo;s daughter. While conducting further surveillance operations, Dfc. Hampton observed the red Mazda CX5 being operated by Jackson and Bordley being the passenger, travel to a convenience store location and observe Bordley conduct hand to hand interactions with individuals in the parking lot that were indicative of CDS transactions. Further Dfc. Hampton observed these same interactions with foot and vehicle traffic being conducted by Bordley, Jackson and Brandford outside of the residence of 103 Riverview Gardens. Dfc. Hampton was able to identify these individuals whom he was familiar with as drug users coming from and going to the apartment or meeting with Bordley, Jackson and Brandford directly in front of 103 Riverview Gardens, with Bordley and Jackson making frequent trips to the apartment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Through the corroborated tips and observations made by Dfc. Hampton, probable cause was developed for a search and seizure warrant for 208 Caroline Apartments, 103 Riverview Gardens, Patrina Brandford, Tamera Bordley and the 2014 Red Mazda CX5 and any other persons within the residence at the time of service. The warrants were authorized by the Honorable Judge Heather L. Price for the Circuit Court of Caroline County. &amp;nbsp;At approximately 0715 hours MSP S.T.A.T.E Team made entry into 208 Caroline Apartments, Denton, Caroline County MD. Through the front door of the apartment that was unsecured. Patrina Monique Brandford (B/F DOB: 10/03/1973) was positively identified and located inside the residence of 208 Caroline Apartments. It is noted no other occupants were located inside the residence. At that time, the Suspect was detained, and a search of the residence was conducted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;During the search of the residence several items of evidentiary value were located. In the rear bedroom of the apartment on the bedside table Lt. Paugh of CCSO located One (1) clear plastic bag containing suspect Cocaine (item A), Two (2) $1.00 bill U.S. currency and clear-cut straw containing suspected Cocaine (item B), One (1) operational digital scale (black in color) containing suspected Cocaine (item C) and $727.00 U.S. dollars in a stack, in multiple denominations (item D). All items of suspected cocaine and of distribution were identified through Dfc. Hampton&amp;rsquo;s training, knowledge and experience as a Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Deputy and a narcotics investigator. Dfc. Hampton has received several hours of specialized training in drug trends, identification, and investigative techniques by subject matter experts in their fields. Further Dfc. Hampton has conducted numerous CDS related investigations throughout his career, leading to arrests and conviction in Caroline County District and Circuit Courts. Further located in a tan in color handbag was a prescription pill bottle with the label rubbed off, inside of the bottle were (4) four Tramadol pills and one (1) white and gold in color Apple IPhone belonging to Brandford (item F). It should be noted that Brandford&amp;rsquo;s phone continued to alert through the entirety of the execution of this search warrant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Cpl. McInerney of the CCDTF located in the top left cabinet of the kitchen, a bulk amount of baking soda. Further Cpl. McInerney located a Pyrex measuring cup that appeared to be wet from being freshly cleaned. &amp;nbsp;Dfc. Hampton knows through training, Knowledge and experience that baking soda is used during the process of converting Cocaine-Hydrochloride to Crack Cocaine and is typically prepared in cooking ware such as Pyrex. At that time a field test was conducted on the Pyrex, utilizing a NIK cocaine ID swab, yielding a positive presence of a very small amount of cocaine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Brandford was advised of her Miranda Rights by Dfc. Hampton at approximately 0723 and read the signed search warrants while she was seated on the living room couch. Brandford voluntarily admitted to using cocaine and stated when advised the $727.00 was being seized &amp;ldquo;that 727 is going to be a loss&amp;rdquo;. All evidence and currency was seized by Dfc. Hampton and processed according to agency policy and procedure. The total amount of $727.00 was deposited at the Caroline County Tax Office where it will be held pending forfeiture. Brandford was released pending an application of charges.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Simultaneously, members of the CCDTF assisted by the Talbot County Narcotics Task Force, Denton Police Department and Maryland S.T.A.T.E Team also, executed the search and seizure warrants on 103 Riverview Gardens, Denton Caroline County Maryland. At that time Tamera Monique Bordley (B/F DOB: 02/16/1999) and Lamonte Damar Jackson (B/M 03/01/1997) were positively identified and located inside the residence of 103 Riverview Gardens. Members of CCDTF advised both Tamera and Lamonte would not open the front door of the residence for entry upon initial contact. M/Tpr. Vansant advised few items of evidentiary value were located inside the residence. M/Tpr. Vasant advised One (1) operational digital scale (black in color) was located on the bedroom entertainment center and (1) blue in color Motorola cell phone located on the bed. M/Tpr. further advised that located in the bedroom of the residence was a black in color duffle bag that contained a safe with the key in the locking mechanism and the safe door was unsecured. It is believed the entry was delayed by Tamera and Lamonte so the contents of the safe could be discarded. Both parties were released pending an application of charges. M/Tpr. Vansant seized and processed all evidence according agency policy and procedure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Subsequent to search warrants, Dfc. Hampton authored two (2) additional search warrants for the cell phones seized during the execution of the residential search warrants, belonging to Patrina Brandford and Tamera Bordley that were reviewed and signed by the Honorable Judge Heather Price. Downloads of both phones are currently pending.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; All evidence was transported to the CCDTF office and processed according to agency policy and procedure. The suspected cocaine was field tested with a NIK swab and immediately turned blue showing the positive presence of Cocaine, a schedule II drug. The items were stored according t policy and will be forwarded to the lab for additional testing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; All events did occur in Caroline County, Maryland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I request this case remain open pending further investigation and application of charges.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 09:47:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/21/2023 12:14:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McInerney</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5935</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hampton</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>TF0223</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>512399</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0233</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>3</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/26/2023 09:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0233</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 10:17:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 10:17:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>512399</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>3</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/26/2023 09:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/20/2023 12:44:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 12:44:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>49</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 10:13:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 10:13:45</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>109430</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Brandford</LastName>
               <FirstName>Patrina</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Monique</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/03/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2016 14:31:43</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B653</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P365</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Brandford</LastName>
               <FirstName>Patrina</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Monique</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/03/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B653</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P365</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2016 14:31:43</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4506</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Main</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Grasonville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.20616606068438</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.95883670505541</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>739</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5463</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/26/2016 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 10:13:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 10:17:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 10:17:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 09:54:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 10:40:01</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>3.0 grams of powder cocaine</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256504</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>3</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 09:57:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 10:38:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Two (2) $1.00 bills of US currency and one (1) cut straw containing suspected powder cocaine. Total weight:0.1 grams</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256505</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>3</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 10:00:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 10:35:03</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) pill bottle with prescription label removed, containing four (4) Tramadol pills,  </Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256506</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>H</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>4</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 10:01:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 12:55:23</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One (1) black in color working digital scale with suspected powder cocaine residue.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256507</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>B</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 10:03:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 12:51:48</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>C</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>CSH</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>727</PropertyValue>
         <Value>727</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256509</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>0</Quantity>
         <Amount>727</Amount>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 10:05:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 12:51:37</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One Apple iPhone seized for further invesigation</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>489</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256510</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>WHI</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>GLD</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>Apple</Make>
         <Model>Iphone</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/14/2023 10:47:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 12:51:26</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>One working digital scale from 103 Riverview Gardens Apartment</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>101</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256512</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>SIL</SecondaryColor>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/28/2023 13:24:55</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/28/2023 13:24:55</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40F</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:19:56</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 13:24:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #4 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>See Attached GPS Order.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/28/2023 13:32:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/28/2023 13:32:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nichols, II</LastName>
            <FirstName>Leonard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2436</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hampton</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>TF0223</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>5</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/21/2023 10:48:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/21/2023 10:48:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40F</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/18/2024 17:19:56</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE SENT</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 10:48:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #5 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size:14px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On November 14, 2023, I, Cpl. Hampton #0223, authored a cellular phone download search warrant to extract all content for Patrina Brandford&amp;#39;s cellular phone number 410-829-2582, that was seized on 11/09/2023 during the execution of residential search warrant of 208 Caroline Apartments, Denton Caroline County Maryland. The Honorable Judge Heather Price of the Caroline County Circuit Court reviewed and ultimately signed the Cellular phone download search warrant. That warrant was submitted to Cpl. Hafer of the Caroline County Sheriff&amp;#39;s Office on November 14, 2023.&amp;nbsp; On November 28, 2023, I, obtained those results and found the following messages showing the phone is used by Brandford and for the purpose of distributing CDS.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strand #1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 2:43 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &amp;ldquo;Can you come to me?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 2:44 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 4435263293 &amp;ldquo;Im at work until&amp;nbsp; 7 I&amp;#39;m trying to get outta here early&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 2:44 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 4435263293 &amp;ldquo;Unless you send Dionus to me&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 2:45 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &amp;ldquo;Can you cook&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 3:05 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 4435263293 &amp;ldquo;He knows were to get it done at right ther where we live&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153873887"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 3:05 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&lt;/a&gt; &amp;ldquo;The same stuff?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 3:06 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 4435263293 &amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153873836"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 3:09 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 4435263293 &lt;/a&gt;&amp;ldquo;Ask him of major can come to him&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153873990"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 4:00 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 4435263293 &amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hey&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 4:00 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &amp;ldquo;You off?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 4:00 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 4435263293&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;No&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 4:00 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 4435263293&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;Tell major to pick him up nd come to me&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153874190"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 4:41 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 4435263293&amp;nbsp; &lt;/a&gt;Guess who&amp;#39;s about to get off&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153881754"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I know through my training knowledge and experience as a law enforcement officer and a narcotics investigator &lt;/a&gt;that powder cocaine is &amp;ldquo;cooked&amp;rdquo; utilizing baking soda and Pyrex containers during the process of converting Cocaine-Hydrochloride to Crack Cocaine. I believe the above message &amp;ldquo;Can you cook&amp;rdquo; is the CDS user requesting Brandford to cook crack cocaine. It is noted, during the execution of the search warrant to Brandford&amp;rsquo;s residence on 11/09/2023, a Pyrex container was located in the kitchen that when field tested utilizing a NIK cocaine swab, resulting in a positive result.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Strand #2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153874037"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 8:30 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 2677685029&amp;nbsp; &lt;/a&gt;- Yoooo hit me important&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 8:36 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 2677685029&amp;nbsp; Yooo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 8:41 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 2677685029&amp;nbsp; That shit last night Is not right this is too much I can have this shit on my conscious&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 8:41 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 2677685029&amp;nbsp; (photo of positive fentanyl home test)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 21, 2023&amp;nbsp; 8:50 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 2677685029&amp;nbsp; Wake up wake up wake up!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I know through my training knowledge and experience as a law enforcement officer and a narcotics investigator that CDS distributors will often utilize fentanyl as a cutting agent in various different types CDS to encourage the reputation or &amp;ldquo;street credit&amp;rdquo; of the CDS they are distributing. The above thread is Brandford messaging the individual she purchased an unknown amount of CDS from that appears to have resulted in a positive home test for fentanyl. Due to the picture of an home fentanyl test strip showing the positive presence of fentanyl and the message &amp;ldquo;That shit last night Is not right this is too much I can have this shit on my conscious&amp;rdquo; that Brandford is unhappy that she purchased an amount of CDS for distribution from a larger CDS distributor and does not want to distribute the CDS that contains fentanyl.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strand #3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153874235"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 01:57 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &lt;/a&gt;&amp;ldquo;Are you up&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153874285"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:18 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; &lt;/a&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am now&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153874308"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:18 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &lt;/a&gt;&amp;ldquo;Can I come&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:19 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;Depends what&amp;#39;s the number&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:19 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:21 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;Ok I gotta make it&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:22 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;Can I come there&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:23 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;No&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:23 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; Imma text when to leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:30 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; Come on&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153874572"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:32 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; &lt;/a&gt;Going bk to bed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153874726"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:34 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &lt;/a&gt;I had to get ready. Do you want to wait?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:35 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; Dionus is there waiting smh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:37 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; He&amp;#39;s probably PISSED YALL NEED TO STOP PLAYING CRACKHEAD GAMES HES PUT THERE RISKING HIS LIHE AND YALL PKAYING GAMES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153874777"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:38 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &lt;/a&gt;No one is playing games I&amp;rsquo;m getting yelled at and baby is out of formula. Do you know anywhere open?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153874803"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:40 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; &lt;/a&gt;Rachel I don&amp;#39;t have shir to. Do with that u asked. For something and he&amp;#39;s there and u still home bc Rachel you know the same spots I do now you call dionus and tell him it&amp;#39;s ok tell me how that goes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:40 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 - What&amp;rsquo;s his number&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153874858"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:42 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; &lt;/a&gt;U got his number stop playing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153874877"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:43 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &lt;/a&gt;- No we don&amp;rsquo;t&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:43 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; 4 o&amp;#39;clock in the Fuckin&amp;nbsp; morning you asking for shit u cant even pay for&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:43 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a name="_Hlk153874973"&gt;Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582 &amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m sorry what,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153875103"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:43 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &lt;/a&gt;It has nothing to do with money I have money.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153875036"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:45 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; &lt;/a&gt;4103107662 just call him and tell him ya lies I hope he smack the fuck outta you!! This not the first time u doing this&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153875211"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:45 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 443-526-3293&amp;nbsp; &lt;/a&gt;No u don&amp;rsquo;t just call him&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 03:50 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; Yes I do. Major is being a dick.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 04:00 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; Can I send it on his cash app?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 04:02 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; - Call me&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 04:07 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &lt;a name="_Hlk153883328"&gt;Major had the 200 im trying to send him $50 for waiting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 04:08 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; Can he come out there?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 04:10 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; I can&amp;rsquo;t reach anyone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153875305"&gt;October 22, 2023&amp;nbsp; 04:11 AM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &lt;/a&gt;Can you answer me?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I know through my training knowledge and experience as a law enforcement officer and a narcotics investigator that powder cocaine is &amp;ldquo;cooked&amp;rdquo; utilizing baking soda during the process of converting Cocaine-Hydrochloride to Crack Cocaine. Further the telephone number in this message thread is the same individual requesting Brandford to cook in message thread #1. The message &amp;ldquo;Ok I gotta make it&amp;rdquo; is Brandford advising that she has to cook the powder cocaine into crack cocaine. Further Brandford refers to this individual to be &amp;ldquo;playing crackhead games&amp;rdquo; and the term &amp;ldquo;crackhead&amp;rdquo; is street terminology for a person who is addicted to crack cocaine. I further know that the message &amp;ldquo;Major had the 200 im trying to send him $50 for waiting&amp;rdquo; is the CDS user advising they had the money to purchase $200.00 worth of CDS and wanted to provide and extra $50.00 for prolonging the CDS transaction.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strand #4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;a name="_Hlk153876901"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 12:01 PM&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Are you working today&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 12:02 PM &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Outgoing 443-473-5770 &amp;nbsp;Yes what&amp;rsquo;s up&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 12:03 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Just trying to get up with you to get something&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 12:03 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing 443-473-5770&amp;nbsp; I&amp;#39;m on Kent island&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 12:03 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I&amp;#39;m on my way to the outlets can I come to you&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153877079"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 12:18 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing 443-473-5770&amp;nbsp; &lt;/a&gt;Yes just bring food like you door dash lmk when u otw I&amp;#39;ll tell u what to grab and send address&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 12:21 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; K&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 12:55 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Spanky&amp;#39;s design at the outlets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153877099"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 12:55 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/a&gt;Spankies is at the outlets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 12:56 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing 443-473-5770&amp;nbsp; Ok I&amp;#39;ll take that what&amp;#39;s on the menu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 12:57 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I text you back in a minute&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 13:00 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing 443-473-5770&amp;nbsp; I want catfish nuggets greens and potato salad&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 13:06 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing 443-473-5770&amp;nbsp; 204 shipping creek drive Stevensville Md&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 13:39 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Outgoing 443-473-5770&amp;nbsp; You left the outlets yet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;a name="_Hlk153877359"&gt;November 2, 2023&amp;nbsp; 13:39 PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Incoming&amp;nbsp; 410-829-2582&amp;nbsp; &lt;/a&gt;I am here i&amp;#39;m not going on the door&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;I know through my training knowledge and experience as a law enforcement officer and a narcotics investigator &lt;/span&gt;and a law enforcement officer, that CDS users and distributors will often utilize code or vague terminology when conducting transactions. I believe the message &amp;quot;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Just trying to get up with you to get something&amp;quot; is the CDS user requesting to purchase CDS from Brandford. I further know due to prior text messages I have observed during this investigation, Brandford has requested the CDS user to purchase food and deliver it to Brandford&amp;#39;s place of employment. I know the message &amp;quot;Yes just bring food like you door dash lmk when u otw I&amp;#39;ll tell u what to grab and send address&amp;quot; is&amp;nbsp;Brandford portraying the CDS user as a food delivery service to disguise the CDS transaction. I further know the message&amp;nbsp; &amp;quot;204 shipping creek drive Stevensville Md&amp;quot; is Brandfords place of employment that has been identified earlier in this investigation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; At this time I request this case remain open pending the indictment of Brandford through the Caroline County States Attorneys Office.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Case Status:Open&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>TF0223</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 10:49:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>TF0223</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/26/2023 09:42:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nichols, II</LastName>
            <FirstName>Leonard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2436</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40F</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hampton</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>TF0223</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>