<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002632</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/21/2023 22:48:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/21/2023 22:48:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/21/2023 22:48:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/21/2023 22:48:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI Ariel Duffy</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/21/2023 23:06:12</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 22:38:53</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>COASTAL HWY/ 45TH ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>537262</AddressId>
      <City>MDC208</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/21/2023 23:06:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/29/2023 10:58:20</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>537262</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Coastal</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.070502</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.371251</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4501-4535 COASTAL HWY / 0-0 45TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4401-4439 COASTAL HWY / 0-0 45TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 COASTAL HWY / 1-20 45TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4401-4499 COASTAL HWY / 0-0 45TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/21/2023 23:06:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/21/2023 23:06:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/30/2023 06:51:41</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/21/2023 23:06:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP marked vehicle V-11 is equipped with a mobile recording device  Defendant: Ariel Shacurtis Duffy Driver license #: MD D-100-071-765-103 Date of Birth: 2/8/1992 Date of Arrest: 1/21/23 Time of Arrest: 2307 DUI #: 23-96-015 PBT Results: .15 Intoximeter Results: .14 Subsequent Offender: NO CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING -Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On January 21, 2023, at approximately 2248 hours, Trooper First Class C. Shubert #7062 with the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack was on-duty operating unmarked patrol vehicle V-11 in the area of Coastal Highway and 42nd St, Ocean City, Worcester County, Maryland 21842. At that time I was traveling northbound in lane two when I observed in front of me in lane two a tan Chevy Malibu bearing Maryland registration (8EX8054) that appeared to be traveling above the posted speed limit of 35MPH. I then activated my Kustom Golden Eagle radar unit front antenna and obtained a digital speed reading of 44MPH in a posted 35MPH speed zone. My radar unit was tested prior and after my shift and was working properly. While following the vehicle, the vehicle made and illegal U-turn in a construction zone at 45th St. I then activated my emergency equipment. The vehicle did not stop immediately when I activated my emergency equipment. The vehicle eventually moved to the right side of the road and stopped.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I exited my patrol vehicle and made contact with the driver and passengers and advised them why they were being stopped. While speaking with the driver I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the drivers breath and person and bloodshot and glassy eyes, slurred speech. I asked the driver for her license and registration. The driver handed me their license and I identified them as Ariel Shacurtis Duffy (B/F, 2/8/92) through their Maryland license. I asked Duffy how many alcoholic beverages she consumed prior to driving to which she advised Nothing.I then observed her not giving me any eye contact when she answered the question. I then returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine MVA checks, once completing MVA checks, I returned to Duffys vehicle and asked her to step out and walk to the front of her vehicle to conduct the standardized field sobriety test and to continue my investigation to which she consented. While at the front of my patrol vehicle I continued to smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. I asked Duffy how many alcoholic beverages she consumed prior to driving to which she advised A beer earlier. I asked her how long ago she consumed the alcoholic beverage to which she advised Around seven Oclock.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on Coastal Highway where Duffys vehicle made a complete stop. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 45 degrees. Duffy appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. My front emergency lights were deactivated during all tests.  I asked Duffy the following questions: Glasses- NO Medication- NO Physical disabilities-NO  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (_6_/_6_ clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. A black and gray pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12-15 inches from Duffys eyes. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Her pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. She was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked if she understood the instructions and she stated Yes. 1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes   WALK AND TURN (_2_/_8_ clues observed) Prior to Duffy performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. She was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. She was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat to her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. She was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. She was to keep her hands flat to her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, I explained and demonstrated for Duffy to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her lead foot to turn completely around. I again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps was to be performed identically to the first series. Duffy was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was complete, keep her hands down by her sides, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Duffy if she understood the test and she stated Yes. Instructional Stage: Completed as demonstrated Walking stage (1st Nine): 1). Stepped off of the line more than an inch on steps 2,3 Walking stage (2nd Nine): 1). Stepped off of the line more than an inch on step 1 2). Missed heel to toe contact more than half an inch on steps 2-9 Turn: Completed as demonstrated  ONE LEG STAND (_3_/_4clues observed) Prior to Duffy performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. She was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, Duffy was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand-two), and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Duffy if she understood the test, and she stated Yes. Left foot Seconds 0-10: 1). Raised arms more than six inches away from body on second 2,5 2). Put foot down on second 3 3). Swaying from left to right more than six inches on second 6  Seconds 11-20: 1). Raised arms more than six inches away from body on second 14 2). Swaying from left to right more than six inches on second 15 3). Put foot down on second 20    Seconds 21-30: Completed as demonstrated  Additional field test: (1).I asked Duffy if she knew the English alphabet to which she advised Yes. I asked her if she could start at the letter H. And go to the letter T. Without singing the alphabet to which she advised Yes. Duffy started at the letter H and stopped at Z, Duffy sang the alphabet (2).I then asked Duffy if she could count backwards from 57 to 36 to which she stated Yes. Duffy counted from 57 to 1 and stopped.    Duffy had the opportunity to take a preliminary breath test. Duffy consented to a preliminary breath test with the result of .15 BrAC. Duffy advised she consumed 4-5 Corona alcoholic beverages prior to driving ARREST: Based on the following, I had reason to believe Duffy was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: * Driving behavior *Admitting to consuming alcohol *My observed signs of impairment  At approximately 2319 hours, I placed Duffy under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I later checked her mouth for any foreign objects and did not locate any. Duffy was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. While placing Duffy in my vehicle she almost fell over. While on-scene I played the English audio version of the DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Duffy via the MVA official website with a paper copy in front of her to read. At the conclusion of the DR-15 form, I verbally repeated the possible suspensions and sanctions that can be imposed by the MVA per the DR-15 form. Duffy refused the Intoximeter test and signed the same at approximately 0109 hours. Alcohol Concentration Test Result: Cpl. Morgan #3742 with the Ocean City Police Department, is a certified Intoximeter operator and checked Duffys mouth for any foreign objects and did not locate any. Cpl. Morgan administered the Intoximeter test at approximately 2341 hours with the result of .14 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  Duffy was later released to a sober adult. Duffy received pertinent copies of paperwork. Duffy was charged with the following: 21-902 (A1i) Driving motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol 21-902 (B1i) Driving vehicle while impaired by alcohol 21-902 (A1ii) Driving vehicle while under the influence of alcohol PER SE 21-801.1 Exceeding posted maximum speed limit 44MPH in a posted 35MPH zone 21-301 (A) Failure to drive vehicle on right half of roadway when required  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland. Case closed.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 11:39:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/29/2023 11:39:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Drew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7062</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492015</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/21/2023 22:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 10:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/29/2023 10:59:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492015</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/21/2023 22:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 10:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/29/2023 10:59:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492015</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/21/2023 22:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 10:59:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/29/2023 10:59:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492015</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/21/2023 22:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 10:59:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/29/2023 10:59:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492015</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/21/2023 22:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 10:59:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/29/2023 10:59:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>30</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 11:31:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>183384</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Duffy</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ariel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shacurtis</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/08/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2018 13:48:36</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A640</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Duffy</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ariel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shacurtis</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/08/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A640</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2018 13:48:36</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>425</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Decatur</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21804</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2180</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.582591</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.377543</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>365</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4845</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2018 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 11:38:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:39</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 11:38:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:41</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 10:59:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/29/2023 10:59:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149211</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 11:32:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/29/2023 11:32:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MAL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>TAN</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8EX8054</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>