<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-015439</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/01/2023 00:50:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/01/2023 00:50:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/01/2023 00:16:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/01/2023 00:16:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>A verbal argument between Fiances resulted in them both making claims of assault. Upon further investigations, there was lack of evidence on scene to properly charge either party. Information for victims of abuse, and avenues to potentially place charges in the future were provided to both parties before they were separated.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/01/2023 00:50:42</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5951</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 08:41:49</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I695 / CAMP MEADE NB TO I695 WB</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>596769</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/01/2023 00:50:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 01:42:51</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>596769</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I695</StreetName>
         <City>Linthicum Heights</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3631-3720 I695 / 1-250 CAMP MEADE NB TO I695 WB</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3251-3630 I695 / 1-250 CAMP MEADE NB TO I695 WB</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/01/2023 00:50:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/01/2023 00:50:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>06/05/2023 08:41:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/01/2023 00:50:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5951</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 08:41:49</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car camera operational. Trooper #7362 BWC camera was functioning and used during this incident.    ATTACHMENTS:  1. Photographs of Brathwaites and Chews claimed injuries   2. Copy of Brathwaites and Chews Witness Statements     SCENE PROCESSING:  Janelle Nicole Brathwaite (B/F DOB: 07/06/1979) claimed that Timothy Allen Chew (B/M DOB: 05/15/1987) assaulted her while Brathwaite was driving Westbound on Maryland Route 695 in the area of Maryland Route 295. Brathwaite stopped on the side of the road and attempted to separate herself from Chew.    COMPLAINANT/VICTIM:  1.Janelle Nicole Brathwaite (B/F DOB: 07/06/1979)  2.Timothy Allen Chew (B/M DOB: 05/15/1987)    WITNESS/NEIGHBORHOOD CHECKS:       Brathwaite and Chewwere interviewed individually on scene and given the opportunity to provide an official Maryland State Police form 076 Witness Statement.      NARRATIVE:    On 05/01/2023, at approximately 0018 hours, I, Trooper Litz #7362, responded to the area of Westbound Maryland Route 695 and Maryland Route 295 to a call regarding Domestic Violence. Upon my arrival, Anne Arundel County Police Officers were on scene, and behind a gray Infiniti sedan bearing Maryland registration 9FC3442. Both occupants of the Infiniti were already outside of the vehicle and separated from each other. I introduced myself to the driver and identified her by her Maryland drivers license asJanelle Nicole Brathwaite (B/F DOB: 07/06/1979). I asked Brathwaite to come to the front of the vehicle and speak with me individually. Trooper Garvey #7075 arrived on scene to assist me, and I had him speak with the passenger, who was identified by his Maryland drivers license asTimothy Allen Chew (B/M DOB: 05/15/1987).  While speaking with Brathwaite, she informed me that she was taking Chew, her fianc, home from her house, and while she was diving, Chew removed her glasses from her face and broke the radio knob in her car. She also stated that earlier that day while at her house in Prince Georges County, Chew had been heavily drinking and choked Brathewaite with his hands. At that time, I looked but could not see any evident markings on her neck. Brathwaite informed me once she pulled the Infiniti to the shoulder area and came to a stop, Chew threw her glasses and a knife he was possessing out the window, directly next to the Infiniti. Multiple attempts were made by multiple Officers to locate both items, but none were successful in doing so. Brathwaite also informed me that once the car was parked, both parties remained inside the vehicle until police arrived on scene. I thanked Brathwaite for her answers, and explained she would be filling out a Maryland State Police (MSP) form 076 Written Statement with her official statement on the events leading up to my arrival.  Once I returned to my marked patrol vehicle, I spoke with Trooper Garvey about his interaction with Chew. Chew informed Trooper Garvey that Brathwaite, his fianc, struck him in the mouth and on the left eye. I then had Trooper Garvey speak with and provide Brathwaite the MSP form 076 while I spoke with Chew. Chew informed me that while Brathwaite was driving, he adjusted the radio. Brathwaite smacked his hand, then punched the right side of his mouth and his left eye. I observed a small, dried and scabbed-over cut on Chews lower right lip, but saw no markings on his left eye. The cut on Chews lip appeared to be an older wound, not having been caused within the time frame of the incident between Brathwaite and Chew. When asked, Chew stated he did not touch Brathwaite. I asked Chew about Brathwaites glasses, and he informed me they were Gucci glasses, he did not know where she put them and he did not remove them from her face. Chew also informed me that he did not have any knives in his possession because Brathwaite took them away from him. I thanked Chew for his response, and had him fill out a MSP form 076 as well.      After each party completed their MSP form 076s, I took pictures of their persons where they claimed they were struck. While doing so with Brathwaite, she informed me, for the first time, that Chew had also struck her in the mouth, and presented her bottom right lip. I observed small red cuts on the inside of her lip that looked extremely new. The cuts on Brathwaites lip did not appear consistent with being struck in the mouth, but did appear consistent with recently biting ones own lip. I also looked at Brathwaites knuckles for evidence of her punching Chew, but did not see any markings on her hands. Based on the lack of evidence presented to me by Brathwaites and Chews statements, and lack of injury markings on their persons to support their statements, I chose not to charge Brathwaite or Chew with Domestic Violence or Assault in any degree at that time. I provided Brathwaite and Chew with a Victims Awareness Pamphlet, explained the next steps in the process if they felt they wanted to press charges on one-another at a later time, explained there are multiple resources for emotional and physical support during, and after, an assault of any kind, provided them with my contact information in the event they wanted to speak with me directly about anything in the future and provided them with the incident information. I also explained neither party was to contact the other for at least 24 hours, to which they both agreed. I then had Brathwaite drive away from the scene in the Inifiniti. After a few minutes, and without disclosing the location to Brathwaite, I drove Chew to a gas station in the area where he could safely contact a family member or friend to pick him up.                        All events listed above occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.    Irequest this case be closed. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 02:11:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 14:59:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Garvey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Killian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7075</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Swigert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4622</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derek</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5951</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Litz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Simon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7362</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>43</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 01:57:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:24</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>15240</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Brathwaite</LastName>
               <FirstName>Janelle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/06/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/15/2014 20:23:46</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B633</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Brathwaite</LastName>
               <FirstName>Janelle</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/06/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B633</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/15/2014 20:23:46</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 01:57:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 01:57:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 01:57:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 02:01:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:57</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375980</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Chew</LastName>
               <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Allen</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/15/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/03/2023 02:00:58</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T530</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Chew</LastName>
               <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Allen</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/15/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T530</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/03/2023 02:00:58</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 02:01:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 02:01:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 02:01:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152589</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 02:05:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 02:05:31</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JN1BV7ARXFM390724</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>INFI</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9FC3442</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>