<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-028156</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40L</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/09/2023 15:36:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/09/2023 15:36:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/09/2023 15:34:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/09/2023 15:34:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Assist Greenbelt PD</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/09/2023 15:36:07</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1897</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 09:21:33</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>376834</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/09/2023 15:36:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/13/2023 17:21:00</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>376834</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>6510</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Lake Park</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
         <SubNumber>204</SubNumber>
         <City>Greenbelt</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20770</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.874348</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.981229</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/09/2023 15:36:03</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/09/2023 15:36:03</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40L</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>11/14/2023 09:18:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/09/2023 15:36:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP1897</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 09:18:32</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Report This report documents assistance provided to the Greenbelt Police Department related to the disappearance of Mariame Sylla.   Narrative  Background On 8/9/2023, I, Corporal John Wildman #6591  Maryland State Police Homicide Unit, was contacted by Detective Rodas-Flores of the Greenbelt Police Department and asked to assist with the analysis of Verizon records associated with a missing person investigation.    Call Detail Record Analysis I ingested the dataset into CASTViz, a mapping tool developed by the FBI. I have received formal and on-the-job training in the use of CASTviz. I also ingested Verizon tower locations for the Washington and Philadelphia markets. I observed cellular interactions with known Verizon towers and conducted a preliminary analysis of these network interactions for use by the investigative team. As detailed below, I conducted a general timeline-based analysis and a separate temporal analysis related to the specific timeframe during which Mariam reportedly departed from her house and did not return. I also ingested the dataset into PLX, an analysis tool developed by Penlink. I have received formal and on-the-job training in the use of PLX. I utilized PLX to visualize communication events. I observed a number of communication events and conducted a preliminary analysis of these events for use by the investigative team. I conducted a general analysis of dialed and received numbers for both Mariam and Mohamed, analysis of communication patterns, and also created readable export files reflecting time-zone amended communication events. I provided relevant preliminary findings to the Greenbelt Police Department investigative team. I have attached my notes to this report as reference.   Interview with Mohamed Aziz Sylla Djim On 8/21/2023, I assisted Detective Davis of the Greenbelt Police Department with an interview of Mohamed Aziz Sylla Djim. The interview was conducted at the Prince Georges County Detention Center and was audibly recorded by Detective Davis. Mohamed was Mirandized for the interview and agreed to answer questions. Detective Davis authored a report documenting the interview.   Forensic Download of Mohamed Aziz Sylla Djims Cellular Phone  On 8/25/2023, I initiated a forensic exam of Mohamed Aziz Sylla Djims Samsung Galaxy A42. The forensic analysis was completed pursuant to a Prince Georges County search warrant. I documented the extraction and analysis off-line via MSP Digital Forensic Lab reporting (Case 23-08-243).   Case Status CLOSED  ASSIST OTHER AGENCY </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6591</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/13/2023 17:22:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6591</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/13/2023 17:42:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40L</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Knight</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1897</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wildman</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6591</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>