<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-015809</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/03/2023 21:25:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/03/2023 21:25:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/03/2023 20:01:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/03/2023 20:01:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Victim was assaulted by her significant other. A witness had a knife pulled out on him. Female victim's children were taking by the suspect without her permission.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 21:25:32</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4993</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/09/2023 11:29:38</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>BRG</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>KD</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>THT</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>414919</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 21:25:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/04/2023 22:45:07</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>414919</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1301</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Flamingo</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Salisbury</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.59652372510608</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.38817087773468</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/03/2023 21:25:28</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/03/2023 21:25:28</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 11:10:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 21:25:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 19:56:02</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was not captured on In-car camera, E-12. In-car camera working properly.  This incident was captured on BWC. BWC working properly.  https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=7428ab5ac48344d9aa4a20e081a342a3partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=7f9e8810986947c39d6867ae20fd9522partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=e70ad7cc8a4a4a11833d0b8cf3faebdbpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1   SCENE PROCESSING:    I observed and captured digital photographs of victims injuries.   ATTACHMENTS:    Six (6) digital photographs of victims injuries due to an assault (uploaded to the report) (uploaded to Veripic).    Nine (9) digital photographs of victims injuries the day after the assault (uploaded to the report) (uploaded to Veripic).    Two (2) digital photographs of victims hospital visit summary indicating fractured sternum (uploaded to the report) (uploaded to Veripic).    One (1) digital photographs of an apparent suicidal note located which was left by Tyler Gaskins at 5651 Rip Wil Drive (uploaded to the report) (uploaded to Veripic).    One (1) MSP Form 246 (Domestic Violence Supplemental Report) (uploaded to the report) (uploaded to Veripic).    One (1) MSP Form 076 (Written Statement) from victim (uploaded to the report) (uploaded to Veripic).    One (1) MSP Chain Of Custody Log (uploaded to the report) (uploaded to Veripic).    Five (5) digital photographs of victims vehicle found at TidalHealth (uploaded to the report) (uploaded to Veripic).    One (1) MSP Form 076 (Written Statement) from Paul Silberquit (uploaded to the report) (uploaded to Veripic).    One (1) MSP Form 076 (Written Statement) from Roberto Lopez-Lopez (uploaded to the report) (uploaded to Veripic).  NARRATIVE:     On May 3rd, 2023 at approximately 2005 hours, I, TFC. Hopkins #7202 was dispatched to 1301 Flamingo Drive, Salisbury, Maryland 21801 for a report of a disorderly.     Upon my arrival, I observed one white male and one hispanic male later identified as, Paul Silberquit (W/M 04/17/1964), and Roberto Lopez-Lopez (H/M 07/17/1989). Paul advised, a female and male that he never met entered his residence and were arguing. As I entered the residence through the back door, I observed a white female later identified as, Ashley Lauren Long (W/F 02/28/1994), crying hysterically saying, please dont let him come in. Ashley was shaking uncontrollably to the point where she had a very hard time explaining what had occurred. I observed Ashley to have two (2) black eyes, her face was swollen, and observed her to have multiply injuries to both of her arms, neck, and ribs. Ashley advised, she had been in an altercation with her significant other who was identified as, Tyler Andre Gaskins (B/M 05/09/1993). Ashley stated, that Tyler assaulted her multiply times because he suspected Ashley was cheating on him with another male. Ashley advised, he forced her into the car along with Ashleys two (2) children and began driving towards 1301 Flamingo Drive, Salisbury, Maryland 21801 to confront the other guy he thought Ashley was cheating on him with. Ashley further stated, while holding her 3-month-old daughter, Tyler began repeatedly punching Ashley in her face.     Ashley stated, after arriving to the Flamingo Drive address, Tyler demanded Ashley to knock on the door. While Ashley knocked on the door, he stated to her that he was going to kill her if the male subject didnt open the door. Ashley then stated, no one answered the door, but the door was unlocked. Ashley advised, Tyler entered the residence where he did not have permission from the two (2) occupants of the residence. After Tyler entered the residence with Ashley, he began demanding for Roberto Lopez-Lopez (H/M 07/17/1989). Ashley stated, she and Tyler went to Robertos room and Tyler stated to Roberto, Is this what you want, you can have this bitch. Ashley then stated, Tyler demanded her to leave with him, but she refused. When Ashley refused, Tyler began to assault her where she fell to the ground in the hallway. Ashley stated, Tyler grabbed her by her legs to try and drag her down the hallway, but was unable to. Ashley further stated, Tyler grabbed Ashley by her hair to begin dragging her down the hallway, and then proceeded to punch her in her head multiply times with a closed fist. Ashley advised, Tyler then got on top of her, and held her down and grabbed her by her neck with two hands and began to strangle Ashley. Ashley stated, she was unable to breath and while looking at Tyler she kept pointing to her throat indicating she couldnt breathe, but Tyler kept chocking her while saying Just tell me the truth. Ashley advised, she was in fear for her life. I observed injuries to Ashleys neck and throat that would be consisted with Tyler chocking her. I observed a red in color mark located on the right side of Ashleys neck where it was apparent that Ashleys blood vessel had bust while being strangled by Tyler.    Ashley advised, Tyler then fled the residence in her vehicle with her two (2) children, Kylie Jones (W/F 11/10/2011), and Willow Gaskins (01/29/2023), which was described as a 2020 black Hyundai Tucson, with Maryland registration (1FB6234). The vehicle is solely registered to Ashley and Tyler did not have permission from Ashley to take her vehicle. It should be noted that Kylie Jones is not Tylers child and did not have permission from Ashley to take Kylie and flee the scene. Ashley also stated, that Tyler took her Iphone 13 (unknown serial number) without her permission when he fled the scene of Flamingo Drive. Ashley advised her cellphone had a purple case. Ashley stated, within the last 48 hours, on 05/03/2023, Tyler assaulted her by punching her in the arm, face, chest, and kneeing her in her ribs. I observed many marks on Ashleys arms, to the point where they had turned blue and yellow in color. EMS was dispatched to the Flamingo Drive address, where she was then transported to Tidal Health for her injuries. While speaking to Roberto on scene, he stated, Tyler pulled out a pocket knife and pointed it directly at Roberto. Roberto noted, that Tyler was less than five (5) feet from Roberto, and he was in fact in fear for his life.    At approximately 2330 hours, I followed Ashley and EMS to TidalHealth to be treated for her injuries. While following EMS to the hospital, it was learned that Tyler had dropped of Kylie and Willow in the middle of the street in front of 5995 Stonehedge Drive, Salisbury, Maryland, which was Ashleys aunts residence. After Tyler dropped Kylie and Willow off, he left the residence at a high rate of speed. While at the hospital, it was learned that Wicomico County Sheriffs office pinged Tylers cellphone. Tylers cellphone would ping in the area of 22213 Deep Branch Road, Nanticoke Wicomico County, Maryland 21840 (LAT: 38.314706) (LONG: -75.847560). Due to the phone ping, I began driving my Maryland State Police car towards the area. While traveling southbound on Nanticoke Road, I noticed a vehicle traveling northbound, and it appeared to be traveling at a high rate of speed. The road conditions were wet due to the heavy down pour of rain. When the vehicle passed my location, my Maryland State Police issued left LPR (License Plate Recognition) was able to capture a Maryland tag of (1FB6234), which came back to a black 2020 Hyundai Tucson, which was registered to Ashley. I would then advise over the radio that the vehicle passed me to alert other law enforcement officers. As I quickly slowed my patrol vehicle and made a U-turn to catch up to the vehicle, I was unable to, as the vehicle was already traveling at a high rate of speed. After some time passed, Deputys located the vehicle again heading northbound on Nanticoke Road at a high rate of speed, but Deputies were unable to catch up to the vehicle.    I responded to the Salisbury barrack where typed up application for charges against Tyler. Later during the night an arrest warrant was generated for Tyler.    At approximately 2315 hours, I, responded to TidalHealth, where I met with Ashley. An MSP Form 246, Domestic Violence Supplemental Report was completed where Ashley screened in as an Automatic High-Danger Assessment, due to the responses Ashley gave to me when being asked the questions. Ashley also completed an MSP Form 076, Written Statement. A Wicomico County Life Crisis counselor identified as, Stacey Sollars.     On May 4th, 2023 at approximately 1751 hours, I, responded to 5995 Stonehedge Drive, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21801 to conduct a secondary interview with Ashley. During the interview Ashley indicated there was a verbal argument between her and Tyler during the late evening of May 2nd, 2023 in the living room of their residence. Ashley stated, Tyler would accuse Ashley of cheating on him with another guy. Ashley then stated, Tyler left the residence for approximately one (1) hour, and then returned to the residence, but this time Tyler had apparently calmed down. Ashley advised, she and Tyler went to bed at approximately 2300 hours. Approximately between the morning of 0200 and 0300 hours on May 3rd, 2023, Ashley was suddenly woken up to Tyler grabbing her by the arms and shaking her while stating, Why are you cheating on me. Ashley stated, when she told Tyler she was not cheating, he grabbed her by the neck with both of his hands and began chocking Ashley saying, Why are you cheating, why are you doing this to our family. Ashley stated, after being chocked, Tyler punched her in the head multiply times.    Ashley advised, after the assault in the bedroom, Tyler stormed off into the living room very irate. Ashley followed behind Tyler to try and reassure Tyler that she was not lying. Ashley further advised, while trying to calm Tyler down, Tyler pinned Ashley in the corner near the front door where he proceeded to knee Ashley in her ribs with his right knee one (1) time. After the assault took place, Tyler and Ashley then went back to bed at approximately 0400 hours. When they woke back up around 0700 hours on May 3rd, 2023, Ashley stated, everything was back to normal as if nothing never occurred.     I captured nine (9) digital photographs of Ashleys injuries which shows her injuries the day after the assault. I also captured Ashleys hospital visit form where it shows Ashleys primary diagnosis was a Fracture of Breastbone (fractured sternum). After the interview was completed myself and my shift partner assisted Ashley and family member with a domestic escort, so she could retrieve essential items for her and her children. Upon our arrival at, 5651 Rip Wil Drive, Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland 21804, we observed the house to be in disarray. I noticed the front door frame to be completed broken off. While Ashley was retrieving her items, she noticed a note on her bed that Tyler had written and left her. Ashley confirmed that the handwriting on the note was Tylers handwriting. The note appeared to be an apparent suicidal note, as he was apologetic for what he had done. The writing was written with a blue ink pen.    After Ashley retrieved her items she left and went to the Wicomico County Commissioners office to file for a protective order.    On May 5th, 2023 at 1901 hours, I, responded to TidalHealth where I was able to locate Ashleys vehicle in car lot six (6). Ashley was contacted and made aware of her vehicles location. She advised she would possibly retrieve her vehicle on May 6th, 2023.    On May 6th, 2023, at 1737 hours, I, contacted Ashleys mother, Theresa Ward (W/F 06/26/1971), who advised, Ashley did retrieve her vehicle from the hospital. Theresa further stated, that Ashley went to the Wicomico County Detention Center, where she was able to retrieve her keys to her vehicle and her cellphone. The cellphone and keys were in Tylers possession when he was taken into custody on his warrant on May 4th, 2023. I did also confirm with Theresa that, Ashley did obtain a protective order against Tyler.    I request this case be, OPEN, pending further investigation.  All events occurred in Wicomico County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/04/2023 17:04:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7202</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 12:28:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zaykoski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7068</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hopkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dra'karr</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7202</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pardoe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3431</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckrich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hopkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dra'karr</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7202</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505228</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1420</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/03/2023 20:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1420</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 04:23:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7202</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/14/2023 05:34:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/04/2023 22:48:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:18</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>376125</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Long</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ashley</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lauren</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/28/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/04/2023 22:47:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Long</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ashley</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lauren</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/28/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/04/2023 22:47:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>588</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9895</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/04/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 05:35:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 05:35:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 05:35:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 05:35:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 04:28:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:11</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>298934</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Gaskins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Andre</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/09/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/01/2021 08:29:57</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T460</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Gaskins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Andre</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/09/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T460</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/01/2021 08:29:57</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>322</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mill Pond</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>921</SubNumber>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21804</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.5618646</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.4090153</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 05:36:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 05:36:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>11</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 04:30:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:16</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>376986</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Jones</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kylie</FirstName>
               <DOB>11/10/2011 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/14/2023 04:29:59</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Jones</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kylie</FirstName>
               <DOB>11/10/2011 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/14/2023 04:29:59</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 04:38:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>BB</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 04:31:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:11</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>376987</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Gaskins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Willow</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/29/2023 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/14/2023 04:31:28</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Gaskins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Willow</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/29/2023 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G252</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/14/2023 04:31:28</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 04:31:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 04:36:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:15</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>376989</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lopez-Lopez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <DOB>07/17/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/14/2023 04:36:13</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L124</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lopez-Lopez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <DOB>07/17/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L124</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/14/2023 04:36:13</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1301</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Flamingo</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.59652372510608</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.38817087773468</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 04:36:24</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>59</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 04:37:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:14</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>376990</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Silberquit</LastName>
               <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/17/1964 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/14/2023 04:37:23</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Silberquit</LastName>
               <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/17/1964 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/14/2023 04:37:23</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1301</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Flamingo</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.59652372510608</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.38817087773468</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 04:37:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/19/2023 10:26:33</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/19/2023 10:26:33</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 11:10:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 10:26:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 19:56:02</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Incident:First Degree Assault Defendant:Tyler Gaskins (B/M 5/9/1993) Location:1301 Flamingo Dr Salisbury MD 21801  Body Worn Camera:https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=b10a1127a0d644ee8daadabb4a4f8f9dpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  Scene Processing: -Paul Silberquit witness statement -Roberto Lopez Lopez witness statement -Ring video footage   Narrative: On 5/3/2023 at approximately 2001 hours, I TFC Eckrich, was dispatched to 1301 Flamingo Dr Salisbury MD in reference to an assault. Upon my arrival, I observed the victim in the incident identified as Ashley Long (W/F 2/28/94), seated in a chair at the kitchen table. Long was visibly distraught, and when I had entered the residence she immediately started screaming for us to quickly shut the door, as she was scared that the suspect would return and harm her. I noticed Long had numerous visible injuries such as bruises on her arms, and her face appeared to be swollen. TFC Hopkins had called for EMS to respond to evaluate her injuries, while also gathering the facts from her. When EMS did arrive and knocked on the front door, Long jumped up in fear and ran down the hallway because she thought it was Gaskins returning to the residence. Long had made a statement that she was scared and that she did not want Gaskins to find her. While being evaluated by EMS, a Wicomico Sheriffs deputy had knocked on the door, and Ahsley again jumped from her seat and began to go down the hallway in fear.  Long was eventually transported to Tidal Health for her injuries. I remained on scene and gathered statements from a witness and an additional victim. The additional victim identified as Roberto Lopez Lopez (H/M 7/17/89), approached me in the front yard and was on the phone with a family member of Longs identified as David. David is Longs uncle. At that time David advised me that Gaskins had dropped the children off in front of his residence in the roadway and had sped off. I quickly relayed the information to other units, so we could make contact with the children. I made contact with the caller, identified as Paul Silberquit (W/M 4/17/64), who is a resident at 1301 Flamingo Dr. Silberquit advised that he was in his bedroom at approximately 1950 hours, when he suddenly heard someone banging on the back door to the residence. Silberquit initially thought it was a family member of his roommate. Silberquit exited his bedroom and went into the kitchen to see that a male and female had entered the residence. These subjects were later positively identified as Ashley Long and Tyler Gaskins (B/M 5/9/93). Silberquit stated that Gaskins immediately began to demanding to see Roberto and asked where he was at. While Gaskins was screaming, Roberto heard the noise from his bedroom and opened the door to see what was going on. Silberquit advised that Gaskins took Long into Robertos bedroom and began yelling at Roberto. Silberquit advised he could hear Gaskins mention something about Long sucking his dick referring to Roberto and that Roberto owes money to Long now because of it. Silberquit advised that they all continued to argue, so he told them to take it outside. At that point Silberquit witnessed Gaskins pull Long by her hair causing her to fall into the hallway. Gaskins then dragged Long down the Hallway for a short period of time before quickly letting go of her and running out of the residence. Silberquit did describe Gaskins as wearing a neon yellow shirt and had a beard. Silberquit completed a written statement on what he observed.   I also asked Roberto to complete a written statement on the incident. Roberto advised he can not write English very well, so he verbally told me the story and I wrote the statement down. Roberto advised he was in his bedroom when Long and Gaskins had arrived at the residence. He stated he could hear Silberquit calling for him, and he opened his bedroom door. At that time Gaskins and Long entered into his bedroom, and Long kept asking Roberto to give Tyler money. Roberto then observed Gaskins open a pocket knife and point it at it him, while he was also screaming at Roberto. According to Roberto, Gaskins was approximately 2 feet away from him when he pulled the knife out. Roberto stated he heard Long say something along the lines of that she had to lie to Gaskins, so she would be able to leave the house. Roberto advised he was scared that Gaskins was going to stab him with the knife.  I was then able to obtain video surveillance of the door in which Gaskins and Long used to enter the home. In the video it shows Gaskins (wearing a neon colored shirt as described), and Long approach the door. Long begins knocking on the door, and then the video footage stops before Long and Gaskins enter the residence. The timestamp on the video was 5/3/2023 1958 hours. The video then switches to the next time is detects motion, which was at 2000 hours. The second video shows Gaskins running quickly out of the house while looking behind him. I was able to get the video downloaded from Roberto.  After obtaining the written statements and the video footage I cleared the scene.  All events occurred in Wicomico County Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 10:27:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7047</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/29/2023 20:19:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pardoe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3431</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckrich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/19/2023 14:40:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/19/2023 14:40:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 11:10:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 14:40:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 19:56:02</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>  On May 19th, 2023 I was able to obtain and review video footage of Tyler and Ashley arriving at 1301 Flamingo Drive on May 3rd, 2023 at 1958 hours and Tyler leaving alone at 2000 hours. Tyler is observed wearing brown beanie, bright yellow long sleeve shirt, brown pants, and brown work boots.     Ashley is observed wearing a long sleeve purple shirt, black pants, and green and black shoes. By 19:58:51 both Ashley and Tyler enter the residence and I can hear Tyler and Ashley talking. At 20:00:44, I observed Tyler quickly running out the back door and out of the cameras view. I immediately hear what appears to be a car speeding off quickly.    It should be noted when I first made contact with Ashley at the Flamingo Drive address, she was observed wearing the same clothing as seen in video footage. When I assisted Ashley with a domestic escort on May 4th, 2023, I observed the same long sleeve bright yellow shirt laying on the couch at 5651 Rip-Wil Drive that Tyler was seen wearing on camera footage on May 3rd, 2023.    On May 20th, 2023 at approximately 1040 hours, I, contacted Tylers mother, Kristy Leigh Jarmon (W/F 12/1/1975), where I conducted a phone interview with Kristy. Kristy advised, she has no knowledge of Tyler assaulting Ashley in the past. Kristy was only made aware of the assault that occurred on May 3rd, 2023.    Kristy advised, her son Tyler does have a drug problem and believes that during the assault, Tyler was possible on drugs at the time. Kristy advised, Tyler gets extremely irate when he is taking or is on drugs. Kristy stated, she believes Tyler tends to use heroin, and or Meth.     While speaking with Kristy, she stated that Tyler was arrested in the past for assaulting his wife who he is technically still married to, Ashley Gaskins. Kristy stated, Tyler was released from jail less than two (2) years ago.    On May 20th, 2023 at approximately 1000 hours, I contacted Ashleys uncle, David Jason Frontera (W/M 04/28/1983), where I conducted a phone interview with David. David stated, on May 2nd, 2023, Ashley and Tyler came to his house, because Tyler stated he wanted to get help and thought it was best for David to try and help Tyler. David stated, he is part of his churchs minister group.     David stated, while they were sitting down talking and having lunch, Tyler was very irate but would eventually calm down after he started eating. David further stated, Tyler then received a phone call from a friend, possibly a John Beachump subject, when Tyler immediately left Davids residence in a hurry. David believes Tyler uses drugs, but is unsure what kind of drug Tyler uses. David advised, Ashley told him that Tyler also wanted help because Tyler has a drug problem.    David advised, Ashley told David that on May 2nd 2023 while Tyler and Ashley were in the car driving, Tyler was shoving on her. David stated, Ashley told him that Tyler was driving approximately 80 MPH through Salisbury with Ashleys kids in the car. David stated, he doesnt know of any other assaults between Tyler and Ashley.    On May 20th, 2023 at approximately 1225 hours, I, contacted Ashleys mother, Theresa Lynn Ward (W/F 06/26/1971), where I conducted a phone interview with Theresa. During the interview, Theresa stated, she was never made aware of previous assaults that may have occurred between Ashley and Tyler. Theresa stated, during Ashleys pregnancy with Willow Gaskins, she was unable to communicate with Ashley, as she believes Tyler was controlling her and preventing her from communicating with her. Theresa stated, after Ashleys pregnancy she was finally able to communicate with Ashley. Theresa advised, she asked Ashley why she was unable to communicate and Ashley stated, she chose not to talk with her mother during her pregnancy.    Theresa found this odd, because she stated, before Ashley and Tyler moved in together, Theresa stated, she and Ashley had a very close relationship, and they would talk all the time.    I request this case remain OPEN, pending further interview.  All event occurred in Wicomico County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 11:09:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7202</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/20/2023 13:09:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pardoe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3431</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hopkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dra'karr</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7202</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>47</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 11:08:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377520</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Jarmon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kristy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leigh</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/01/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/20/2023 11:07:40</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Jarmon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kristy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leigh</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/01/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/20/2023 11:07:40</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>880</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5640</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 11:08:04</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 12:11:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:17</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377521</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>U</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Frontera</LastName>
               <FirstName>David</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jason</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/28/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/20/2023 12:10:43</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F653</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Frontera</LastName>
               <FirstName>David</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jason</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/28/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F653</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/20/2023 12:10:43</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>497</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6604</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/20/2023 12:11:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/21/2023 11:40:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/21/2023 11:40:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 11:10:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 11:40:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 19:56:02</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Incident:Interview with Pamela Owen Date:5/4/2023 Time:1749 hours   Narrative: On 5/4/23 at approximately 1749 hours, I TFC Eckrich, responded to 5995 Stonehedge Dr Salisbury MD 21801 to assist TFC Hopkins with a follow-up to the investigation. Upon my arrival, I made contact with the victims Aunt identified as Pamela Owen. Owen asked to speak with me in regards to a situation she was concerned about involving Kylie Jones. Owen explained that earlier in the day, Kylie was speaking with one of her uncles when she brought up a situation that occurred on an unknown date. Kylie had told the Uncle that one day while her mom was work, Tyler Gaskins got upset with Kylie and stood over top of her while she was on her parents bed. Kylie told the Uncle that Gaskins hit her with a belt on her legs. The Uncle tried to inquire more about the incident, but Kylie became very upset and told the Uncle she did not want to talk about it anymore. I asked Owen if she observed any injuries on Kylie, and she advised that she had not checked for any at that time. I then made contact with Ashley Long in the kitchen of the residence. I asked Ashley if she knew of this incident occurring, and she said she did not know about it. Long did advise that after hearing about it she checked Kylie for any injuries and did not observe anything.  At this time Kylie has not spoken with anyone any further regarding this incident.  All events occurred in Wicomico County Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 11:41:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7047</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/21/2023 11:48:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pardoe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3431</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckrich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/10/2023 12:28:30</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/10/2023 12:28:30</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 11:10:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP4993</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 12:28:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 19:56:02</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #4 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On June10, 2023 at 1205 hours, I attempted to make contact with the victim, Ashley Long at the phone number provided. The phone rang, and an automatedmessage played stating, the person youare trying to reach is not acceptingcalls at this time, please try your call again later, followed by immediate disconnection without the ability for me to leave a message.  A check through secure case search was completed and I found results for interim, temporary, and final protective orders. The interimand temporaryprotective orders were granted according to the secure case search. The final protective order was denied due to petitioner requested dismissal.  The interim and final protective order PDF is attached. I was unableto attach the temporaryprotective order as it would not open through secure case search.  The verbiage for the temporaryprotective order is as follows:                                 D-023-FM-23-000108                                  Case / Order Information                                                                          Case Number:             D-023-FM-23-000108             Court System/County             Wicomico County District Court                                     Case Caption:             Long Vs. Gaskins             Filing Date:             May 4, 2023                                     Order Issue Date:             May 5, 2023             Order Expiration Date:             May 12, 2023                                     Order Service Date:             May 5, 2023             Action:             Granted                                     Order Stage:             TEMPORARY             Order Type:             DV PROTECTIVE                                     Related CaseId:                                                                                                                                  Petitioner Information:                                                                                                                                                      Respondent Information:                                                                                                                 Person(s) Eligible For Relief:                                                                                                                                                                             Long,Ashley    Feb 28, 1994    Petitioner    May 5, 2023    May 12, 2023    May 5, 2023    Wicomico County District Court    Granted    Temporary Protective    Long Vs. Gaskin       </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4993</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 12:29:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4993</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 12:41:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bruce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6083</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Long</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tabitha</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4993</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>5</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/21/2023 15:03:10</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/21/2023 15:03:10</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 11:10:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/21/2023 15:03:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 19:56:02</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #5 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was not captured on In-car camera. In-car camera working properly.  This incident was not captured on BWC. BWC working properly.  ATTACHMENTS:     One (1) digital photograph of Longs injury the day after the assault (uploaded to the report).  NARRATIVE:    On June 15th, 2023 at approximately 1125 hours, I contacted Leonna Lashae Horsey (B/F 08/08/1994) via cellphone, reference to any knowledge of previous domestics between Gaskins and Long.    When talking to Horsey, she advised she has never been informed of any type of verbal or physical domestics between Gaskins and Long. Horsey only advised, there are most likely a history of domestic violence, but nothing she can confirm.    Horsey stated, she was only aware of the physical assault that had occurred on May 3rd, 2023. Horsey was unable to give me any other information regarding Gaskins and Longs relationship.   All events occurred in Wicomico County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7202</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/21/2023 15:04:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7202</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/21/2023 15:05:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mareck</LastName>
            <FirstName>Keven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3258</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hopkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dra'karr</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7202</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>6</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/29/2023 07:55:14</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/29/2023 07:55:14</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40M</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 11:10:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/29/2023 07:55:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 19:56:02</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Interview of Ashley Long</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of Supplemental Report:   Interview of Ashley Long  Suspect:  Name: Ashley Lauren Long   DOB: 2-28-1994   Sex: Female Race: White   Address: 5651 Rip Wil Drive, Salisbury, Maryland   Phone: 443-880-6411  Evidence:   One (1) Compact Disc containing a recorded interview of Ashley Lauren Long, stored in agency case file.  Narrative:   On Thursday, May 18, 2023, I S/T Garrett Dick #6158 of the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division Eastern Region conducted an interview with Ashley Lauren Long [hereinafter referred to as Long] concerning a false report she attempted to make at the Wicomico County District Court Commissioners office. The interview was conducted in the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack interview room and was audibly and visually recorded. Below is a synopsis of the interview and not a transcript therefore some paraphrasing may be used;   On Thursday, May 18, 2023, Long responded to the Wicomico County District Court Commissioners Office and advised she was coached to file charges or Robert Lopez [hereinafter referred to as Lopez].  Long advised that Tyler Gaskins [hereinafter referred to as Gaskins] contacted her and told her to file charges on Lopez about assaulting her and sexually assaulting her.  Long advised she was manipulated/coached by Gaskins in an attempt to help Gaskins charges get dropped.  Gaskins wanted Long to say that Lopez abused Long on 5/3/2023 (this documented incident from the Salisbury Barrack Troopers)  Long reiterated that Gaskins is the one who assaulted her in this investigation.  Long advised Gaskins called her from jail yesterday (5/17/2023) and today date (5/18/2023) telling her to seek false charges on Lopez.  While at the commissioners office Long completed the paperwork and that is when Long advised she admitted lying because she did not want to get into trouble for perjury.    Long went into detail again about the events that occurred in this investigation which is all detailed on the attached Compact Disc inside the case file.  My portion of this investigation is CLOSED. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6158</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/29/2023 07:55:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6158</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/29/2023 09:35:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hager</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6001</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40M</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Garrett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6158</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>