<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025541</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/17/2023 13:09:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/17/2023 13:09:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/17/2023 13:09:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/17/2023 13:09:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>NCMEC CT 166497806 / 166590285</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 13:09:27</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 11:31:21</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>CAC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>HANOVER CCU</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>701184</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 13:09:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 07:05:34</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>701184</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Hanover Ccu</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/17/2023 13:09:24</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/17/2023 13:09:24</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1700</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>07/19/2023 11:50:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 13:09:27</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 11:31:13</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments - NCMEC Cybertips 166497806 / 166590285 / 165139804  163034628 / 162296403 /162234738  162114307 / 162725699 (Unavailable from NCMEC at this Time) - Signed Google Search Warrant  Narrative  On 07/17/2023, the Maryland State Police Computer Crimes Section / Maryland Internet Crimes Against Children Task Force received NCMEC CyberTips # 166497806 and 166590285 (Collectively Associated CyberTips). The Associated CyberTips, generated by Google, indicated that a subject uploaded child pornography to the internet. Both CyberTips were assigned to TFC Zachary Crowe #6726 for investigation.   The Associated CyberTips both provided the same information pertaining to the suspect: Name: Khudles Koxxx Mobile Phone: +13016132173 (Verified 05-21-2023 20:24:57 UTC) Date of Birth: 03-05-1984 Email Address: mascnpanties@gmail.com (Verified) Email Address: itsjustbusiness26@gmail.com  The Associated CyberTips contained 51 reported child pornography files. TFC Crowe reviewed the reported child pornography files and determined that 51 files constitute child pornography as it is defined under Maryland law. Three of these files are described below:  CyberTip: 166590285 Filename: a23331023bf7d91eadf77219e883f28e-VID_20230510_022436_184.mp4 Description: This is a 1:50 (min:sec) color video with an opening title Baby Lexxa 2008. The video file appears to be a compilation of videos involving an adult male engaged in sexual conduct with an infant. Based on overall size and development, the child is reasonably believed to be between six months and 12 months of age. The video closes with scrolling text that reads, What a sexy little baby cunt!  CyberTip: 166590285 Filename: 8af5b551b3b2194345fdd73b04b885cd-VID_20230510_022348_923.mp4 Description: This is a 50 second color video depicting a juvenile male being sodomized by the penis of an adult male. Based on overall size and development, the child is reasonably believed to be between 6 months and two years of age.  CyberTip: 166590285 Filename: 17c9b47340606e935af43e7eac1bb792-VID_20230516_222229_387.mp4 Description: This is a 10 second color video depicting a juvenile female engaged in vaginal intercourse with the penis of an adult male. The juvenile female is devoid of pubic hair, narrow through the hips, and based on overall size and development, is reasonably believed to be between two and four years of age.  The CyberTip indicated that the following IP address 2601:14b:4181:ea10:ac41:c508:97ca:7ec4 was utilized to upload the reported contraband files.  TFC Crowe conducted a query of the upload IP address through an open-source database and determined that it is registered through Comcast and geo-locates generally to the Greenbelt area of Prince Georges County, Maryland. TFC Crowe also conducted an open-source query of the phone number, 301-613-2173, and determined the phone number is registered through T-Mobile.  TFC Crowe transmitted investigative subpoena requests to the Howard County Office of the States Attorney requesting subscriber and service address information from Comcast and T-Mobile.   TFC Crowe observed a number of additional Cyber Tips that are linked to the reported Google accounts by IP addresses. TFC Crowe requested these additional Cyber Tips be transferred and consolidated under this report number. The additional Cyber Tips are as follows:  Cyber Tip:165139804 Reporting ESP: Instagram Suspect Information:  Name: khudles koxx Phone: +15714121073 Date of Birth: 02-26-1985 Approximate Age: 38 Email Address: absolutelynolimitz@gmail.com (Verified) Screen/User Name: legitpansexual_   Cyber Tip: 163034628 Reporting ESP: Twitter Suspect Information:  Email Address: absolutelynolimitz@gmail.com Screen/User Name: abslutlynolimit   Cyber Tip: 162725699 Reporting ESP: Instagram Suspect Information:  No .pdf Attached   Cyber Tip: 162296403 Reporting ESP: Instagram Suspect Information:  Name: mascnpanties2 Phone: +12409231289 Date of Birth: 03-05-1985 Approximate Age: 38 Email Address: ianwest8526@gmail.com (Verified) Screen/User Name: mascnpanties2    Cyber Tip: 162234738 Reporting ESP: Twitter Suspect Information:  Phone: +13014488023 Email Address: masculinecrossdresser2@gmail.com Screen/User Name: mascnpanties2   Cyber Tip: 162114307 Reporting ESP: Twitter Suspect Information:  Email Address: ianwest8526@gmail.com Screen/User Name: mascnpanties3  On 07/18/2023, TFC Crowe authored an application for a search and seizure warrant related to the reported Google accounts. The warrant was signed by the Honorable Donnell Turner, Judge of the Circuit Court for Prince Georges County. TFC Crowe transmitted the signed warrant to Google via their secure law enforcement portal the same day.  Case Status OPEN / PENDING ADDITIONAL INVESTIGATION</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 07:06:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6726</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 11:27:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Crowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6726</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/20/2023 13:22:10</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/20/2023 13:22:10</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/22/2023 13:31:58</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/20/2023 13:22:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 11:31:13</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments - Google Records Certification - Google Pay Documents - Comcast Return - Comcast Records Certification  Offline Attachments - Google Production  Narrative  Since the last update, TFC Crowe received production from Google and Comcast. In response to a request for subscriber and service address information related to the IP address utilized to upload the reported files, Comcast provided the following information:  Subscriber Name: ROBERT BALLARD Service Address: 405 HURTT PL, FORT WASHINGTON, MD 207444733 Billing Address: 405 HURTT PL, FORT WASHINGTON, MD 20744 Telephone #:  (240) 515-2833 Type of Service: Internet Account Number: 8299420610788401 Account Status:  Disconnected 7-25-2023 IP Assignment:  Dynamically Assigned Private Network  TFC Crowe conducted an analysis of the materials provided by Google and discovered a total of 3,919 video/image files were contained within the reported Google accounts, mascnpanties@gmail.com, and itsjustbusiness26@gmail.com. TFC Crowe conducted a review of these materials and discovered there to be 233 unique files. Of the 233 unique files, 99 files constitute child pornography, as the term is defined under Maryland law. A description of three files is detailed below:  File Name: VID_20230508_233751_592-1j4kgpdkwxs9u.mp4 Description: This is a 51 second color video depicting a prepubescent juvenile female undressing to full nudity in a bathroom. The focus of the video is on her nudity and at one point the juvenile female spreads her buttocks in order to display her anus and vagina. The juvenile is flat chested, devoid of pubic hair, and reasonably believed to be approximately seven to ten years of age.  File Name: VID_20230510_014453_637-1j4ke6xxpunnm.mp4 Description: This is a one minute color video depicting a juvenile female being vaginally penetrated by the erect penis of an adult male. The juvenile female is devoid of pubic hair, under developed through the hips, and is reasonably believed to be approximately three to six years of age.  File Name: VID_20230508_164807_819-1j4ke6xxog336.mp4 Description: This is a 24 second color video depicting an adult female with her breasts exposed performing fellatio to a juvenile male. The male is devoid of pubic hair, has under developed testicles, and is reasonably believed to be approximately five to eight years of age.  TFC Crowe conducted a review of the additional materials in the account and located the GooglePay.BillingInfo document related to the email address itsjustbusiness26@gmail.com which provided the following information, set forth below, in relative part:  Added on: 2023-02-11 02:51:55 UTC Deleted on: N/A Billing Name: David Watson Instrument Description: Yep  7007 Instrument Type: Credit Card Card Number: 4985031178007007 Expiration Date: 2/2027 Card Product Name: N/A Card Scheme: CARD_SCHEME_VISA Card Class: CARD_CLASS_DEBIT Prepaid: N/A Corporate: N/A Country of Issue: USA Cloud Primary Account Number: 4479311304389047  Added on: 2023-03-29 21:14:01 UTC Deleted on: N/A Billing Name: David Watson Instrument Description: PayPal: mascnpanties@gmail.com Instrument Type: Paypal  TFC Crowe then located the GooglePay.BillingInfo document associated with the email address, mascnpanties@gmail.com. TFC Crowe observed the following information, set forth below, in relevant part:  Added on: 2023-06-29 01:24:10 UTC Deleted on: N/A Billing Name: David Watson Instrument Description: Mastercard  2752 Instrument Type: Credit Card Card Number: 5295800097972752 Expiration Date: 9/2026 Card Product Name: N/A Card Scheme: CARD_SCHEME_MASTERCARD Card Class: CARD_CLASS_DEBIT Prepaid: N/A Corporate: N/A Country of Issue: USA Cloud Primary Account Number: 5274828480266792  Added on: 2023-06-29 01:21:01 UTC Deleted on: N/A Billing Name: David Watson Instrument Description: Visa  4296 Instrument Type: Credit Card Card Number: 4116000160204296 Expiration Date: 3/2026 Card Product Name: N/A Card Scheme: CARD_SCHEME_VISA Card Class: CARD_CLASS_DEBIT Prepaid: true Corporate: N/A Country of Issue: USA  Added on: 2023-06-29 01:22:57 UTC Deleted on: N/A Billing Name: David Watson Instrument Description: Visa  7007 Instrument Type: Credit Card Card Number: 4985031178007007 Expiration Date: 2/2027 Card Product Name: N/A Card Scheme: CARD_SCHEME_VISA Card Class: CARD_CLASS_DEBIT Prepaid: N/A Corporate: N/A Country of Issue: USA Cloud Primary Account Number: 4479311308127732  TFC Crowe would note that both email addresses appear to have a single VISA credit card in common and both accounts appear to be linked to David Watson. TFC Crowe conducted a law enforcement query of the Motor Vehicle Administration for the name David Watson and located a record for an individual with a registered address of 405 Hurtt Place, Fort Washington, MD 20744, which directly correlates to the service address provided by Comcast in relation to the IP address utilized to upload the reported files. The following information was observed from the MVA record:  Name: WATSON, David J. DOB: 02/26/1985 (Age: 38) Maryland SDX: MD-10272425090 Address: 405 Hurtt Place, Fort Washington, Maryland 20744   Utilizing WATSONs MVA photo as comparison, TFC Crowe observed multiple videos in both Google accounts depicting WATSON, demonstrating ownership and control of both accounts.  On 09/22/2023, TFC Crowe conducted physical surveillance at the residence located at 405 Hurtt Place, in Fort Washington. At approximately 0846 hours, TFC Crowe observed an individual resembling WATSON exit the residence wearing black pants and an Amazon shirt. The individual entered a black Chevy Equinox bearing Maryland registion, 6EW0966, and drove away from the premises. The vehicle is registered to Covelle Watson (DOB: 01/04/1957), who is believed to be WATSONs mother based on a query of social media. TFC Crowe also observed an image of WATSON wearing an Amazon shirt matching the one observed during surveillance, on Covelle Watsons public Facebook page.  Case Status Open / Pending Residential Search Warrant </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/20/2023 13:23:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6726</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/22/2023 11:52:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Crowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6726</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/11/2023 08:01:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/11/2023 08:01:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 10:42:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/11/2023 08:01:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 11:31:13</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments - Return of Service (Signed Residential Warrant Included) - Property Held P-344657 - Chain of Custody Log - Room Labels - MSP Report of Polygraph Examination  Offline Attachments (Available Upon Request) - Body Worn Camera Footage (Interview) - Search Warrant Images - Entrance and Exit Videos  Narrative  On 10/05/2023, at approximately 0800 hours, Troopers of the Maryland Internet Crimes Against Children Task Force, along with Special Agents from Homeland Security Investigations, and Detectives from Prince Georges County Police Department, executed a residential search and seizure warrant at 405 Hurtt Place, Fort Washington, Maryland. Troopers knocked and announced their presence at the main entrance of the household and the door was answered by an adult female. Troopers made entry without incident and identified the suspect, WATSON, David J. (01/M DOB: 02/26/1985), as he exited the basement to the main entrance on command. All occupants were notified they were being audibly and visually recorded.  TFC Crowe and SGT Pitcher escorted WATSON to a nearby covert Maryland State Police vehicle for a voluntary interview. This interview was audibly and visually recorded on Body Worn Camera. WATSON was advised of his Miranda rights and consented to answering questions without the presence of an attorney. During the course of the interview, WATSON admitted to viewing, retaining, and distributing images and videos depicting child pornography. WATSON admitted to ownership of the email addresses and accounts reported in the associated CyberTips, as well as additional accounts. Before the end of the interview, WATSON revealed to Troopers that he had viewed and masturbated to images or videos depicting child pornography as recent as the night before. WATSON denied any sexual contact with juveniles, and agreed to a voluntary polygraph examination. Despite the admissions made by WATSON related to possessing and distributing child pornography, WATSON showed signs of deception when asked about passwords/PIN information utilized to access his cell phone.  During the course of the search, Troopers seized numerous devices from WATSONs residence, which were transported to the Criminal Enforcement Division Headquarters building and placed in temporary storage pending a full forensic examination. Occupants were provided with the proper paperwork related to the seized items and a copy of the warrant was left on scene. TFC Crowe provided WATSON with a voluntary transport to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack for the polygraph examination. WATSON was released to SGT Mario Farfan for the voluntary polygraph examination with the understanding that WATSON was free to leave at anytime.  That evening, TFC Crowe was notified that WATSON had disclosed that he walks around the house naked while his biological daughter (9 yo) and her half sister (13 yo) are present. WATSON further disclosed that he allows both juvenile females to be nude in the household and has allowed them to view pornography. TFC Crowe reported the disclosures made by WATSON and necessary details related to the investigation to the Maryland Department of Social Services / Child Protective Services screening center. TFC Crowe also contacted the mother of both girls, Nakia Mitchell, to notify her of the investigation, and a safety plan was put in place. Upon contact, TFC Crowe discovered Ms. Mitchell is an employee for the Prince Georges County Department of Social Services / Child Protective Services. Because Ms. Mitchell is an employee, the case was transferred to Charles County CPS for further investigation. Forensic Interviews for both juvenile females are set to take place Friday, 10/13/2023 in Charles County.  Also, the same evening, TFC Crowe contacted Special Agents from Homeland Security Investigations, who were able to fast track forensic analysis of WATSONs devices, with a focus on WATSONs cell phone. On 10/06/2023, the seized items were transported to the Baltimore Customs House for forensic analysis. These items were returned on 10/12/2023. At the time of this report, analysis of the devices is still underway.  Case Status OPEN / PENDING FORENSIC ANALYSIS</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/11/2023 08:02:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6726</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 11:08:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Crowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6726</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/15/2023 12:29:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/15/2023 12:29:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40B</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/20/2023 11:31:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 12:29:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP4989</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 11:31:13</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments - Supplemental Report (23-MSP-025541) - Consent Search and Chain of Custody (Victim Phones) - MSP Form 180 Advice of Miranda - Criminal Complaint  Offline Attachments (Available Upon Request) - Body Camera Footage (Second Interview and Arrest) - Body Camera Footage (Consent to Search and Seizure)  Narrative  This supplement was created to upload a .pdf format supplement created outside of this reporting system in order to create/insert numerous photos, tables, and items that were needed to display such a large amount of data in a comprehensive manner. The Supplemental report is attached to this supplement along with the listed attachments above.  On 11/06/2023, Troopers and Special Agents of the Maryland Internet Crimes Against Children Task Force located, interviewed, and arrested David Jamal WATSON (DOB: 02/26/1985) related to a criminal complaint and federal arrest warrant issued for charges of possession and distribution of child pornography. WATSON was seen for an initial appearance at the US Federal Court House in Greenbelt the same day. A detention hearing took place on 11/08/2023, and WATSON was ordered to be detained through the remainder of his court proceedings. In the coming days, WATSON will be indicted on charges of possession of child pornography, distribution of child pornography, and production of child pornography.  Though this case will remain closed by arrest, production from online accounts related to WATSON may still provide additional evidence leading to new charges.  Case Status Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6726</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/15/2023 12:30:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6726</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/16/2023 07:51:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zeller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4989</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40B</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Crowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6726</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>