<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025838</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/19/2023 22:36:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/19/2023 22:36:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/19/2023 22:18:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/19/2023 22:18:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/Accident</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 22:36:56</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5948</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/18/2023 03:23:50</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>473266</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 22:36:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 22:36:57</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>473266</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2207</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Pulaski</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Edgewood</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.30674439430742</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.4366024586416</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/19/2023 22:36:54</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/19/2023 22:36:54</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/09/2023 20:24:30</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 22:36:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:27:57</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP Unmarked Vehicle, D-08: In-Car/Body Camera Operational  Case # : 23-MSP-025838  Arrestee Information:      Defendant: Williams, Adrian Jerrod      Date of Birth: 03/20/1985      Date of Arrest: July 19, 2023      Time of Arrest: 2250 hours     CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING      Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration      Certified in A.R.I.D.E(Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement) to enhance skills to observe, identify, and articulate the signs of impairment related to drugs, alcohol, or a combination of both      A distinguished graduate of Marylands DUI Institute, a rigorous 40-hour program that provides specialized training on enforcing laws related to driving under the influence.      Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police      I have apprehended more than 75 impaired drivers during my tenure as a Law Enforcement Officer to date.     VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On July 19, 2023, at approximately 2218 hours, the Maryland State Police Bel Air barrack received a report of females fighting in the roadway in the area of 2207 Pulaski Highway in relation to a motor vehicle accident that had just occurred. I was dispatched at approximately 2219 hours to respond to the area.  I arrived in the area at approximately 2228 hours but had trouble locating the involved parties. I was eventually able to locate the involved parties in the parking lot of DMs Tiki Bar and Crab Deck. I arrived at the scene and observe multiple vehicles in the parking lot, and I was able to determine that the accident involved only two Honda Accords.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I made contact with the involved parties, confirming they were the callers, and they were not actively fighting. As I waited for additional units, I spoke with the other party and received her side of the story regarding the accident that occurred in the parking lot of Taco Bell.  I made contact with Adrian Jerrod Williams, who was later identified and confirmed as the operator of the vehicle during the accident. Williams provided his statement, stating that We were getting food, and he never felt any friction or nothingnor anyone hitting anyone. I observed that Williams eyes were bloodshot and glassy, and while Williams spoke, his speech was heavily slurred. I could also smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Williams breath and person.  I confirmed there was damage to each vehicle and later observed a video of the accident provided by Taco Bell. You could see the collision occur then William, the operator at the time of the accident continue on, fleeing the scene of the accident. Once additional units arrived on the scene, I pulled Williams to the side and explained to him that I suspected that he was impaired due to Williams being unaware of the collision, the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person, and his eyes being bloodshot and glassy.  Williams explained that hed recently lost his fianc in the month of March on his birthday, but seemed to become increasingly frustrated as he stated I dont even know what to say to you, are yall going to arrest me?. I asked if Williams had consumed an alcoholic beverage that night, and Williams stated he had and that he was driving his friends car, so he made sure he could make it to work in the morning. I asked Williams how many alcoholic drinks hed consumed that night, and William could not answer.  I asked if William would be willing to submit to field sobriety testing, and Williams agreed.  NOTE: Williams had made several remarks that night he was driving his friends car because she was drunk and that he did not want her to crash because she was driving erratically.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was completed in the parking lot. The surface was dry, level, and free from any visible debris. The weather was clear and approximately 75 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of natural moonlight.   I WAS UNABLE TO COMPLETE HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS TESTING BECAUSE WILLIAMS DID NOT FOLLOW MY INSTRUCTION, COMPLAINING THAT IT WAS DUE TO A RECENT EYE INJURY.  I ASKED WILLIAMS MULTIPLE TIMES TO FOLLOW MY INSTRUCTIONS, BUT HE DID NOT AND CONTINUE TO MOVE HIS EYE WHILE FOLLOWING THE STIMULUS.  I ATTEMPTED TO MOVE ON PAST THE HGN TESTING TO WALK AND TURN AND WHILE GIVING INSTRUCTIONS FOR THE TEST, WILLIAMS STARTED BEFORE ME PERMITTING HIM TO, THEN BECAME FRUSTRATED AND STATED THAT WE MIND AS WELL ARREST HIM. I WAS STILL PATIENT WITH WILLIAMS WHILE ATTEMPTING TO PUT HIM BACK IN THE CORRECT POSITION FOR TESTING HE AGAIN BECAME FRUSTRATED THEN I PLACED WILLIAMS UNDER ARREST.  ARREST:  Based on the following, I had probable cause to arrest Williams for driving while impaired:      My observed signs of impairment as Williams attempted to perform field sobriety tests      The motor vehicle collision that occurred and Williams lack of awareness that one had occurred      Williamss admittance to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to operating the vehicle      Opened alcoholic beverages containers in the vehicle Williams was operating     Williams was placed under arrest at 2250 hours.  A search of Williamss person was conducted in front of my patrol vehicle, and nothing of evidentiary value was found.  Williams was transported to the Bel Air Barrack for further processing.  Williams was read a DR15 and agreed to submit to a test of breath.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD:  Nothing to report.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: .19  INTOXIMETER TEST ADMINISTERED BY SERGEANT DUDEK # 5037  I request the case be closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7208</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 05:19:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7208</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 08:22:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Henry</LastName>
            <FirstName>Glenn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6366</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7015</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dudek</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5037</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Montgomery</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7208</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515282</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/19/2023 22:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7208</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/20/2023 02:53:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7208</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 05:15:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7208</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/20/2023 02:53:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:16</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383014</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Wiliams</LastName>
               <FirstName>Adrian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jerrod</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/20/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/20/2023 02:25:13</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A365</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Wiliams</LastName>
               <FirstName>Adrian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jerrod</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/20/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A365</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/20/2023 02:25:13</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>913</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Holgate</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>C</SubNumber>
               <City>Essex</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21221</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.447747</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.30477</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7208</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 05:17:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7208</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 05:17:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/21/2023 03:06:08</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/21/2023 03:06:08</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/09/2023 20:24:30</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/21/2023 03:06:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:27:57</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MARYLAND STATE POLICE BEL AIR BARRACK D HARFORD COUNTY, MARYLAND This incident was recorded. Marked Unit D-10s in-car camera and Tpr. Rowes body worn camera were working properly.  OFFENDER Case #: 23-MSP-025838 Defendant: Hope Lillian Leetta Wills Date of Birth: 08/16/1979 Date of Arrest: 07/19/2023 Time of Arrest: 2306 hours DUI #: 23-180 DUI Citation #: 1D10XD3  SUBSEQUENT DUI OFFENSE  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING:  *I am trained to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  *I am trained and certified to conduct preliminary breathalyzer tests by the Maryland State Police.  *I received Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement(ARIDE) training through the Maryland State Police in April 2022.  Phase #1 - Vehicle in Motion    On 7/19/2023, at approximately 2255 hours, I, Trooper Rowe (#7015), currently assigned to the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack, responded to a motor vehicle accident to assist TFC Montgomery(#7208). TFC Montgomery advised the passenger, identified as Hope Lillian Leetta Wills (DOB: 8/16/1979), took control of the vehicle, with the vehicle running and the keys in the ignition, ordering the original driver, identified as Adrian Jerrod Williams (DOB: 3/20/1985), to get in the vehicle to flee the scene. TFC Montgomery arrested Williams for DUI. I made contact with Wills.  Phase #2 - Personal Contact    Upon making contact with Wills, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and/or person. I asked Wills what happened that night. Wills stated that nothing was happening that night. I observed Wills eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I asked again, advising that i had just gotten there, and Wills stated nothing happened. After asking a few more times, Wills stated she was just trying to get a room at the motel with her friend. Wills stated she did not know what she had done wrong. I asked her if she did not remember anything from that night. Wills stated she did remember but was confused why the police were there. I informed Wills that we were there to investigate the accident that occurred. I again asked Wills what happened. Wills stated she did not know. I stated that nothing happened, and Wills stated she really did not know, honestly. Wills asked why I was asking her anything. I told her that we have reason to believe she was driving her vehicle. She stated she was definitely was not driving. I asked Wills why she was in the drivers seat when TFC Montgomery had pulled up. Wills then asked why I was there when my officers pulled up. I arrived on scene much later than the other officers on scene. I told Wills that I had just showed up. Wills stated Cool. I asked Wills why she was in the drivers seat. Wills stated she was never driving the car, Williams wasnt, and she didnt know. I confirmed with Wills that she just stated that Williams was not driving the car. Wills shook her head no. I asked Wills multiple times how much alcohol she had that night. Wills muttered to herself Im gonna get arrested. I asked Wills if she was going to work with me. Wills stated she was. I informed Wills that she wasnt, explaining that she wasnt answering any of my questions and was barely even talking to me.I again asked how much alcohol she had that night. Wills asked what you said? How much? I stated yes. Wills stated a couple glasses. I asked of what? Wine? Wills confirmed it was wine. I asked her what kind of wine was it, and she stated she didnt know. I asked Wills if she just had two glasses. Wills then stared at me and stated that my eyes were black. I couldnt hear her and asked excuse me. Wills again stated my eyes were black. I confirm restating my eyes are black and Wills nodded her head. I asked Wills what she meant by that. Wills told me to think about it.I then requested Wills to conduct Standardized Field of Sobriety Tests, to which she refused. Wills began arguing about how she was not driving and how Williams was driving. I asked her to stop lying to me because she had been stating that Williams was not driving up until that point. I offer a breath test, to which she also refused.  Phase #3 - Pre-Arrest Screening  Wills refused all Standardized Field of Sobriety Tests.  Wills was placed under arrest for DUI/DWI at approximately 2306 hours. A search incident to arrest was conducted on Wills person, no contraband found. I had Wills open her mouth to check for any foreign material that would interfere in taking a breath test, nothing was observed. I then placed her in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. I check the vehicle to see if I could find her phone, so she could call a ride to pick her up at the barrack. An open bottle of liquor was located on the passenger floor board without a cap and spilling over in the vehicle.  OBSERVATIONS:  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage. -Bloodshot and glassy eyes. -Admitting to consuming alcohol earlier that night. -Open container in the passenger area of the vehicle. -Suspended license and ignition interlock restriction. There was no interlock device in the vehicle.  Post Arrest:  While I was transporting Wills to the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack, Wills became extremely aggressive, cussed and insulted me with derogatory terms, and screamed in my face. At the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack D, Wills was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, so she could follow along as the DR-15 Advice of Rights was read out loud. Willsrefused to sign the DR-15 at approximately 2346 hours, acknowledging her refusal to take the test.Wills was issued all pertinent documentations regarding the incident. Wills was then released to a sober ride, at approximately 0100 hours.  All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.  I request this case to be closed by arrest.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 07:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5037</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/09/2023 20:24:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7015</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dudek</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5037</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7015</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7015</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515282</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/19/2023 23:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 07:45:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 07:46:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515282</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17578</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/19/2023 23:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 07:45:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 07:47:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515282</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3096</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/19/2023 23:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 07:45:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 07:47:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515282</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/19/2023 23:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 07:45:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 07:48:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515282</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/19/2023 23:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 07:45:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 07:49:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515282</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/19/2023 23:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 07:45:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 07:50:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515282</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>20996</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/19/2023 23:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 07:45:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 07:50:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>43</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 07:45:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:18</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>8139</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Wills</LastName>
               <FirstName>Hope</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lillian L</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/16/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.30627616E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>02/04/2014 01:46:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H100</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Wills</LastName>
               <FirstName>Hope</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lillian L</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/16/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.30627616E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>W420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H100</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/04/2014 01:46:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>220</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Perrywood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>302</SubNumber>
               <City>Aberdeen</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21001</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.204038</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.479497</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>272</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5091</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/04/2014 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 07:52:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 07:52:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 07:52:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7015</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 07:45:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7015</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 07:45:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>