<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-031092</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/04/2023 02:15:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/04/2023 02:15:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/04/2023 01:45:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/04/2023 01:45:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>HAROIAN "R" 23-480</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/04/2023 02:15:12</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/26/2023 07:35:40</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>EASTERN,MIDDLE RIVER</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>705890</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/04/2023 02:15:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 23:09:01</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>705890</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Eastern Middle</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RIV</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.4375305666667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.3318720666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/04/2023 02:15:10</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/04/2023 02:15:10</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/26/2023 07:35:41</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/04/2023 02:15:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E) TEAM* MVR Statement: The following incident was captured on in-car and Body camera. Title: HAROIANR 23-480. ID: 23-MSP-031092 Arrested: Haroian, Melisa Marie. Certification and training  -Trained in Field Sobriety Test through Maryland State Police Academy.  -Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E)  -Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  - Graduated from The Institute of Advanced Law Enforcement Studies Driving Under the Influence Institute-University of Maryland.  - I am a certified EC/IR II Intoximeter operator.  - I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor.  - I have apprehended more than 250 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On September 04, 2023, at approximately 0144 hours, I, TFC. I. Riba Tankari # 7058 with Maryland State Police was traveling westbound MD-150 (Eastern Blvd) east of MD-43 (White Marsh Blvd), Baltimore County, Maryland in lane #2 (right lane). My issued patrol vehicle is Maryland State Police unmarked unit DUI-6. At that time, I observed a white Acura TL bearing Maryland registration 8DW7243 traveling westbound MD-150 in lane #1 (left lane) appeared to be traveling over the posted speed limit and unable to stay within a single lane. I observed the Acura had crossed the dotted white line from lane #1 into lane #2 by one tire width on one occasion. I observed the Acura had changed lane into lane #2 then swerved into lane #1 by one tire width on one occasion. I followed the Acura and observed the Acura had crossed the dotted white from lane #2 into lane #1 by one tire width on one occasion. I continued to follow the Acura, accelerated to 86 MPH to get close enough, and with my properly functioning patrol vehicle Golden Eagle II radar unit set activated, I obtained a speed reading of 80 in a posted 45 MPH zone. I initiated a traffic stop on the Acura using my emergency equipment. The Acura delayed in coming to a stop. The Acura eventually came to a stop in the area of Old Eastern Avenue and MD-150, Baltimore County, Maryland. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the Acura on the driver side and made contact with the driver (sole occupant) of the vehicle. I introduced myself and explained to her the reason for the traffic stop, and she stated oh I am so sorry. I asked the driver where she was coming from, and she stated I am coming from Bowleys Quarters. I asked her where she was heading, and she stated to woodlawn, my house. I requested her drivers license and registration card. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I observed that the driver had glassy eyes. I observed the drivers movements were slow while attempting to retrieve the requested document. While speaking with the driver, I noticed her speech was slow. The driver was identified through her Maryland drivers license as Haroian, Melisa Marie. I returned to my patrol vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with. I returned to the Acura and I requested Haroian to exit her vehicle and she complied. I asked Haroian how many alcoholic beverages she had consumed, and she stated one. I asked her one of what, and she stated one of Grand Mayan, when I was at the club, but it was a while ago, I take only one drink because I know it is no good to drive under the influence. I asked her what time was her last drink, and she stated I didnt clock it, it was during daylight. I asked her if it was bottle or cup, and she stated it was like one shot. While speaking with Haroian outside her vehicle, I again detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. I asked Haroian to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and she agreed.  The evaluation surface was dry, flat, and free of debris. No surface defects were observed. My patrol flashlight, surrounding lightnings, and overhead lamps lit the area. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Haroian appeared to be in good physical conditions and was wearing high heel shoes which she removed during the test and wore slippers. I asked Haroian the following questions: Medical conditions: actually I recently had like an issue where I had a nearly fatal accident. Medications: right now I am taking, it was like oxycodone, but I havent been taking that for over two weeks. Its only Naproxen the last time I took it was early this morning. Anything that will prevent you from walking on straight line or standing on one leg: No Glasses or contact: No. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: (6/6 clues observed). The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus - Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes - Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes - Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Notes: * During the HGN test, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Haroians breath. WALK AND TURN: (4/8 clues observed). The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Haroian stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage: Haroian lost her balance to the right on three separate occasions and stood with her right foot next to her left. Notes *Im sorry, are you trying to arrest me? Walking Stage (1st Nine): Missed touching heel to toe by more than half inch on counts 1, 5, 6, and 8. Stepped completely offline by one shoe width on counts 9. Turn: The turn was not completed correctly; instead Haroian turned to her left failing to take a series of small steps as instructed and demonstrated. Walking Stage (2nd Nine): Missed touching heel to toe by more than half inch on counts 2 and 4. One Leg Stand Test (2/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Haroian stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Left foot raised during the test. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: Raised arms more than six (6) inches from her side for balance. Seconds 11-20: Left foot hit the ground one time. Seconds 21-30: Raised arms more than six (6) inches from her side for balance. Preliminary Breath Test:  I explained and offered a PBT to Haroian. Haroian refused to consent to the PBT. ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Haroian was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a motor vehicle safely:    - Driving over the posted speed limit (80 Mph in 45 Mph speed limit zone)  -Unable to stay within a single lane/driving patterns.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath as she conversed with me.  -Glassy eyes.  -Her admissions to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to driving.  -Observed signs of impairment as she performed the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  Haroian was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a motor vehicle at 0208 hours and was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack. Upon arrival at Barrack, Haroian was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and it was read to her from the MVA website in English, and she refused to consent to the Intoximeter EC/IR II test at 0237 hours. A properly functioning instrument and operator were available. Haroian was polite and cooperative during the encounter. Haroian was given pertinent paperwork and released from the Barrack to her boyfriend pending an appearance in the District Court of Maryland for Baltimore County at a later date.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 23:14:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/20/2023 11:23:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>520541</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/04/2023 02:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 23:09:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 23:11:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 23:09:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 23:12:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>387109</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>HAROIAN</LastName>
               <FirstName>MELISA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MARIE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/25/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/05/2023 23:00:53</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H650</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M420</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>HAROIAN</LastName>
               <FirstName>MELISA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MARIE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/25/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H650</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M420</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/05/2023 23:00:53</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>36</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Charles</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21201</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3100</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.615483</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.287945</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>841</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0239</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 23:12:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 23:12:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 23:12:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 23:10:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 23:10:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156822</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 23:14:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 23:14:19</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>19UUA66265A042847</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2005</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>ACUR</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ATL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8DW7243</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleValue>1000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>