<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-036034</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/14/2023 01:18:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/14/2023 01:18:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/14/2023 00:43:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/14/2023 00:43:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>MYERS "R" 23-550</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 01:18:55</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/04/2023 21:55:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>709847</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 01:18:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/18/2023 09:42:43</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>709847</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Eastern</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Essex</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.46035</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.31628</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OLD EASTERN AVE / EASTERN BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/14/2023 01:18:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/14/2023 01:18:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/04/2023 21:55:32</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 01:18:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 16:26:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E) TEAM* MVR Statement: The following incident was captured on in-car and Body camera. Title: MYERS R 23-550. ID: 23-MSP-036034 Arrested: Myers, Brandon Nathaniel. Certification and training  -Trained in Field Sobriety Test through Maryland State Police Academy.  -Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E)  -Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  - Graduated from The Institute of Advanced Law Enforcement Studies Driving Under the Influence Institute-University of Maryland.  - I am a certified EC/IR II Intoximeter operator.  - I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor.  - I have apprehended more than 260 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On October 14, 2023, at approximately 0039 hours, I, TFC. I. Riba Tankari # 7058 with Maryland State Police was traveling westbound MD-150 (Eastern Blvd) east of Wilson Point Road, Baltimore County, Maryland in the left turning lane. My issued patrol vehicle is Maryland State Police unmarked unit DUI-6. At that time, I observed a white sedan later found to be a white Lincoln MKZ bearing Maryland registration 49882HT traveling westbound MD-150 in lane #1 at a high rate of speed. I followed the Lincoln, accelerated to 106 MPH to get close enough, and with my properly functioning patrol vehicle Golden Eagle II radar unit set activated, I obtained a speed reading of 99 in a posted 45 MPH zone. On one occasion, I observed the Lincoln had crossed the dotted white from lane #1 into lane #2 by one tire width and continued traveling partially between the two lanes. I initiated a traffic stop on the Lincoln using my emergency equipment. The Lincoln delayed in coming to a stop. I observed the Lincoln had crossed the solid white line into left turning lane then made left turning onto southbound Old Eastern Avenue crossing the double yellow into northbound Old Eastern Avenue by more than half vehicle width before coming to a stop in the area of southbound Eastern Avenue and south of MD-150, Baltimore County, Maryland in the traveling lane. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the Lincoln on the driver side and made contact with the driver (the sole occupant) of the vehicle. I introduced myself and explained to him the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver where he was coming from, and he ignored my questions. The driver handed me his drivers license prior to my request. I then requested his registration card. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I observed that the driver had glassy eyes. The driver was identified through his Maryland drivers license as Myers, Brandon Nathaniel. While returning to my vehicle, Myers stated he wanted to talk to the commanding officer and rolled up his window while I was talking to him. TFC. White # 6932 assisted me with the traffic stop. I returned to the Lincoln and I requested Myers to exit his vehicle and refused to comply. Myers continued asking for commanding officer and rolling his window up while talking to him. Myers was told the commanding officer was not available, and he continued to refuse to exit his vehicle. Officer Peters #6257 with Baltimore County Police responded on scene and a Baltimore County supervisor on duty was called. Sgt. Payvon #4550 with the Baltimore County Police Department responded on scene and Myers was again asked to exit the vehicle multiple times, and he refused to exit the vehicle. At that Myers was pulled out of his vehicle and was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: (Refused). Nothing to report, Myers refused the test. WALK AND TURN: (Refused). Nothing to report, Myers refused the test. One Leg Stand Test (Refused) Nothing to report, Myers refused the test. Preliminary Breath Test: Nothing to report, PBT was not offered. ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Myers was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a motor vehicle safely:  - Driving over the posted speed limit (99 Mph in 45 Mph speed limit zone)  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle.  -Glassy eyes.  -Refused to exit vehicle to performStandardized Field Sobriety Tests.  Myers was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a motor vehicle at 0118 hours. After his arrest, Myers requested to use the bathroom and was told to hold it until we get to the barrack, and he stated Im about to piss on myself. Myers was asked to get inside my vehicle, and he continued being uncooperative and stated since when do suspects get in front seat, I am trying to sit on my own in the backseat where I belong. Due to Myers being uncooperative he was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack by OFC Peters #6257. A search incident to arrest revealed no weapons or contraband. While securing his vehicle a can of Natural Ice beer was recovered underneath the drivers seat (see attachments). Upon arrival at the Barrack, Myers again requested to use the bathroom I agreed. While removing the handcuffs, Myers urinated himself (see attachments) and stated I asked, I told you. Myers was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and it was read to him from the MVA website in English. Myers refused to answer if he was taking the test or not and the test was marked as refusal at 0233 hours. Myers refused to sign the DR-15 advice of rights and DR-15A order of suspension. A properly functioning instrument and operator were available. Myers was not cooperative during the encounter, he was told he was released and was offered ride home, and he refused to leave the building. Myers started walking around, continued asking if he was released and keep looking around. Due to his unusual behavior and level of impairment, EMS was called and Myers refused to answer their questions. Myers was escorted to the lobby. While being escorted, Myers dialed 911. I later made contact with Myers father via telephone who agreed to come pick him up.  Myers was given pertinent paperwork and released from the Barrack to his father pending an appearance in the District Court of Maryland for Baltimore County at a later date. All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland. Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 10:01:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/02/2023 12:48:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525495</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 01:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 09:44:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/18/2023 09:45:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>36</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 09:44:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/18/2023 09:47:21</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390663</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>MYERS</LastName>
               <FirstName>BRANDON</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>NATHANIEL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/18/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/18/2023 09:17:01</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>MYERS</LastName>
               <FirstName>BRANDON</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>NATHANIEL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/18/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/18/2023 09:17:01</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Strawberry</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Middle River</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21220</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1280</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.369946</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.361612</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 09:47:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 09:47:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 09:47:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 09:44:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/18/2023 09:44:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158158</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 10:01:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/18/2023 10:01:14</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3LN6L2G95DR806595</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>LINC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MKZ</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>49882HT</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>4</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleValue>1000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>