<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-036644</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/18/2023 23:11:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/18/2023 23:11:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/18/2023 22:17:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/18/2023 22:17:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 23:12:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/03/2023 09:31:10</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>EASTON BYP/ TRISTAN DR</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>710353</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 23:12:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 03:05:59</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>710353</AddressId>
         <StreetName>MD 322</StreetName>
         <City>Easton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.0715615</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.7468775</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/18/2023 23:11:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/18/2023 23:11:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/31/2023 04:08:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 23:12:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 16:27:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Alcohol Influence Report Patrol Vehicle Information  I-26 (Marked) is not equipped with a mobile recording device, however, I am equipped with a BWC (Body Worn Camera), which was operational.  Defendant: Willey, Kellie Denise Date of Birth: 03/03/1972 Date of Arrest: 10/18/2023 Time of Arrest: 2217 Maryland SDX: MD1027260174 License Status  Valid License Restrictions  None Registration Violations  None  Officers Training/Experience * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Anne Arundel County Police Department, Maryland State Police Department, and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police * Certified Drug Recognition Expert since 2017 * Graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute 2019 *2023 Frederick Police Department Green Lab  *Repeat Offender* - No  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  I was on routine patrol in the area of the Maryland State Police Barrack, located at 7053 Ocean Gateway, Easton, Talbot County Maryland. A look out was broadcasted over our dispatch. The lookout was for a gray Audi that was operating on the wrong side of Ocean Gateway, heading towards the Trappe area from Cambridge. I started traveling east bound on Ocean Gateway, and parked my patrol vehicle on Boh Brooks Road, facing the west bound traffic on Ocean Gateway, with my patrol vehicles head lamps still activated. After waiting a few moments, I observed a gray Audi coupe, traveling in lane 2, on west bound Ocean Gateway, now traveling on the correct portion of the highway. I pulled out of Boh Brooks Road, and began following the Audi. While traveling behind the Audi on Ocean Gateway, prior to the south end of the Easton Bypass, or Route 322, I observed the Audi, drift across the solid white line separating the shoulder of the highway and lane 2, for a second or two. The vehicle then quickly jerked to the left, now swerving into lane 1 of Ocean Gateway. At no point did I observe a turn signal activate on the Audi. The Audi, now traveling in lane 1 of Ocean Gateway, turned into the turn lane, to exit off of Ocean Gateway and onto the Easton Bypass. The Audi was traveling in the far right turn lane, as it approached the steady red circular red light, located at east bound Ocean Gateway. The Audi, stopped, with its two front tires, in front of the solid white stop line of the intersection. Prior to the light turning green, the Audi, slowly moved forward, entering the intersection, now crossing the solid white stop line with all four of its tires. As the Audi moved slowly into the intersection, with the steady red light still activated, I observed a large truck and trailer traveling east bound on Ocean Gateway in lane 1, at the same intersection, coming only a few feet from striking the Audi.  The light turned green, and the Audi, continued, traveling on the Easton Bypass, now headed to South Washington Street. I conducted a traffic stop, and the Audi pulled over into the right shoulder of the highway. The Audi, came to a complete stop, over the solid white line, in the shoulder, however, it was less than a foot from being on the white line. The Audi had several more feet to move further to the right, over in the shoulder.    PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I made contact with the driver of the vehicle at the driver side B pillar. The driver was later positively identified via her Maryland drivers license as Kellie Denise Willey. Willey was advised that I was a Trooper with the Maryland State Police and that the stop was being recorded with audio and video.  When I first came up to the driver side B pillar, I could see Willey, with both of her hands up, off of the steering wheel, palms facing toward the steering wheel. Kellie looked back at me. The vehicle was on with the keys still in the ignition. I could see her eyes were extremely bloodshot. Kellie then looked forward and grabbed a hold of the steering wheel with both hands. As I introduced myself, Kellie looked forward and back at me several times, with her hands still on the steering wheel.  Kellie then moved her hands off of the steering wheel and held them in front of her chest, with her palms now facing her. Kellie was asked to provide her license, registration, and proof of insurance.  Kellie stated she did not have that documentation, stating that her boyfriend took it from her. I asked Kellie, where she was coming from. Kellie stated Easton, Maryland. Kellie then quickly changed her mind and said Cambridge, Maryland. Kellie stated, 403 sawway court. I asked Kellie where she was headed. Kellie, stated, home. I asked where home was. Kellie took a deep breath and paused, muttering to herself.  Kellie then stated she was just in a really bad argument with her boyfriend. Kellie stated she had just came from Cambridge, and wanted to go to her house. Kellie was now sulking, with her head in her hands, appearing to be crying.  At this point, I could smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from within the vehicle. Kellie had blood shot eyes and was slurring her speech. Kellie was asked to step out of the vehicle. Kellie shook her head side to side, indicating that she did not want to step out. Kellie was now visibly crying holding her hands to her face. Kellie stated, no. Kellie stated, no, again. Kellie was asked if she was ok, and if she needed an ambulance. Kellie shook her head side to side, with no verbal response, indicating to me, that she was ok, and did not need an ambulance. Kellie was asked if she had any injuries. Kellie refused to answer this question, holding her hands to her face. Kellie then stated she was being harassed by her malicious boyfriend. Kellie repeated herself, stating that she just left Cambridge, and she was just trying to go home. Kellie stated she was very upset, and had to gather her thoughts. Kellie stated she was going to sit in the car. Kellie was now ordered out of the vehicle. Kellie failed to obey this lawful order, and continued sitting in the driver seat, still buckled. Kellie stated, that my family are State Troopers. Kellie was told to step out again. Kellie stated, that she wasnt going to do that. Kellie was ordered several times to step out of the vehicle and each time, Kellie would refused to comply. Kellie stated that her boyfriend is harassing her.  Talbot County Sheriffs Office was on scene with me as well and were asked to talk with her and attempt to de-escalate the situation, with no success.  I came back and made another approach to speak with Kellie. Now the vehicle was turned off and the windows were rolled up. After knocking on the window, Kellie cracked the window to speak with me. Kellie held her phone in her hands, stating that she was going to call her lawyer. Kellie was asked about the argument that she had with her boyfriend. Kellie stated that he set her up. Kellie was upset, saying that everything she says will be used against her.  Kellie was asked about consuming alcohol. Kellie denied consuming any alcoholic beverages. Kellie was asked again to step out of the vehicle. Kellie stated that she was not getting out of her vehicle. Kellie was asked again to step out. Kellie, again, denied stepping out of the vehicle. I told Kellie, that if she does not exit the vehicle, I will forcibly remove her. Kellie then told me that I was going to give her a few minutes to call her attorney. Kellie was now speaking on her phone with someone.  Kellie rolled up her windows, while she spoke on the phone. I opened her driver door, and told her not to do that. Kellie told the person on the phone where she was at, stating that she was by the Saint Peter and Paul. Kellie was asked to step out of the vehicle again. And again, she refused. I requested to speak with the individual. Kellie then called the person back and I spoke with them. I requested that she attempt to convince Kellie out of the vehicle. The female on the other end of the phone, began talking to Kellie, requesting that she listen to the officer.  Kellie finally took her seatbelt off and exited the vehicle. As she exited, she had a drunk-like walk, swaying to her left, as she took a few steps and made it to the rear of her vehicle.  Kellie was asked to preform standardized field sobriety tests. Kellie stated, that she would rather wait for Carrey, who was the individual speaking with her on the phone. Kellie stated she was really nervous. It should be noted that at this point, I could smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath.  Willey would eventually consent to conducting the first test with me.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Willeys eyes. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Willey pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting Nystagmus. Willey indicated that she understood the directions.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Vertical Nystagmus  Present  Observation : Willey had to be reminded of the instructions.  WALK AND TURN (0/8)  REFUSED                        ONE LEG STAND (0/8)  REFUSED   A PBT was offered and refused. Willey was asked about rating herself on the scale of 0-10, with 0 being sober, and 10 being the most drunk shes ever been, where she thought she was right now. Willey stated, she didnt know how to answer that question. Willey stated that she did not understand the scale.  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Willey was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol.  -6/6 HGN -Vertical Nystagmus -REFUSED all other field sobriety offered  -Drunk-like walk -Impaired memory  couldnt recall where she was coming from -Emotional -Lack of concentration  had to be reminded instructions of simple test -Strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from breath -Blood shot eyes -Slurred speech -Inability to maintain lane travel on roadway -Inability to stop vehicle appropriately at intersection   Due to the number of observations, I concluded Willey was driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. I placed Willey under arrest at 2310 hours. Willey was placed in handcuffs and seated in the front seat of my patrol vehicle. Willey was then read aloud the DR-15 Advice of Rights form using the MVA audio file in my patrol vehicle. Willey was provided a copy of the same form to read along. Willey was transported to the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack. After hearing her rights, Willey would refuse to complete a test for alcohol concentration at 2318 hours. While seating in my patrol vehicle, with the windows up, the odor of an alcoholic beverage was now overwhelming.  Willey refused to sign her copies of the MVA related paperwork. Willey was issued the following traffic citations : driving while under the influence of alcohol, driving while impaired by alcohol, negligent driving, reckless driving, failure to obey properly placed traffic control device, driver failing to stop at steady red circular signal, and failure to drive on right half of roadway. Willey was issued her copies of the MVA related paperwork and released to a sober driver.    All events occurred in Talbot County, Maryland.   Intoximeter Result : Refused. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/19/2023 03:32:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 05:14:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Caraballo</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5793</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dadds</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5551</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Del Vecchio</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Koehler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7524</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>526106</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/18/2023 22:17:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/19/2023 03:07:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 03:07:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>51</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/19/2023 03:14:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 03:14:20</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390711</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Willey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kellie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Denise</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/03/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/19/2023 03:13:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Willey</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kellie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Denise</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/03/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/19/2023 03:13:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>28501</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sawgrass</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Easton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.0876898</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.7578659</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>463</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7652</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/19/2023 03:14:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/19/2023 03:14:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/19/2023 03:07:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 03:07:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158182</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/19/2023 03:25:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 03:25:16</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>TRUC1AFV0H1002443</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>AUDI</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>CP</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1FM9341</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>8</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>