<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009715</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/17/2023 21:11:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/17/2023 21:11:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/17/2023 20:17:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/17/2023 20:17:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Suspects assaulted each other with personal weapons. Suspect hindered completion of police objective.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 21:12:03</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0266</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 08:26:46</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OBT</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>ROCK HALL RD/FAIRLEE,CHESTERTOWN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>687648</AddressId>
      <City>MDC126</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 21:12:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 15:19:46</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>687648</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Rock Hall</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.157999</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.221728</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/17/2023 21:11:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/17/2023 21:11:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>80</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/19/2023 22:16:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 21:12:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>INCIDENT CAPTURED ON BODY CAM  ATTACHMENTS:  PH #343558 Civil Citation Statement of probable cause State of Charges  PHOTOGRAPHS:  Injuries of both parties taken.  Damage to Blockstons vehicle.   NARRATIVE:    On Friday March 17th, 2023 at approximately 2020 hours, I was dispatched to respond to Rt. 20 in the area of Fairlee Rd regarding a possible domestic dispute between the female caller and her male boyfriend. Prior to arrival, MSP Centreville dispatched advised they were in a silver Nissan Sentra, the female caller stated she had been assaulted and her boyfriend had taken her phone and was now walking in the field away from the roadway.   Upon arrival I observed a silver Nissan Sentra facing Westbound on Rt. 20 East of Fairlee Rd. The vehicle was angled towards the right shoulder of the roadway and the drivers side rear tire of the vehicle still in the roadway. I observed a female standing in the roadway next to TFC Mulhearn. The female was crying, talking and screaming about damage to her car and returning to work. A male subject was walking near the Nissan Sentra. I advised the female to step out of the roadway and speak with me. The female, later identified as Cheyenne Lee Blockston, came to the front of my patrol vehicle with me. The male asked where we were going, I stated to the male that I was going to speak with her. At the front of my patrol vehicle, Blockston was sobbing and stated she and the male, later identified as Markel Laquis Norfleet, had gotten into an argument in the vehicle after she had asked him a question. She stated Norfleet blew the situation out of proportion and started hitting her. I observed blood on Blockstons neck and advised her of the blood. I asked her if she wanted an ambulance to respond to the scene which she declined. While speaking with me Norfleet began walking towards where Blockston and I were standing asking how did I push you? Norfleet was advised to remain where he was standing so I could speak with Blockston. I began speaking with Blockston again and offered her a paper towel to wipe her neck. We stepped to the rear passenger side door of my passenger vehicle where Blockston wiped blood off of her neck. Blockston told me again that they argued and stated that the injury on her neck came when Norfleet had tried to move her out of the way. Blockston allowed me to view the injury and leaned her head back. At that time I observed a scrape on her neck approximately a quarter of an inch long. Blockston also stated that she hit Norfleet as well but she was unaware if he had any injuries. During the conversation I ascertained that Blockston and Norfleet have been in a relationship involving sex for approximately 6 months however they do not reside together. I also learned that the argument between the two of them stemmed from Blockston asking a question about juice in the vehicle and Norfleet assuming Blockston was accusing him of infidelity. I then advised Blockston to remain standing at the rear of my patrol vehicle while I speak with Norfleet.   I then spoke with Norfleet who was standing with TFC Mulhearn and Cpl Holson in the grass next to TFC Mulhearns patrol vehicle. Norfleet was wearing a black hooded sweat shirt and had the neck pulled up so that it was covering his mouth. Norfleet was also using his cell phone to record the police response. Norfleet would only state that he and Blockston got into an argument. Norfleet stated no assault had occurred. Norfleet was then placed under arrest for domestic assault. As Norfleet was being taken into custody and was advised that Blockston had a cut on her neck, Norfleet then stated that his lip was injured and added I just dont snitch on shit. When I first made observations of Norfleet, I did not observe any signs of injury. Norfleets father arrived on scene while he was being placed into custody. As Norfleet was being searched and placed into TFC Mulhearns vehicle, a handrolled cigarette containing suspected marijuana was located in Norfleets pocket.   Norfleet remained with TFC Mulhearn and Cpl Holson as I returned to my patrol vehicle to clear off the seat to transport Norfleet. Blockston was leaning on the passenger side rear quarter panel of my vehicle. I advised Blockston to step to the rear of my patrol vehicle. Blockston asked why Norfleet was under arrest. I advised her he was being placed under arrest for domestic assault. Blockston stated but I hit him too and remained standing in the same spot next to my patrol vehicle. Blockston was advised that I was going to be placing Norfleet in my patrol vehicle. After my fourth request for Blockston to step away from my patrol vehicle, she stated Im not stepping over there. She repeated this statement two more times. I advised Blockston that if Norfleet had visible injuries, she would be placed under arrest as well. Blockston still physically and verbally refused to step away from my patrol vehicle. I advised Blockston that she was hindering me from completing what I am required to do. I requested again that Blockston step away from my patrol vehicle in order for me to place Norfleet in my patrol vehicle. Blockston stated that Norfleet would not be getting into my vehicle because it was a two way thing. I then advised Blockston to step away from my patrol vehicle and if she needed to be placed under arrest I would do so after. During the interaction between Blockston and I she relocated herself from the rear quarter panel of my car to the crease in between the front and rear passenger side doors. Where Blockston was standing I would not have been able to open the front passenger door without it coming into contact with Blockston. Her location also would have allowed for Norfleet to be within reach of her if I attempted to place him in my patrol vehicle. During this interaction, Blockstons vehicle was still partially in the roadway, and (3) police vehicles were on the shoulder with overhead lights activated. Vehicles passing on Rt. 20 had to slow and/or move across the center of the roadway in order to safely pass the scene. Blockstons continued refusal to move away from my patrol vehicle extended the time in which other vehicles had to conduct themselves outside of a regular traffic pattern to safely pass the scene.I requested Blockston step away from my patrol vehicle seven times at this point, and Blockston had repeated back to me ten times that she was not going to move. I then requested TFC Mulhearn or Cpl Holson to respond to where Blockston and I were standing.   Cpl Holson walked over and I stated again to Blockston that she needed to step away from my patrol vehicle to which she replied youre not locking him up. Cpl Holson advised Blockston that she would be placed under arrest for interfering with the arrest. Blockston repeated that she was not moving and that Norfleet was not under arrest. Blockston was then taken into custody and placed in my patrol vehicle without further incident. While in my patrol vehicle, Blockston stated that Norfleet had jumped on the front of her vehicle causing damage to the front of the vehicle. (Photos taken) Blockston was also concerned that she could not find her phone. When I offered to have someone call her phone in an attempt to locate it, Blockston stated that her phone was off.   Once Blockston was secured in my patrol vehicle, I took photos of the damage to Blockstons vehicle. I then spoke with Norfleet while he was seated in TFC Mulhearns patrol vehicle. I observed swelling to Norfleets lips. (Photos taken) Blockston gave permission for Norfleets father to move her vehicle out of the travel portion of the roadway. Cpl Holson attempted to located Blockstons phone with negative results.  Both suspects were transported to the Centreville barrack and processed. At 23:58 hours Norfleet requested medical attention for the injury to his lip. EMS arrived at the barrack at 00:06 hours. Norfleet was assessed and refused to be transported to a medical facility. Both suspects were transported to the Kent County Commissioners office at separate times. Blockston received a $15,000 unsecured bond and was released from the commissioners office. Norfleet received a $10,000 unsecured bond and was released from the commissioners office.   ALL OF THE ABOVE EVENTS OCCURRED IN KENT COUNTY, MARYLAND.           </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 15:48:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4349</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 18:49:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mulhearn</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6494</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Holson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Troy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6575</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joyce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4349</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wiley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6097</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joyce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4349</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joyce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4349</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499115</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/17/2023 20:57:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 15:31:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4349</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 15:40:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499115</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0043</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/17/2023 20:17:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0043</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 15:40:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4349</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 15:40:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499115</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0055</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/17/2023 20:17:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 0055</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 15:41:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4349</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 15:41:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 15:31:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>277254</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Norfleet</LastName>
               <FirstName>Markel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Laquis</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/17/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/25/2020 13:48:05</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N614</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M624</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Norfleet</LastName>
               <FirstName>Markel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Laquis</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/17/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>N614</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M624</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/25/2020 13:48:05</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>10260</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>BIG STONE</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>MILLINGTON</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21651</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.811351</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.256801</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>810</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4816</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/25/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>282</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6230</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 15:38:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 15:38:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 15:38:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 15:43:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>19</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 15:39:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371913</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Blockston</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cheyenne</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/02/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/18/2023 14:54:48</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B423</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Blockston</LastName>
               <FirstName>Cheyenne</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/02/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B423</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/18/2023 14:54:48</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>23152</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Woodsedge</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Chestertown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21620</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.167688</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.233964</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>480</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2419</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 17:57:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 17:57:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 15:42:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 15:41:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4349</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 15:41:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 17:33:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4349</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 17:33:07</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>HAND ROLLED CIGARETTE</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>245625</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.8</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>