<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-006391</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/18/2023 22:01:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/18/2023 22:01:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/18/2023 21:52:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/18/2023 21:52:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>23-96-038 Ehrisman DUI, 2nd degree assault on LEO, MDOP, Disorderly Conduct</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 22:01:10</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1773</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 07:34:39</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>MDOP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY/ GOLF COURSE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>529788</AddressId>
      <City>MDC208</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 22:01:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 15:43:17</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>529788</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.105139</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.336217</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50 BESIDE THE BRDGE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WINE RACK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OUTBACK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 PAST GOLF COURSE/ PULLING INTO THE OUTLETS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12747-12821 OCEAN GTWY / 10002-10025 GOLF COURSE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50 / GOLF COURSE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>50 IN FRONT OF OUTLETS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12812-12820 OCEAN GTWY / 9927-9941 GOLF COURSE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12747-12821 OCEAN GTWY / 9942-10001 GOLF COURSE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12822-12824 OCEAN GTWY / 9927-9941 GOLF COURSE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12823-12849 OCEAN GTWY / 9942-10001 GOLF COURSE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12800-12850 OCEAN GTWY / 0-0 GOLF COURSE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12773-12799 OCEAN GTWY / 10000-10051 GOLF COURSE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12773-12799 OCEAN GTWY / 10052-10084 GOLF COURSE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12800-12850 OCEAN GTWY / 9807-9899 GOLF COURSE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/18/2023 22:01:06</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/18/2023 22:01:06</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/08/2023 09:54:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 22:01:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/16/2023 21:12:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MD Soundex: E-625-115-564-381 DUI #: 23-96-038 Subsequent offender: Yes MSP unmarked unit V-24 isequipped with a camera system. This incident was recorded on my agency issued body worn camera. The Worcester County Sheriffs Office and Ocean City EMS were also on scene.  Property Damaged (Total Value $570.00):    MSP unmarked vehicle V-24 front windshield - Total Value: $450  MSP unmarked vehicle V-24 passenger side air conditioning vent - Total Value: $120  Narrative:   On 02/18/2023 at approximately 2148 hours I, TFC Bradley, was on patrol in the area of southbound Philadelphia Ave near 2nd Street Ocean City, MD 21842.  Phase One - Vehicle in Motion:    While on patrol, I observed a gray Volkswagen traveling behind me in lane three, and it appeared to be traveling at a high rate of speed. The vehicle passed me and continued to be traveling at what appeared to be above the posted speed limit. When thevehicle was approaching the turn to head westbound on US RT 50 from Philadelphia Ave, the operator did not slow down to a reasonable speed and jerked the wheel very rapidly to maneuver the turn. After witnessing this driving behavior, I began to follow the Volkswagen bearing MD registration 4FD0398. I observed the vehicle to be traveling at what appeared to be above the posted speed limit of 35 mph across the Harry Kelly Bridge. I activated my Kustom Golden Eagle II radar front antenna and obtained a speed reading of 51 mph. I am a certified RADAR operator through the Maryland State Police and my radar unit was tested before and after use and appeared to be functioning correctly. I also observed the vehicle cross over the center dotted white line into lane one approximately a tires width prior to Inlet Isle Ln. I conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle in the area of westbound US RT 50 and Golf Course rd.  Phase Two - Personal Contact:    I made contact with the operator at the drivers side window, advised her for the reason of the stop and asked to see her drivers license and registration. I could detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle as she explained that she was coming from Seacrets in Ocean City. She also advised that she consumed two alcoholic beverages and one shot prior to driving. I then returned to my vehicle, called for a second unit, and conducted a license and wanted check. I was able to identify the operator by her Maryland Drivers license as Chelsea Lynn Ehrisman.  Phase Three - Pre-Arrest Screening:    I returned to the vehicle and asked Ehrisman to exit the vehicle, which she agreed. I escorted Ehrisman to the front of her vehicle where I could still detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage. I asked Ehrisman if she had consumed any other alcoholic beverages prior to driving.Ehrisman responded by saying I had more than I probably should have drank.Ehrisman continued to say that she could not afford to be in trouble and I advised that we would be completing some tests, andshe interrupted by saying I will not pass.Ehrisman stated that her friend might be safe to drive, but she didnt know if she was safe to drive at this point.  I asked Ehrisman if she wore glasses or contacts, and she stated she was currently wearing contacts. Ehrisman stated she did not have any injuries and did not take any medications. My front facing lights were deactivated prior to administering tests.  The first test administered was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test:    Iexplained and demonstrated the test to Ehrisman. Ehrismanadvised she understood the instructions and did not have any questions. Prior to beginning the test, I held my pen twelve (12) to fifteen (15) inches from Ehrismansnose, slightly above eye level. During the test, Ehrismandisplayed equal pupil size and equal tracking. Ehrisman displayed lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes. A check for Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was conducted with positive results.  A total of six (6) clues were observed during this test.  The second test administered was the Walk and Turn Test:    Iexplained and demonstrated the test to Ehrisman. Prior to my instructions, I advised Ehrisman to stand on an imaginary line with her right foot in front of her left in a heel to toe manner, tokeep her arms down at her sides and to not begin until I tell her to start.Ehrisman was unable to maintain balance at any time during my instructions.  Upon completion of my explanation and demonstration of the test,Ehrisman advised she understood the instructions and did not have any questions. On the first series of nine heel to toe steps,Ehrisman only took eight steps.Ehrisman raised her arms on every step greater than six inches from her body.Ehrisman stepped off-line on steps one, three, and five.Ehrisman missed stepping heel to toe on steps three, four, and five.Ehrisman did not complete the turn as instructed.Ehrisman kept both feet planted and spun in one complete motion.Ehrisman then stopped walking and asked if she should walk back. I advisedEhrisman to walk back, and she resumed the test. On the second series of nine heel to toe steps,Ehrisman raised her arms greater than six inches from her body on every step.Ehrisman missed stepping heel to toe on steps one, three, and seven.  A total of seven (7) clues were observed during this test.  The third test administered was the One Leg Stand Test:    Iexplained and demonstrated the test to Ehrisman. Upon completion of my explanation and demonstration, Ehrisman advised she didunderstand the instructions and had no questions.Ehrisman balanced on her left foot. Approximately two seconds in to the test,Ehrisman swayed from side to side, raised her arms greater than six inches from her body, and placed her right foot on the ground.Ehrisman did these exact same clues at 6, 8, 14, and 23 seconds. After fourteen seconds into the test,Ehrisman kept her arms raised for the duration of the test.  A total of three (3) clues were observed during this test.  Upon completion of the tests, I offered Ehrisman to submit to a Preliminary Breath Test, which she refused.  Based on my training at the Maryland State Police Academy, knowledge, experience and prior DUI arrests, I placed Ehrismanunder arrest for Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol at approximately 2159 hours on 02/18/2023.    While Ehrisman was handcuffed in my front seat, she was able to slip her left hand through the handcuff and free herself. I ordered Ehrisman out of the vehicle which she initially refused. Ehrisman exited my vehicle and was screaming that she would not get back into my vehicle and that she would not be handcuffed again. Ehrismans passenger was on scene and was assisting trying to calmEhrisman down. I was able to eventually get Ehrisman handcuffed again and placed back inside my vehicle. Ehrisman was handcuffed in the front and secured in my vehicle with a seat belt lock. I began to transport Ehrisman to the MSP Berlin Barrack.     While enroute to the MSP Berlin Barrack, Ehrisman began kicking the inside of my vehicle and flailing her body around. Ehrisman got herself so worked up that she stated she could not breathe. I immediately pulled over in the area of westbound US RT 50 and Herring Creek Ln Ocean City, MD 21842 and contacted the MSP Berlin Barrack to dispatch EMS to my location. While waiting for EMS to arrive, Ehrisman leaned back into the passenger seat and placed her feet on the dashboard. Ehrisman began kicking the dashboard repeatedly and destroyed the air conditioning vent located in the right corner of the dashboard. Ehrisman then raised her feet again and began kicking the windshield. Ehrisman repeatedly kicked the windshield until it shattered on the passenger side. The approximate value of the windshield is $450.00 and the approximate value of the air conditioning vent is $120.00. Photographs were taken of all the damaged property in accordance with agency policy. WhileEhrismanwas screaming and acting unruly, her mouth began to fill with white spit or foam.Ehrismanwas so worked up that we were unable to get her attention to help her calm down.    Upon the arrival of Ocean City EMS, Ehrisman was brought out of my vehicle by paramedics to be evaluated by EMS. Ehrisman sat down on the ground and began screaming again. Ehrisman continuously screamed that we should let her go and kept rolling around in the grass. Ehrisman would not allow EMS to fully evaluate her and Ocean City EMS determined that they would have to administer medication to sedate Ehrisman. Ocean City EMS advised that Ehrisman would need to be on the stretcher in order to administer medication. Prior to moving Ehrisman, she began rolling around and kicking her legs, so we could not move her. While Ehrisman was kicking, she struck Worcester County Sheriffs Deputy Jones in the right knee. After this incident, Deputy Jones was evaluated at Atlantic General Hospital. Ehrisman was ultimately lifted by Ocean City EMS and Deputy Jones and carried over to the stretcher approximately ten feet away.Ehrisman was buckled into the stretcher by EMS personnel andgiven sedation medication. Ocean City EMS then transported Ehrisman to Atlantic General Hospital (AGH)(EMS# 23-00484). The sedation medication given by EMS proved to be ineffective. This led me to believe thatEhrismanmay have taken some sort of controlled dangerous substance. I believed this because of the white spit/ foam in her mouth, and her still flailing her body around after being sedated. TFC Brittingham and TFC Phillips followed EMS to AGH and I responded to the MSP Berlin Barrack to start working on charges forEhrisman. Cpl. Lenz also responded to AGH to assist.    Upon Ehrismans arrival to AGH, she began screaming and disturbing the entire emergency room. Ehrisman was evaluated quickly by AGH staff, cleared medically, and issued her discharge paperwork. AGH staff then requested Ehrisman be removed from the emergency room due to her disorderly behavior. Ehrisman was removed from the emergency room and transported to the MSP Berlin Barrack. Upon Ehrismans arrival to the MSP Berlin Barrack, I was walked outside to help assist her inside. I observedEhrisman laying on her back inside the Ocean City Police transport wagon. Cpl. Lenz assistedEhrisman in sitting up. Then Cpl. Lenz and TFC Brittingham assistedEhrisman to the door and out of the transport wagon.Ehrisman was then escorted into the MSP Berlin Barrack by Cpl. Lenz and TFC Phillips and placed in cell #2.Ehrisman was uncuffed in the cell and a search was completed by TFC Brittingham. Once the search was complete Troopers exited the cell and shut the door.Ehrisman ran towards the cell door and began screaming and banging on the cell door.    Ehrisman was read her DR-15 Advice of Rights. Due to Ehrismans violent and erratic behavior, it was determined that it was not safe for her to be removed from the cell and brought to the processing room for a breath test.Ehrismanspent approximately four hours in cell #2 at the MSP Berlin Barrack. For the entire duration,Ehrismanwas pounding her fists on the cell door and screaming.Ehrismanwas checked on regularly and monitored via the cell camera to ensure she was physically ok.    Ehrisman was brought before the Ocean City District Court Commissioner for the following charges:    CR 3-203 Assault second degree on LEO  CR 3-203 Assault second degree  CR 6-301 Malicious destruction of property less than $1,000  CR 10-201 (c)(2) Disorderly conduct  TA21-902 (a) (1): Driving Vehicle under the Influence of Alcohol  TA21-902 (b) (1): Driving While Impaired by Alcohol  TA 21-902 (c1i): Driving vehicle while so far impaired by drugs  alcohol cannot drive safely  TA 21-901.1(a): Reckless driving vehicle in wanton and willful disregard for safety of persons and property  TA 21-901.1 (b): Negligent Driving in Careless and Imprudent Manner Endangering Property, Life, and Person  TA 21-309(d): driver failure to obey designated lane direction  TA 21801.1: Exceeding posted maxim speed limit: 51 mph in a posted 35 mph zone    Ehrismanwas ultimately released on a $5,000.00 unsecured bond. Contact was made withEhrismans mother who advised that she could respond to the MSP Berlin Barrack to take custody of her daughter.Ehrismanwas released to her mother at 0413 hours. UponEhrismans release, I observed her wrists to be red due to the fact that she was pounding the cell door for two hours.    I request this case beclosed by arrest.    All events occurred in Worcester County, MD </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 03:05:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/26/2023 02:25:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phillips</LastName>
            <FirstName>Riley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7211</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7100</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495787</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1416</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1416</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 15:48:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 15:48:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495787</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 15:48:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 15:48:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495787</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3 4025</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3 4025</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 15:48:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 15:48:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495787</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>2 0050</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>2 0050</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 15:48:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 15:48:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495787</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 15:52:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 15:52:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495787</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 15:52:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 15:52:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495787</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 21:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 15:52:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 15:52:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 15:50:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>285835</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ehrisman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Chelsea</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/20/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/11/2020 16:18:21</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C420</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ehrisman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Chelsea</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/20/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>E625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C420</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/11/2020 16:18:21</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7328</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Division</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Willards</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21874</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1165</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.348242</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.3909</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>783</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2932</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/11/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 16:41:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:48</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 16:41:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:48</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 15:56:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:37</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369552</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Kyle Jones</LastName>
               <FirstName>Worcester County Deputy</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/19/2023 15:54:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W622</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Kyle Jones</LastName>
               <FirstName>Worcester County Deputy</FirstName>
               <SLastName>K425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W622</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/19/2023 15:54:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Market</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>W</StreetSuffixCode>
               <City>Snow Hill</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21863</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.393073</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.176588</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 15:56:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 15:59:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369553</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>U</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>U</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Maryland state police</LastName>
               <FirstName>Barrack "V"</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/19/2023 15:57:36</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M645</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B621</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Maryland state police</LastName>
               <FirstName>Barrack "V"</FirstName>
               <SLastName>M645</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B621</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/19/2023 15:57:36</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9758</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Ocean Gateway</StreetName>
               <City>Berlin</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21811</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.231607</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.345914</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>641</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3101</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 15:59:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/26/2023 01:55:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/26/2023 01:55:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 16:02:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 16:02:49</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Front windshield of MSP unmarked vehicle V-24</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>996</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>450</PropertyValue>
         <Value>450</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243958</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>MVE</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>Ford</Make>
         <Model>Explorer</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/19/2023 16:02:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 16:02:49</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Passenger air conditioning vent in MSP unmarked vehicle V-24</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>996</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>120</PropertyValue>
         <Value>120</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>243959</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>Ford</Make>
         <Model>Explorer</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/25/2023 17:49:28</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/25/2023 17:49:28</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/08/2023 09:54:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6722</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:49:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/16/2023 21:12:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*Axon Body Camera footage available for this incident*  On 02/18/23 at approximately 2216 hours, I, TFC. Brittingham #6722, responded to the area of westbound Ocean Gateway and Golf Course Road to assist TFC. Bradley #7100 with an arrestee. Upon my arrival on-scene, TFC. Bradley asked if I would be willing to follow him to the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack while he transported his arrestee. TFC. Bradley advised he was able to secure the female subject into his patrol vehicle; however she had already slipped the handcuffs once while they were placed behind her back. TFC. Bradley stated that he decided to handcuff her in the front and secure the subject in the front seat of his patrol vehicle. TFC. Bradley was concerned that the female subject may attempt to get out of her handcuffs again while in transport and felt that having an additional Trooper follow him to the barrack may help in the event she attempts to escape.  I then briefly approached the passenger side of TFC. Bradleys patrol vehicle to assess the subjects current mental state and to see how she was placed in the patrol vehicle. Ehrisman was visibly upset and extremely irate. Ehrisman was demanding her handcuffs to be taken off while screaming, crying and yelling profanities. I attempted to explain to Ehrisman the process that was to follow and that she would soon be out of the handcuffs, in hopes that she would be given some peace of mind or calm down. Given her emotional and mental state at that time, I do not believe she heard anything I said. While I was standing at the passenger window attempting to calm Ehrisman down, I could smell and extremely strong odor of alcohol coming from within the interior of the vehicle. I then retreated back to my patrol vehicle to begin following TFC. Bradley to the Berlin barrack.  While in transport, TFC. Bradley proceeded to move to the shoulder of westbound Ocean Gateway in the area of Herring Creek Road. I positioned my patrol vehicle behind TFC. Bradleys patrol vehicle and exited my vehicle to assist him. I immediately approached the passenger side of the vehicle once more. Ehrisman was still irate and furious about being in handcuffs. Ehrisman had begun kicking the interior of TFC. Bradleys vehicle and uncontrollably flailing around in the passenger seat. Ehrisman advised she could not breathe. She demanded that she needed water and that she needed to be out of her handcuffs. I attempted to talk to Ehrisman and direct her through some controlled breathing. Multiple times I advised Ehrisman to breathe in through her noses and to blow out through her mouth. I attempted to reassure Ehrisman that she was going to be ok and that she was ok. I advised Ehrisman that she would be released from the handcuffs at the Berlin barrack. She just continued to yell, scream and cuss the entire time myself and TFC. Bradley tried to speak to or reason with her. In the process of kicking the front dash of TFC. Bradleys patrol vehicle, she completely broke the front right air vent of the patrol vehicle. I advised the barrack of the damage and TFC. Bradley requested EMS (due to her stating she could not breathe) and a caged transport vehicle (to safely transport her). While waiting for EMS and a separate transport vehicle to arrive, TFC. Bradley and I proceeded to monitor Ehrisman and attempted to calm her down. I advised Ehrisman that she was going to cause herself to hyperventilate and cause her physical state to worsen if she did not get her breathing under control. I advised Ehrisman that we were trying to help her, while TFC. Bradley was also trying to reassure her that she would be ok. Ehrisman was unable to focus on anything other that wanting to get out of her handcuffs, getting out of the patrol vehicle, getting out of the seatbelt and having some water. She continued to yell and scream profanities while also proceeding to kick the front windshield of TFC. Bradleys patrol vehicle, causing the glass to shatter. For her safety and ours, TFC. Bradley moved the passenger seat back further away from the dash. We kept Ehrisman seated in the patrol vehicle for her safety and ours.  Moments later, EMS personnel arrived on-scene to do an assessment. Ehrisman continued to be uncooperative and unwilling to follow directions. She did not show any signs of visible injury from the damages she caused inside of TFC. Bradleys patrol vehicle.It should be noted that Ehrisman did have a pre-existing abrasion on her left knee, to which Ehrisman advised she caused while shaving her legs days prior. EMS personnel decided to help escort Ehrisman out of the vehicle to further evaluate her and attempt to calm her down. Ehrisman was still uncooperative, and screaming profanities at the EMS personnel trying to assist her. Ehrisman was irate, slurring her words, demanding to be taken out of handcuffs and aggressively moving about on the ground. Eventually, Ehrisman proceeded to stand herself up and began yelling and screaming in the faces of EMS personnel on-scene as well as in the faces of Troopers/Deputies.  At this time, Ehrisman was assisted to the stretcher to be prepared for sedation. I guided her head as she was placed on the stretcher to make sure she did not hit her head on the metal frame. I then positioned myself to hold her right arm down in order for EMS to buckle the strap which was placed across her lap and to prevent staff from being hit. I then held her arm still in order for EMS to administer a sedative in her right deltoid area. Once the medication was administered, I moved to the end of the stretcher to hold her lower leg because she proceeded to slide her legs out of the stretcher straps holding her legs in place. I feared she may kick another law enforcement officer or EMS staff if I did not hold her legs in place. I continued to reassure Ehrisman as she was being secured on the stretcher before being placed into the ambulance.  I then followed the ambulance to Atlantic General Hospital. Upon my arrival, Ehrisman was moved into a room of the ER and transferred onto a hospital bed from the stretcher without incident. The ER doctor entered the room, did an extremely brief visual scan of Ehrisman and advised he would be releasing Ehrisman from the Emergency Room immediately. While waiting for Ehrismans paperwork releasing her from the hospitals care, Ehrisman became agitated and irate all over again.  The barrack was advised of Ehrismans release, and we again requested a caged transport vehicle to respond to our location to transport Ehrisman to the barrack given the above facts. Myself and TFC. Phillips #7211 waited with Ehrisman in the hospital room while awaiting the arrival of the transport vehicle. While waiting, Ehrisman continued to yell and scream profanities. Her behavior was so irate and loud that multiple ER staff members entered the room to correct her behavior and ask her to stop. As I attempted to calm Ehrisman down and re-explain the process moving forward, she did not want to listen to my advice, and she proceeded to slap my Stetson off my head while I stood next to her bedside. Ehrisman moved herself to the end of the hospital bed and eventually onto the floor. I bent down and offered to help Ehrisman up, however she was not interested. I gave Ehrisman the option of walking herself outside to wait with TFC. Phillips and I out there, however she was also not interested in that either. The ER staff became very irritated with Ehrismans behavior and loud profanity, so much so that we were advised to leave the ER given that Ehrisman was released from their care. TFC. Phillips and I tried to reason with Ehrisman numerous times, in an attempt to have her exit the hospital on her own. Ehrisman refused to do so, until ER staff proceeded to come into the room and physically remove her from the floor and into a wheelchair.  ER staff then began to push the wheelchair toward the exit, but Ehrisman proceeded to quickly jump from the wheelchair, which appeared to be in an attempt to flee down the hallway given her body position and direction. Ehrisman was grabbed and placed back into the wheelchair to be escorted out of the ER. Ehrisman was so erratic with her movements I then grabbed the middle portion of the handcuffs to gain control of her hands. I did not want her to hit TFC. Phillips, myself of ER staff. I held onto the middle chain portion of the handcuffs to remain in control of her hands as ER staff began pushing the wheelchair once more. Ehrisman then had a firm grip on my wrist/arm with both of her hands as I held the handcuffs. Ehrisman then began to put her feet down to prevent the wheelchair from moving forward. ER staff, TFC. Phillips and myself proceeded to escort Ehrisman through the hallway at the entrance of the ER when she then aggressively exited the wheelchair demanding she be taken out of her handcuffs. Ehrisman then threw herself down on the floor and proceeded to sit against the wall while trying to prevent any of us from escorting her from the ER. I then extended my hand down to Ehrisman to help walk her outside of the ER, however she was unwilling to after numerous attempts. Yet again, ER staff proceeded to lift Ehrisman off the floor and into the wheelchair. I then grabbed Ehrismans left leg to help assist her lower body onto the chair. I then proceeded to push the wheelchair out into the parking lot.  Ehrisman was still trying to exit the wheelchair. She was continually kicking, failing and arching her back to lift herself from the chair. For safety, I stood near her feet and legs to prevent her from kicking. Ehrisman also attempted to position her feet under her bottom to have her feet on the seat of the wheelchair. I removed her feet from under her (placing them back in front of her) in fear she would flip the chair and fall backwards, causing injury to either herself of the Troopers on-scene. Eventually, the transport vehicle arrived on-scene and Ehrisman refused to enter the vehicle on her own. We then proceeded to place Ehrisman into the transport vehicle. Cpl. Lenz and TFC. Phillips each grabbed one arm and I grabbed her left leg to lift her up the steps and into the transport vehicle. From there she was transported to the Berlin barrack for processing. Once the transport vehicle arrived to the barrack, we again had to assist Ehrisman out of the vehicle given she would not exit on her own. She was essentially assisted out of the vehicle very similarly to how she was placed in it. I again assisted with lifting her legs. I grabbed both pant legs to slide her feet toward the step for her to stand up. Ehrisman would not stand, so I then grabbed her legs and placed her feet down onto the step. She was assisted to stand upright and escorted onto the sidewalk and into the barrack.  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6722</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 17:50:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6722</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/01/2023 11:29:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Walls</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bradley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3805</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brittingham</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6722</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/25/2023 22:31:41</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/25/2023 22:31:41</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/08/2023 09:54:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 22:31:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/16/2023 21:12:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> This incident was captured audibly and visually by my Axon Body Worn Camera((X60A66590)    On 2/19/2023 at approximately 2324 hours, I responded to Atlantic General Hospital to assist TFC Phillips and TFC Brittingham with an intoxicated and combative DUI suspect/ arrestee, Chelsea Ehrisman.   Upon my arrival, to the emergency room entrance(1:02 on my BWC), I observed hospital staff and TFC Phillips and TFC Brittingham lifting a yelling Ehrisman(handcuffed in the front) from the floor into a wheelchair. TFC Phillips grabbed a hold of her right leg, TFC Brittingham grabbed a hold of her left leg and all together they placed Ehrisman gently into the wheelchair as she continued to scream. She was thrashing both legs and her arms and torso about nearly falling from the wheelchair, as I walked up and grabbed onto her left upper arm(1:12 BWC) and braced her against the back of wheelchair. As the wheelchair was pushed out of the ER, TFC Phillips placed his right hand onto her right arm to keep her from sliding from chair, but Ehrisman continued to violently kick her legs. As AGH Security attempted to grab Ehrismans legs, she repeatedly screamed that she was raped..and she slid downwards nearly falling from the wheelchair. We stopped the chair, together lifted her and re-positioned her into the wheelchair seat and rolled the wheelchair outside to await the OCPD transport van. Ehrisman continued kicking her legs while on the pavement, so to avoid her injuring her feet by kicking or thrashing her legs on the parking lot, I stated, Lets roll her to the mulch., and we rolled the chair to the mulch break area.    As we waited for the OCPD transport van to arrive, Ehrisman continued to scream and cry and yell that we were, .. raping her, and that she was being raped, while she was stomping her feet on the ground and the wheelchair while thrashing her body and arms. Ehrisman continually thrashed her upper body and arms, attempting to free herself from us and the wheelchair. Ehrisman was using all of her strength attempting to get up from the wheelchair and I found it increasingly difficult to simply hold her by her arms. I reached beneath Ehrismans arm/shoulder and secured my grip onto the wheelchair frame, behind Ehrismans back. This braced my forearm against Ehrismans upper arm/shoulder, which allowed me to use leverage not my diminishing strength to safely secure her upper body into the wheelchair. I instructed TFC Phillips to do the same, as I realized that this was more effective and safer for us and Ehrisman. She nearly escaped our grasp several times when we were only holding her arms with our hands.   At approximately, 2340 hours, the OCPD transport van arrived and we rolled Ehrisman in the wheelchair to the vans rear door(9:40 BWC). For several minutes, I continuously and repeatedly attempted unsuccessfully to convince, persuade and encourage Ehrisman to walk into the rear door of the OCPD transport van on her own. We attempted to assist Ehrisman to walk into the van by lifting her to a standing position by her arms, but she stiffened her legs and pushed herself rearward and sat again into the wheelchair. I lifted Ehrisman by her left arm(13;33 BWC), TFC Phillips lifted her by her right arm and we both simultaneously lifted Ehrisman gently upright then into the rear of the transport van and placed her into a seated position, onto the floor of the van. TFC Phillips then held her under arms and gently slid her on her buttocks/ rearward, toward the front of van, as TFC Brittingham gently lifted her left leg as she slid to ensure both of her legs were inside the van as well. Ehrisman did not sit on the bench as we requested and the OCPD officer-transport driver stated that she could remain seated on the floor. Ehrisman continued to yell as the OCPD officer secured the van door and transported Ehrisman to the Berlin Barrack.   At approximately 2344 hours, I responded to Berlin Barrack with the OCPD transport van. As I walked to the van, I could hear Ehrisman yelling and pounding from inside the closed van from several feet away. The van door was opened(21:19 BWC) and I observed Ehrisman, lying on the floor crying, with her back toward the door, her head resting on the bench. I asked Ehrisman to come out of the van several times, but she did not move and continued crying. I entered the van, and gently rotated her legs toward the door. I then lifted/ supported her upper body by her right arm, as TFC Brittingham lifted/ supported her legs and together we slid her on the floor of the van, on her buttocks, toward the door. Ehrismans feet were then placed gently onto the ground as I supported her upright in a seated position on the floor of van.   I supported Ehrisman at her right shoulder,TFC Phillips supported her at her left shoulder and together we assisted her to her feet and escorted Ehrisman into the barrack and into cell #2, where she was then gently seated onto the bench. TFC Phillips and I maintained control of her arms as the handcuffs were removed.TFC Phillips and I maintained control of Ehrismans arms, as I observed a secondary search performed by TFC Brittingham.   After the completion of the search, all troopers exited the cell and I secured the interior door then the exterior door, as Ehrisman screamed and pounded on something inside the cell.    </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/25/2023 22:33:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4839</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/26/2023 03:38:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lenz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4839</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/27/2023 12:06:47</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/27/2023 12:06:47</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/08/2023 09:54:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7211</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/27/2023 12:06:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/16/2023 21:12:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was captured audibly and visually by my Axon body camera (X60A61668) On February 18th, 2023 I was dispatched to the area Westbound Route 50 at Golf Course Road to assist TFC Bradley #7100 with an intoxicated driver. Upon arriving on scene, TFC Bradley was escorting Chelsea Lynn Ehrisman to his vehicle after placing her under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. After being placed in the passenger seat of V-24, Ehrisman began to scream and shift back and forth. Soon after this, she slipped out of her cuffs and pulled her hands to the front. I grabbed her wrist in an attempt to bring her out of the vehicle so she could be cuffed again. She refused and crossed her arms. Both TFC Bradley and myself attempted to deescalate the situation and have her step out of the vehicle on her own, by giving verbal commands She eventually exited the vehicle on her own and Ehrisman refused to turn around to be cuffed. After trying to convince her for several minutes by giving her verbal commands. TFC Bradley made the decision to cuff her in the front. I grabbed Ehrismans right arm to assist in cuffing her. After being cuffed she raised her hands above her head and dropped to the ground. I attempted to help her stand with by lifting her right arm. She pulled away again and began to scream hysterically to have the cuffs taken off. After several more minutes, she stepped inside V-24 on her own accord. She began to twist her wrists in an attempt to get the cuffs off. TFC Bradley checked the cuffs again before departing for the Berlin Barrack. I parked Ehrismans vehicle in a nearby parking lot and retrieved her phone/keys. At 2247 hours, I again responded to the area of W/B Route 50 at Maryland 707 to assist TFC Bradley with Ehrisman. On arrival Ehrisman began kicking the V-24 side dash vent and windshield damaging both. She began hyperventilating and claiming she couldnt breathe. EMS was on route prior to my arrival. When EMS arrived, Ehrisman became even more aggressive with the EMTs. The EMTs attempted to guide Ehrisman out of the vehicle but she threw herself on to the grassy shoulder. The EMTs lifted Ehrisman to sit her upright. She continued to scream and be aggressive with EMS. She rolled around on the ground screaming for us to take the cuffs off. Ehrisman eventually stood and again threw herself to the ground. EMS and law enforcement personnel lifted Ehrisman in an attempt to guide her to the stretcher to be transported to Atlantic General Hospital. I lifted her left leg to assist in carrying her to the stretcher. Once being placed on the stretcher, Ehrisman began to kick and resist being strapped in. I held her leg down against the stretcher to stop her from kicking. She eventually was placed into the ambulance where she continued to kick and be aggressive. During this, it was brought to my attention that DFC Jones #6028 was kicked in the knee. He was transported to Atlantic General Hospital as well. I responded to Atlantic General Hospital to assist TFC Brittingham #6722 after the hospital released her after only a few minutes. On arrival at 2315 hours, Ehrisman was still crying and throwing herself back and forth onto the hospital bed. She stood up and began screaming at me. Then again dropped to the floor. While this was occurring, hospital personnel continued to come to the bed in an attempt to stop her from screaming due to other patients being in the emergency room. They also insisted that we leave the hospital. Ocean City Police were called to assist with their transport van. We continued to attempt to reason with Ehrisman by using verbal commands.  Hospital nurses and other personnel brought a wheelchair and lifted Ehrisman into the chair. She resisted them. While being wheeled out, Ehrisman threw herself out of the chair backing into me. I caught her before she fell to the ground. I then lifted Ehrisman into the wheelchair. She continued to resist, knocking off my body camera. While being rolled out to the parking lot in the wheelchair, she stood up again and began to resist by swinging her arms back and forth and throwing herself to the ground. I grabbed her arm in an attempt to guide her back to the chair. She again threw herself to the ground. Hospital personnel again lifted her into the chair. I assisted by lifting her right leg. Once in the chair she began kicking and attempted to get out of the chair. I held onto Ehrismans right arm to try to keep her from falling out of the chair onto the concrete. She had to be lifted to keep her upright in the chair. The wheel chair was rolled to the mulch to prevent her from falling on the concrete. I continued to hold her right arm. After her resisting more, CPL Lenz #4839, ordered me to place my right arm under Ehrismans arms and to hold the wheel chair. This kept Ehrisman upright and provided leverage preventing her from throwing herself forward. The cuffs were again loosened by TFC S. Schubert #6944. While waiting for the OCPD transport van, Ehrisman continued to kick, twist, and scream. When the OCPD transport van arrived, Ehrisman refused to enter the vehicle. I held her arm to guide her into the vehicle. After several minutes of attempting to convince Ehrisman to enter on her own, we lifted her to guide her into the vehicle. Once inside the van, I pulled under both of Ehrismans arms to attempt to pull her further into the transport van. She resisted this again and refused to be buckled. Ehrisman was secured in the vehicle and transported to Berlin Barrack. On arrival at the BerlinBarrack,at 2345 hours, I secured my weapon and assisted with transporting Ehrisman to the cell. Ehrisman refused to exit the OCPD transport van going limp. After CPL Lenz guided Ehrisman to the door of the transport van, I assisted. I held onto her arm as she walked into the barrack. I continued to hold her arm while TFC Brittingham conducted a secondary search. After the completion of the search, all troopers exited the cell. The cell was secured, as Ehrisman screamed and pounded on the cell door. No involved Troopers were injured during this incident.Worcester County Deputy Jones 6028 was treated at Atlantic General Hospital after being kicked by Ehrisman.Ehrisman had no apparent injuries. She was transported and released from Atlantic General Hospital. All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7211</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/27/2023 12:07:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7211</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/27/2023 12:07:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Walls</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bradley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3805</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phillips</LastName>
            <FirstName>Riley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7211</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>4</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/08/2023 08:55:52</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/08/2023 08:55:52</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/08/2023 09:54:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 08:55:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/16/2023 21:12:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #4 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> On 2/18/2023 at approximately 2152 hours, TFC Bradley stopped and arrested Chelsea Ehrisman for DUI, Assault, MDOP and related charges.   I responded to Atlantic General Hospital to assist with a physically-combative Ehrisman, which resulted in use of force and subsequently, a Blue Team Use of Force Report.   In my original supplement narrative, I mistakenly reported the incident occurring on 2/19/2023 instead of the correct date, which is 2/18/2023.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4839</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 08:58:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4839</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 09:33:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lenz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4839</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>5</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/16/2023 18:35:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/16/2023 18:35:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/16/2023 21:12:45</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 18:35:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/16/2023 21:12:45</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #5 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Incident was recorded on AXON Body Worn Camera (BWC, X60A5638S)  On February 18, 2023 at approximately 2321 hours. I Tfc. S. Shubert #6944 was on duty for late shift. At that time, I was dispatched to Atlantic General Hospital in reference to assist Tfc. Phillips and Tfc. Brittingham with a disorderly/uncooperative arrestee.  Upon my arrival, I observed the female who was identified as Chelase Ehrisman to be extremely uncooperative. I observed the female to be wheeled out from the entrance of the rear hospital door in a wheelchair due to her high intoxication levels and not being able to walk. Ehrisman attempted to remove herself from the wheelchair and was advised to remain calm until Ocean City Police Department arrived on scene at approximately 2344 hours with a cage patrol vehicle. Ehrisman refused and began to stand up on the chair. Cpl. Lenz and Tfc. Phillips held Ehrisman down on the wheelchair, so she could not stand up and hurt herself. Once Ocean City Police Department Ehrisman refused to get into the cage patrol vehicle.  Cpl. Lenz and Tfc. Phillips asked Ehrisman politely to enter the patrol cage vehicle. Ehrisman refused and stiffened her legs so she could not physically walk into the cage patrol vehicle. Cpl. Lenz and Tfc. Phillips grabbed Ehrismans arms and gently lifted her. Tfc. Brittingham gently lifted Ehrismans left leg and placed her inside the Ocean City Police Department cage patrol vehicle. Ocean City Police Department transported Ehrisman back to the Maryland State Police Berlin barrack for processing.  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/16/2023 18:36:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/16/2023 20:02:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>