<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-019970</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/04/2023 02:41:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/04/2023 02:41:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/04/2023 02:19:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/04/2023 02:19:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/04/2023 02:41:17</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/12/2023 07:58:01</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>COASTAL HWY/ 60TH ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>666700</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/04/2023 02:41:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/04/2023 02:41:17</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>666700</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Coastal</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.066983</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.383465</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 COASTAL HWY / 1-20 60TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>6001-6021 COASTAL HWY / 100-120 60TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/04/2023 02:41:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/04/2023 02:41:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/12/2023 07:36:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/04/2023 02:41:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:05</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Jose Antonio Borrero 3rd Delaware SOUNDEX: 9309278  Breath Test Result: .Refused DUI Citation # 6100T5Y DUI Tape #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-019970 (Axon View XL Software)  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. * Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.). * Completed and graduated from the DUI Institute. * Completed and graduated from the SFST Instructor school  NARRATIVE -PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION- On June 04, 2023 at approximately 0218 hours, I (TFC. S. Shubert #6944), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating unmarked MSP vehicle V-08 in the area of northbound Coastal Highway at 56th Street, Ocean City, Worcester County, Maryland.   At that time, I observed blue Ford mustang bearing Maryland registration (WEPA) traveling northbound Coastal Highway in lane one. I observed the blue Ford mustang appeared to be traveling above the posted 35 MPH speed limit. The in-car Kustom Golden Eagle II front radar antenna was activated (same direction mode) and had been checked before (and later after) my shift and appeared to be functioning properly. I am certified through the Maryland State Police to operate Radar/Lidar. I made the following observations:   A speed of 51 MPH in a posted 35 MPH zone was displayed on my in-car radar unit (Same direction mode) as the vehicle entered the influence of the radar beam.  I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop.  -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT- I exited my patrol vehicle and made contact with the driver via the driver side door. I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle. I informed the driver the reason for the traffic stop and requested his drivers license and registration card. I also observed the driver to display a dazed/expression look on his face. The driver was identified through his Delaware drivers license as Jose Antonio Borrero 3rd. I asked Borrero where he was coming from and Borrero stated I am coming from Seacrets. I asked Borrero how many alcoholic beverages he consumed prior to operating his motor vehicle and Borrero stated Two drinks. I observed Borreros movements to be lethargic. As Borrero spoke, I observed his eyes to be glassy and bloodshot. I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Borrero.   I then returned to the blue Ford mustang and asked Borrero to step out of his vehicle and walk to the back of it. Borrero did as I requested. I asked Borrero where he was coming from and Borrero stated Seacrets. I asked how many alcoholic beverage Borrero consumed prior to operating his motor vehicle and Borrero stated Two crown and cokes. I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I asked Borrero if he wanted to submit to standardized field sobriety tests to ensure he was not impaired, Borrero agreed to submit to standardized field sobriety tests.   -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING- STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs) The evaluation was performed on the roadway area. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of overhead lights, headlights and flashlight. Borrero appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any limps. Borrero advised that he had a broken meniscus tear. However, did not go into detail in reference to which leg.   Borrero was wearing blue jeans and a blue jacket.   **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**  1. Borrero displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  2. Borrero displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes. 3. Borrero displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes. ^^^I observed vertical gaze nystagmus during the test^^^  **WALK AND TURN: 5 of 8 clues** -Could not maintain balance during instructional phase. First nine steps: -Stepped off line by approximately three inches on step 2,4,7 Turn: Completed unsatisfactory, lifted lead foot  Second nine steps: -Missed heel-to-toe by approximately three inches on step 4,9 -Stepped off line by approximately three inches on step 2 -Took 10 steps when instructed to take 9 steps  **ONE LEG STAND: 2 of 4 clues** -Raised arms from sides by approximately twelve to fourteen inches one time during the test.  -Firmly placed left foot down two times during the test.   I then asked Borrero if he could recite the English alphabet starting at the letter H ending at the letter T. Borrero stated the following: H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P-Q-R-S-T-U-V  After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Borrero the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Borrero gave two insufficient breath samples to submit to the preliminary breath test.  -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING- ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Borrero was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.  * I observed clues during his performance in SFST *lethargic movements   I placed Borrero under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0236 hours on June 04, 2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Borreros mouth for any foreign objects and none were found.    ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) Borrero was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Borrero was given his Advice of Rights via the audio version of the DR-15 Form. I placed a copy of the DR-15 in front of Borrero. Once the DR-15 was completed being played Borrero stated that he understood his Advice of Rights. At approximately 0252 agreed to submit to the Intoximeter test. I then transported Borrero to the Ocean City Police Department for processing.   Intoximeter: Sgt. Morgan and myself checked Borreros mouth for any foreign objects. Borrero did not have any foreign objects or liquid located in his mouth. Borrero gave six invalid breath samples.   PROCESSING During all aspects of processing (mugshot, completion and explanation of the DR-15A Form, issuance and explanation of citations), the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Borrero continued to be strong.  CHARGES Borrero was charged with the following citations: 1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (6100T5Y) 2. Driving While Impaired By Alcohol (6110T5Y) 3. Negligent driving(6120T5Y) 4. Exceeding the maximum posted speed limit (60Z0T5Y)  Case closed by arrest. All events occurred in Worcester County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 20:50:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 20:50:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509404</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/04/2023 02:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 22:03:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 22:03:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 22:03:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>379399</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Borrero 3rd</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jose</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Antonio</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/10/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/09/2023 21:56:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B666</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Borrero 3rd</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jose</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Antonio</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/10/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B666</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/09/2023 21:56:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 22:05:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 22:05:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 22:03:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 22:03:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153952</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 21:54:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/09/2023 21:54:01</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2016</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MUS</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLU</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>DE</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>WEPA</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>