<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009908</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/19/2023 02:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/19/2023 02:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/19/2023 02:46:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/19/2023 02:46:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 02:56:20</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2864</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 18:46:01</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN HWY/ PEGGY NECK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>585136</AddressId>
      <City>MDC217</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 02:56:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 04:54:35</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>585136</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Princess Anne</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.66655</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.260908</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB 13 / JUST NORTH OF PEGGY NECK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13848-14120 OCEAN HWY / 31259-31279 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13647-13844 OCEAN HWY / 31298-31853 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13647-13844 OCEAN HWY / 31280-31297 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13656-13847 OCEAN HWY / 31259-31279 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13845-14111 OCEAN HWY / 31280-31297 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/19/2023 02:56:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/19/2023 02:56:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/27/2023 11:47:08</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 02:56:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:15</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police  Princess Anne Barrack X  Tpr. Bynum IBM 7345  Field Operation Bureau  (03/19/2023)   Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle: X-5 is an unmarked 2021 blue Ford Explorer equipped with MVR system.  Type of Report: DUI/DWI  Case Number: 23-MSP-009908  DUI Case Number: 23-95-020  Victim: Society  Driver/Suspect: John Anthony Egerton  Date of Birth: 11/23/1993  License Number: DE (1696377)  PH Number(s): N/A  Troopers Training/Experience: * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).  * Trained and certified to operate Radar and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  * NHTSA certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E).    Narrative: This report has been prepared based upon the observations of this trooper and/or those of other troopers relative to the offense(s). The facts contained herein are intended solely to give the prosecuting authority a basic understanding of the facts pertaining to this case. The facts contained herein are not intended to be an exhaustive recitation of the facts pertaining to pretrial or trial issues. Instead, this trooper anticipates that during the pretrial proceedings in this case, the prosecutor will take the opportunity to interview this trooper in order to ascertain any and all relevant facts which might be the subject of this troopers testimony during court proceedings.   Phase #1 - Vehicle In Motion:  On the morning of 03/19/2023 at approximately 0246 hours, I Trooper Bynum was monitoring traffic in the area of southbound US Route 13 South of Eden Allen Road, in Somerset County, Maryland. At that time a vehicle passed my location with an inoperative headlight. I positioned my patrol vehicle behind the violator vehicle and performed a traffic stop on that vehicle at that time. That vehicle was identified as a 2019 gray Kia Forte bearing Delaware registration of 382390.   Upon activating my emergency lights the vehicle pulled to the right shoulder from the number two lane and continued pulling to the right until the two right tires left the roadway into the grass. The vehicle was now halfway on and halfway off the roadway. The vehicle then came to a stop in that position.  Phase #2 - Personal Contact:    As I approached the vehicles drivers side the operator later identified as John Anthony Egerton opened the drivers door. Immediately upon Egerton opening the drivers door I detected the overwhelming odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. The odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from the open drivers side door was so strong it was burning the inside of my nostrils as I approached and spoke with Egerton. When Egerton opened the drivers door he appeared to be moving slowly and sluggish. Egerton had a dazed and confused look on his face. Egerton was unable to provide a drivers license or registration card for the vehicle. When asked what his first name was he responded John Egerton. While speaking with Egerton I also noticed he was slurring his words and seemed to be staring blankly. Additionally while speaking with Egerton I noticed a bottle in the drivers floorboard area which was later identified as an open bottle of Jack Daniels with approximately half, to two-thirds of the bottle gone. I returned to my patrol vehicle and waited for a second unit before I attempted to put the driver through field sobriety testing.  I re approached the drivers side of the vehicle and asked Egerton to step out of the vehicle. Egerton then asked for what? I informed him I smelled alcohol coming out of the car and asked him if he had been drinking. Egerton stated no. I asked Egerton if he would mind doing some tests for me, referring to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Egerton again responded no. I said whats that? and Egerton again responded no. To clarify I asked Egerton you dont want to do them? and he responded no and what sounded like, I dont want to do them. I told Egerton to come talk to me for a second and he began to exit the drivers seat of the vehicle. Egerton used his right hand on the steering wheel and his left elbow on the outside of the car to assist him in standing up. Once he stood up Egerton placed his right hand on the inside of the drivers door appearing to do so for balance.  Once outside of the vehicle I spoke with Egerton at the rear of the vehicle. I had Egerton look at me and noticed his eyes were extremely glassy and bloodshot. I continued to try and have Egerton complete field sobriety tests and he again declined. I asked Egerton where he was coming from and he said uh friends house. I asked where that was and he said down the way. I asked if it was in Maryland or Delaware, Egerton shrugged and again stated down the way. I told Egerton it reeks in the car of alcohol and he responded okay. I then mentioned his bloodshot and glassy eyes, and the fact that he was slurring his words and Egerton responded sure. I told Egerton I was trying to offer him the field sobriety tests and he cut me off and stated I dont want it.   At this point I made the decision, due to all the facts listed above, to place Egerton under arrest for DUI/DWI. Egerton was taken into custody without incident.   Phase #3 - Pre-Arrest Screening: Standardized Field Sobriety Tests Were Refused  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Standardized Field Sobriety Tests Were Refused  Walk and Turn Standardized Field Sobriety Tests Were Refused  One Leg Stand Standardized Field Sobriety Tests Were Refused  Preliminary Breath Test Not Offered  Arrest and Transport  I placed a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights form in Egertons lap in my patrol vehicle. I asked Egerton if he could see the paper in his lap okay, referring to the DR-15 and he responded yeah. Egerton was played the DR-15 Advice of Rights audio from the MVA Maryland.gov website, in its entirety. Egerton ultimately refused to submit to the breath test at approximately 0309 hours on 03/19/2023. While riding in the patrol vehicle with Egerton the inside of the patrol vehicle began to smell of an alcoholic beverage. Egerton asked to use the bathroom once we arrived at the barrack. Once asked to sign the DR-15 Egerton asked and what if I dont sign that? I asked whats that and Egerton again responded so what happens if I dont sign that I ended up writing, refused to sign, in place of Egertons signature. Egerton also refused to sign the DR-15A, under the drivers certified statement as well as under the temporary license. While speaking with Egerton I could smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his person/breath. This odor was also able to be smelled in the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack.   Breath Test Refused. The instrument was available and a certified breath test operator was available to perform the test.   Charging  Driving Vehicle While Under the Influence Of Alcohol (Driving Veh. While Impaired By Alcohol   DIRECTING AND PERMITTING HWY. VEH. OPERATION CONTRARY TO LAW   FAILURE TO PROPERLY EQUIP AND LOCATE HEADLAMPS ON MOTOR VEH. FAIL TO DISPLAY LICENSE ON DEMAND FAILURE TO DISPLAY REGISTRATION CARD   NEGLIGENT DRIVING RECKLESS DRIVING  Egerton was released to a sober driver after being issued the appropriate documentation.  I request this case be closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Somerset County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 05:02:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 15:50:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brown</LastName>
            <FirstName>Clinton</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7569</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3325</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bynum</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7345</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499308</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499308</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499308</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17272</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499308</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17016</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17016</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499308</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499308</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499308</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 05:02:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:34</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371944</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Egerton</LastName>
               <FirstName>John</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anthony</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/23/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 04:25:53</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E263</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Egerton</LastName>
               <FirstName>John</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anthony</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/23/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>E263</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 04:25:53</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>34256</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>High Tide</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>N</StreetSuffixCode>
               <City>Millsboro</City>
               <StateCode>DE</StateCode>
               <Zip5>19966</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 06:49:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 06:49:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 06:49:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 04:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>