<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009738</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/17/2023 23:23:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/17/2023 23:23:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/17/2023 22:52:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/17/2023 22:52:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI Cresencio Felipe Duran</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 23:23:32</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/12/2023 03:47:03</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>570410</AddressId>
      <City>MDC132</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP7419</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:12:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 14:13:46</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>570410</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Park</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.96617</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.98473</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>RT 193 @ WEST PARK DR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/17/2023 23:23:31</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/17/2023 23:23:31</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/12/2023 03:36:29</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 23:23:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Incident was recorded. Body worn camera was equipped.  Defendant: Cresencio Felipe Duran Date of Birth: 09/22/1983 Date of Arrest: 03/17/2023 Time of Arrest: 2323 hours DUI #23-062  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic and Safety Administration  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On March 17th, 2023, I, Trooper Caleb Bowling, assigned to the College Park Barrack, was operating marked patrol vehicle Q-29 in lane 1 of University Boulevard westbound at Stadium drive at approximately 2245 hours. At this time, I observed a blue GMC Yukon traveling in lane 1 of westbound University Boulevard in front of my patrol vehicle. I observed the GMC Yukon to be following a passenger vehicle approximately 4 feet from the vehicles rear bumper. I then observed the GMC cross the dotted white line from lane 1 into lane 2 by approximately a tires width, then jerk left back into lane 1. The vehicle then turned into lane 2 and crossed the solid white line into the shoulder by approximately a tires width. The GMC then jerked left and crossed the dotted white line from lane 2 into lane 1, then jerked right back into lane 2. The vehicle again crossed the dotted white line from lane 2 into lane 1 by approximately a tires width and jerked right back into lane 2. All of the above occurred between Stadium drive and Adelphi Road. After crossing Adelphi Road, the vehicle again crossed the dotted white line from lane 2 into lane 1 by approximately a tires width. I then activated my lights and sirens and pulled the vehicle over. The vehicle pulled onto West Park Drive and came to a complete stop. After the vehicle came to a complete stop, I made contact with the driver.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)    I made contact with the operator of the vehicle via the drivers side window. Upon my approach, I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from inside the vehicle. I introduced myself, advised that the stop was being audibly and visually recorded, and informed the driver for the reason of the stop. I requested the drivers license and registration card. The driver was identified by his Maryland license as Cresencio Felipe Duran. I asked Duran where he was coming from and where he was heading to. He advised me that he was coming from home and heading to work. As I was speaking to Duran, I observed his eyes to be glassy and bloodshot and his head and body movements to be slow and lethargic. I returned to my vehicle and conducted routine checks on Duran.    I approached the vehicle again and asked Duran to exit his vehicle and walk to the front, so I could talk to him outside his vehicle. Duran asked me if I wanted him to move his vehicle forward, to which I said no and that I wanted him to exit his vehicle. Duran complied and exited his vehicle. Once in front of his GMC, I asked Duran again where he was heading to, and he said he didnt speak much English. I asked again and he said he was going to work. I asked Duran if he had drank any alcohol, and he said yes. I asked how many drinks he had, and he said 3 beers. I asked Duran what size beers he had drank, and he said 12 ounces and that they were Bud-Lights. I asked Duran how long ago he had drank the beers and his reply was, The Campus. While talking to Duran outside his vehicle, I smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I informed Duran I wanted him to perform field sobriety tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)    The evaluation was performed in front of Durans GMC on West Park Drive.The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was cloudy and approximately 50 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlamps, patrol vehicle headlamps, Durans GMCs headlamps, spotlight, and my flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during the tests. Doe appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6 OUT OF 6 CLUES OBSERVED) Prior to beginning the test, I instructed Duran to stand with his feet together and his arms down at his sides. He was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. He was then given the instructions for the test and was asked if he understood to which he said Mmhmm. His pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. During the test, Duran stopped looking at the stimulus and said Sir, its only 3 beers. I advised Duran to keep looking at the tip of the stimulus and continued the test.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit: Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation: Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees: Present in both eyes Vertical Gaze Nystagmus: Present in both eyes  WALK AND TURN (6 OUT OF 8 CLUES OBSERVED)  Prior to Duran performing the test, I demonstrated and instructed him to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot touching heel to toe and to place his arms down at his sides. Duran was unable to get into and stay in the starting position. I then demonstrated and instructed how the test should be conducted. As soon as I finished demonstrating and instructing the test, Duran stated Ok.  INSTRUCTIONAL STAGE: 1.) Lost balance, was unable to stay in the instructional position. 2.) Began test before instructed  WALKING STAGE (First 9): 1.) Stepped off-line by a foots width on step 1 2.) Stepped off-line by a foots width on step 9 3.) Took 23 steps instead of the instructed 9 steps *I had to advise Duran to turn around and complete the second series of 9 steps*  WALKING STAGE (Second 9): 1.) Missed heel to toe on step 2 2.)Stepped off-line by more than a foots width on step 10 3.) Missed heel to toe on steps 10 to 11 4.) Took 13 steps instead of the instructed 9 steps *I had to tell Duran to sop the test because he lost his balance and almost fell*  TURN: 1.) Improper turn: I had to advise Duran to turn around, at which point he turned to his right and stopped.  ONE LEG STAND (TEST WAS REFUSED)  Prior to Duran performing the test, I demonstrated and instructed how the test should be conducted. Duran was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. After the instructions were given, Duran started to complain of knee pain. Tpr. Gonzales #7442 then arrived at the scene and spoke with Duran. Duran advised he did not want to take the test.  *After speaking with Tpr. Gonzales, Duran advised him that he had drank three 16 ounce Bud-Lights. Duran also advised Tpr. Gonzales that he did not want to take the Preliminary Breath Test.*  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Duran was driving a motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol:  *Following a vehicle too closely *Drifting out of his lane multiple times *Jerking his vehicle back into his lane *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his vehicle *Bloodshot and Glassy eyes *Slow and lethargic head and body movements *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person *Admitted to consuming 3 beers *My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests  I arrested Duran for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 2323 hours. I searched Durans person and then placed him in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported him to the Maryland State Police - College Park barrack. Once at the barrack, I gave Duran a copy of the English and Spanish DR-15 Advice of Rights and played the Spanish audio DR-15 Advice of Rights in its entirety. At the conclusion of the form, Tpr. Gonzales informed me that Duran did not want to take the intoximeter test. Duran was given all pertinent paperwork and citations and was released to his family. Duran was polite and cooperative throughout the process.  All of the above events occurred in Prince Georges County. Case closed by arrest.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7419</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:30:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7419</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 19:18:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gonzales</LastName>
            <FirstName>Javier</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7442</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McGee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McNamee</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7450</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McGee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bowling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Caleb</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7419</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499138</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/17/2023 22:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7419</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:20:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7419</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 14:20:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499138</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/17/2023 22:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7419</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:21:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7419</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 14:21:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7419</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:25:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:24</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371856</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>DURAN</LastName>
               <FirstName>CRESENCIO</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>FELIPE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/22/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 23:57:44</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D650</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C625</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>DURAN</LastName>
               <FirstName>CRESENCIO</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>FELIPE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/22/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D650</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C625</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 23:57:44</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6140</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Springhill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>TER</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>BLDG</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>302</SubNumber>
               <City>Greenbelt</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20770</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.90182</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.005373</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>821</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8447</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7419</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:25:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7419</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:25:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7419</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:25:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7419</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:25:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7419</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 16:28:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7419</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 16:28:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150981</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7419</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:28:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7419</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 14:28:39</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1GKFK66817J339346</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2007</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>YUKONXL1500</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>DBL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>DBL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>TX</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>169376C</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/17/2023 23:58:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/17/2023 23:58:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/12/2023 03:36:29</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 23:58:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>INCIDENT WAS RECORDED. Q-8 IS MVR EQUIPPED, BODY-WORN CAMERA OPERATIONAL.  On March 17, 2023 at approximately 2257 hours, I, Trooper Gonzales #7442 of the Maryland State Police was en route to assist Trooper Bowling #7419 with a traffic stop. Trooper Bowling requested an additional unit for standardized field sobriety testing and due to a language barrier he had with the operator, he requested for a Spanish-speaking officer. I arrived on scene and made contact with the male operator of a dark blue GMC Yukon. The male operator was the sole occupant of the GMC. I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath/person. The male operator was subsequently identified as Cresencio Felipe Duran (H/M DOB: 09/22/1983) through his Maryland drivers license. I introduced myself to Duran and asked him if he preferred English or Spanish to which he replied he preferred Spanish. I told Duran the reason for the stop and asked him preliminary questions. I asked Duran if he had physical conditions or injuries to which replied he has knee pain. He remarked he started playing in a soccer tournament a month prior. I also asked Duran if he had any alcoholic beverages to drink tonight. He replied he had three (3) beers an hour prior. I asked of what brand and what size to which he replied Bud Light and that they were the 16 ounce size. Trooper Bowling advised me that Duran was unable to proceed with the one leg stand component of standardized field sobriety testing due to him complaining of knee pain. I asked Duran if he would like to continue field sobriety testing to which he declined. I also asked if he would consent to a Preliminary Breath Test to which he also declined. Trooper Bowling placed Duran under arrest at 2323 hours as he was transported to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack for processing.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 00:00:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7442</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 16:12:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Parsons</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5657</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gonzales</LastName>
            <FirstName>Javier</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7442</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>