<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009748</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/18/2023 00:07:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/18/2023 00:07:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/17/2023 23:42:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/17/2023 23:42:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 00:07:53</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/16/2023 13:08:14</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>VIETNAM VETERANS MEMORIAL HWY/ SINGER RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>581846</AddressId>
      <City>MDC308</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 00:07:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 13:36:27</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>581846</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Vietnam Veterans Memorial</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Abingdon</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>-0 VIETNAM VETERANS MEMORIAL HWY / 0-0 SINGER RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 VIETNAM VETERANS MEMORIAL HWY / 113-120 SINGER RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 VIETNAM VETERANS MEMORIAL HWY / 0-0 SINGER RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 VIETNAM VETERANS MEMORIAL HWY / 200-499 SINGER RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/18/2023 00:07:49</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/18/2023 00:07:49</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/15/2023 01:27:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 00:07:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The incident was audibly and visually recorded from my BWC. MSP unmarked unit D-24 is equipped with MVR equipment. DEFENDANT: JAMES HOWARD HENSON Date of Birth: 01/30/1972 (51 years old) Date of Arrest: 03/18/2023 Time of Arrest: 0018 hours DUI #: 23-077 (Bel Air Barrack, Harford County) Subsequent Offender: YES Minor in the vehicle: No MD-DL. # MD-10272645424 CDL: No Certificate and Training: *I am a certified police officer in the state of Maryland with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with participants at the Maryland State Police Academy and prior DUI/DWI arrests and convictions. *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *RADAR / LIDAR Certified 2019. *Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator Certified. *Advance Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement Certified (ARIDE): Attended ARIDE with the Maryland State Police in January 2021 *UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND DUI INSTITUTE: I attended the University of Maryland DUI Institute, and I completed the course with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with live participants (From June 5 to June 10, 2022) *Certified as SFST witness expert by Honorable Judge Martin H. Schreiber II in Baltimore City Circuit Court on September 27, 2022. *Certified SFST witness expert by Honorable Judge David E. Carey in Harford County District Court on October 11, 2022. *I have apprehended more than 170 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On March 17, 2022, at approximately 2342 hours, I, Trooper First Class Reckeweg # 7214 of the Maryland State Police currently assigned to the Bel Air Barrack (unmarked MSP patrol vehicle D-24), was traveling on southbound Route 24 prior to Plumtree Road. At this time, I observed ahead of my patrol vehicle a blue Infiniti QX80 in lane two (2). The Infiniti appeared to be traveling above the posted speed limit of 55mph. I accelerated my patrol vehicle to 70mph, attempting to pace the Infiniti, but the Infiniti was pulling away from my patrol vehicle at some speed greater than 70mph. I then activated my in-car moving radar system (Golden Eagle II) and selected the front radar dish for speed acquisition. My radar system registered a continuous radar tone and speed reading of 80mph, while there was only one vehicle (the Infiniti) in front of my patrol vehicle within the operating range of my radar system. The radar tone and radar speed matched my visual speed estimate of the Infiniti. I also observed the Infiniti swerve to the right four (4) times and go over to the right shoulder, crossing the solid line dividing lane two (2) from the right shoulder by its tires width. The Infiniti regained control and returned to lane two (2). I pulled behind the Infiniti, and a traffic stop was initiated as I activated my emergency equipment. The Infiniti stopped on the right shoulder of southbound Route 24 prior to Singer Road, Bel Air, Harford County. I then observed the Infiniti bearing Maryland registration 8EC0716. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the Infiniti via the passengers side window, made contact with the driver, and explained to the driver the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver for his drivers license and registration. The driver handed me a Maryland drivers license and insurance card. The driver was identified as HENSON, JAMES HOWARD (B/M, DOB 01/03/1972, Maryland Soundex MD-10272645424), registered owner. I asked HENSON where he was coming from and where he was going. HENSON advised that he was coming from Baltimore City and going to his house. While talking to HENSON, I instantly noticed his eyes were glassy and bloodshot. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from inside the Infiniti. HENSONs speech was slurred. I asked HENSON how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed that evening, and he stated, two (2) beers I asked HENSON to exit and walk to the front of my patrol vehicle. HENSON exited his vehicle and left the front drivers door fully open. I observed HENSON was stumbling while walking to the front of my patrol vehicle. At the front of my patrol vehicle, I could now detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on HENSONs breath and person. HENSON had difficulty keeping his balance as he swayed from left to right and leaned against my patrol vehicle for balance. I advised HENSON that I would perform standardized field sobriety tests on him, which he agreed to submit. The summary of the first contact is as follows: I offered HENSON medical attention, and he refused. Attitude: cooperative Eye Condition: Glassy/bloodshot Mental State: Normal. Walk: Normal. Speech: Slurred. I asked HENSON the following questions: Medication- No Medical Conditions- No Glasses: Yes (Yes, wearing glasses) Any pain in the body- No PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The below standardized field sobriety tests were performed on the right shoulder. That area of the road was level and free of debris. Before beginning the standardized field sobriety tests below, I turned off my front emergency lights. The weather conditions were clear. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and my patrol vehicle headlights. HENSON appeared in the good physical condition and did not display any visible signs of injury. I explained and demonstrated the standardized field sobriety tests below to HENSON. HENSON stated he understood my instructions and had no questions about the standardized field sobriety test. -HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN) / (6/6 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: Yes) The first test given was the horizontal gaze nystagmus test. The tip of my index finger from my right hand was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from HENSONs eyes, slightly above his eyebrows. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. HENSONs pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I observed his eyes to be red. HENSON was positioned to ensure that passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked HENSON if he understood the instructions, and he stated, Yes. The following clues and observations were made during the test: Lack of Smooth Pursuit- Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation- Present in both eyes The onset of Nystagmus Prior 45 Degrees- Present in both eyes Additional test Vertical Gaze Nystagmus- Present in both eyes -WALK AND TURN (WAT) / (5/8 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: Yes) Before HENSON performed the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. HENSON was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. HENSON was instructed and demonstrated to put his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until instructed to begin. HENSON was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on each step. HENSON was asked to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count each step out loud. On the ninth step, HENSON was explained, and I demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and planted and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around to his left. HENSON was again explained, and I demonstrated that the second series of nine (9) steps would be completed identically to the first. Keep his hands by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. I asked HENSON if he understood the test. HENSON stated, Yes. HENSON was instructed to begin the test. Instructional Stage: Unable to keep balance. HENSON started the test before being instructed. Walking Stage (1st Nine) HENSON stepped offline on steps 3 and 5. HENSON missed heel to toe by approximately 2 inches on steps 2 and 6 Walking Stage (2nd nine): HENSON stepped offline on steps 1 and 5 HENSON missed heel to toe by approximately 2 inches on steps 2, 4 and 8 Turn: Completed Unsatisfactory. HENSON did not leave his front foot planted and used both feet to walk in a circle. -ONE LEG STAND (OLS) (LEFT LEG) (3/4 CLUES OBSERVED, REFUSED TEST) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: YES) Before HENSON performed the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. HENSON was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given during the test. HENSON was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to watch his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (thousand-one, thousand-two), and continue the test until told to stop. I asked HENSON if he understood the test. HENSON stated, Yes. HENSON lifted his left foot. Instructional Stage: Nothing to report. Balance and Count Stage: 1. Sways: HENSON swayed on the 02 and 05-second mark. 2. Raise arms: HENSON raised his arms more than 6 inches on the 7, 9, 12, and 15-second mark. 3. Hopping: HENSON hopped on the 06-second mark.  -PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT) (REFUSED)- The final test offered to HENSON was the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT). HENSON was advised that he could refuse this test. HENSON refused to submit to the PBT. ARREST Based on my knowledge, training, and experience as an MSP Trooper, previous DUI arrests, and clues gathered thus far, I had reason to believe HENSON was driving a motor vehicle while impaired (under the influence of Alcohol). *Driving over the posted speed limit of 80/55MPH * Physical control of a motor vehicle *admission of consumption of alcoholic beverage *Odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person *Bloodshot eyes *Slurred speech *Watery eyes * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety ARREST / ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) / CERTIFIED BREATH TEST (REFUSED)/(Maryland State Police). I arrested HENSON for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 2342 hours. HENSON was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to Maryland State Police Bel Air-Barrack for processing, where a mouth check was performed 20 minutes before his submission to the breath test. HENSON was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along with as the DR-15 advice of rights was played to him from the official MVA website. At the conclusion of the DR-15, HENSON refused to submit to the intoximeter test and refused to sign the DR-15, indicating the same at approximately 0044 hours. HENSON was given all copies of pertinent paperwork, and HENSON was released to a sober adult that came to Bel Air Barrack. INTOXIMETER RESULT: REFUSED HENSON was cooperative during the processing. Case Status  Closed by arrest. All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 01:59:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/05/2023 19:23:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Atkinson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5623</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499148</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/18/2023 00:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 13:47:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 13:48:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>51</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 13:47:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>97682</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Henson</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Howard</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/30/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>04/19/2016 03:52:07</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Henson</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Howard</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/30/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>H525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/19/2016 03:52:07</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5369</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>King Arthur</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Rosedale</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21237</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.465057</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.358508</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 13:58:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 13:58:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 13:58:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 13:47:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 13:47:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>