<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002676</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/22/2023 03:58:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/22/2023 03:58:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/22/2023 03:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/22/2023 03:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI, WARRANT</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 03:58:05</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/29/2023 00:49:28</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>RHODE ISLAND,COLLEGE PARK</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>681380</AddressId>
      <City>MDC253</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 03:58:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 00:24:29</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>681380</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Rhode Island College</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PARK</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.92175045</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0127727166667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/22/2023 03:58:02</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/22/2023 03:58:02</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/26/2023 02:11:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 03:58:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/26/2023 02:11:26</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI #: 23-008 Incident was recorded. In car camera and body camera are operational.  Defendant: Tario Portillo, Javier, A  MD DL #: T616376044932 (NO LICENSE)  Date of Birth: 12/07/1982  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the MarylandState Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. I am trained and certified to conduct preliminary breathalyzer tests by theMaryland State Police  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On January 22nd, 2023, at approximately 0303 hours, I, Trooper Barnhart #7328, was dispatched to the area of Rhode Island Ave at Hollywood Road to assist Trooper Savilisky #7460 on a traffic stop.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I was operating a marked patrol vehicle Q-14. Upon arrival and after speaking with Trooper Savilisky about the cause for the stop, I went up to the vehicle, a black Mazda CX9 bearing MD temporary registration T1782705, and made contact with the driver, who was later identified by his passport as Javier Alejandro Tario Portillo (DOB 12/07/1982, H/M). While speaking with Tario at the driver side of the vehicle, I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath/person.  I then asked Tario how much alcohol he had; he replied he had 3 beers at 11:00pm in Spanish.  Trooper Savilisky attempted to get a translator on scene, but no one was available. Trooper Savilisky and I used Google Translate to communicate with Tario.  A check through MVA was conducted. At that time, Trooper Savilisky asked Tario to perform standardized field sobriety tests using Google Translate, todetermine if he was safe to drive, and he agreed.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on Rhode Island Service Rd at Hollywood Rd. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris.Tario appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visibleinjuries. Prior to beginning the test, Trooper Savilisky deactivated his vehicles forward-facingemergency lights. I asked Tario the following questions:  Medical Conditions  None  Medications- None       Illnesses - None  Glasses/Contacts - None HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of a pen wasused as the testing stimulus. It was held approximately 12-15 inches from Tarioseyes, slightly above his eye level. Tario was instructed to look forward, keep hishead still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. Tario was positioned ina manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with thetest results. Tarios pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes  Vertical Gaze Nystagmus present.  WALK AND TURN (8/8 clues observed)  The test was explained and demonstrated. Tario was instructed to place his rightfoot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on a straight-line. Tariowas then instructed to remain in that position until told to begin. Tario wasadvised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step.On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take aseries of small steps around his lead foot to turn completely around. Afterthe turn, Tario was instructed to complete the second series of nine (9) steps inthe same heel to toe fashion. Tario was instructed to keep his hands flat at hissides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, count every step aloud, and once he beganthe test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed.  Instructional Stage:   Could not keep balance  Starts too soon  Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Arms raised (For duration of test)  Missed heel to toe (3rd, 4th, and 9th step)   Steps off-line (4th, and 9th step)  Turn: Performed satisfactorily (Paused in the middle of turn, didnt know where to walk back) Walking Stage (2nd Nine):    Arms raised (For duration of test)     Incorrect number of steps (11 steps taken)  Steps off-line (6th and 8th step)   margin-left:8px"&gt;Stops walking   ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed):  The test was explained and demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raisethe foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch the raised foot, and to count out loudby thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, etc) and to keep his handsdown by his side. I asked Tario if he understood, Tario responded yes. Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10:    Raised arms  Put foot on ground   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Sways  While on scene, I informed Tario of his Preliminary Breath Test Rights. Tariowas offered a PBT, to which he refused.   ARREST  Based on the following totality of circumstances, I had reason to believe Tariowas driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:    Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from breath/person.   Glassy bloodshot eyes.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Clues during Standardized Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (6/6), WAT (8/8), OLS (3/4).   Driver admitting to consuming alcohol within the past four hours.  Due to the number of observations, I concluded Tario was driving under theinfluence of alcohol and was unable to operate a vehicle safely.At approximately 0357 hours, I placed Tario under arrest for driving while underthe influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack, and conducted a mouth check and placed him in my patrol vehicle and transported him to the College Park barrack.Tario was read his DR-15 Advice of Rights in Spanish from the Maryland MotorVehicle Administration website. Tario was also given a paper copy to read alongwith. At approximately 0431 hours, Tario refused to take an alcohol concentrationtest. The defendant was issued copies of the following documents:    Citations  DR-15 Advice of Rights.   margin-left:8px"&gt;DR-15a Order of Suspension.  At approximately 0435 hours, the College Park barrack PCO confirmed that there was an active Failure to Appear warrant for Tario. Tario was then transported to the Upper Marlboro Department of Corrections located at 13400 Dille Dr, Upper Marlboro, MD 20772. At approximately 0651 hours, Tario was released from my custody to the Department of Corrections custody. (Warrant # ODY15-D17075951-4) The Mazda was towed by his own disposition.   All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7328</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 01:28:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7328</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/25/2023 02:37:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Savilisky</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zack</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7460</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derek</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5951</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barnhart</LastName>
            <FirstName>Clay</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7328</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492059</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/22/2023 03:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7328</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 00:27:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7328</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 00:27:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492059</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/22/2023 03:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7328</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 00:28:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7328</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 00:28:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492059</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/22/2023 03:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7328</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 00:33:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7328</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 00:33:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492059</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3096</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/22/2023 03:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3096</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7328</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 00:38:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7328</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 00:38:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7328</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 00:47:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:18</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366929</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>TARIO PORTILLO</LastName>
               <FirstName>JAVIER</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ALEJANDRO</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/07/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:46:01</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T616</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J160</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>TARIO PORTILLO</LastName>
               <FirstName>JAVIER</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ALEJANDRO</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/07/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T616</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J160</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:46:01</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11407</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Dewey</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Silver Spring</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20906</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.085742</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.043972</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>052</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2888</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7328</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 01:26:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7328</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 01:15:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7328</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/25/2023 01:15:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149077</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7328</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/26/2023 02:02:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7328</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/26/2023 02:02:23</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JM3TB3MA7A0213967</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2010</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MAZD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8FE3181</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/23/2023 02:48:32</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/23/2023 02:48:32</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/26/2023 02:11:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 02:48:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/26/2023 02:11:26</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Supplement DUI#: 23-008 Case#: 23-MSP-002676    Narrative:  On January 22nd, 2023, at approximately 0300 hours, I, Trooper Savilisky (ID#7460) with the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, observed a black Mazda CX-9, bearing Maryland Registration (T1782705) (VIN: JM3TB3MA7A0213967) traveling southbound on Rhode Island Avenue, at Baltimore Avenue, College Park, Maryland. I observed the black CX-9 traveling southbound on Rhode Island Avenue, prior to Odessa Road, cross the solid yellow dividing line by one tire width, two separate times. The black CX-9 then crossed the white solid line dividing the southbound lane and the right shoulder by one tire width while traveling southbound on Rhode Island Avenue, at I-495.  I then activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle came to a stop on Rhode Island Avenue Service Road, at Hollywood Road, on the right shoulder. I approached the front driver window, made contact with the driver, introduced myself, and explained the reason for the stop. Upon contact with the driver, I detected the strong odor of and alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I observed the driver, who was later identified by his CASA identification card and passport, as Javier, Alenandro Tario Protillo, to have bloodshot, watery, and glassy eyes. The driver was also displaying a slurred, slow, and lethargic speech.  I obtained the drivers CASA identification card and passport and proceeded back to my patrol vehicle. Upon the arrival of Trooper Barnhart (ID#7328), with the Maryland State Police College Barrack, Trooper Barnhart proceeded to conduct Standard Field Sobriety on Protillo. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 02:49:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7460</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 08:15:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derek</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5951</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Savilisky</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zack</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7460</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149077</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/26/2023 00:47:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7460</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/26/2023 00:47:56</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JM3TB3MA7A0213967</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2010</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MAZD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8FE3181</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>