<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013156</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/13/2023 21:28:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/13/2023 21:28:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/13/2023 21:07:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/13/2023 21:07:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 21:28:42</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 09:26:24</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>PHILADELPHIA AVE/ 30TH ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>591678</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 21:28:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 19:42:18</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>591678</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Philadelphia</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.074241</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.358929</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB COASTAL/ 30TH</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3001-3021 PHILADELPHIA AVE / 0-0 30TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 PHILADELPHIA AVE / 100-112 30TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/13/2023 21:28:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/13/2023 21:28:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/23/2023 08:17:38</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 21:28:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:47</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Roland Sarazin Jr Maine SOUNDEX: 1883143 Breath Test Result: Refused  DUI Citation # 5WB0T5Y DUI Tape #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-013156 (Axon View XL Software)  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. * Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.). * Completed and graduated from the DUI Institute. * Completed and graduated from the SFST Instructor school  NARRATIVE -PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION- On April 13, 2023 at approximately 2107 hours, I (TFC. S. Shubert #6944), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating unmarked MSP vehicle V-08. At that time, I was on routine patrol on northbound Coastal Highway at 33rd Street, Ocean City, Worcester County, Maryland.   At that time, I observed a gray Jeep Wrangler bearing Virginia registration (TTS9574) traveling southbound on Coastal Highway at 33rd Street. I observed the two front head lamps to be inoperable. I safely made a U-turn and positioned my patrol vehicle directly behind the gray Jeep. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop.  -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT- I exited my patrol vehicle and made contact with the driver via the driver side door. I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle. I requested his drivers license and registration card. I also observed the driver to display a dazed/expression looks on his face. The driver was later identified through his Maine drivers license as Ronald Sarazin Jr. I asked Sarazin where he was coming from and Sarazin stated Restaurant up the street. Heading back to our hotel. I asked Sarazin how many alcoholic beverages he consumed prior to operating his motor vehicle and Sarazin stated A couple beers. I returned to my patrol vehicle and conducted a routine drivers license check.  I then exited my patrol vehicle and walked up to the drivers side window and asked Sarazin to walk to the front of his motor vehicle. Sarazin did as I asked. I observed Sarazin chew a piece of gum an attempt to disguise the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. I asked Sarazin to spit out the gum and Sarazin did as I asked. I then I asked where Sarazin was coming from and Sarazin stated I think it was called Fagers. I asked if he consumed any alcoholic beverages prior to operating his motor vehicle and Sarazin stated Glass of wine. I think I had two glasses. I asked Sarazin if he wanted to voluntarily submit to Standardized Field Sobriety tests to insure he was not impaired. Sarazin agreed to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety tests.   -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING- STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs) The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder area. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of headlights, overhead lights and flashlight. Sarazin appeared to be in good physical condition.   Sarazin was wearing blue jeans, a red dress shirt and sandals.   **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**  1. Sarazin displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  2. Sarazin displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes. 3. Sarazin displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.  ^^^ I observed vertical nystagmus during the test^^^  **WALK AND TURN: 4 of 8 clues** First nine steps: -Missed heel-to-toe by approximately two inches on step 6 -Stepped off-line by approximately three inches on steps 2,9 -Took 10 steps when instructed to take 9 steps Turn: Completed unsatisfactory, lifted lead foot Second nine steps: -Missed heel-to-toe by approximately two inches on steps 6,8 -Stepped off-line by approximately three inches on steps 9   **ONE LEG STAND: 1 of 4 clues** Firmly placed right foot down six times during the test.  I then asked Sarazin if he could recite the English alphabet from A-Z and Sarazin stated Yes. I then asked Sarazin to recite the English alphabet starting at the letter H ending at the letter T. I asked Sarazin if he understood my instructions and Sarazin stated Yes. Sarazin stated the following: H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P-Q-R-T-S-U  After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Sarazin the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Sarazin refused to submit to the preliminary breath test.  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Sarazin was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.  * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests.  *lethargic movements    I placed Sarazin under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 2128 hours on April 13, 2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Sarazins mouth for any foreign objects and none were found.   ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) Sarazin was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Sarazin was given his Advice of Rights via the audio version in English of the DR-15 Form. I placed a copy of the DR-15 in front of Sarazin. While the DR-15 was being played Sarazin began to argue about his wife walking back to the hotel. I stopped the audio of the DR-15 to explain to Sarazin that I tried to his wife a taxi and Sarazin stated I dont respect you as a man. After I patiently explained everything I resumed the DR-15. Once the DR-15 was completed, Sarazin stated he understood the Advice of Rights form. However, was still arguing about his wife. I transported Sarazin back to the Ocean City Police department.   While en route, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Sarazins breath and person.   Once we arrived to Ocean City Police Department. I unbuckled Sarazin and asked his to exit my vehicle. Sarazin quickly exited and struck me with his left shoulder. Once we were sitting down in the processing room. I asked Sarazin if he wanted to submit to the Intoximeter test and Sarazin stated No. I dont think it is in my best interest to take it. Sarazin refused to submit to the Intoximeter test at 2155 hours.   While walking out of Ocean City Police Department. I explained I will give Sarazin a ride back to his hotel. Sarazin refused and stated I just want to walk. I dont need a ride. After explaining to Sarazin that I needed to give him a ride and release him to someone. Sarazin then entered into my patrol vehicle and stated were good officer Shubert. and refused to discuss anything else. Once we arrived to the Marriott hotel on 15th Street. Sarazin then began to argue about the citations and pointed at me stated you never explained anything before you had me sign any of the documents. Sarazin then argued again about his wife walking back to the hotel. Sarazin began to shout Come on lets go to his wife and walked into the hotel. I released Sarazin to his wife.   PROCESSING During all aspects of processing (mugshot, completion and explanation of the DR-15A Form, issuance and explanation of citations), the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Sarazin continued to be strong.  CHARGES Sarazin was charged with the following citations: 1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (5WB0T5Y) 2. Driving While Impaired By Alcohol (5WC0T5Y) 3. Negligent driving (5WD0T5Y) 4. Driving without two front head lamps when required (5WF0T5Y  Case closed by arrest. All events occurred in Worcester County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/20/2023 20:48:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/21/2023 02:52:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502561</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/13/2023 21:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 19:48:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 19:48:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>59</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 19:48:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374298</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sarazin Jr</LastName>
               <FirstName>Roland</FirstName>
               <DOB>03/28/1964 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/14/2023 19:45:12</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R453</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sarazin Jr</LastName>
               <FirstName>Roland</FirstName>
               <DOB>03/28/1964 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R453</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/14/2023 19:45:12</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 19:49:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 19:49:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/14/2023 19:48:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 19:48:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152151</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 19:19:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 19:19:30</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>WRG</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>TTS9574</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>