<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-010768</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/25/2023 21:05:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/25/2023 21:05:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/25/2023 20:37:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Accident / DUI Arrest</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/25/2023 21:05:38</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0266</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 12:05:15</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>227829</AddressId>
      <City>MDC219</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/25/2023 21:05:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:04:24</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>227829</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>915 </StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Bennett Point </StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Queenstown</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21658</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.169534</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.9453</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/25/2023 21:05:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/25/2023 21:05:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>80</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/07/2023 10:29:10</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/25/2023 21:05:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police CentrevilleBarrack S MSP unmarked vehicle S-12   Defendant: Brendan Matthew Bonner  Date of Birth: 08/15/1994  Date of Arrest: 03/25/2023  Timeof Arrest: 2105hours  DUI #: 23-034(Centreville Barrack)  Accident Report / ACRS completed in Delta Plus  Intoximeter Results - .21 BRAC  CERTIFICATION  TRAINING  * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA). * Trained and certified to operate radar and lidar through the Maryland State Police. * Trained in administering AdvancedRoadside ImpairedDrivingEnforcement(ARIDE)      VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)   On 03/25/2023, at approximately 2037hours, I TrooperFirst Class Maranto #7116 of the Maryland State Police Centreville Barrack was on patrol operating unmarked MSP vehicle S-12, when I was dispatched to Bennett Point Road and Hemsley Drive, Queenstown, Maryland 21658 for the report that a passing motorist saw a vehicle off the road down in a ditch.  PERSONAL CONTACT ( PHASE 2):   Upon my arrival, I observed a vehicle off the roadway to the left down an embankment in a ditch off of Bennett Point Road past Hemsley Drive. The driver had actually crashed on the property of 915 Bennett Point Road, Queenstown, Maryland 21658. The vehicle was a gray Volvo S60 bearing Maryland registration 6DD1123. The property owner was there attempting to pull his vehicle out of the ditch using his John Deere tractor. He was later identified as Christopher James Mood (2/M DOB: 05/08/1968) of 915 Bennett Point Road, Queenstown, Maryland 21658. I observed a white male wearing a dark bluesweatshirt. I asked who was driving, and the male in the dark blue sweatshirt raised his right hand. The male said I got stuck in the ditch Im not familiar with the area. The male stated I took the wrong turn, came down into the ditch, and this man is trying to help me out. He advised he was driving down Bennett Point Road, that he had forgotten something, and then was backing up to go back down to the Bennett Point General Store. He told me he tried to back onto the driveway, but The road wasnt the road. He told me he was visiting his girlfriend and wasnt from the area. I and asked the driver if he needed EMS, or if he lost consciousness. The driver had slow and slurred speech, and stated No. I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. His eyes were red, glassy, watery, and bloodshot. I asked him for his license. I asked him numerous times if he had anything to drink tonight, and he continued to deny and state he had nothing to drink at all. The driver finally handed me his license. A Maryland Drivers License positively identified him as Brendan Matthew Bonner(W/M DOB: 08/15/1994) of 209 Overcreek Road, Phoenixville, Pennsylvania 19460. I asked Bonner again, if he had alcoholic drinks he had tonight, and he again stated No. Bonner advised that his license was currently suspended, and that his registration was expired from January 2022. Bonner continued to deny having any alcoholic beverages. Due to red, glassy, watery, and bloodshot eyes, the strong odor of an alcoholic beverageemitting from his breath,slurred and slow speech,I asked Bonner to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):  The surface was dry, level, and free from debris. The weather was cloudy. Before administering the Standardized Field Sobriety Test, I asked Mr.Bonner if he had any prior injuries that would stop himfrom completing the tests correctly. Mr. Bonner stated, No.  I asked Mr.Bonner the following questions:  Glasses or Contacts- No (Has 20/20 corrected vision.) Medical Conditions- No Medications-Vyvanse  30mg and Depression Medication. Injuries- No.  Surgeries in the past year  No. Mental Disabilities  No.   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was a Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Mr. Bonners eyes. Mr. Bonner was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hiseyes,until told to stop. I asked Bonner if he could see the tip of my pen while I was holding it in front of him, and he said Yes. I asked him if he understood the instructions. I asked him if he had any questions about the test, and he said No.  1) Lack of Smooth Pursuit: Was present in both eyes. 2) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation:Was present in both eyes. 3) The onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees: Was present in both eyes. 4) Vertical Nystagmus - Not Present.   WALK AND TURN (7/8 clues observed)      Prior to Mr. Bonner performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Mr. Bonner was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and heel to toe touching. Mr. Bonner was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin the test. Mr. Bonner was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Mr. Bonner was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keeping his eyes focused on his feet and to count out every step aloud. On the ninth step, Mr. Bonner was explained and demonstrated to follow his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to the left to turn completely around. Mr. Bonner was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Mr. Bonner was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keeping hishands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count aloud each step. I asked Mr. Bonner if he understood the test, and he stated, Yes.  Instructional Stage:  1.) Unable to maintain balance (unable to keep feet heel to toe.)  2.) Starts too soon      Performance Stage:   3.) First Nine Steps: Raises Arms  4.) First Nine Steps: Misses Heel to Toe  5.) First Nine Steps: Steps Off Line  6.) Second Nine Steps: Raises Arms  7.) Second Nine Steps: Misses Heel to Toe  8.) Second Nine Steps: Steps Off Line  9.) Turn AroundCompleted Unsatisfactory  10.) * Took 10 steps instead of instructed 9 steps, on the second set of steps.  ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)  Prior to Mr. Bonner performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Mr. Bonner was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of hischoice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While hisleg was raised, he was asked to keep hisleg straight, watch hisraised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Mr. Bonner was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, Keep my foot up until you tell me to put it down.  1, Raises Arms 0 - 10 seconds, 11 - 20 seconds, 21 - 30 seconds. 2. Sways - 0 - 10 seconds, 11 - 20 seconds, 21 - 30 seconds.  Bonner got to 23 seconds when 30 seconds had elapsed.    PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST:   Offered and accepted.  On the first couple of tries, Bonner was purposely not exhaling, and was breathing in. I finally gave him one last chance to do the test properly. PBT reading was .235    Maryland State PolicePBT Serial Number: 70014940    I then asked Bonner what time his last alcoholic drink was this evening. Bonner stated My girlfriend drove us home from Baltimore around 4pm, so around 4pm. I asked him what he had been drinking, and he said A beer. A Sierra Nevada. He told me had had no shots of liquor or mixed drinks. I asked him if he had two or three beers, and he said Yeah probably about three. I asked him on a scale of 1-10, 1 being completely sober and 10 being completed drunk, he stated I put myself a pretty much a zero. Im fairly sober.   ARREST:Based on the following, I had reason to believe Mr. Bonner was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:   * Slurred and Slow Speech * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from breath. * Red, glassy, watery, and bloodshoteyes. * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests. * Admission to drinking an alcoholic beverage.      Based on my knowledge and training with the Maryland State Police, I believed that Mr. Bonner was driving under the influence of alcohol. I placed himunder arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at 2105hours. After placingBonner under arrest, he said This is the worst night of my life, I did it to myself. During a search incident to arrest, I located the vehicle keys in his pocket. He told me that it was just him in the vehicle, and no one else was in the car while he was driving. I then spoke with the witness who was attempting to help Bonner. Mr. Mood advised that he saw him pull into the driveway, and then he backed in and went down into the ditch. Bonner then ran up to and stated he needed help. I asked Mood if he could smell the alcohol on him, and he said Yeah. I locked and secured his vehicle. I transported Mr. Bonner to the Maryland State Police Centreville Barrack S for further processing. On the way back to the barrack, Bonner stated Im so utterly fucked. Damn Im a fucking idiot. At 2145 hours, I played the DR-15 Advice of Rights to Mr. Bonner in English. Mr. Bonner agreedto submit to a Intoximeter test. Bonner stated I wont do this again, I just messed up I shouldnt have been driving. After completing the necessary paperwork, I gave Bonner a ride to his girlfriends house. While in the processing room, I continued to smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath. Bonner continued to have slurred speech. Bonner was remorseful for his actions, was polite and respectful during the entire encounter.   INTOXIMETER TEST RESULTS:  Cpl. Baker #6562 conducted the breath test for Bonner. Mr. Bonner ACCEPTED the test, with the results of .21 BRAC. Mr. Bonner was issued the appropriate citations for driving while impaired by alcohol. Iissued Mr. Bonner a series of traffic citations. Mr. Bonner was then given a ride back to his girlfriends house in Queenstown, Maryland. All the above events occurred in Queen Annes County, Maryland. Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:54:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/29/2023 03:46:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Winiarski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Corey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7078</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Maranto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7116</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Baker</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6562</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Maranto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7116</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Maranto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7116</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:44:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:44:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:45:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:45:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3096</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19760</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3074</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>12</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>12</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>13</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15558</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>13</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>14</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16626</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>14</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500171</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>15</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>15</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 20:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:50:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>28</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:36:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:42</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372746</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bonner</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brendan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Matthew</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/15/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.09745659E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 22:27:37</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B560</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bonner</LastName>
               <FirstName>Brendan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Matthew</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/15/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.09745659E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>B560</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B653</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 22:27:37</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>209</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Overcreek</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Phoenixville</City>
               <StateCode>PA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>19460</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>610</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>937</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9707</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:53:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:53:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>54</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:40:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>113758</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mood</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>James</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/08/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/01/2016 15:02:18</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mood</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>James</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/08/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/01/2016 15:02:18</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>915 </StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Bennett Point </StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Queenstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21658</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.169534</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.9453</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>871</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0855</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/01/2016 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:40:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 22:44:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 22:44:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151355</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7116</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 23:07:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7116</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 23:07:30</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>YV1612FS4D2187453</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>VOLV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>S60</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6DD1123</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2022</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>