<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-001755</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/15/2023 04:01:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/15/2023 04:01:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/15/2023 03:26:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/15/2023 03:26:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Disabled vehicle with impaired driver.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 04:01:22</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2637</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 23:48:05</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>CONOWINGO RD/ SPREADY OAK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>681331</AddressId>
      <City>MDC221</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 04:01:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/21/2023 18:23:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>681331</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Conowingo</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Rising Sun</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21911</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.11935</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.69487</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/15/2023 04:01:18</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/15/2023 04:01:18</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/23/2023 13:30:42</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 04:01:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:31</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>CASE NUMBER: 23-MSP-001755 DUI NUMBER: 23-012 DUI CITATION NUMBER: 1SY0V1W  CRIME: Driving Vehicle While Under the Influence of Alcohol DEFENDANT: Steven Clifford Carlton DATE OF BIRTH: 10/19/1993 LICENSE STATE  NUMBER: (MD) C-643-777-119-807 COMMERCIAL DRIVERS LICENSE: Yes VEHICLE INFORMATION: 2019 White Ford F-150 (MD: 6EV3669) COMMERCIAL VEHICLE: No DATE  TIME OF INCIDENT: 01/15/2023 at 0326 hours LOCATION OF INCIDENT: Conowingo Road  Westwood Road, Rising Sun, Maryland 21911 DATE  TIME OF ARREST: 01/15/2023 at 0407 hours SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER: No ACCIDENT INVOLVED: No NATURE OF CALL FOR SERVICE: Disabled Vehicle Stuck in a Ditch WEATHER  SURFACE: Clear Weather / Pavement Free of Debris LIGHTING: Dark TYPE OF TEST: Alcohol Concentration Test LICENSE RESTRICTION(S): B  E   SCENE PROCESSING: * Interview of Driver * SFSTs * Arrest for DUI/DWI * Vehicle Tow * Interview of Reporting Person(s)  BARRACK PROCESSING: * DR15 (Advice of Rights) * DR15A (Officers Certification  Order of Suspension) * Citations * MSP Form 225  CERTIFICATES  TRAINING: * I am trained and certified to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) and Preliminary Breath Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  * I am trained and certified to administer Advanced Roadside Impairment Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  * I am trained and certified to administer Drug Recognition Expert Evaluations (DRE) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  * I have attended and successfully completed the Advanced Driving Under the Influence training course through the Maryland State Police S.P.I.D.R.E. Team.  * I have successfully completed the Marijuana DUI Investigation online course through the Central Valley California HIDTA.  * I attended the six-month Maryland State Police Academy in Sykesville, Maryland. While there, I was also trained in the detection, identification and processing of numerous controlled dangerous substances. Prior to becoming a Maryland State Trooper, I was a prior Police Officer for approximately four years in the State of Pennsylvania working in high crime areas (Cities of Philadelphia and Chester) known for drug trafficking. During my time as a Maryland State Trooper, I was temporarily assigned for approximately six months to the Wicomico County Narcotics Task Force (WINTF) where I assisted with investigations involving Controlled Dangerous Substances. I have also attended specialized training involving the possession, sale, and processing of controlled dangerous substances, and continue to do so.  NARRATIVE:  PHASE #1  VEHICLE IN MOTION:  On Sunday, January 15, 2023, at approximately 0326 hours, I, TFC. M. Hughes #7111 responded to the area of Conowingo Road and Westwood Road, Rising Sun, Maryland 21911 in reference to a single vehicle off the roadway disabled in a ditch.    Upon my arrival, I observed a 2019 white Ford F-150 displaying Maryland registration 6EV3669 off the roadway on the westbound side of Conowingo Road facing eastbound in the ditch. I then observed a male standing behind the vehicle in the ditch. As I approached the male, he attempted to climb out of the ditch; however, he fell down several times before ultimately getting out of the ditch on foot.  PHASE #2  PERSONAL CONTACT:   While observing the male (sole occupant), who was later identified by Maryland Commercial Drivers License (CDL) as Steven Clifford Carlton DOB 10/19/1993, I observed he was clearly under the influence. I directed him to stand by his vehicle, where I observed him to have an unsteady walk as he staggered from side to side taking stutter steps. I then asked Carlton what happened, which he reported the truck is two-wheel drive, and he couldnt get out of the ditch. I next asked Carlton the following questions:   * Alcoholic Beverages Consumed Prior to Driving: A good amount (4-5 Jack  Coke single glasses). * Place Where Alcoholic Beverages Were Consumed: Sweeneys Sports Bar (196 Conowingo Road). * Arrival and Departure Times for Sweeneys: Arrived near closing time (0200 hours), and left approximately one hour prior to question. * Self-Assessment Impairment Scale (zero to ten): A five impairment out of ten.    While speaking with Carlton I observed the additional following signs of impairment:  * Swaying while standing * Bloodshot/glassy eyes * Strong odor of alcoholic beverages coming from breath/person * Thick, slurred speech   PHASE #3  PRE-ARREST SCREENING:  I asked Carlton to participate in Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Carlton agreed to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  PRE-SCREENING QUESTIONS:  I asked Carlton a series of questions prior to performing Standardized Field Sobriety Tests:  * Glasses/Contacts: Glasses on. * Injuries/Disabilities: A right hip flexor. * Medications or Drugs: None. * Mouth Check: Clear.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS TEST:    I explained the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test (HGN) to Carlton. After explaining the test, I asked Carlton if he understood the test which he stated he understood the test. I then completed the following checks before beginning the test.   Resting Nystagmus: No Equal Tracking: Yes Equal Pupil Size: Yes  Lack of Smooth Pursuit: Present Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation: Present Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees: Present Vertical Gaze Nystagmus: Present    During this HGN test, Carlton was advised twice to not move his head and five times to follow the stimulus with his eyes.  Total Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Clues: 6 of 6  WALK  TURN TEST:  WEATHER: Clear SURFACE: Road pavement free of debris FOOTWEAR: Sneakers  I proceeded by attempting to instruct Carlton into the instructional Walk and Turn Test (WAT) stance. After extreme difficulties to put Carlton into the instructional stance due to him almost falling over several times as he used hands for balance and broke his heel to toe stance, I advised him just to stand there. I next demonstrated the test and gave Carlton additional instructions. After explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked Carlton if he understood the test. Carlton advised he did and then was advised to get into the instructional stance and to begin. When starting the test, Carlton counted number one out loud without taking a step causing his count number two to be his first step taken.  INSTRUCTIONAL PHASE: Could not keep balance Starts to soon  WALKING STAGE 1ST NINE: Missed heel-to-toe: steps four and six. Stepped off-line: steps two three (almost fell over), five (almost fell over), seven and eight (almost fell over). Stopped walking: step eight. Incorrect number of steps: eight steps taken. Used arms for balance (beyond six inches from the sides)  TURN: Unsatisfactorily: used both feet (turned towards his right)  WALKING STAGE 2ND NINE: Missed heel-to-toe: all steps. Stepped off line: all steps (almost falling over several times). Stopped walking: steps five and six.  Used arms for balance (beyond six inches from the sides)  Total Walk and Turn Clues:8 of 8  ONE LEG STAND TEST:  LEG RAISED: Right  I next explained and demonstrated the One Leg Stand Test (OLS) to Carlton. I then asked Carlton if he understood the test, and he stated he did. Carlton then began the test by picking up his right foot.   During the instructions, Carlton was observed swaying while standing.  SECONDS 1-10: Puts foot down (twice while almost falling over) Used arms for balance (beyond six inches from the sides) Swayed Hopped  SECONDS 11-20: N/A  SECONDS 21-30: N/A   After almost falling over twice during the first several seconds of the OLS test, I stopped the test for safety reasons fearing Carltons severe impairment may cause injuries if he proceeded by attempting to complete the test.  Total One Leg Stand Clues:4 of 4   PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST:  Not Offered/Not Available  ARREST  TRANSPORT:    Based on the following, I had reason to believe Carlton was driving a motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol:  * Carlton drove off the opposite side of the road * Carlton observed with bloodshot/glassy eyes * The odor of alcoholic beverages detected coming from Carltons person and breath * Carlton heard with a thick, slurred speech * Carlton admitting to consuming alcoholic beverages at a local bar prior to driving * Carltons self-assessment of being a five impairment out ten * Carlton observed with an unsteady walk while almost falling over many of times throughout the tests.  * My observed signs of impairment  Due to my observations, I placed Carlton under arrest for driving a vehicle while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0407 hours.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD:   While en route to Maryland State Police Barrack F North East, I played the audio version of the DR-15 Advice of Rights to Carlton while providing him with a copy of the DR-15 on the computer screen to follow along with. Upon our arrival to Maryland State Police Barrack F North East, Carlton agreed to the alcohol concentration test signing the DR-15 at approximately 0445 hours.  ALCOHOL CONCENTRATION TEST:  INSTRUMENT SERIAL NUMBER: 011750 CERTIFIED EXPIRATION DATE: 06/30/2023 TEST TECHNICIAN: CPL. Davis #4976     At approximately 0459 hours, Carlton gave a breath specimen which was found to contain an alcohol concentration of .16 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.    DISPOSITION:  After processing, Carlton was released to his girlfriend who was waiting in the front lobby at Maryland State Police Barrack F North East. Carlton was given copies of all pertinent paperwork. Carlton was extremely polite and cooperative throughout the entire process.  All times in this report are approximate. All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 10:32:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 12:46:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4976</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hughes</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7111</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491137</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/15/2023 03:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/21/2023 18:24:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/21/2023 18:24:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/21/2023 18:40:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366813</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Carlton</LastName>
               <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Clifford</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/19/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/21/2023 18:39:35</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C643</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Carlton</LastName>
               <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Clifford</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/19/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C643</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/21/2023 18:39:35</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>634</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Brenda</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Aberdeen</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21001</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1713</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.173551</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.524076</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/21/2023 18:40:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:34</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/21/2023 18:40:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:34</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/21/2023 18:40:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:34</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/21/2023 18:24:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/21/2023 18:24:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>