<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013482</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/16/2023 03:50:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/16/2023 03:50:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/16/2023 03:39:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/16/2023 03:39:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI, Accident.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 03:50:47</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4913</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/09/2023 13:19:38</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>ROSCOE ROWE TO US-50 WB / US-50</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>390846</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 03:50:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6278</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/02/2023 20:41:20</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>390846</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Rowe BLVD @ W/B Rt. 50 exit ramp</StreetName>
         <City>Annapolis</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21401</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.51700000000017</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.9954500382278</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I595 WB EXIT 24 RAMP 7 / 0-0 ROWE BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/16/2023 03:50:46</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/16/2023 03:50:46</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/02/2023 20:59:37</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 03:50:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:43</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police Annapolis Barrack The Incident was captured on my in-car camera and body-worn camera Defendant: Geyner Felipe Rojas Torres  Date of Birth: 02/03/1999 Date of Arrest: 04/17/2023 Time of Arrest: 0401 Maryland Drivers License: MD10272722155  DUI# J-23-055  *I am trained by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Transportation Safety Administration to administer field sobriety tests. *I am preliminary breath test operator certified. *I have completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE).   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On 04/17/2023 at approximately 0339 hours, I (TFC Hill #6278) was on routine patrol in my marked patrol vehicle in the area of the southbound Rowe Blvd, at US 50 in Annapolis, Anne Arundel County, Maryland. As I drove past the exit from northbound Rowe to westbound US 50, I observed a gold Volkswagen Jetta bearing Maryland registration 1FC2834 stopped on the right shoulder with heavy front-end damage. I also observed damage to a traffic sign support pole and tire tracks which traveled onto an embankment and stopped where the Volkswagen came to rest. I activated my emergency equipment and positioned my patrol vehicle behind the Volkswagen.    PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I made contact with the operator of the Volkswagen while standing outside his vehicle. Upon making contact with the driver, I could smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I informed the driver that I was there to help with the vehicle collision and requested his drivers license. I asked the driver what happened during the vehicle collision and he advised he did not know. The driver was unable to locate his drivers license on his person or in his vehicle. I later located the drivers license/wallet on the front passengers seat of his vehicle. The driver was identified by a search through the MVA as the registered owner of the Volkswagen and later by his Maryland drivers license as Geyner Felipe Rojas Torres 5/M DOB: 02/03/1999. While asking Rojas Torres to look for his drivers license he stated I crashed. I asked Rojas Torres if anyone else was in the vehicle, and he advised he was the only occupant of the Volkswagen. As I spoke with Rojas Torres, I intentionally observed Rojas Torres speech to be slurred and his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I asked Rojas Torres where he was coming from, to which he repeated he was from Columbia. I returned to my patrol vehicle to perform routine checks.  I returned to the Volkswagen and requested Rojas Torres walk to the front of my patrol vehicle, to which he complied. While standing in front of my patrol vehicle, I continued to speak with Rojas Torres. I asked him how much he had to drink and he advised 2 beers. I again asked Rojas Torres where he was coming from, and he advised he was coming from Annapolis. As Rojas Torres spoke, I again could smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I informed Rojas Torres that I would be performing field sobriety tests on him, to which he agreed to submit too.    PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of the ramp from northbound Rove Blvd to westbound US 50. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 65 degrees. The lighting conditions consisted of the streetlamps and my flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Rojas Torres informed me that he was not injured during the vehicle collision and did not show any signs of injuries that would affect his ability to walk or stand.  I asked Rojas Torres the following questions: Medical Conditions - No Injuries  No Medication  No Contacts  No  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Rojas Torres eyes. Rojas Torres was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Rojas Torres pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Rojas Torres was asked if he understood the directions, and he stated Yes. Rojas Torres was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results.    HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) 1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes 2. Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both.  Other observations: 1. Vertical Nystagmus was present in both eyes.    WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)  Prior to Rojas Torres performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Rojas Torres was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Rojas Torres was instructed to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Rojas Torres was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Rojas Torres was told to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. Rojas Torres was demonstrated and explained to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Rojas Torres was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. After explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked Rojas Torres if he completely understood the instructions and he stated yes.   Instructional Stage:  1. Lost balance-feet broke apart on one (1) occasion.  Walking Stage (First 9 Steps)  1. Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 4, 7, and 9. 2. Took 13 steps. 3. On step 13 he stopped walking to ask if he could turn around.  Turn: 1. Nothing to report.  Walking Stage (Second 9 Steps) 1. Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 3 through 9.     ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)  Prior to Rojas Torres performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Rojas Torres was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his side while the instructions were given. Rojas Torres was instructed not to begin the test until he was told to start and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, keep his hands down by his side, and count out loud by thousands (one thousand - one, one thousand - two), and continue the test until told to stop. Rojas Torres was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated Yes. Rojas Torres stood on his right leg which was not injured.   Instructional Stage: 1. Nothing to report.  Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10. 1. Nothing to report  Seconds 11-20 1. Put foot down on 1 (1) occasion.  Seconds 21-30  1. Put foot down on one (1) occasion.  2. Raised arms away from body by more than 6 inches.   ARREST:  Based on the following: *Driving off the roadway causing a single-vehicle collision into a traffic sign support pole and embankment. *Inability to locate his license (on the front passengers seat). *Stating that he crashed. *Stating he was the only occupant in the Volkswagen.  *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. *Slurred Speech. *His glassy and bloodshot eyes. *Admitting to consuming an alcoholic beverage (2 beers). * My observed signs of impairment as he performed the Standardized Field Sobriety Test.    Given the aforementioned observations, I determined Rojas Torres could not operate a motor vehicle safely and he was placed under arrest at approximately 0401 hours on 04/16/2023 for driving under the influence of alcohol. Rojas Torres was transported in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle to the Maryland State Police Annapolis Barrack for processing. While at the barrack, I played the Spanish version of the DR -15 Advice of Rights from the MVA website for him in its entirety (also provide a copy for him to read along). At the conclusion of the form, Rojas Torres refused to submit to the intoximeter test and refused to sign the DR-15 indicating the same (0503 hours).   Alcohol concentration RESULT: ***Rojas Torres refused alcohol concentration test***   Rojas Torres was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to a sober driver (sister). Rojas Torres was polite and cooperative during the encounter. I had no issues communicating with Rojas Torres in English. The odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Rojas Torres breath and person was detected throughout his time in custody. Case closed by arrest. All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 05:26:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/23/2023 07:15:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6278</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Engleman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jonathon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5835</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6278</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6278</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502889</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 04:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 06:41:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 05:30:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502889</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 04:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 06:41:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 05:30:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502889</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 04:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 06:41:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 05:30:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502889</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 04:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 06:41:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 05:30:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502889</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/16/2023 04:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 06:41:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 05:30:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 06:41:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:30</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374434</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Rojas Torres</LastName>
               <FirstName>Geyner</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Felipe</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/03/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/16/2023 06:23:14</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R223</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G560</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Rojas Torres</LastName>
               <FirstName>Geyner</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Felipe</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/03/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R223</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G560</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/16/2023 06:23:14</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2106</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Peaceful</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>301</SubNumber>
               <City>Odenton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21113</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.718546</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.098654</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>865</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>805</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0984</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6278</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 04:21:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6278</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 04:21:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6278</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 04:21:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6278</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 04:21:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/16/2023 06:41:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/16/2023 06:41:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152021</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 04:25:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 04:25:07</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3VWD07AJ0EM216112</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>VOLK</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>JET</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4D</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GLD</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GLD</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1fc2834</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>6</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehicleValue>0</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>