<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-010803</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/26/2023 02:15:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/26/2023 02:15:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/26/2023 01:31:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/26/2023 01:31:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI 23-58-060</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/26/2023 02:15:54</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 15:00:00</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>415269</AddressId>
      <City>MDC139</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/26/2023 02:15:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 00:08:14</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>415269</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>11379</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Greensboro</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Denton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.81965154703893</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.91987787219994</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/26/2023 02:15:52</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/26/2023 02:15:52</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/23/2023 04:50:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/26/2023 02:15:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:30</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> DWI #23-58-060  This incident was captured via AXON bodycam.  https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=d5f8a653eaa542feadaafce116e2fa5fpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  Defendant: Lambert, Heather Nicole Date of Birth: 03/24/1984 Date of Arrest: 03/26/2023 Time of Arrest: 0156 Hours MD DL #: L-516-302-630-339  TRAINING CERTIFICATES:  I am trained by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Administration to administer standardized field sobriety tests. I am certified by the Maryland State Police in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.).   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1):  No Observations  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):  On 03/26/2023 at 0132 hours, I TFC Smith #6758, was dispatched to the area of 11379 Greensboro Road, Denton for a report of a vehicle in a ditch. The caller, Heather Lambert, called the Easton Barrack on a recorded line and stated that she had gotten her vehicle stuck. Upon arrival, I observed a silver Toyota Corolla bearing Maryland registration, 9ET621, stuck in the grass off the roadway. As I approached the two female subjects outside the vehicle, I observed one leaning on the rear of the vehicle. The other female explained that the vehicle got stuck while attempting to negotiate a turn in order to return home. I requested the drivers license from the subject leaning against the vehicle. She then moved to the front of the vehicle and struggled to maintain her balance. As the subject sat in the passengers side of the vehicle, she was searching through her belongings that were located in the drivers seat. She then produced a cigarette and exited the vehicle. As I spoke with the female, I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from her breath and person, and observed that the subject had bloodshot and glassy eyes. I asked the operator how much alcohol she had consumed prior to driving, to which he responded, enough. She then stated that she was the registered owner of the vehicle. I requested her name, to which she identified herself as, Lambert, Heather Nicole (#2/F/3-24-1984/L-516-302-630-339). A check through MVA revealed that Lambert had a valid Maryland drivers license.  While standing next to her vehicle, Lambert struggled to maintain her balance. Lambert stated that she was not driving. I then asked the passenger, and she responded saying, Ill take it. Implying that she would accept responsibility for her friends actions. She then stated that she didnt want her friend to get in trouble.  I requested Lambert to follow me towards my vehicle in order to conduct a field sobriety test, as she began to follow, she fell backwards onto her vehicle.I again detected the odor of a strong alcoholic beverage on her breath and person, despite being more than an arms length away for safety purposes.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):  The evaluation was performed on the right side of Greensboro road in Denton north of Rt 404. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear. Lighting conditions consisted of my vehicles headlights. Lambert appeared to be in good physical condition.  I asked Lambert the following questions:  Glasses or Contact  Contacts Medical Conditions  None Injuries  Back and neck injury Medication  Oxycodone  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (0/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The test was administered as per NHTSA standards. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Lamberts eyes. Lambert was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Lamberts pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Lambert was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic, or the lights of the emergency equipment on scene would interfere minimally with the test results. While conducting the test, Lambert had to constantly be reminded to only follow the stimulus with her eyes. After numerous attempts, I switched the stimulus to a small pen light. After continuing to have trouble getting Lambert to conduct the test, she refused to continue due to the wind. On scene there was some fog, however there was no noticeable wind.    WALK AND TURN (2/8 clues observed)  Prior to Lambert performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. The test was administered as per NHTSA standards. Lambert was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe on the line on the shoulder of the roadway. Lambert was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her side and to remain in that position until told to begin. LAMBERT was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. LAMBERT was instructed to keep her hands flat at his side, keep her eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, LAMBERT was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to the left to turn completely around. LAMBERT was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. LAMBERT was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her side, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked LAMBERT if she understood the test and she stated that she would not attempt the test until I allowed her to use the bathroom. Lambert then refused to continue with the Walk and Turn Test.  Instructional Stage:  1.) Started too soon, prior to giving an explanation, Lambert began walking. 2.) unable to keep balance, Lambert was unable to maintain the instructional position.   ONE LEG STAND (0/4 clues observed)  While explaining the test, Lambert stated, Im going to save you the breath, okay? Because if you did not allow me to go to the bathroom mm-hmm. Where I need to go to the bathroom, yeah. Were not going to do any of this  I then asked Lambert if she was refusing testing, to which she stated yes.  While on scene, Lambert was offered a preliminary breath test which she refused. ARREST:  Based on the following, I had reason to believe LAMBERT was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  *Results from Standardized Field Sobriety Test *Admission to drinking prior to driving *Poor motor skills and balance *Bloodshot and glassy eyes   Due to the number of observations, I concluded LAMBERT was driving under the influence. At approximately 0155 hours, I placed LAMBERT under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. A preliminary search of LAMBERT was conducted on scene. LAMBERT was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle per department policy. On scene I spoke with the passenger and she stated, again that she would have taken the DUI charge in her place. LAMBERT was transported to the Caroline County Sheriffs Office for processing. At 0223 hours, the DR-15 Advice of Rights was read to Lambert in English, at which time she refused the Intoximeter test. Lambert received copies of all paperwork and all pertinent information prior to being released to the custody of a sober driver.  Intoximeter Result: refused  All events occurred in Caroline County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6758</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/12/2023 21:27:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6758</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 17:55:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Walker</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6758</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Del Vecchio</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Walker</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6758</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Walker</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6758</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500206</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 01:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6758</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 00:07:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6758</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 00:09:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6758</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 00:07:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:19</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>8158</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lambert</LastName>
               <FirstName>Heather</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/03/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14069082E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>02/04/2014 04:08:09</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L516</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H360</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lambert</LastName>
               <FirstName>Heather</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/03/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.14069082E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>L516</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H360</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/04/2014 04:08:09</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>512</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Cannon</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Chestertown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21620</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.071826</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.210574</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>24731</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Langford</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>B</SubNumber>
               <City>Chestertown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21620</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2162</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.113072</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.186095</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>101</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Sunset</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Greensboro</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21639</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.805795</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.973802</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>222</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Main</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Sudlersville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21668</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.852752</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.187793</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>739</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7778</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/06/2018 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>743</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0838</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/04/2014 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6758</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 00:09:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6758</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 00:09:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6758</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/28/2023 00:08:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6758</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 00:08:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>