<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002660</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/22/2023 01:52:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/22/2023 01:52:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/22/2023 01:06:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/22/2023 01:06:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 01:52:28</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4913</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 13:35:15</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I97 NB,MILLERSVILLE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>681366</AddressId>
      <City>MDC479</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 01:52:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 04:32:32</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>681366</AddressId>
         <StreetName>N/B I-97</StreetName>
         <City>Millersville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21108</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RTE</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.63818</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.069346</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/22/2023 01:52:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/22/2023 01:52:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/23/2023 04:19:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 01:52:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:23:05</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Incident recorded on J-6s in-car-camera and Body-worn camera. DUI NARRATIVE Nathaniel Hitch 7051  DUI INFORMATION Defendant:RODRIGUEZ MILLA, GLORIA XIOMARA Date of Birth: 09/17/1981 License Number: MD - R362282928721 Date of Arrest: 01/22/2023 CC#: 22-MSP-002660 (Annapolis Barrack) Time of arrest: 0150 hours.  Training and Awards Recipient of the Maryland Highway Safety Offices DUI award for 2021. Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Trained in administering the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Trained in A.R.I.D.E. (Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Attended the MSP Enhanced DUI class provided through the Maryland State Police SPIDRE Team. Attendee of the 2022 Ocean City DUI conference.  Vehicle in Motion (Phase 1)  On 01/22/2023 at approximately 0105 hours, I TFC. Hitch # 7051 received a BOLO dispatch through the Glen Burnie barrack for a white SUV bearing a Maryland vehicle registration of 6ER3618 traveling northbound I-97 at the 2 mile marker. The dispatch stated that a separate vehicle had called the Barrack and advised that the white SUV was unable to drive within a single lane, and was traveling significantly under the speed limit of 65 miles per hour.  I located the vehicle traveling northbound I-97 at Route 32 in lane 1. The vehicle was a white Jeep Grand Cherokee bearing the aforementioned registration. I observed the following traffic violations:   The Jeeps front and rear passenger tires crossed over the dotted white line by over two tire widths and straddled the lane line for approximately 5 seconds.   margin-left:8px"&gt;I paced the vehicle at equal distance and equal speed to be traveling approximately 48 miles per hour in the leftmost lane. The Jeep failed to move right while traveling under the posted 65 mile per hour speed limit [TA-21-301-b1].  I activated my emergency lights and siren. The Jeep pressed on its brakes in reaction to my emergency equipment, however, the Jeep did not pull over for approximately 60 seconds. The Jeep moved from lane 1 into lane 2, then continued driving, then slowly moved into lane 3 and repeated, then finally pulled into the ending-entrance ramp lane, and finally stopped halfway on the shoulder, and halfway in the ending-entrance ramp lane. Personal Contact (Phase 2)  I made contact with the operator and front-seat passenger of the Jeep. The driver was later identified by her Maryland drivers license as RODRIGUEZ MILLA, GLORIA XIOMARA (MD - R362282928721; DOB - 09/17/1981; Hispanic Female). The front seat passenger was later identified by his Maryland drivers license as MEJIA BACILA, ANGEL IVAN (MD - M212067347366; DOB - 05/14/1985; Hispanic Male).  Immediately upon approaching the vehicle I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I advised the occupants of the reason for the traffic stop and asked if they were doing okay. Mejia Bacila responded that they were doing well. However, Rodriguez Milla did not speak during my initial interaction with her. As I interacted with Rodriguez Milla, I observed that her eyes were bloodshot and watery and she moved slowly while obtaining her drivers license and vehicle registration.  I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine MVA/METERS checks. At that time, Tpr. Fuller #7354 arrived on scene, and I requested he remain on scene to assist me.  I returned to Rodriguez Millas vehicle and requested she step out of her car. Rodriguez Milla did not respond, and remained in her vehicle. I asked Rodriguez Milla two more times before she stepped out of her car. I asked Rodriguez Milla to walk to the front of her vehicle. As Rodriguez Milla walked to the front of her vehicle, the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanated from her person. Rodriguez Milla also walked slowly.  Once in front of Rodriguez Millas vehicle, I advised her that I had detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her person and I asked her how much she had to drink that night. Rodriguez Milla did not respond and looked back of Mejia Bacila instead. Rodriguez Milla walked to the passenger side of the vehicle and began speaking to Mejia Bacila in Spanish. I asked Mejia Bacila if she needed a Spanish interpreter, at which time Mejia Bacila said yes.  I contacted the Annapolis barrack Duty Officer (Sgt. Gerber #5226) and requested a Spanish speaking officer arrive on scene to assist.  I then separated Rodriguez Milla from Mejia Bacila again and began to use my cell phones google translation to speak with Rodriguez Milla while I waited for a Spanish speaking officer.  Using the translation application I advised Rodriguez Milla that I had smelled the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her, and I asked Rodriguez Milla how much did she have to drink tonight that night. Rodriguez Milla raised two fingers to denote two drinks. I then asked her how long ago she had drank, she raised two fingers again for two hours. I then asked Rodriguez Milla what she had to drink, she responded whiskey. When Rodriguez Milla spoke, the odor of an alcohol beverage emanated off her breath as well as person.  Due to the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Rodriguez Millas breath and person, her admission to drinking, and the nature of her driving, I suspected that Rodriguez Milla was driving under the influence of an intoxicating substance. Using my cell phone for translation, I requested that Rodriguez Milla perform the Standardized Field Sobriety tests to ensure she was sober to drive. Rodriguez Milla submitted to the tests.  Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3) The evaluation was performed in front of Rodriguez Millas vehicle. The roadway was lit by my flashlight and my vehicles front facing lights. The evaluation was performed on a dry and level surface. My front-facing emergency lights were deactivated for the duration of the field sobriety testing. I asked Rodriguez Milla the basic medical questions as they relate to the Standardized Field Sobriety Test twice. The first time using my cell phone with google translate, and the second time with the translation of Cpl. Morales. Rodriguez Millas answers from the second instance are located below: Are you wearing contacts  No. Do you have any head, neck, back, or leg injuries  No. Do you take any medications  Naproxen and pills for Diabetes. Do you have any medical issues I need to be aware of  Migraines and Diabetes.  The weather conditions were cold and dry. Rodriguez Milla appeared to be in good physical condition.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6) The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Rodriguez Millas pupils were equal in size and no resting Nystagmus was observed. I observed equal tracking in both eyes. Rodriguez Milla advised she was able to see my finger as a stimulus. Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus  Observed in both eyes.   After the completion of the HGN test, I advised Rodriguez Milla that we would continue the test when a Spanish speaking officer arrived on scene. We waited on scene until Cpl. Morales #2264 of the Anne Arundel County Police Department arrived on scene to translate. I reiterated the medical questions as stated above. Walk and Turn (5/8 clues observed)  The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual with Cpl. Morales as a translator. Rodriguez Milla affirmed that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Phase:  Broke from instructional phase. First 9 Steps:  Incorrect number of steps: 8  Stopped test at step 8 to ask questions. Turn:  Improper turn. Used her back foot to pivot instead of lead foot as demonstrated. Second 9 Steps  Stepped off line on step 1.  One Leg Stand (0/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Rodriguez Milla affirmed that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Rodriguez Milla raised her left leg. Rodriguez Millas results are as follows: First 10 seconds  Nothing to report Second 10 seconds  Nothing to report Third 10 seconds Nothing to report  PBT Test  0.095 BrAC.  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Rodriguez Milla was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol. *My observations of Rodriguez Millas driving. *Odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. *Bloodshot eyes. *Admission to drinking. *Observed signs of impairment based off SFST results.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: 0151 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULTS: Refused.  CHARGES Charges are attached to report.   Rodriguez Milla was placed under arrest at approximately 0150 hours. Rodriguez Milla was transported to the Annapolis Barrack. Cpl. Morales responded to the Barrack to assist further. While at the barrack, Rodriguez Millawas read a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights using the online DR-15 Spanish recording. Rodriguez Milla advised she understood her rights and refused the intoximeter test. Rodriguez Milla was charged with driving Under the Influence of Alcohol under citation number 24W0VP2. Rodriguez Milla was released to a sober driver (MORENO REYES, JULIO SANTOS; MD - MD10272460122) at 0320 hours.  All events occurred in Anne Arundel County Maryland.  Case Closed by Arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 04:29:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 04:10:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fuller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hitch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathaniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7051</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gerber</LastName>
            <FirstName>Elix</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5226</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hitch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathaniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7051</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hitch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathaniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7051</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492043</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/22/2023 01:50:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 04:27:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 04:37:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>41</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 04:27:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:12</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366855</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Rodriguez Milla</LastName>
               <FirstName>Gloria</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Xiomara</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/17/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 04:20:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R362</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G460</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Rodriguez Milla</LastName>
               <FirstName>Gloria</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Xiomara</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/17/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R362</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G460</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 04:20:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3229</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Leverton</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21224</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2225</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.570321</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.291742</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>527</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3500</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>683</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6269</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 04:38:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 04:38:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 04:38:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 04:32:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 04:32:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148925</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/22/2023 04:45:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 04:45:21</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C4RJECG9JC407096</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2018</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>GCH</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>LL</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6ER3618</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>8</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>