<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-007272</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/26/2023 00:29:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/26/2023 00:29:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/26/2023 00:08:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/26/2023 00:08:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/26/2023 00:29:10</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 10:14:37</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>BROADVIEW AVE/ BEL AIR RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>685512</AddressId>
      <City>MDC107</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/26/2023 00:29:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/28/2023 03:09:49</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>685512</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Broadview</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Bel Air</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.36381</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.51748</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 BROADVIEW AVE / 820-899 BEL AIR RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/26/2023 00:29:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/26/2023 00:29:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/08/2023 06:45:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/26/2023 00:29:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:52:55</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The incident was audibly and visually recorded from my B.W.C. M.S.P. unmarked unit D-24 is equipped with M.V.R. equipment. DEFENDANT: NATHAN THOMAS GARRISON Date of Birth: 03/22/1992 (30 years old) Date of Arrest: 02/26/2023 Time of Arrest: 0028 hours D.U.I. #: 23-055 (Bel Air Barrack, Harford County) Subsequent Offender: No Minor in the vehicle: No MI-DL. # MD-10273703327 CDL: No Certificate and Training: *I am a certified police officer in the state of Maryland with over 40 hours of training in D.U.I. detection with participants at the Maryland State Police Academy and prior DUI/DWI arrests and convictions. *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *RADAR / LIDAR Certified 2019. *Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator Certified. *Advance Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement Certified (A.R.I.D.E.): Attended A.R.I.D.E. with the Maryland State Police in January 2021 *UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND DUI INSTITUTE: I attended the University of Maryland D.U.I. Institute and I completed the course with over 40 hours of training in D.U.I. detection with live participants (From June 5 to June 10, 2022) *Certified as S.F.S.T. witness expert by Honorable Judge Martin H. Schreiber II in Baltimore City Circuit Court on September 27, 2022. *Certified S.F.S.T. witness expert by Honorable Judge David E. Carey in Harford County District Court on October 11, 2022. *I have apprehended more than 160 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On February 26, 2023, at approximately 0008 hours, I, Trooper First Class Reckeweg # 7214 of the Maryland State Police currently assigned to the Bel Air Barrack (unmarked M.S.P. patrol vehicle D-24), was traveling on Southbound Route 1 north of Tollgate Road. At that time, I observed ahead of my patrol vehicle a black Audi Coupe in lane 2. The Audi appeared to be traveling above the posted speed limit of 45mph. I accelerated my patrol vehicle to 55mph, attempting to pace the Audi, but the Audi was pulling away from my patrol vehicle at some speed greater than 55mph. I then activated my in-car moving radar system (Golden Eagle II) and selected the front radar dish for speed acquisition. My radar system registered a continuous radar tone and speed reading of 65mph, while there was only one vehicle (the Audi) in front of my patrol vehicle within the operating range of my radar system. The radar tone and radar speed matched my visual speed estimate of the Audi. I pulled behind the Audi, and a traffic stop was initiated as I activated my emergency equipment. The Audi stopped in lane one (1) on Broadview Avenue at Route 1, Bel Air, Harford County. I then observed the Audi bearing North Carolina registration RED3366. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Audi via the drivers side window, made contact with the driver, and explained to the driver the reason for the traffic stop. I also observed a front passenger inside the Audi, whom I later identified as Lentz, Katherine L (W/F DOB 02/15/1993). I asked the driver for his drivers license. The driver was identified as GARRISON, NATHAN THOMAS (W/M, D.O.B. 03/22/1992, Maryland Soundex MD-10273703327) by his Maryland drivers license. I asked GARRISON where he was coming from and where he was going. GARRISON advised that he was coming from a restaurant and was going home. While talking to GARRISON, I instantly noticed his eyes were glassy and bloodshot. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from inside the Audi. GARRISONs speech was slurred. I asked GARRISON how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed that evening, and he stated, I had four (4) small drinks 2-3 hours ago. I asked GARRISON to exit and walk to the front of my patrol vehicle. At the front of my patrol vehicle, I could now detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on GARRISONs breath and person. I observed GARRISON having difficulty keeping his balance as he swayed from left to right. I advised GARRISON that I would perform standardized field sobriety tests on him, which he agreed to submit. The summary of the first contact is as follows: Attitude: Cooperative Eye Condition: Glassy/bloodshot Mental State: Normal. Walk: Normal. Speech: Slurred. I asked GARRISON the following questions: Medication- Yes (Medical marijuana, smoked at least 24 hours ago) Medical Conditions- Yes (P.T.S.D. and depression) Glasses: No (No wearing contacts) Any pain in the body- No. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The below standardized field sobriety tests were performed in lane one (1) on the roadway. That area of the road was level and free of debris. Before beginning the below standardized field sobriety tests, I turned off my front emergency lights. The weather conditions were clear. Lighting conditions included street lights, patrol vehicle headlights, and flashlights. GARRISON appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible signs of injury. I explained and demonstrated each of the below standardized field sobriety tests to GARRISON. GARRISON stated he understood my instructions and had no questions about the standardized field sobriety test. -HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (H.G.N.) / (6/6 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: YES)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my index finger from my right hand was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from GARRISONs eyes, slightly above his eyebrows. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. GARRISONs pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I observed his eyes to be red. GARRISON was positioned to ensure passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked GARRISON if he understood the instructions, and he stated, Yes. The following clues and observations were made during the test: Lack of Smooth Pursuit- Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation- Present in both eyes The onset of Nystagmus Before 45 Degrees- Present in both eyes Additional test Vertical Gaze Nystagmus- Present in both eyes -WALK AND TURN (W.A.T.) / (5/8 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: Yes) Before GARRISON performed the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. GARRISON was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. GARRISON was instructed and demonstrated to put his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until instructed to begin. GARRISON was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on each step. GARRISON was asked to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count each step out loud. On the ninth step, GARRISON was explained, and I demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and planted and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around to his left. GARRISON was again explained, and I demonstrated that the second series of nine (9) steps were to be completed identically to the first. Keep his hands by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. I asked GARRISON if he understood the test. GARRISON stated, Yes. GARRISON was instructed to begin the test. Instructional Stage: Cannot Keep Balance: GARRISON could not keep balance as he placed his right foot in front of his left foot, and his feet broke apart. GARRISON started before instructed Walking Stage (1st Nine) GARRISON stepped offline on steps 1 and 9. GARRISON missed heel to toe by approximately 2 inches on steps 2, 3, 5 and 8 Walking Stage (2nd nine): GARRISON stepped offline on steps 3 and 7 GARRISON missed heel to toe by approximately 2 inches on steps 2, 3 and 5 Turn:  Completed Unsatisfactory. GARRISON did not leave his front foot planted and used both feet to walk in a circle. -ONE LEG STAND (O.L.S.) (LEFT LEG) (2/4 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: Yes) Before GARRISON performed the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. GARRISON was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given during the test. GARRISON was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to watch his raised foot and count out loud by thousands (thousand-one, thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked GARRISON if he had any questions about the test (O.L.S.) which he replied, no. GARRISON raised his left foot. Instructional Stage: Nothing to report. Balance and Count Stage: 1. Hopping: GARRISON hopped on the 2-second mark. 2. Puts foot down: GARRISON puts her foot down on the 03 and 26-second mark -PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT) (REFUSED)- The final test offered to GARRISON was the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT). GARRISON was advised that he could refuse this test. GARRISON refused to submit to the PBT. ARREST Based on my knowledge, training, and experience as an Maryland State Police Trooper, previous driving under the influence arrests, and clues gathered thus far, I had reason to believe GARRISON was driving a motor vehicle while impaired (under the influence of Alcohol). *Driving over the posted speed limit of 65/45MPH *Physical control of a motor vehicle *Admission of consumption of alcoholic beverage *Odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person *Bloodshot eyes *Slurred speech *Watery eyes * My observed signs of impairment as he performed standardized field sobriety test. ARREST / ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) / CERTIFIED BREATH TEST (REFUSED)/ SGT. SANDER # 5429 (Maryland State Police). I arrested GARRISON for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0028 hours. GARRISON was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to Maryland State Police Bel Air-Barrack for processing, where a mouth check was performed 20 minutes before his submission to the breath test. GARRISON was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along with as the DR-15 advice of rights was played to him from the official M.V.A. website. At the conclusion of the DR-15, GARRISON refused to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the DR-15, indicating the same at approximately 0055 hours. GARRISON was given all copies of pertinent paperwork, and GARRISON was released to a sober adult that came to Bel Air Barrack. INTOXIMETER RESULT: Refused GARRISON was cooperative during the processing. Case Status  Closed by arrest. All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 03:06:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 12:11:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Atkinson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5623</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496669</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/26/2023 00:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 03:08:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/28/2023 03:10:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>30</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 03:08:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:31</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370155</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Garrison</LastName>
               <FirstName>NATHAN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>THOMAS</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/22/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/26/2023 03:00:01</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N350</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Garrison</LastName>
               <FirstName>NATHAN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>THOMAS</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/22/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N350</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/26/2023 03:00:01</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 03:11:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 03:11:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 03:11:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 03:08:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/28/2023 03:08:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150281</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/28/2023 03:12:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/28/2023 03:12:40</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WAUCGAFR5FA029224</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>AUDI</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>NC</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>KED3366</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>