<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-028561</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/13/2023 00:10:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/13/2023 00:10:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/12/2023 23:52:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/12/2023 23:52:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI / DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 00:10:39</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 01:19:23</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>9613 LIBERTY,RANDALLSTOWN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>703743</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 00:10:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:00:39</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>703743</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>9613</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Liberty Randallstown</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.815622</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.3769081666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/13/2023 00:10:35</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/13/2023 00:10:35</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/20/2023 01:24:16</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 00:10:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:04:55</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>R-29 equipped with in-car camera and body-worn camera. Contact Sgt. Twardowski (joseph.twardowski@maryland.gov) for camera footage.  Case# 23-MSP-028561 Defendant: Tierra Danae Cotton Date of Birth: 04/05/1990  Date of Arrest: 08/13/2023 Time of Arrest: 0008 hours DUI #: 23-427 Citation #: 5D80XD0 Breath Result: Refused   Certificates and Training *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration  *Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) Certified  *Certified Emergency Medical Technician by the Maryland Institute of Emergency Medical Services Systems  *Certified RADAR/LIDAR operator by the Maryland State Police  *Certified License Plate Reader (LPR) operator by the Maryland State Police  *Apprehended over 150 impaired drivers while working as a Maryland State Trooper  *2023 Distinguished graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute  Vehicle In Motion (Phase 1)  On August 12th, 2023 at approximately 2352 hours I, Trooper Sigman #7376, currently assigned to the Golden Ring Barrack, was on routine patrol of W/B Liberty Road prior to Owings Mills Boulevard when I observed a Gray Honda HRV bearing Maryland registration of 4DF9711 traveling in lane 1. I observed that the Honda was unable to maintain a single lane of travel and slowly drifted into lane 2 with both passenger side tires. The Honda then slowly drifted back into lane 1 then crossed over the solid double yellow line with both drivers side tires into oncoming traffic. The Honda then returned to lane 1 but again drifted both into lane 2 and the center turn lane as it was unable to maintain a single lane of travel. The Honda then approached the traffic signal at Liberty Road and Owings Mills Boulevard. The Honda then entered the dedicated turn lane to make a left at the light. The Honda then stopped at the solid red arrow. After sitting stationary at the red arrow, the Honda then accelerated into the intersection and continued traveling W/B on Liberty Road from the dedicated left turn lane. I then activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the Gray Honda HRV bearing Maryland registration of 4DF9711. The Honda then slowly pulled to the right shoulder.  Personal Contact (Phase 2)  I then made a drivers side approach of the Gray Honda HRV bearing Maryland registration of 4DF9711. I then identified myself, the reason for the stop, and requested the drivers license. Upon arriving at the drivers side window I could immediately detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I also observed that the driver had bloodshot glassy eyes as well as slurred speech. The driver advised that she was trying to follow somebody. While following her vehicle I did not observe any other vehicles that she appeared to be following. The driver then began to search around her vehicle. While searching I observed that her motor movements were uncoordinated. She then handed me her US passport which identified her as Tierra Danae Cotton (05/05/1990). Cotton stated that her wallet containing her license had been stolen. I then asked Cotton how many alcoholic beverages she had consumed prior to driving. Cotton replied one and advised that she had been drinking Jack Daniels. Cotton advised that her last alcoholic beverage was a half hour ago.  I then asked Cotton to exit and walk to the front of her vehicle. While stepping out I observed that Cotton displayed gait ataxia and had difficulty balancing. Cotton then advised that she was driving to around the corner. Cotton stated that she was driving from the lounge and was driving to a friends house. I then asked Cotton how many alcoholic beverages she had consumed prior to driving. Cotton then changed her answer to two. I then asked Cotton if she would submit to standardized field sobriety testing. Cotton agreed.  Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3)  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of Liberty Road. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 74 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlights, and overhead lights, and my vehicles takedown lights. My vehicles front facing emergency lights were deactivated for the duration of the field sobriety tests. Cotton appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries and or defects.  I asked Cotton the following questions:  Injuries- none Medical conditions- none Medications- none Glasses or contacts- none Alcoholic beverages- two drinks of Jack Controlled dangerous substance- denied    Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The test was explained. I then began the test. I did not observe any resting nystagmus. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit - present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - present in both eyes *Vertical Gaze Nystagmus - present in both eyes  During the test Cotton had to be reminded to follow the stimulus. Cotton was attempting to guess where the stimulus was going to be instead of following it as I moved it.     Walk and Turn (5/8 clues observed)  Prior to Cotton performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. I asked Cotton if she had any questions. Cotton stated that she understood the test.    Instructional Stage: Steps out of the starting position. While standing in the starting position Cotton advised me that she normally does not walk straight. I advised Cotton that the instructions were to walk on the imaginary straight line.   Walking Stage (1st Nine):  Steps off line on every step Misses heel to toe on every step Stops walking    Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  Misses heel to toe on every step Steps off line on every step      Turn: Incorrect, turns counterclockwise in one jerky uncoordinated motion  One Leg Stand (3/4)  Prior to Cotton performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Cotton advised that she understood the test.  Instructional Stage: Sways from side to side     Balance and Count Stage  Seconds 0-10: Sways from side to side Raises arms for balance Puts foot down      Seconds 11-20: Sways from side to side Raises arms for balance Puts foot down      Seconds 21-30: Sways from side to side Raises arms for balance Puts foot down    I then offered my PBT to Cotton . Cotton agreed and the results were .11 on serial #218942  Arrest  Based on the following, I had probable cause to believe Cotton was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  *Unable to maintain a single lane of travel *Failure to stop at steady red arrow *Going straight through an intersection while in a dedicated turn lane *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on her breath and person *Glassy eyes *Admission to consuming multiple alcoholic beverages *slurred speech *Gait ataxia *Poor SFST     At this time Cotton was placed under arrest for DUI. Cotton was then handcuffed, searched, and placed in the front seat of R-29 and seat belted inside. Cotton was then transported to the Baltimore County Police Woodlawn Precinct.  Once at the precinct Cotton was handed a physical DR15 and the audio version was played aloud. Cotton stated that she could read the DR15 and was able to understand it. At the conclusion of the audio Cotton stated that she did not wish to take the intoximeter test. The time of the refusal was 0041 hours  20-Minute Observation Period:  N/A     Intoximeter Result:  N/A  Cotton was then issued the appropriate citations as well as a DR15A. Cotton was then released to her husband in the front parking lot of the Woodlawn Precinct.  All above events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 11:09:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 11:13:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wilson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4772</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sigman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7376</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518006</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518006</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518006</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518006</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518006</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15566</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15566</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518006</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518006</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518006</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518006</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15561</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15561</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518006</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 23:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:05:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:05:28</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>385009</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>COTTON</LastName>
               <FirstName>TIERRA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>DANAE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/05/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/13/2023 01:04:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C350</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>COTTON</LastName>
               <FirstName>TIERRA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>DANAE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/05/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C350</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/13/2023 01:04:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6510</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Woodgreen</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Lochearn</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21207</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5587</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.727536</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.332043</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:05:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:05:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:05:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:05:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:02:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156079</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/13/2023 01:12:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/13/2023 01:12:49</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3CZRU6H5XJG707631</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2018</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>HR-V</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4DF9711</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>