<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-033520</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/23/2023 23:37:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/23/2023 23:37:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/23/2023 23:04:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/23/2023 23:04:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI Traffic Arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 23:37:50</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 11:35:04</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>576954</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:23:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 05:24:01</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>576954</AddressId>
         <StreetName>N/B MD RT 3 @ MD RT 450</StreetName>
         <City>Bowie</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20715</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.709027</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.985715</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/23/2023 23:37:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/23/2023 23:37:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/01/2023 03:58:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 23:37:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP unmarked vehicle Q-41 is equipped with a mobile recording device. Body Worn Camera worn and operational.    Defendant: Rebecca Beth Christenson  Date of Birth: 01/09/1991  Date of Arrest: 09/23/2023  Time of Arrest: 2336 hours  DUI #: 23-215  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  (PHASE 1) On Saturday, September 23, 2023, at approximately 2304 hours, I, Trooper Webb of the Maryland State Police  College Barrack was on routine patrol in my unmarked MSP vehicle Q-41. At this time, I was dispatched to a two vehicle collision in the area of Route 3 and Maryland 450.Once on scene I observed a white Nissan Altima with rear end damage and a gray 2018 Lincoln MKZ bearing Maryland registration 8FF0132, with front end damage pulled off the roadway into a gas station parking lot. Both vehicle operators were standing outside their vehicles.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the driver of the gray Lincoln MKZ at the front of her vehicle where she was standing and noticed that she had glassy, bloodshot eyes. I advised the driver of my: rank, name, ID number, agency and that the stop was being audibly/visually recorded. I asked the driver what happened tonight, and she stated, I did not stop my vehicle in time and hit the car in front of me. I requested her drivers license and registration card. I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her person and breath. Her movements were slow and lethargic. I identified her by her Maryland drivers license as Rebecca Beth Christenson. I asked Christenson where she was coming from, and she replied, Fat Boys Crab House. I then asked how much she had to drink, and she replied Two beers. I walked back to my vehicle and conducted routine MVA checks on Christenson and her vehicle. I continued to speak with Christenson outside her vehicle and as Christenson spoke, I continued to smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. I informed Christenson that I wanted her to perform field sobriety tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed out of the roadway in a parking lot. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 60 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlamps, patrol vehicle headlamps, spotlight, and my flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Christenson appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries.  I asked Christenson the following questions: Injuries  No Medication  No Medical Conditions  No Glasses  No  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pointer finger was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Christensons eyes. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Christensons pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking and no resting Nystagmus was observed. She was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Christenson if she understood the instructions, and she stated yes.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes  WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed) Prior to Christenson performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Christenson was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Christenson was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Christenson was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Christenson was to keep her hands flat at her side, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Christenson was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Christenson was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Christenson was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her side, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Christenson if she understood the instructions, and she stated yes.  Instructional Stage: 1.) Nothing to report.  Walking Stage (1st Nine): 1.) Missed heel to toe on step 2. 2.) Stepped off line on step 2. 3.) Used arms for balance. Her arms were more than 6 inches from her sides.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): 1.) Missed heel to toe on steps 4, and 6. 2.) Stepped off line on step 4, and 6. 3.) Used arms for balance. Her arms were more than 6 inches from her sides.  Turn: 1.) Improper  Christenson turned in one fluid motion and then stumbled backwards.  ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)  Prior to Christenson performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Christenson was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Christenson if she understood the instructions, and she stated yes.   Instructional Stage:  1.) Nothing to report  Balance and Count Stage:   Seconds 0-10:  1.) Puts her foot down.  2.) Used arms for balance. Christensons arms were more than 6 inches from her sides.  Seconds 11-20: 1.) Used arms for balance. Christensons arms were more than 6 inches from her sides.  Seconds 21-30:  1.) Put her foot down.  2.) Used arms for balance. Christensons arms were more than 6 inches from her sides.  Christenson submitted to a preliminary breath test with a .21 BrAC result.  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Christenson was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle. * Slow and lethargic head and body movements. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot with a gazed look. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. * My observed signs of impairment as she performed field sobriety tests.  I arrested Christenson for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0205 hours. She was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. Christenson was transported to the Maryland State Police  College Park Barrack for processing. Once inside the barrack, at 0015 hours I played the English audio DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Christenson in its entirety. She was given a paper copy to read along. At the conclusion of the form, Christenson verbally advised that she would submit breath samples for the intoximeter test and signed the form indicating the same.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the observation period on Christenson in its entirety starting with her time of arrest. I escorted Christenson into the arrest processing room and remained in her custody until the time of test. Christensons mouth was checked and no foreign objects or piercings were observed.  INTOXIMETER RESULT:  The intoximeter test was administered within the two hour statutory time frame. This test was administered by a certified breath technician on equipment approved by the Chief Toxicologist in the Department of State Police Forensic Science Division.   .14 BrAC PER 210 LITERS OF BREATH  Christenson was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to her girlfriend at 0115 hours. Christenson was polite and cooperative throughout the process.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 03:50:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 15:59:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bowling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Caleb</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7419</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dunlap</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6273</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Webb</LastName>
            <FirstName>Noah</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7303</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/23/2023 23:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/23/2023 23:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/23/2023 23:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/23/2023 23:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/23/2023 23:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/23/2023 23:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/23/2023 23:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15654</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/23/2023 23:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15654</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:27:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 05:27:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388599</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Christenson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Rebecca</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/09/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/24/2023 04:58:56</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C623</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R120</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Christenson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Rebecca</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/09/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C623</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R120</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/24/2023 04:58:56</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>BALDWIN CT APT H</StreetName>
               <SubNumber>h</SubNumber>
               <City>Catonsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21228</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.7594</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.281333</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:27:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:27:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:27:47</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 05:25:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157394</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 05:28:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 05:28:25</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>LINC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MKZ</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8FF0132 </VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>