<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-030179</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/27/2023 00:46:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/27/2023 00:46:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/27/2023 00:31:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/27/2023 00:31:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 00:46:11</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 15:06:37</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>705100</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 00:46:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 03:06:20</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>705100</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>21043</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Garrett</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Oakland</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-79.328865</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.519175</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/27/2023 00:46:09</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/27/2023 00:46:09</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/01/2023 09:10:46</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 00:46:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>* This stop was captured on my agency issued body worn camera and in car camera systems   Training and Certifications  -NHTSA certified to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Testing-November 2014 -Preliminary Breath Test operator certified-November 2014 -Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE)-March 2-3, 2016 -SPIDRE Enhanced DUI Training-March 9, 2016    Assignment  On August 27, 2023, at approximately 0031 hours, I was conducting roving traffic enforcement in the area of 21043 Garrett Highway, Oakland, Garrett County, Maryland. I was on duty, in uniform operating my assigned unmarked patrol vehicle W-4.   Vehicle in Motion (Phase I)   I observed a white Chevrolet Silverado, bearing Pennsylvania registration ZWH6234, traveling northbound. I was directly behind the vehicle. The vehicle crossed over the solid white fog line, and was driving on the shoulder of the roadway, at a slow speed. The vehicle then veered back into the northbound lane and accelerated quickly, but then would slow back down, veering back across the solid white fog line. As the vehicle continued northbound, it quickly accelerated and then slowed back down. The vehicle could not maintain a constant speed. The vehicle then slowed down, almost to a stop, in the lane of travel. The vehicle quickly accelerated again, then crossed the solid white fog line by approximately half the vehicles width. The vehicle veered back over into the lane of travel and accelerated once again. Again, the vehicle crossed over the solid white fog line. Prior to stopping the vehicle, I observed several pedestrians walking along the shoulder of the roadway throughout the early morning hours and late hours of the previous evening. Based on the erratic driving behavior of the vehicle, I activated my emergency equipment to initiate a traffic stop. The vehicle stopped on the right shoulder of the roadway.   Personal Contact (Phase II)   I conducted a drivers side approach and made contact with the driver, Keegan Leroy Horstman, who was later identified by his Michigan drivers license. I introduced myself and stated the reason for the traffic stop. I observed Horstmans eyes to be red and bloodshot. Horstmans speech was slurred, and his physical actions appeared sluggish. Horstman struggled to retrieve his drivers license and registration card, and attempted to hand me a Pokmon card instead of the documents I requested. Horstman was able to obtain his drivers license eventually, but did not retrieve the vehicles registration card. I observed Horstman to have a bottle of water in his hands. The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanated from inside the vehicle. Horstman advised he was coming from the Green Turtle. Horstman was traveling the wrong direction to be coming from the Green Turtle, as the Green Turtle was located north of his location, and he was traveling northbound. Horstman commented wanna just arrest me? and he was more than under the influence.    Based on these observations, I asked Horstman to step out of the vehicle, to which he complied. Horstman exited the vehicle, and I asked him to step in front of his vehicle. While outside of the vehicle, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Horstmans breath and person.   Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase III)   Horstman was not wearing contacts or glasses. Horstman stated he did not have any physical disabilities. Horstman stated he has Type I Diabetes. Horstman was placed on a flat, dry, debris free asphalt surface. The weather was overcast and warm. While conducting HGN, Horstman stated I am drunk and Im not gonna lie to you. Horstman advised he consumed six full beers.   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus   Horstman displayed equal pupil size and equal tracking. I did not observe resting nystagmus.     I observed the following clues of HGN:   Lack of smooth pursuit-present in both eyes   Distinct and sustained nystagmus a maximum deviation-present in both eyes   Onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees-present in both eyes   Total clues observed: 6/6   Walk and Turn    I attempted to place Horstman into the instructional phase of the test, prior to demonstrating the walk and turn test to him. I then demonstrated the test to Horstman. Horstman initially advised he could not perform the test, but then attempted it. Horstman was unable to maintain balance in the instructional phase. I observed Horstman take 4 steps forward, stop, then turn right, taking 4 additional steps. I instructed Horstman to stop walking forward, as he was going to walk into the guardrail.   The following clues were observed of the walk and turn:   Instructional phase: Cannot keep balance   First nine steps: missed heel to toe, steps off-line, incorrect number of steps   Second nine steps: missed heel to toe, steps off-line, incorrect number of steps   Turn: completed unsatisfactorily   Total clues observed: 6/8   One Leg Stand    I demonstrated the one leg stand to Horstman. As I demonstrated the test to Horstman, Horstman lost his balance and stumbled backwards.Horstman refused to complete the one leg stand test.   Preliminary Breath Test      I offered the Horstman the PBT to which he refused.   Action Taken   Prior to me taking Horstman into custody, Horstman stated Would you like me to put my hands behind my back? Horstman was placed into custody at 0045 hours.   Horstmans vehicle was secured on the shoulder of the roadway. I transported Horstman to the Maryland State Police McHenry Barrack for processing.   During transport, Horstman fell asleep and slumped over. At the barrack, Cpl. Davis assisted me to awaken Horstman and help him exit the vehicle. Horstman struggled to exit the vehicle.   Inside the barrack, Horstman stated that he was drunk on multiple occasions.    I read Horstman his DR-15 Advice of Rights, to which he initially stated he would submit to the intoximeter test. Horstman struggled to sign the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Horstman then vomited all over the floor, desk, and chair in the barracks DUI room.   Based on his high level of intoxication, EMS was requested to check Horstman. EMS responded to the barrack to check Horstman. Horstman refused medical treatment, signing a refusal form.   Horstman was unable to complete the intoximeter after vomiting profusely, was determined he would not be able to follow through with the breath sample.   I completed a DR-15A, to which he struggled to sign.    Horstman was temporarily placed inside the holding cell, until myself and Cpl. Davis cleaned the vomit from inside the room. While in the holding cell, Horstman fell asleep.   Horstman was provided copies of his citations, DR-15, and DR-15A.   A sober ride responded to the barrack, to which Horstman was released.   Case closed by arrest.   All events occurred in Garrett County, Maryland.      </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6274</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 03:11:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6274</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/01/2023 09:06:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ervin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Darian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bond</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0200</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ervin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Darian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ervin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Darian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519628</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/27/2023 03:07:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6274</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 03:07:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6274</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 03:08:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519628</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/27/2023 03:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6274</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 03:07:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6274</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 03:09:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6274</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 03:07:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6274</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 03:09:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386246</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Horstman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Keegan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leroy</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/23/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/27/2023 02:58:01</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H623</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Horstman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Keegan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Leroy</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/23/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H623</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/27/2023 02:58:01</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>206</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Barry</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Haslett</City>
               <StateCode>MI</StateCode>
               <Zip5>48840</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>517</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>410</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4839</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6274</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 03:09:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6274</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 03:09:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6274</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 03:07:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6274</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 03:07:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>