<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-028521</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/12/2023 16:34:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/12/2023 16:34:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/12/2023 15:53:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/12/2023 15:53:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI / DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:34:53</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/23/2023 12:27:56</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I695 / SOUTHWESTERN BLVD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>584127</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:34:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:46:38</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>584127</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I695</StreetName>
         <City>Halethorpe</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>BLVD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.69142</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.25106</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L I-695 @ SOUTHWESTERN BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L BETWEEN EXITS 11 AND 12</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 4900-4999 SOUTHWESTERN BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 4601-4601 SOUTHWESTERN BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L I-695 AT SOUTHWESTERN BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L BETWEEEN EXIT 11 AND 12   SOUTHWESTERN BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 0-0 SOUTHWESTERN BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L BY SOUTHWESTERN BLVD   LEFT SHOULDER</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OUTER LOOP //SOUTHWESTERN BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/12/2023 16:34:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/12/2023 16:34:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/20/2023 01:57:04</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:34:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:04:54</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>R-29 equipped with in-car camera and body-worn camera. Contact Sgt. Twardowski (joseph.twardowski@maryland.gov) for camera footage.  Case# 23-MSP-028521 Defendant: Taylor Njeri Jackson Date of Birth: 12/14/1999  Date of Arrest: 08/12/2023 Time of Arrest: 1605 hours DUI #: 23-425 Citation #: 5C20XD0 Breath Result: .00, refused DRE   Certificates and Training *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration  *Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) Certified  *Certified Emergency Medical Technician by the Maryland Institute of Emergency Medical Services Systems  *Certified RADAR/LIDAR operator by the Maryland State Police  *Certified License Plate Reader (LPR) operator by the Maryland State Police  *Apprehended over 125 impaired drivers while working as a Maryland State Trooper  *2023 Distinguished graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute  Vehicle In Motion (Phase 1)  On August 12th, 2023 at approximately 1553 hours I, Trooper Sigman #7376, currently assigned to the Golden Ring Barrack, was on routine patrol of the outer loop of I695 prior to Southwestern Boulevard when I observed a green Honda Accord bearing Maryland registration of 7FJ4479 traveling in lane 1 following the vehicle in front of it within one car length while traveling at highway speeds. I observed that the passenger was smoking what appeared to be a hand rolled cigarette then handed it to the driver who then began to take multiple puffs of the unknown cigarette. I then observed the Honda make a sudden and unsafe lane change from lane 1 all the way across to lane 3 forcing other vehicles to take evasive action to prevent a collision. I then began to pace the Honda while in lane 3 at 70mph in a posted 55mph zone. The Honda continued to accelerate towards other vehicles occupying lane 3 then slammed on the brakes upon getting within one car length almost causing a collision. The Honda then slowly drifted further away from the vehicle in front of it before again accelerating and following at one car length. I then observed the Honda slowly drift from lane 3, into lane 4 with both passenger side tires. The Honda then slowly drifted back into lane 3. I then activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the green Honda Accord bearing Maryland registration of 7FJ4479. The Honda then slammed on its brakes and almost came to a complete stop in lane 5 of I695. The Honda then traveled at 26mph in lane 5 before abruptly crossing onto the right shoulder.  Personal Contact (Phase 2)  I then made a drivers side approach of the green Honda Accord bearing Maryland registration of 7FJ4479. Upon arriving at the drivers side window I immediately detected the strong odor of burnt cannabis emanating from the vehicle. I then identified myself, the reason for the stop, and requested the drivers license. The driver then began to giggle and handed me her wallet stating that she was unable to pull it out. I then asked the driver when the last time she had smoked cannabis was. The driver then began to giggle and said yesterday. I then advised the driver that I could smell burnt cannabis emanating from the vehicle. The driver then stated I mean I was hitting it a little bit. Yeah. Or a lot. I then retrieved the drivers license from her wallet which identified her as Taylor Njeri Jackson (12/14/1999). While speaking with Jackson I observed that she had eyelid tremors as well as bloodshot eyes with large pupils.  I then requested Jackson to exit and walk to the front of her vehicle. Jackson then advised me that she was driving from home to a restaurant in Baltimore City. I then asked Jackson how much cannabis she had consumed while driving. Jackson replied It was literally like two hits then began to laugh. I then asked Jackson if she would submit to standardized field sobriety testing. Jackson agreed.  Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3)  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of I695. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 86 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of normal daylight. My vehicles front facing emergency lights were deactivated for the duration of the field sobriety tests. Jackson appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries and or defects.  I asked Jackson the following questions:  Injuries- none Medical conditions- none Medications- none Glasses or contacts- none Alcoholic beverages- none Controlled dangerous substance- cannabis cigarette    Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (0/6)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The test was explained. I then began the test. I did not observe any resting nystagmus. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit - not present in either eye Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - not present in either eye Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - not present in either eye *Vertical Gaze Nystagmus - not present in either eye  Lack of convergence was observed.     Walk and Turn (7/8 clues observed)  Prior to Jackson performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. I asked Jackson if she had any questions. Jackson stated that she understood the test.    Instructional Stage: Steps out of the starting position to prevent falling over. While falling out of the starting position Jackson stated I dont have that much good balance then began to laugh   Walking Stage (1st Nine):  Steps off line on steps 1, 5, and 9 Misses heel to toe on steps 1, 5, and 9 Stops walking Raises arms for balance Takes 10 steps. (After 10 steps Jackson stopped walking and asked how to continue with the test. I advised Jackson to continue just as I had demonstrated)    Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  Misses heel to toe Steps off line       Turn: Incorrect, moves both feet to turn counterclockwise  One Leg Stand (3/4)  Prior to Jackson performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Jackson advised that she understood the test.  Instructional Stage: Sways from side to side     Balance and Count Stage  Seconds 0-10: Sways from side to side Raises arms for balance      Seconds 11-20: Puts foot down Raises arms for balance Sways from side to side      Seconds 21-30: Sways from side to side Puts foot down  Jackson continued to laugh throughout the test.  Modified Romberg Balance Test  I instructed Jackson to stand with her feet together and arms by her side. Jackson was instructed to close her eyes and estimate the passage of thirty seconds. Jackson was instructed to open her eyes and say done when thirty seconds had passed. Jackson stated that she understood the test.  Jackson estimated thirty seconds had passed in 35 seconds Eyelids tremors were observed    I instructed Jackson to stand with her feet together and arms by her side. I instructed Jackson to extend the index finger of both hands while down at her side. I advised that when I say right Jackson was to lift her right index finger, touch the tip of her nose, then put it back down at her side. Jackson was instructed to do the same with her left index finger when I said Left.. Jackson stated that she understood the test.   Right- Left- misses nose Right- Left- misses nose Left- misses nose Right-      Arrest  Based on the following, I had probable cause to believe Jackson was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of cannabis, a schedule I controlled dangerous substance:  *Unable to maintain a single lane of travel *Unsafe lane change almost colliding with another vehicle *Following other vehicles within one car length while traveling highway speeds *Strong odor of burnt cannabis emanating from the vehicle *Admission to smoking cannabis while driving *Bloodshot eyes *Eyelid tremors *Gait ataxia *Poor SFST     At this time Jackson was placed under arrest for DUI. Jackson was then handcuffed, searched, and placed in the front seat of R-29 and seat belted inside. Jackson was then transported to the Golden Ring Barrack.  Once at the Golden Ring Barrack Jackson was walked inside and placed in the intoximeter room. A physical copy of the DR15 was placed in front of her and the audio version was played aloud. At the conclusion of the audio Jackson stated that she wished to take the intoximeter test. The time was 1651 hours.  20-Minute Observation Period:  Nothing observed     Intoximeter Result:  .00 at 1714 hours. CPL Wilson was the intoximeter operator.  I then asked Jackson if she would submit to a DRE evaluation. Jackson refused the DRE.  Jackson was then issued the appropriate citations. Jackson was then released to her brother in the front parking lot of the Golden Ring Barrack.  All above events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/15/2023 10:27:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 11:08:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wilson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4772</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sigman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7376</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517966</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 15:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517966</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 15:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517966</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 15:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517966</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 15:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517966</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 15:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517966</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15647</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 15:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15647</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517966</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15550</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 15:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15550</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517966</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 15:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517966</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 15:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517966</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>20996</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/12/2023 15:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>20996</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>23</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:51:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:51:03</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>384988</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>JACKSON</LastName>
               <FirstName>TAYLOR</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>NJERI</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/14/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/12/2023 16:50:19</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T460</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>JACKSON</LastName>
               <FirstName>TAYLOR</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>NJERI</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/14/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T460</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/12/2023 16:50:19</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3509</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Seapines</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Randallstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21133</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2447</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.819899</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.368805</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:51:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:51:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:51:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:51:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:48:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156074</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/12/2023 16:56:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/12/2023 16:56:53</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/12/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>J250785631949</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2009</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ACCORD</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRN</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7FJ4479</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>