<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-019847</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/03/2023 03:53:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/03/2023 03:53:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/03/2023 03:31:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/03/2023 03:31:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>THOMAS "R" 23-310</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/03/2023 03:53:39</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/30/2023 11:48:59</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>91 MM I70 EB, WINDSOR MILL</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>696355</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/03/2023 03:53:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/03/2023 23:15:35</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>696355</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>91</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I70 Eb Windsor</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ML</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.77283225</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.3069199666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/03/2023 03:53:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/03/2023 03:53:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/30/2023 11:49:00</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/03/2023 03:53:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E) TEAM* MVR Statement: The following incident was captured on in-car and Body camera. Title: THOMAS R 23-310. ID: 23-MSP-019847 Arrested: Thomas, Raisa Sharone. Certification and training  -Trained in Field Sobriety Test through Maryland State Police Academy.  -Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E)  -Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  - Graduated from The Institute of Advanced Law Enforcement Studies Driving Under the Influence Institute-University of Maryland.  - I have apprehended more than 220 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On June 03, 2023, at approximately 0330 hours, I, TFC. I. Riba Tankari # 7058 with Maryland State Police was traveling inner loop I-695 east of I-70, Baltimore County, Maryland in the I-70 exit lane. My issued patrol vehicle is Maryland State Police marked unit DUI-3. At that time, I observed a white Honda Pilot bearing Maryland registration 3DD8602 traveling inner loop I-695 in lane #3 (right lane) passed my marked patrol vehicle then changed lane from lane #3 into the exit lane in front of my marked patrol vehicle and appeared to be traveling over the posted speed. I followed the Honda and observed the vehicle was unable to stay within a single lane and continued traveling at a high rate of speed. I observed the Honda had swerved from the ramp right lane into the right shoulder by one tire width then swerved into the left ramp lane by almost vehicle width and continued traveling partially between the two lanes before returning into the right ramp lane. I observed the Honda had served from the ramp right lane into the right shoulder by more than one tire width on two separate occasions. I observed the Honda had changed lane into lane #2 (middle lane). I changed lane into lane #2, continued to follow the vehicle, and with my properly functioning patrol vehicle Golden Eagle II radar unit set activated, I obtained a speed reading of 103 in a posted 55 MPH zone. I initiated a traffic stop on the Honda using my emergency equipment. The Honda came to a stop in the area of eastbound I-70 east of Security Blvd, Baltimore County, Maryland on the right shoulder. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the Honda on the driver side and made contact with the driver (the sole occupant) of the vehicle. I introduced myself and explained to her the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver where she was coming from, and the driver stated Baltimore. I asked the driver where she was heading, and she stated home. Prior to my request the driver handed me her drivers license, I then requested registration card. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I observed that the driver had glassy eyes. While speaking with the driver I noticed her speech was slow. I observed her movements were slow and lethargic while retrieving her registration card. The driver was identified through her Maryland drivers license as Thomas, Raisa Sharone. I returned to my patrol vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with. I returned to the Honda and I requested Thomas to exit her vehicle and walk to the front of her vehicle and she complied. I asked Thomas how many alcoholic beverages she had consumed, and she stated she had two (2) shot of Tequila an hour ago. While speaking with Thomas outside her vehicle, I again detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. I asked Thomas to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and she agreed.  The evaluation surface was dry, flat, and free of debris. No surface defects were observed. My patrol flashlight and her vehicle headlights lit the area. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests.Thomas appeared to be in good physical conditions and was wearing sandals which she removed during the test. I asked Thomas the following questions: Medical conditions: Anemia and anxiety. Medications: yes, anemia and anxiety medications. I asked her the last time she took one, and she stated last night. Anything that will prevent you from walking on straight line or standing on one leg: my medicine does, but its ok. Glasses or contact: No glasses but was wearing contacts. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: (6/6 clues observed). The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus - Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes - Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes - Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Notes: * During the HGN test, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Thomas breath. WALK AND TURN: (5/8 clues observed). The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Thomas stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage: Thomas lost her balance to the right on three separate occasions and stood with her right foot next to her left. Thomas started too soon on two separate occasions. Walking Stage (1st Nine): Missed touching heel to toe by more than half inch on counts 3 and 7. Turn: Nothing to report, the turn was completed correctly. Walking Stage (2nd Nine): Stepped completely offline by one shoe width on count 2. Stopped walking on counts 2. One Leg Stand Test (1/4 observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Thomas stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Right foot raised during the test. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: Noting to report Seconds 11-20: Swayed body to the right and left. Seconds 21-30: Swayed body to the right and left. Preliminary Breath Test:  I explained and offered a PBT to Thomas. Thomas elected to consent to the PBT and results were .15 BAC. Notes * I just want to go home to my family, my husband is Lieutenant for Howard County, if you want my husband can come get me. ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Thomas was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a motor vehicle safely:  - Driving over the posted speed limit (103 Mph in 55 Mph speed limit zone)  -Unable to stay within a single lane/driving patterns.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath as she conversed with me.  -Glassy eyes.  -Her admissions to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to driving.  -Observed signs of impairment as she performed the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  - Preliminary Breath Test result of .15 BrAC.  Thomas was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a motor vehicle at 0348 hours and was transported to the Baltimore County Police department Towson Precinct. Upon arrival at the Precinct, Thomas was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and it was read to her from the MVA website in English, and she elected to consent to the Intoximeter EC/IR II test at 0445 hours. 20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Thomas at 0423 hours. A search revealed that she had nothing in her mouth. She remained in my custody from that time. Nothing was introduced to her mouth at any time. The test was conducted by Officer Washburn Intox ID #585 of the Baltimore County Police department on a certified instrument and a result of .15 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath was obtained at 0454 hours. Thomas was given pertinent paperwork and released from the Precinct to her husband pending an appearance in the District Court of Maryland for Baltimore County at a later date.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/03/2023 23:19:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/28/2023 06:46:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509281</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/03/2023 03:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/03/2023 23:14:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/03/2023 23:16:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/03/2023 23:14:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:01</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378882</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>THOMAS</LastName>
               <FirstName>RAISA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>SHARONE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/31/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/03/2023 23:05:26</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>THOMAS</LastName>
               <FirstName>RAISA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>SHARONE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/31/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/03/2023 23:05:26</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9470</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Latchkey</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ROW</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Columbia</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21045</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4417</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.838964</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.199096</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>812</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5822</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/03/2023 23:18:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/03/2023 23:18:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/03/2023 23:18:20</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/03/2023 23:15:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/03/2023 23:15:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153752</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/03/2023 23:19:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/03/2023 23:19:08</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5FNYF6H0XHB060700</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>PLT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3DD8602</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>12</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleValue>1000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>