<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-033539</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/24/2023 01:57:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/24/2023 01:57:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/24/2023 01:39:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/24/2023 01:39:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/24/2023 01:58:02</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4027</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/17/2023 09:39:01</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>707870</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/24/2023 01:58:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 15:20:32</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>707870</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>94.2</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I95 Sb</StreetName>
         <City>Perryville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.048437</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.599131</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/24/2023 01:57:59</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/24/2023 01:57:59</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>62</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/12/2023 19:01:27</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/24/2023 01:58:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:55</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>M-11 is equipped with audio and video recording equipment. Incident captured. DUI #: 23-081 (JFK Highway Barrack)  CASE 23-MSP-033539  ATTACHENTS: Copy of MSP DR-15 Advice of Rights Copy of MSP DR-15A order of suspension Copy of MSP 33 intoximeter results printout Copy of Maryland Drivers license Copy of Maryland vehicle registration Copy of Traffic citations  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING:  * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police.  PHASE 1  VEHICLE IN MOTION: On 09/24/2023 at approximately 0140 hours I, TFC. K Manuel #6917, was patrolling in the area of south bound I95 at Mile Marker 96, Perryville, MD 21903. At that time I observed a 2014 Honda Pilot bearing MD registration: 5CT8398, which passed me at a high rate of speed in the right lane. I accelerated and was able to catch the vehicle. I maintained equal distance and speed from the vehicle and observed the speed of my calibrated speedometer to be 105 mph in a posted 65 mph zone. The vehicle also passed several other vehicles to the right. The road way was saturated from the rain. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle at the 94.2 MM south bound I-95.  PHASE 2 - PERSONAL CONTACT:  I made contact with the driver, later identified by his MD drivers license as, Christopher J Birdow DOB: 05/28/1966 B/M. I informed Birdow the reason for the stop. Prior to Birdow speaking I already was detecting a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I asked Birdow where he was coming from, and he stated he was heading home from his sons college football game. I observed Birdows eyes to be bloodshot, watery and glassy, his eyelids were heavy, his speech was slow and slurred, and I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from Birdows person. I asked Birdow when he had last consumed an alcoholic beverage. He stated he had an alcoholic beverage about couple of hours prior.  Based on the above observations including: The drivers watery bloodshot eyes, slow and slurred speech, heavy eyelids, the drivers admission of consuming an alcoholic beverage, and the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage, I suspected that he was impaired by an alcoholic beverage. I requested that Birdow submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Testing to which he complied.  PHASE 3 - PRE ARREST SCREENING:  SFSTs were administered on the right shoulder of south bound I95 Mile Marker 94.2, Perryville, MD 21903. The area was flat, and free of debris that would inhibit testing. Before starting the tests I ensured the emergency lights of the patrol vehicle were deactivated. Birdow stated he did not wear glasses and was able to see the tip of my finger when I held it up approximately 12-15 inches away. I asked Birdow if he was on any medications prescribed or otherwise. He stated he was on blood pressure medication. I asked Birdow if he had any injuries or surgeries, he stated he has two bad knees and has had both knees replaced, but it would not prevent him from completing the tests.   SFSTs (STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS) All tests were instructed and demonstrated according the NHTSA Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Manual. Birdow indicated that he understood the instructions of all subsequent tests.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues  Birdow pupils were equal in size and both eyes tracked equally prior to the test. -Lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes: PRESENT. -Distinct and sustained nystagmus, in both eyes, at maximum deviation: PRESENT. -Onset of nystagmus, in both eyes, prior to a 45 degree angle: PRESENT.   WALK AND TURN: 7 of 8 total clues -Starts too soon: N/A. -Loses balance during the instructional portion: observed 2 times, and did not return until instructed to do so. -Misses heel to toe during walking phase: Observed on steps 3 and 7, of the first set. Observed on steps 1, 4, and 7 of the second set. -Steps off line during the walking phase: Observed on step 3, 4, 6, 7 and 8 of the first set. Observed on steps 1, 4, and 7 of the second set. -Improper Turn: Did not turn correctly, instead Birdow took small choppy steps with both feet. - Stops walking during the test: Observed to stop for approximately 2-3 seconds on step 1 of the second set. -Uses arms for balance during test: Observed periodically throughout the entire test. -Incorrect number of steps: Observed 11 steps taken on the first set. Observed 16 steps on the second set.    ONE LEG STAND: 3/4 total clues  -Puts foot down during test: Observed 3 times. -Uses arms for balance during the test: raised arms approximately 5-10 inches throughout the test. -Sways during the test: Observed to sway back and forth approximately 3-5 inches. -Hops during the test: N/A  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT):  Birdow was offered a PBT. Birdow agreed to take a PBT and registered at .18  ACTION TAKEN:  Based on my knowledge, training, and experience in the field of DUI/DWI enforcement, and the evidence gathered thus far, I determined that Birdow was impaired by an alcoholic beverage. Birdow was taken into custody and was transported to the JFK barracks. Birdow was read his DR-15 advice of rights. Birdow signed the form at 0218 hours and agreed to submit to an alcohol intoximeter breath test. The intoximeter test was administered by SGT. Allanband #4279. Birdow provided an adequate breath sample. Birdow registered at .14  Birdow was issued the appropriate traffic citations and was issued copies of all the appropriate paperwork.  Birdow was released from the barrack to his sister. All events occurred in Cecil County, MD.    CASE CLOSED   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6917</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 17:07:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6917</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 20:43:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allaband</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4279</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allaband</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4279</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Manuel</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kurtis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6917</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522994</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/24/2023 01:39:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6917</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 17:01:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6917</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 17:01:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>57</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6917</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 16:59:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6917</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 17:05:28</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390042</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Birdow</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>J</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/28/1966 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 16:19:59</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Birdow</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>J</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/28/1966 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/10/2023 16:19:59</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Fannies Meadow</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Westminster</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21158</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4414</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.026423</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.573842</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6917</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 17:05:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6917</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 17:05:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6917</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 17:05:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6917</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 17:01:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6917</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 17:01:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>