<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-034778</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/03/2023 23:11:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/03/2023 23:11:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/03/2023 22:16:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/03/2023 22:16:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Chestertown Police Department Disorderly BOLO - Traffic Stop - DUI/Resisting Arrest - Use of Force</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 23:11:28</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0266</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/31/2023 09:22:42</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>RSA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OLD WORTON RD/ WORTON RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>708895</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 23:11:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 02:49:45</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>708895</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Old Worton</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Worton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.094535</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.282227</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11070-11180 OLD WORTON RD / 10900-11099 WORTON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/03/2023 23:11:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/03/2023 23:11:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>80</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/14/2023 00:13:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 23:11:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:03</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Captured on in car camera and body worn camera.  CRIME- DUI/Resist arrest  SUSPECT- Gary Andre Sorrell Jr          DOB 10/08/1997  On October 3, 2023 at approximately 2216 hours I, ST Nickerson #5702 of the Maryland State Police Centreville Barrack, overheard deputies from the Kent County Sheriffs Office get dispatched to Sudsn Soda, located at 1014 Washington Ave, Chestertown, Kent County, Maryland 21620 for a disorderly subject. When I arrived at scene the clerk advised that the subject in question had just left the store on RT 297 heading towards Worton. The clerk advised that subject was driving a Silver Mazda passenger vehicle with Maryland registration. The clerk advised that when the subject drove into the parking lot, he struck a telephone pole with this vehicle. The clerk advised that the subject was upset that she would not sell him more alcohol and that he seemed to be very impaired.  I then left the store and traveled towards Worton. Kent County Emergency Dispatch was able to obtain a tag number for the suspect vehicle, 1DS7509 Maryland. As I approached the town of Worton I observed a lone passenger vehicle ahead of me. As I traveled closer to the vehicle, I observed the vehicle to drive from the travel portion of the roadway on to the shoulder approximately 3 times. As I got directly behind the vehicle, in the area of RT 297 and Worton Park, I observed the car to be bearing Maryland registration 1DS7509. The vehicle then turned on its left turn single and turned onto Old Worton Road, at that time I activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the vehicle for the traffic violations and for an investigatory stop for the incident that had just occurred at Sudsn Soda.  I made contact with the driver and advised him for the reason for the stop. I requested the drivers license and registration. The driver seemed to be confused and the request and began to look around the vehicle and checking his pockets. I then asked the driver if the vehicle was registered to him, and he advised yes. The driver then searched his center console and was able to produce his registration card. I asked the driver if his name was Gary Sorrell or Gary Sorrell Jr, both names were listed as the registered owner of the vehicle. The driver advised he was Gary Sorrell Jr. Sorrell Jr eventually located his wallet which was located in the front pocket of his sweatshirt. Sorrell Jr produced a Maryland drivers license with the date of birth of 10/08/1997. While speaking with Sorrell Jr I could smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. Sorrell Jrs eyes were also extremely glassy and bloodshot.  I asked Sorrell Jr about the incident that just occurred at Sudsn Soda, and he had no recollection of being in the store or having any issue with the clerk.  I then went back to my patrol vehicle and had the Maryland State Police Centreville Barrack run Sorrell Jr though METERS/NCIC. Sorrell Jrs license came back suspended through Maryland. At this time Deputy Griffitts #0065, ST Selba and Sgt Watson #0044 arrived at scene. I then re-approached the vehicle, advised Sorrell Jr that he was suspended, and he advised that he was not, and he had paid the ticket. Sorrell Jr asked for his license and registration back. I advised Sorrell Jr I would when the traffic stop was complete. Sorrell Jr the asked multiples time for me to give him his license and registration. I then asked Sorrell Jr stop step out of his vehicle at 2230 hours and 39 seconds. Sorrell Jr again asked for his license and registration back. I again asked Sorrell Jr to exit his vehicle at 2231 hours and 04 seconds. Sorrell Jr asked why, and I advised him that he was under the influence at 2231 hours and 19 seconds. I then asked Sorrell Jr to exit his vehicle five more times. At that time ST Selba started to converse with Sorrell Jr. At 2234 hours Sorrell Jr was notified he was receiving a lawful order to exit his vehicle. Sorrell Jr stated that he had to put his wallet back in his pocket first and stated but you kill people. Sorrell Jr was still confused on why his license was suspended. At 2236 hours ST Selba advised the Centreville Barrack that Sorrell Jr was refusing to exit his vehicle. At 2237 hours Sorrell Jr was again advised that he was being given a lawful order to exit his vehicle and he again stated why. Also, at 2237 hours Sorrell Jr was advised that he was under arrest for driving while suspended and to again exit his vehicle. At that time ST Selba unlocked Sorrell Jrs drivers door and I opened the door. At 2238 I again advised Sorrell Jr that he was under arrest and I again notified him that I could smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. At 2239 hours ST Selba entered the vehicle through the passengers door and turned the vehicle off and unlocked Sorrell Jrs seatbelt. At 2239 hours I took control of Sorrell Jrs left wrist and ST Selba took control of Sorrell Jrs right wrist. Sorrell Jr was advised multiple times not to reach for anything in the vehicle. At 2241 hours I then took control of Sorrell Jrs right wrist and Sgt. Watson took control of Sorrell Jrs left wrist. ST Selba was applying steady pressure to Sorrell Jrs right shoulder. At 2242 hours I then pulled on Sorrell Jrs left pant leg to attempt to remove Sorrell Jrs leg from the vehicle, since he was actively resisting exiting the vehicle by tensing his body and putting his legs and feet under the dashboard. At 2243 hours myself and Sgt. Watson took control of Sorrell Jrs left arm and was applying steady pressure to remove him from the drivers seat. At 2243 hours I took control of Sorrell Jrs right arm. At 2244 hours Sorrell Jr stated youre asking me to get out of the car but he still refused to exit the drivers seat. At 2245 hours Sgt. Watson and ST Selba hand control of Sorrell Jrs arms and I grabbed Sorrell Jrs sweatshirt, in an attempt to remove Sorrell Jr from the vehicle. At 2247 hours I placed a handcuff on Sorrell Jrs left wrist and ST Selba placed a handcuff on Sorrell Jrs right wrist. Two sets of handcuffs were used, and Sorrell Jr was placed in handcuffs to the front. Also, at 2247 hours ST Selba advised the Centreville Barrack that Sorrell Jr was still actively resisting. At 2247 hours and 47 seconds Sorrell Jr was removed from the driver seat. At 2248 hours Sorrell Jr was placed against to trunk of the vehicle. Also, at 2248 hours Sorrell Jrs handcuffs were attempted to be placed in the rear. Sorrell Jr again actively resisted placing his hands behind his back by pulling his arms away. At 2249 hours Sorrell Jr handcuffs were placed behind his back.  Sorrell Jr was placed in the front seat of my patrol vehicle and I transported him to the Centreville Barrack for processing. While en route to the Centreville Barrack, Sorrell Jr began complaining about his handcuffs being too tight. At 2314 hours myself and ST Selba pulled over and adjusted the handcuffs for Sorrell Jr.  Due to Sorrell Jr actively resisting, I did not offer him Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. At 0010 hours I read Sorrell Jr his DR-15 Advise of Rights. Sorrell Jr refused to take the breath test.  All of the above stated events occurred in Kent County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5702</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 03:00:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5702</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 03:05:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Emerson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Austin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7196</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Selba</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6315</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wiley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6097</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nickerson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tanner</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5702</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524236</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/03/2023 22:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5702</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 02:58:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5702</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 02:58:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>25</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5702</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 02:55:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5702</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 02:59:27</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>294207</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sorrell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Gary</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Andre</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/08/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>01/12/2021 15:15:46</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sorrell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Gary</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Andre</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/08/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>S640</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/12/2021 15:15:46</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11174</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Potts</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Worton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21678</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1963</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.101172</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.285372</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5702</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 02:59:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5702</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 02:59:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5702</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 02:59:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5702</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 02:58:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5702</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 02:58:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/04/2023 01:47:35</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/04/2023 01:47:35</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>80</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/14/2023 00:13:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6315</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 01:47:35</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:03</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police Centreville Barrack DUI S-23-136 Case Number 23-MSP-034778 Primary: Senior Trooper T. Nickerson #5702 Secondary: Senior Trooper A. Selba #6315 Events recorded on AXON equipment.  Suspect: Gary Andrew Sorrell Jr (B/M 10/08/1997) 11174 Potts Road, Worton, Kent County, Maryland 21678 Height: 602 Weight: 168 Hair: Black Eyes: Brown  Narrative: On October 3rd, 2023 at approximately 2216 hours ST Nickerson #5702 notified the MSP  Centreville Barrack that he would be assisting Kent County Sheriffs Office with a disorderly subject at the Sudsn Soda at 1014 Washington Ave #3320, Chestertown, Kent County, MD 21620. I, ST Selba #6315, heard on KCSOs radio that the subject had been in and out of the liquor store several times, harassing the clerk, harassing the patrons, and possibly hit the light pole in the lot earlier in the day. ST Nickerson and I are both in marked MSP patrol vehicles and in full class uniforms wearing AXON Body Worn Cameras (BWC).  ST Nickerson learned the subject in question left prior to his arrival in a silver Mazda north on MD-297. ST Nickerson then conducted a traffic stop at 2222 hours on a silver 2017 Mazda bearing MD registration 1DS7509 and learned Gary Andre Sorrell Jr (B/M 10/08/1997) was operating the vehicle. I arrived on scene to assist at approximately 2230 hours.  I arrived on scene and observed ST Nickerson on the driver side of the vehicle, informed Sorrell Jr he was suspended, inquired about how much did he have to drink, and then ultimately to exit the vehicle. KCSO SGT Watson #0044 and DFC Griffitts #0065. At 2232 heard ST Nickerson asked Sorrell Jr 5 times, Are you going to step out of the car or not? I then introduced my self to Sorrell Jr and informed him we can ask anyone to exit the vehicle without any heightened suspicion and that his license was suspended. After bickering for a few minutes, at 2234 hours I told Sorrell Jr that we were giving him a lawful order to exit the vehicle. Sorrell Jr appeared to intoxicated with his blood shot eyes, slow reactions and demeanor; Sorrell Jr constantly repeated the same questions after we answered them. Sorrell Jr constantly argued with us about why he needed to get out of the vehicle.  At 2236 hours I notified the Barrack that Sorrell Jr was refusing to exit the vehicle. At 2237 hours ST Nickerson told Sorrell Jr he was under arrest. At that time, I reached in through the driver side window, unlocked the door, and opened the door from the inside. I updated the Barrack again that Sorrell Jr was refusing to exit the vehicle and under arrest.  At 2239 hours I went to the passenger side, opened the door, and turned off the vehicle. I then used my left hand to take control of Sorrell Jrs right hand. He became very tense and attempted to pull away from me. Sorrell Jr and I argued more about him exiting the vehicle. For the next 2 minutes Sorrell Jr constantly tried to reach towards his waist line and argue with us about getting out of the vehicle. At 2242 hours ST Nickerson and KSCO SGT Watson then took control of Sorrell Jrs left hand and arm. I then used both hands to control Sorrell Jrs right arm and hand, he constantly tried to reach down; I started to pat Sorrell Jr down for weapons and nothing was felt. At 1043 hours all three of us tried to get Sorrell Jr out of the vehicle. DFC Griffitts took control of Sorrell Jrs right side as I went to the driver side to assist ST Nickerson and SGT Watson. At 2244 hours I used both hands to control Sorrell Jrs right forearm and wrist. All three of us constantly ordered Sorrell Jr to exit the vehicle and to stop resisting. At 2245 hours Sorrell Jr pulled away, knocking my body worn camera off and it fell under the Mazda.  At 2246 hours I repeatedly announced to Sorrell Jr to get out of the car, stop resisting, and he was under arrest. At 2247 hours ST Nickerson put his handcuffs on Sorrell Jrs left hand and I put my handcuffs on his right hand; we then linked handcuffs. At 2248 hours we were able to retrieve Sorrell Jr out of the vehicle and control him against the trunk of the Mazda. SGT Watson accidently acquired my BWC and wore it on his uniform, as I wore his BWC.  At 2249 hours Sorrell Jr continued to pull away from us and knocked my BWC off of SGT Watsons uniform. ST Nickerson had control of Sorrell Jrs left arm and side, SGT Watson had control of his upper back, and I had control of his right arm. At this time TFC Emerson #7196 arrived on scene to assist, I did not notice where TFC Emerson helped to control Sorrell Jr. Sorrell Jr continued to pull away. We were able to transition the handcuffs to behind Sorrell Jrs I ultimately ended up using my left arm to go under Sorrell Jrs right forearm, lift up, and place my left hand on his shoulder arm in order to gain adequate control of his body. At 2250 hours I attempted to calm Sorrell Jr down my just placing my left hand on his upper back and telling him to lean forward and relax while ST Nickerson did his preliminary search.  At 2252 hours SGT Watson and I acquired our correct BWC and placed them on our uniforms. At approximately 2254 hours TFC Emerson placed Sorrell Jr in the front passenger seat of ST Nickersons patrol vehicle S-20. For the next 9 minutes Sorrell Jr constantly argued with officers on scene about his belongings and sequence of events. At 2306 hours ST Nickerson transported Sorrell Jr to the MSP  Centreville Barrack and I followed. At 2314 hours ST Nickerson pulled over and I assisted with adjusting Sorrell Jrs handcuffs. His right handcuff was adjusted so I could get 2 fingers between the cuff and his wrist, his left handcuff was not adjusted because I could get 2 fingers between the cuff and his wrist. We arrived at the MSP  Centreville Barrack at 2334 hours where Sorrell Jr was ultimately placed in a cell.  Events occurred in Kent County and Queen Annes County. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6315</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 01:48:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6315</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 01:48:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Holson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Troy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6575</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Selba</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6315</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/04/2023 01:51:40</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/04/2023 01:51:40</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>80</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/14/2023 00:13:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7196</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 01:51:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:03</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>EVENT CAPTURED:    margin-left:8px"&gt;Event recorded using my in-car and body worn axon camera system.   NARRATIVE:  On October 3, 2023, at approximately 2249 hours, I, TFC Emerson #7196, was on uniformed duty in Maryland State Police vehicle, S-19. While on duty I responded to Old Worton Rd at RT 297, Worton, MD 21768, to assist ST Nickerson #5702 and ST Selba #6315 with a subject actively resisting arrest. The subject resisting arrest was identified as Gary Andre Sorrell JR, B/M/10/08/1997. Upon my arrival I observed ST Nickerson, ST Selba, and Sgt Watson #44 of Kent county Sheriffs department trying to place Sorrell in handcuffs. I observed Sorrell actively pulling away from all officers and passively resisting arrest. While ST Nickerson, ST Selba and Sgt Watson were trying to gain control of Sorrells upper body to place handcuffs; I used a soft open hand technique to grab Sorrells right leg, using both my hands, on the shin and ankle area and lifted his right leg off the ground to avoid him being able to kick any officers or to walk away. I lifted Sorrells right leg behind him in the motion of a quad stretch and not in an unnatural position. I held Sorrells leg for 10 seconds while handcuffs were placed on Sorrell. As soon as Sorrell was placed in handcuffs all use of force stopped on the Sorrell. Sorrell was then placed in ST Nickersons vehicle under his own power. Sorrell was transported back to the Maryland State Police Centreville Barrack for processing. Sorrell never requested Medical attention as a result of the incident.   All events occurred in Kent County, MD </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7196</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 01:52:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7196</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 01:52:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Holson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Troy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6575</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Emerson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Austin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7196</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>