<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-022802</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/25/2023 02:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/25/2023 02:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/25/2023 02:21:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/25/2023 02:21:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>operating vehicle under influence of controlled dangerous substances</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 02:54:47</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/12/2023 10:23:13</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>HANOVER PIKE/ E DEEP RUN RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>688602</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 02:54:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/25/2023 04:44:15</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>688602</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Hanover</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PIKE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Manchester</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>E</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.91251</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.70484</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4800-4810 HANOVER PIKE / 2143-2239 E DEEP RUN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/25/2023 02:54:46</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/25/2023 02:54:46</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/09/2023 08:29:50</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 02:54:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5039</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/01/2023 01:38:58</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI FIELD ARREST REPORT NARRATIVE DATE 06/25/2023 23-MSP-022802  DUI Ref: DUI 23-105  ARREST Ref: 23-56AR000220  DR15A Control No.: NA - no alcohol found on evidentiary testing  DISPATCH No. 2023-00257922  Incident recorded on in-car camera and on multiple worn Axon cameras.  Defendant: DEVINCENTZ, Angela Marie Date of birth: 01/28/1979 Date of Arrest: 06/25/2023 Time of Arrest: 02:53 hours MD License: MD-102726080108 Prior DUIs: YES, 2 DUIs  1 violation of interlock  2020.08.15:Violation of Interlock Program suspension  2019.04.04:Per Se suspension (note- APS/segregated record)  2018.10.08:Per Se .15 or greater suspension  VICTIMS State of Maryland  TRAINING/CERTIFICATIONS Graduate of Maryland State Police Academy, Class 155  Trained in National Highway Traffic Safety Administration Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police  Sykesville, Maryland, October 2022  Refresher training in National Highway Traffic Safety Administration Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police  Pikesveille, Maryland, March 2023  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On 06/25/2023 at approximately 02:20 hours I, Trooper Bukoski # 7570 assigned to Westminster Barrack (90-56) of the Maryland State Police was on routine patrol northbound on Route 30 when I observed a vehicle in operation on the front lawn of a residence alongside the right-shoulder of southbound Route 30.  The vehicles engine was in a reverse gear, as evidenced by the white back-up lights being on and exhaust coming from the tailpipe. Yet the vehicle was stationary due to being stuck in the dirt. From my initial inspection, there was no driver in the vehicle or occupants.  I initiated a check for a suspicious circumstance.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) As I approached, I noticed the white Ford SUV bearing Maryland plates 5EN0184. As I walked from the drivers rear quarter panel, I noticed that the driver was slumped over in the drivers seat below the sheet-metals window rim. I also noticed that vehicles gearshift was in reverse position at this time, as evidenced by an orange R.  At this time, I knocked on the window and lit the driver with my flashlight. The subject awoke to display the following immediately observable behavior:  She woke to the noise but appeared to be confused and unable to tell where it came from. She wiped a string of saliva from her left corner of her mouth. Her head motions were slow and uncoordinated as she looked at me. She rested with her heads center of gravity behind her shoulders and had her chin at a hyper-acute angle and was dazed. She was unable to keep her eyes open for a sustained period of time and had difficulty opening them beyond minimal height to see.  I asked her to put her vehicle in park and she leaned forward in an uncontrolled manner and missed putting her hand on the central consoles gear shifter with her first attempt. The second time she successfully grabbed it and moved the cars shifter from a reverse gear to a park position.  She had slow, slurred speech patterns and was unable to keep her eyes open while looking at me. When asked what was going on, she gave conflicting stories of where she was traveling from and where she planned to go as a destination.  When asked, DEVINCENTZs attempted to find her license in her wallet and fumbled through the cards and items. When asked if she knew who lived in the house on whose front lawn she was parked, she looked over her right shoulder and, after two or three seconds, stated it was her home. She found her ID after looking through her belongings for 30 seconds by the AXON cameras clock. She forgot to retrieve her cars registration and needed prompting to retrieve it.  She leaned over from the drivers side holding onto the outside of her steering wheel to keep her balanced while retrieving a zip-wallet from the glovebox. As she looked for her registration, when I asked a question to observe if her attention would be divided. She completely stopped her task of retrieving her registration to talk to me. At that point, I then asked how much she had had to drink that night, she stated none. DEVINCENTZ then asked me where she kept her registration and if it was in the zip-wallet open on her lap she had retrieved from the glove compartment. I replied that it was wherever she had placed it last.  She leaned over again to dig in the glove compartment again. She initially retrieved several napkins and handed them over to me before realizing they were napkins. She then laughed, leaned back over, and retrieved the correct documents.  At this time, I wanted to test the subject with a field sobriety test and so asked for additional units.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  When I walked back to the drivers side when my backup units were available, I observed the following:  DEVINCENTZ was leaning with her head back resting against the headrest, and her chin was up in the air. Her eyes were closed and she did not alert to attention when I approached. I put my flashlight on its strobe setting and still she remained unresponsive to the light.  DEVINCENTZ awoke to my voice and agreed to perform field sobriety tests to see if she was safe to drive or not.  As DEVINCENTZstepped out of the vehicle, I noted that she used the rolled-down driverside windows rim as a railing to haul herself up with her right hand. Upon standing, she was off balance and notably front-leaning over her toes. DEVINCENTZ tated she had heels on. I offered for her to take them off or change into athletic shoes if she had any in her car. She stated she did and went back to the car.  DEVINCENTZ lowered herself into the drivers seat with a plan on the chairs horizontal pad. She leaned over from the drivers side to the passenger footwall, again holding onto her steering wheel with her left hand. DEVINCENTZ then looked behind the passengers side back seat footwall for about thirty seconds before she retrieved them, all the while still holding onto her steering wheel with her left hand.  Once her high heels were off, it took her over a minute to put on her first shoe. She spent time to unlace her knotted athletic shoe, placed it on her foot, and then re-laced it up while attempting to have a distracting conversation with me by asking off-topic questions. EG, about my shift and the weather while doing so. I asked her to focus on the task at hand and it still took her another 30 seconds to lace up her second shoe.  While walking across the lawn to the field sobriety starting area, DEVINCENTZ was unsteady. Her weight was carried mostly over her feet and she slipped side-to-side to rebalance herself with her arms more than 6 inches from her side.  My evaluation was performed on the flat shoulder of southbound Route 30 at 4700 Hanover Pike Road. The shoulder was level, dry, free of debris, and well-lit. No surface defects were noted and it was dry. When I asked if DEVINCENTZ was able to maintain their balance and if they felt steady on the surface.  Prior to starting the test, all noxious stimuli of front-facing emergency equipment was deactivated and I asked the following screening questions:  Glasses or contacts - denied Medical conditions - her left-lower leg has plates, rods, and screw in it but i can use it just fine Medications - suboxone, gabapentin, vyvanse  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN; note - 0 of 6 clues observed)  The first test given was the HGN. I described the test prior to starting and asked if DEVINCENTZ had any questions, which they denied. I also asked if DEVINCENTZ understood my instructions; they agreed that they did. DEVINCENTZ eyes were equal in size and showed equal tracking to my stimulus.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit - NOT observed (0/2).  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - NOT observed (0/2).  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - NOT observed (0/2).  Vertical Nystagmus was NOT present (not clue).   WALK AND TURN (WAT; note - unable to safely perform, stopped)  The WAT was demonstrated and explained to DEVINCENTZ. I provided DEVINCENTZ with time for any clarifying questions and they declined to ask any. I confirmed DEVINCENTZ understood the instructions for the WAT.  Instructional Stage:  DEVINCENTZ was unable to keep her balance. She kept bringing her feet out from the heel-toe stance to a wider shoulder-width position. DEVINCENTZ started too soon multiple times.  Walking Stage, 1st 9 steps:  MISSED heel-toes STOPPED WALKING STEPPED offline RAISED arms  Turn NA  Walking Stage, 2nd 9 steps: NA  She was unable to do more than 3-4 steps before entirely being so off balance she was in danger of falling twice. At this time I moved to the next step due to safety concerns.  ONE LEG STAND TEST (OLS; note - unable to safely perform, stopped)  The OLS was demonstrated and explained to DEVINCENTZ. I asked if she had any questions. She denied any at that time. I confirmed that DEVINCENTZ understood the instructions. She was unable to safely get into the starting position to listen to my instructions so I moved to the next step due to safety concerns.  Balance-and-count Stages: NA  Seconds 0-10: NA  Seconds 11-20: NA  Seconds 21-30: NA  Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) DEVINCENTZ was offered a PBT by TFC Perrell. DEVINCENTZ agreed to take the BPT.  ARREST Based on the totality of circumstances below, I had reason to believe that DEVINCENTZ had driven a motor vehicle while impaired by a substance:  An inability to balance and stand  Poor performance on divided attention tests to necessitate stopping for safety  An inability to keep her eyes open  Uncoordinated movements  Needing to use objects to steady herself while getting out of her vehicle  Needing to use an object to steady herself to lean over into the glovebox  Her inability to be attentive to her immediate surroundings and any changes of circumstances in them  DISPOSITION DEVINCENTZ was transported to Westminster Barrack and advised of her DR15 rights and her Miranda Rights. She agreed to participate in the evidentiary test and waived her rights.  Evidentiary test was given by Sgt. Smith with resultant 0.000s.  Her impairment was insistent with the observations of field sobriety testing so I requested a drug recognition expert (DRE) to respond to barrack to perform their evaluation. TFC Mills responded to complete the examination.  Upon completing his assessment, TFC Mills determined that DEVICENTZ was impaired by CDS after his examination. DEVINCENTZ disagreed with TFC Mills finding and agreed to go to the hospital to get her blood drawn to determine what, if any, impairing substances were in her body. DEVINCENTZ had her blood drawn at Carroll Healths ER by an RN. The tubes were packaged and sent per MSP policy.  I discharged DEVINCENTZ into the direct care of ER RNs after the blood was drawn due to being unable to safely care for herself with her level of observed intoxication by a DRE and myself.  I request that this case remain open pending results of the blood draw kit. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 18:54:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/12/2023 10:11:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Perrell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Curtis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7140</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dale</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2927</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bukoski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Conrad</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7570</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>512238</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19745</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/25/2023 02:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>awaiting blood test results</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19745</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 18:52:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 20:30:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>44</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 04:46:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>346887</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>DEVINCENTZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>Angela</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/28/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.18989547E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>06/19/2022 21:03:47</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D152</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A524</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>DEVINCENTZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>Angela</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/28/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.18989547E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>D152</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A524</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/19/2022 21:03:47</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4700</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hanover</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PIKE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Manchester</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21102</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1234</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.9102176</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.7024917</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>870</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1551</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/19/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 18:52:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 18:52:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 18:52:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 18:52:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 18:52:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154507</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/25/2023 04:53:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/25/2023 04:53:51</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FMCU9J93JUD26514</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2018</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5EN0184</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/16/2023 21:07:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/16/2023 21:07:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/09/2023 08:29:50</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 21:07:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5039</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/01/2023 01:38:58</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>SUPPLEMENT #1 NARRATIVE:    On 7/16/2023, I uploaded my completed DRE report to this report as an attachment.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/16/2023 21:10:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/16/2023 21:13:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dale</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2927</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mills</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryder</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6784</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/13/2023 02:07:44</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/13/2023 02:07:44</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/19/2023 08:14:45</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 02:07:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5039</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/01/2023 01:38:58</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Bookmarked Narrative for Pending Blood Results.  None obtained at this time so submitted so it is no longer in OverDue Status.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 01:36:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 09:40:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eyler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0670</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bukoski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Conrad</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7570</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/30/2023 03:03:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/30/2023 03:03:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/01/2023 01:38:58</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 03:03:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/01/2023 01:38:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 09/26/2023 at approximately 0713 hours I received a physical letter from the State Attorney notifying me that they had no intent to pursue charges at this time.  I therefore request that the case be closed by State Attorney declining to pursue charges.    CLOSED.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 03:04:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 03:05:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bukoski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Conrad</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7570</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>