<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-021696</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/16/2023 21:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/16/2023 21:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/16/2023 21:17:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/16/2023 21:17:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Two vehicle hit and run accident. The suspect was arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 21:54:17</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6327</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 09:48:04</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>629172</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 01:35:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 01:35:32</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>629172</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Branch</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <StreetSuffixCode>N</StreetSuffixCode>
         <City>Clinton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20735</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.87936</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.75038</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/16/2023 21:54:15</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/16/2023 21:54:15</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/02/2023 09:48:05</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 21:54:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car (L-21) and Body Worn Camera Operational.   Defendant: Takia Monique Matthews  Date of Birth: 12/12/1978  Date of Arrest: 06/16/2023  Time of Arrest: 2154 Hours    DUI:  23-185  Certificate and Training:  Trained in Administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) through the Maryland State Police (MSP) and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA)  Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.)  Soundex:  MD10273537631/Maryland  Narrative: VEHICLE IN MOTION (Phase 1):  On June 16, 2023, at approximately 2040 hours, I, Trooper J. Barlow of the Maryland State Police, currently assigned to the Forestville Barrack, was on duty operating my marked patrol vehicle, when the College Park Police Communication Operator (PCO) dispatched a two-vehicle hit-and-run accident southbound Branch Avenue at Surratts Road, Clinton, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20735 involving a maroon KIA vehicle. While in the area of the collision, I was unable to locate the struck vehicle.   At approximately 2056 hours, I contacted the driver involved who answered the phone stating, What the fuck you want? As I was attempting to advise who I was and why I was calling, the driver stated again, What the fuck do you want? I dont have time, I dont have time then proceeded to hang up the phone. At this time, I proceeded to continue southbound on Branch Avenue towards the Charles County line attempting to locate the vehicle. There were no vehicles fitting the description in or on the side of the roadway southbound on Branch Avenue. I began to make a U-Turn on Branch Avenue, now traveling northbound.   At approximately 2118 hours, I continued on northbound Branch Avenue at Surratts Road where I observed a purple Kia Sorento bearing Virginia registration USC1507 sitting stationary in the left outside turn lane. There was visible disabling damage to the driver side of the vehicle. It appears this was the original accident I was attempting to locate in the southbound lanes.   PERSONAL CONTACT (Phase 2):  Upon contact with the driver, who I identified her as Takia Monique Matthews (B/F DOB: 12/12/1978) by her Maryland drivers license. I asked Matthews what happened to which she advised she was struck by another vehicle who fled the scene. I asked Matthews if she had any description of the vehicle as far as color, make, model, and registration to which Matthews advised she did not. I asked Mathews where was she coming from to which she stated, Waldorf. I asked Matthews what was she doing in Waldorf to which Matthews stated, I was coming from Mechanicsville, Maryland. I asked Matthews was she coming from Waldorf or Mechanicsville, to which she stated, I just left from my girlfriends house in Mechanicsville from getting my hair done. It should be noted, Matthews hair looked recently styled in black and blonde braids.   While talking to Matthews I observed her eyes were glossy, and she was excessively talkative while giving information. Matthews was constantly moving around the area, unable to stay still and be steady. I detected the strong odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. I asked Matthews how many alcoholic beverages had she consumed to which she stated Two cups. I asked Matthews what were the two cups of to which she stated, Tequila. I asked Matthews where she consumed the two cups of tequila at to which she stated, My girlfriends house while I was getting my hair done. I asked Matthews would she perform the voluntary Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) to which she agreed to perform.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (Phase 3):  I asked Matthews had she sustained any injuries from the collision, take any medication, or wear glasses to which she advised no.   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) 6 out of 6 clues observed:  Before performing HGN, I instructed Matthews to stand with her legs and feet together and her arms down by her sides. I instructed Matthews not to move from this position until I instructed her to do so. I asked Matthews if she could see the silver tip of my stimulus to which she advised she could. I instructed Matthews to follow the silver tip of my stimulus with her eyes only, without moving her head, neck, or shoulders. I asked Matthews if she understood the instructions I gave her to which she advised she understood. Matthews showed equal pupil size in both eyes. Matthews did not show equal tracking in both eyes as her eyes lagged while following the silver tip of the stimulus. Matthews moved her head while following the stimulus even though she advised she understood not to move her head from the instructions.   Lack of Smooth Pursuit:  Matthews showed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.   Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation:  Matthews showed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees:  Matthews showed onset nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.   Vertical Gaze Nystagmus:  Matthews did not show vertical gaze nystagmus in either eye.  Walk and Turn (WAT) 4 out of 8 clues observed:  Before performing WAT, I advised Matthews to remove her Nike slides from her feet to perform this portion of the test more efficiently. I instructed Matthews to stand on the solid white lane divider line with her left foot and to place her right foot in front touching heel to toe. I instructed Matthews not to move from this position until I instructed her to do so. I instructed Matthews to take nine (9) heel to toe steps down the solid white line, looking down at her feet, and counting each step out loud. I instructed Matthews once she got to her 9th step, to leave her lead foot planted and take a series of small steps turning around to her left and take 9 more heel to toe steps back down the solid white line. I instructed Matthews once she starts the test, do not stop the test until she completed the test. I demonstrated how the test should be performed. I asked Matthews if she understood the instructions I gave her and the demonstration to which she advised she did. I instructed Matthews to begin the test.   Instructional Phase:  Matthews lost balance, separating her feet by more than one half inch.  Walking Stage (1st Series):  Matthews missed heel to toe by more than one half inch on steps 1 through 9.  Matthews stepped off line by more than one half inch on step 6.  Turn:  Matthews did not turn as instructed, as she lifted both feet off the ground while turning to the left.   Walking Stage (2nd Series):  Matthews missed heel to toe by more than one half inch on steps 1 through 9.   One Leg Stand (OLS) 2 out of 4 clues observed:  Before performing OLS, I instructed Matthews to stand with her legs and feet together with her arms down by her sides. I instructed Matthews not to move from this position until I instructed her to do so. I instructed Matthews to lift either leg of her choosing approximately six inches off the ground. I instructed Matthews to look down at the toes of the raised foot and count out loud in the manner of one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-three, and so on until I instructed her to stop. I demonstrated how the test should be performed and asked Matthews if she understood the instructions and demonstration to which she advised she understood. I asked Matthews which leg did she want to lift off the ground to which she advised and pointed to her left leg. I instructed Matthews to begin the test.   Puts Foot Down:  Matthews put her foot down during seconds 6-8 and 14-19.  Uses Arms for Balance:  No clues observed.  Sways:  Matthews swayed six inches from center during seconds 6.  Hops:  No clues observed.  Arrest:    The strong odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person  The admission of consuming alcoholic beverages   margin-left:8px"&gt;The observations during SFSTs   Preliminary Breath Test:  .21BrAC  At approximately 2150 hours, Matthews was advised of her Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) rights and offered a PBT. Matthews agreed to submit to the PBT with a result of .21BrAC. At approximately 2154 hours, Matthews was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. Matthews was searched prior to being placed in my marked patrol vehicle to be transported to the Forestville Barrack. While enroute to the Forestville Barrack, Matthews was provided a digital copy of the Advice of Rights (DR-015) from the mva.maryland.gov website to follow along while I played the audio version of the form downloaded from the same website in its entirety. Matthews vehicle was towed from the scene.   Intoximeter Test:  .22BrAC  After having been read the DR-015, at approximately 2215 hours, Matthews agreed to take the Intoximeter Test. At approximately 2241 hours, Matthews took the Intoximeter Test with a result of .22BrAC. The Intoximeter Test was administered by Sgt S. Estrin #6052.  Matthews was charged with DUI/DWI and other traffic related incidents.   Matthews was released from the Forestville Barrack to a sober driver.   Case closed by arrest.   All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 00:52:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 00:56:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Manziano</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicole</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7363</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>York</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6327</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511132</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/16/2023 21:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 01:38:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 01:43:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511132</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/16/2023 21:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 01:38:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 01:43:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511132</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/16/2023 21:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 01:38:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 01:42:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511132</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/16/2023 21:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 01:38:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 01:41:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511132</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/16/2023 21:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17272</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 01:38:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 01:46:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511132</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/16/2023 21:17:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 01:40:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 01:40:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>44</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 01:37:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>380472</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Matthews</LastName>
               <FirstName>Takia</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Monique</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/12/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/22/2023 01:04:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Matthews</LastName>
               <FirstName>Takia</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Monique</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/12/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/22/2023 01:04:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3828</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Regency</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PKWY</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>301</SubNumber>
               <City>Suitland-Silver Hill</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20746</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.912656</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.837458</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>292</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7560</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 01:47:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 01:47:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 01:47:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 01:38:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 01:38:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154397</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 01:48:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 01:48:35</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5XYKWDA21BG143034</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2011</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>KIA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SOR</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>PLE</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>USC1507</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/30/2023 08:36:31</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/30/2023 08:36:31</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/02/2023 09:48:05</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6052</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/30/2023 08:36:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>ACRS ATTACHED.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/30/2023 08:36:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/30/2023 08:36:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bowling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0392</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Estrin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6052</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>