<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-045250</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/23/2023 00:35:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/23/2023 00:35:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/23/2023 00:06:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/23/2023 00:06:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>FIGUEROA "N" 23-273</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/23/2023 00:35:39</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/16/2024 18:30:21</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>29 MM CAPITAL BELTWAY WB, SILVER SPRING</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>716793</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/23/2023 00:35:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 09:31:45</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>716793</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>29</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm Capital Beltway Wb Silver</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>SPG</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.9894884166667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0185711166667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/23/2023 00:35:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/23/2023 00:35:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/16/2024 18:30:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/23/2023 00:35:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:25</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E) TEAM* MVR Statement: The following incident was captured on in-car and Body camera. Title: FIGUEROA N 23-273. ID: 23-MSP-045250 Arrested: Figueroa De La Cruz, Yeferson. Certification and training  -Trained in Field Sobriety Test through Maryland State Police Academy.  -Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E)  -Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  - Graduated from The Institute of Advanced Law Enforcement Studies Driving Under the Influence Institute-University of Maryland.  - I am a certified EC/IR II Intoximeter operator.  - I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor.  - I have apprehended more than 280 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On December 23, 2023, at approximately 0003 hours, I, TFC. I. Riba Tankari # 7058 with Maryland State Police was traveling inner loop I-495 west of US-29, Montgomery County, Maryland in lane #3 (right middle lane). My issued patrol vehicle is Maryland State Police unmarked unit DUI-6. At that time, I observed a red Nissan Altima bearing Maryland registration 6ER7945 traveling inner loop I-495 in lane #2 (left middle lane) was unable to stay within a single lane. I observed the Nissan had swerved from lane #2 into lane #3 crossing the dotted white line into lane #4 (right lane) by more than half vehicle width and continued traveling partially between the two lanes before returning into lane #3. I followed the Nissan and observed the vehicle had swerved from lane #3 into lane #2 by more than half vehicle width on one occasion. I observed the Nissan had crossed the dotted white line from lane #3 into lane #2 by more than one tire width on two separate occasions. I observed the Nissan had swerved to the left towards the dotted white and drove on the line on several occasions. I continued to follow the Nissan and observed the vehicle had crossed the dotted white line from lane #3 into lane #4 by more than one tire width on one occasion. I initiated a traffic stop on the Nissan using my emergency equipment. The Nissan delayed in coming to stop. The Nissan eventually came to a stop in the area of inner loop I-495 and west of MD-650, Montgomery County, Maryland on the right shoulder. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the Nissan on the driver side and made contact with the driver (the sole occupant) of the vehicle. I introduced myself and explained to him the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver where he was coming from, and the driver stated Wheaton. I requested his drivers license and registration card. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I observed that the driver had glassy and bloodshot eyes. I noticed his movements were slow while retrieving the requested documents. The driver was identified through his Maryland drivers license as Figueroa De La Cruz, Yeferson. I returned to my patrol vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with. I returned to the Nissan and I requested Figueroa to exit his vehicle and walk to the front of his vehicle and he complied. While outside his vehicle, I again asked Figueroa where he was coming from, and he stated he was coming from Wheaton and was going to Greenbelt. I asked Figueroa how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed, and he stated he had one cup of Corona beer ten minutes ago. While speaking with Figueroa outside his vehicle, I again detected a strong odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I noticed Figueroa was wearing T-top and I requested him to get his jacket and he complied. I asked Figueroa to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and he agreed.  The evaluation surface was dry, flat, and free of debris. No surface defects were observed. My patrol flashlight and his vehicles headlights lit the area. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Figueroa appeared to be in good physical conditions and was wearing crocs. I asked Figueroa the following questions: Medical conditions: No. Medications: No. Anything that will prevent you from walking on straight line or standing on one leg: yeah I need my sandalias grandes to walk. Glasses or contact: No. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: (6/6 clues observed). The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus - Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes - Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes - Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Notes: * During the HGN test, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Figueroas breath. *Moved his head and was talkative. *its too cold papi. WALK AND TURN: (6/8 clues observed). The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Figueroa stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage: Figueroa lost his balance to the right on several occasions and to the left on one occasion and had difficulty staying in instructional position. I instructed Figueroa to return to the instructional position on several occasions. Figueroa started too soon on one occasion. Walking Stage (1st Nine): Raised his arms more than six (6) inches away from his body for balance on counts 5, 6, 8, and 9 and left arm on counts 4 and 7. Notes *Figueroa took nine steps but counted ten. Turn: The turn was not completed correctly; instead Figueroa turned to his left failing to take a series of small steps as instructed and demonstrated. Walking Stage (2nd Nine): Raised his arms more than six (6) inches away from his body for balance on count 1 and his left arm on counts 4. Stepped completely offline by one shoe width on count 1. Took ten actual steps when instructed to take 9. One Leg Stand Test (2/4 observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Figueroa stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Right foot raised during the test. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: Swayed body to the right and left. Raised arms more than six (6) inches from his side for balance. Seconds 11-20: Swayed body to the right and left. Raised arms more than six (6) inches from his side for balance. Seconds 21-30: Swayed body to the right and left. Raised arms more than six (6) inches from his side for balance. Preliminary Breath Test:  I explained and offered a PBT to Figueroa. Figueroa refused to consent to the PBT. ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Figueroa was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a motor vehicle safely:  -Unable to stay within a single lane/driving patterns.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath as he conversed with me.  -Glassy and bloodshot eyes.  -Movements slow.  -His admissions to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to driving.  -Observed signs of impairment as he performed the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  Figueroa was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a motor vehicle at 0030 hours and was transported to the Montgomery County Silver Spring Station. A search incident to arrest revealed no weapons or contraband. While securing his vehicle, I observed an unopened big bottle of Carlo Rossi Sangria on the rear passenger floor mat and an empty big bottle of Carlo Rossi Sangria, two clear plastic cups containing alcoholic beverage residue, and an empty can of Modelo beer on the front passenger floor mat (see attachments). Upon arrival at the Station, Figueroa was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and it was read to him from the MVA website in Spanish, and he refused to consent to the Intoximeter EC/IR II test at 0101 hours. A properly functioning instrument and operator were available. Figueroa was polite and cooperative during the encounter. Figueroa was given pertinent paperwork, released from the Station to his friends pending an appearance in the District Court of Maryland for Montgomery County at a later date.  All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. .</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/03/2024 09:41:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2024 15:33:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534727</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/23/2023 00:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/03/2024 09:32:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 09:33:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>28</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/03/2024 09:32:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 09:35:46</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>396716</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>FIGUEROA DE LA CRUZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>YEFERSON</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>NONE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/05/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/03/2024 09:23:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F263</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Y162</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>FIGUEROA DE LA CRUZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>YEFERSON</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>NONE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/05/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F263</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Y162</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/03/2024 09:23:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>827</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Marcy</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>101</SubNumber>
               <City>Oxon Hill</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20745</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.992072</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.816241</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>421</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4942</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/03/2024 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/03/2024 09:35:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 09:35:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/03/2024 09:35:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 09:35:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/03/2024 09:35:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 09:35:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/03/2024 09:35:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 09:35:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/03/2024 09:32:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 09:32:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>160421</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/03/2024 09:41:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/03/2024 09:41:04</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/03/2024 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1N4AL3AP4FC455097</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ALT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>RED</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2FE2581</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>5</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleValue>1000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>