<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-021596</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/16/2023 04:34:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/16/2023 04:34:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/16/2023 04:12:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/16/2023 04:12:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 04:34:25</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5479</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/07/2023 21:38:47</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>644209</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 04:34:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/16/2023 06:17:07</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>644209</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>I-370 @ I-270</StreetName>
         <City>Gaithersburg</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20877</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.195855</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.12202</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/16/2023 04:34:22</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/16/2023 04:34:22</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/07/2023 21:38:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 04:34:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>N-17 is equipped with a mobile recording device Defendant: Luis Franco Molina  Date of Birth: 09/08/1979 Date of Arrest: 06/16/2023 Time of Arrest: 0433 hours MD SDX: F-652-560-009-699  DUI #: 23-139 (Rockville)  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Certified by NHTSA to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) * Certified as a Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator  * Certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE)  * Attended the 2021 Maryland Impaired Driving Conference in Ocean City, Maryland * Participated in several DUI Special Assignments * DUI Award Recipient for 2021  2022 VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On Friday, June 16, 2023 at approximately 0412 hours, I, TFC Canizalez #7087, was on patrol traveling on westbound I-370 prior to I-270, Gaithersburg, Montgomery County, Maryland operating in marked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle N-17. At that time, I observed a red Nissan Maxima bearing Illinois Registration CS27906 stopped on the right shoulder with their emergency flashers on. I approached the vehicle to conduct a welfare check on the driver.  CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the vehicle to contact the driver on his driver side. The vehicle had music playing very loud and could be heard once I stepped outside of my vehicle even with all windows up. Using my flashlight, I was able to shine a light within the vehicle and was able to observe the driver was asleep behind the wheel with the engine running and keys at hand. I then began to knock on the window and try the door in attempts to check on the drivers welfare. I knocked several times until the driver finally awoke. I introduced myself and asked the driver if he was ok and why he was there and he stated he was asleep and was coming from home and was headed home. I re-asked the question and then the driver stated he was coming from his friends house and was headed home. Observing the drivers address listed on his license, the driver was headed home to Germantown but was headed in the wrong direction and had missed the exit ramp from westbound I-370 towards northbound I-270. While speaking to the driver I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from within the vehicle. I then asked the driver to step out of the vehicle for further questioning. The driver was identified by his Maryland Drivers License as: FRANCO MOLINA, Luis. (MD SDX: F-652-560-009-699, H/M DOB- 09/08/1979). Once outside the vehicle, I asked FRANCO MOLINA a series of questions which allowed me to continue to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath. FRANCO MOLINA was also displaying other sign s of impairment such as bloodshot and glassy eyes. I questioned the driver on how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed the night prior to driving and he stated 6 bottled Modelo beers approximately 4-5 hours prior to driving. I then offered FRANCO MOLINA if he was willing to perform SFSTs and he agreed to do so.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of westbound I-370 prior to I-270. (pavement). The surface was dry, level, and free from any debris. The weather was clear and light conditions consisted of my flashlight. FRANCO MOLINA appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. Prior to beginning the test, I asked FRANCO MOLINA the following questions:  Glasses or Contacts: None. Medical Conditions: None. Injuries: None. Medications: None. *TEST #1 HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN): 6/6 The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from FRANCO MOLINAs eyes, and slightly above eye level. I instructed FRANCO MOLINA to look straight ahead, keeping his head stationary while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. I asked FRANCO MOLINA if he understood the test and he stated, Yes. FRANCO MOLINAs pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes. 4.) Vertical Gaze Nystagmus: Present in both eyes. *TEST #2 WALK AND TURN (WAT): 7/8 Prior to FRANCO MOLINA performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. FRANCO MOLINA was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on a straight imaginary line. FRANCO MOLINA was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin the test. FRANCO MOLINA was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. FRANCO MOLINA was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, FRANCO MOLINA was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to the left to turn completely around. FRANCO MOLINA was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. FRANCO MOLINA was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked FRANCO MOLINA if he understood the test and he stated, Yes.     margin-bottom:11px"&gt;FRANCO MOLINA was unable to maintain his balance during the instructional phase   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;FRANCO MOLINA began the test prior to being instructed to do so.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;FRANCO MOLINA missed heel-to-toe on his 2nd and 5th step during the second set.    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;FRANCO MOLINA stepped off line on his 8th step during his second set.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;FRANCO MOLINA stopped walking on his first step during his first set.    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;FRANCO MOLINA raised his arms for balance during the first set.    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;FRANCO MOLINA took the incorrect number of steps and took 12 steps during both sets.   *TEST #3 ONE LEG STAND (OLS): 1/4 Prior to FRANCO MOLINA performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. FRANCO MOLINA was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count aloud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. FRANCO MOLINA was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, Yes. FRANCO MOLINA performed this test balanced on his left foot.     margin-bottom:11px"&gt;FRANCO MOLINA put his foot down at the 5th and 28th second mark.  I offered FRANCO MOLINA a preliminary breath test and he advised that he would take it. PBT result: BrAC .13 ARREST: Based on the following, I had reason to believe was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of an alcoholic beverage: * FRANCO MOLINA was found asleep behind the wheel with the engine running. * FRANCO MOLINA having two travel size Fire Ball Cinnamon Whiskeys in the front cup holder.  * FRANCO MOLINA continuously asked the same questions at the station * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from FRANCO MOLINA breath. * Bloodshot and glassy eyes.  * FRANCO MOLINA admitting to have consumed 6 bottled Modelo beers approximately 4-5 hours prior to driving.  * While being transported to the barrack, FRANCO MOLINA stated Im drinking yeah! Im not lying to you. Due to the number of observations, I had reason to believe FRANCO MOLINA was driving under the influence of an alcoholic beverage and was unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0433 hours, I placed FRANCO MOLINA under arrest for Driving While Under the Influence of Alcohol. A preliminary search of FRANCO MOLINA was conducted on the scene and it revealed that he had nothing on his person. FRANCO MOLINA was seat belted into my marked MSP patrol vehicle N-17 and was transported to the MSP Rockville Barrack per departmental policy. While conducting the secondary search on FRANCO MOLINA at the barrack, his oral cavity was checked and was clear and had nothing in his mouth. During the 20-minute observation period, FRANCO MOLINA remained in my custody and did not introduce any foreign object in his mouth. The DR-15 Advice of Rights was read to FRANCO MOLINA at 0505 hours. Upon completion of being read the DR-15 FRANCO MOLINA refused to submit to the intoximeter test.  INTOXIMETER RESULT  REFUSED  FRANCO MOLINA was given all pertinent paperwork and was later released to his family at 0600 hours.  Case status: closed by arrest. All events occurred in MontgomeryCounty, Maryland </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/24/2023 05:29:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/24/2023 05:30:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Emerick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6888</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Taylor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5479</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511031</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/16/2023 04:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 06:17:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/24/2023 05:47:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511031</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/16/2023 04:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 06:17:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/24/2023 05:47:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511031</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/16/2023 04:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 06:17:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/24/2023 05:47:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511031</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/16/2023 04:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 06:17:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/24/2023 05:47:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>43</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 06:17:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:06</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>380011</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>FRANCO MOLINA</LastName>
               <FirstName>Luis</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/08/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/16/2023 06:13:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>FRANCO MOLINA</LastName>
               <FirstName>Luis</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/08/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/16/2023 06:13:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>13040</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Shadyside</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>#B</SubNumber>
               <City>Germantown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20874</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.272073</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.193743</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/24/2023 05:49:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:06</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/24/2023 05:49:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:06</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/24/2023 05:49:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:06</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/16/2023 06:17:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/16/2023 06:17:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154209</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/24/2023 05:53:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/24/2023 05:53:12</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1N4BL4CV2LC263839</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MAX</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>RED</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>IL</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>CS27906</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2022</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>