<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-027522</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/04/2023 04:07:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/04/2023 04:07:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/04/2023 03:57:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/04/2023 03:57:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/04/2023 04:07:23</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/23/2023 14:37:35</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>702887</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 00:42:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 00:43:09</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>702887</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Capital Beltway</StreetName>
         <City>Greenbelt</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20770</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.888516</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.99431</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/04/2023 04:07:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/04/2023 04:07:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/14/2023 04:54:54</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/04/2023 04:07:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:59</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Defendant: Gomez Izara, Franklyn Omar Incident Number: 23-MSP-027522 DUI Folder: 23-165 Date of Offense: 08/04/2023 Arresting Officer: Tpr. Fleming #7439 Breath Technician: N/A Subsequent Offender: No  Q-13 IS EQUIPPED WITH AN IN CAR CAMERA THE EVENT WAS AUDIBLY AND VISUALLY RECORDED  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On August 4th, 2023, at approximately 0407 hours, I, Trooper Fleming #7439 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, received a call for service for a report of a disabled vehicle in the roadway. I observed a still running vehicle with the rear drivers side corner up against the guardrail on the left shoulder of northbound I-95 at 198. I identified the vehicle as a blue Honda Civic bearing the District of Columbia registration GV2718. I notified the barrack of my location and the vehicles information. I exited my patrol vehicle to make contact with the driver.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the passengers side of the vehicle in order to make contact with the operator. Upon my approach, I observed man asleep upright in the drivers seat. His head was tilted down and his eyes were closed. The driver did not acknowledge me in anyway when I approached the vehicle and stood next to the front passengers side door. I walked around to the drivers side of the vehicle. The driver also had an open can of beer between his thighs. I knocked on the front drivers side window. The driver slowly started to stretch and rub his face. The driver appeared to go back to sleep. I continued to knock on the window. The driver suddenly jolted awake and rolled down the front drivers side window. The driver appeared to be confused. I asked for the driver to turn off the vehicle and hand me the keys. Even after doing so, the driver still made motions towards the ignition and gear shift as though he was attempting to turn on the vehicle and put it in drive. I had the driver exit the vehicle. The driver did not possess a license and was not carrying any type of identification. I later identified the driver as Gomez Izara, Franklyn Omar (5/M, DOB: 08/24/1997) via his District of Columbia identification card and his Guatemalan identification card. Gomez Izaras speech was slurred and mumbled. His movements were slow and lethargic. His eyes were bloodshot and glassy as well. There was a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage from his breath and person. I asked Gomez Izara where he was coming from. Gomez Izara stated he was coming from Landover, MD and pointed north (the opposite direction of Landover). I attempted to clarify with Gomez Izara where he was coming from and going to; however I received no clarity. EMS/Fireboard arrived on scene. EMS/Fireboard determined that Gomez Izara did not need or want to be transported to hospital. Due to the dangerous weather conditions, increasing traffic flow, and lack of space, I determined that field sobriety would be offered to Gomez Izara at the Maryland State Police College Park Q Barrack.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) I asked Gomez Izara the following questions: Medical Condition  Gomez Izara stated that he took medication for diabetes. Gomez Izara also stated that he took pain medication for an injury to his left leg. Gomez Izara stated that he took the pain medication about four hours ago. Physical Condition  Gomez Izara appeared to be in good physical condition. Gomez Izara stated that his left leg was weak due to a prior injury. Glasses or Contacts  Gomez Izara did not wear glasses or contacts.  ARREST Based on the totality of circumstances, I concluded Gomez Izara was driving a motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol. The vehicle was running while Gomez Izara was asleep at the wheel. Gomez Izaras eyes were bloodshot and glassy. Gomez Izaras slow movement. Gomez Izaras slurred and mumbled speech. An open alcoholic beverage was located inside the vehicle. The odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Gomez Izaras breath and person. On May 21st, 2023, at approximately 0442 hours, I placed Gomez Izara under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack. A search incident to arrest of Gomez Izaras person was conducted. The search of Gomez Izaras person was negative. I transported Gomez Izara to the College Park Barrack. Gomez Izara was played the DR-15 Advice of Rights English recording provided by MVA. Gomez Izara was provided with a copy of the DR-15 to read along as well. At approximately 0527 hours, Gomez Izara refused to take an alcohol concentration test.  The evaluation was performed in the DUI Processing Room at Maryland State Police College Park Q Barrack (10100 Rhode Island Avenue, College Park, Maryland 20740). The area was level and dry. Gomez Izara appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 Clues Observed) The test was explained. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus. The stimulus was held approximately 12-15 inches from Gomez Izaras eye, slightly above eye level. Gomez Izara was instructed to look straight ahead, keep his head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. Gomez Izaras pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Before beginning the test, I asked Gomez Izara if he understood my instructions, to which he confirmed. Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Additional Observations  Resting gaze nystagmus was not present. Vertical gaze nystagmus was not present.  WALK AND TURN TEST (3/8 Clues Observed) The test was explained and demonstrated. Gomez Izara was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Gomez Izara was then instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and remain in that position until told to begin. Gomez Izara was advised to take nine steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line, and take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Gomez Izara was instructed to complete the second series of nine steps in the same heel to toe fashion. Gomez Izara was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, to count every step out loud, and once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Gomez Izara if he understood, and he confirmed that he did. Instructional Phase  Walking Stage (First Nine Steps)  Raises Arms  On steps five through nine of his first nine steps, Gomez Izara raises his arms greater than six inches from his body. Gomez Izara keeps his arms raised for the remainder of his first nine steps. Actual Number of Steps  Gomez Izara stepped eight times. Gomez Izara counted his first step when he was still in the beginning position. Improper Turn  Gomez Izara turned counterclockwise when his right foot was in front and his left foot was at the rear which resulted in an awkward and unnatural turn. Walking Stage (Second Nine Steps)  Raises Arms  On step seven of his second nine steps, Gomez Izara raises his arms greater than six inches from his body.  ONE-LEG STAND TEST (2/4 Clues Observed) The test was explained and demonstrated. Gomez Izara was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch the raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two, etc.), and not put his foot down until the end of the test. I asked Gomez Izara if he understood the test, and he confirmed. Seconds 1-10 Seconds 11-20 Raises Arms  Gomez Izara would raise his arms greater than six inches from his body once during the second ten seconds. Puts foot down  Gomez Izara lowered his foot to the ground, touching the ground with his entire foot once during this period. Seconds 21-30  Gomez Izaras vehicle was towed by NS Towing. I processed Gomez Izara and released him to a sober adult. Gomez Izara was issued the following citations. TA - 21-902(a1i) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL TA - 21-902(b1i) DRIVING VEH. WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL TA - 21-201(a1) DRIVER FAILURE TO OBEY PROPERLY PLACED TRAFFIC CONTROL DEVICE INSTRUCTIONS TA - 21-801(b) FAILURE TO CONTROL VEHICLE SPEED ON HIGHWAY TO AVOID COLLISION TA - 16-101(a1) DRIVING, ATTEMPTING TO DRIVE MOTOR VEHICLE ON HIGHWAY WITHOUT REQUIRED LICENSE AND AUTHORIZATION TA - 21-901.1(b) NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON The defendant was issued copies of the following documents: -Citations (listed above) -DR-15 Advice of Rights -DR-15a Order of Suspension All documents were forwarded to the Prince Georges County, State Attorney Office. All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 03:02:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 03:03:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Alvarado</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alexander</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7429</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Aaron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fleming</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sierra</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7439</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516966</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/04/2023 03:57:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/04/2023 09:57:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/04/2023 09:57:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>25</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/04/2023 09:58:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 00:43:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>384236</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Gomez Izara</LastName>
               <FirstName>Franklyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Omar</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/24/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/04/2023 10:48:24</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G522</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F652</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Gomez Izara</LastName>
               <FirstName>Franklyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Omar</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/24/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G522</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F652</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/04/2023 10:48:24</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1221</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Missouri</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>NW</StreetSuffixCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>1</SubNumber>
               <City>Washington</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20011</Zip5>
               <Zip4>7633</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.029042</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.961626</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 00:43:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 00:43:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 00:43:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 00:43:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/04/2023 09:57:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/04/2023 09:57:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155725</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 00:45:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 00:45:04</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/04/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2HGFG11918H511007</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2008</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CIV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>DC</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>GV2718</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>6</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>