<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-039847</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/11/2023 01:36:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/11/2023 01:36:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/11/2023 01:22:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/11/2023 01:22:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI / DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 01:36:40</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4725</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 09:10:24</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>BEAGLIN PARK DR/ S PARK DR</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>529572</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 01:36:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 14:02:31</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>529572</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Beaglin Park</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Salisbury</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>S</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>DR</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.57291</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.35247</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 BEAGLIN PARK DR / 901-941 S PARK DR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 BEAGLIN PARK DR / 900-913 S PARK DR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 BEAGLIN PARK DR / 902-999 S PARK DR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/11/2023 01:36:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/11/2023 01:36:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/04/2023 09:10:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 01:36:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/15/2023 16:54:32</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DEFENDANT: Joshua Neal Brooks Date of Birth: 10/30/1992 Date of Arrest: 11/11/2023 License #: B-620-440-626-835  DUI # : 23-54-224 Case # : 23-MSP-039847 Tape # :   Body Cam SFST / Arrest / Transport / Dr-15: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=123d7bbb9923405f955a71cf5e9d5629partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1   Front Camera Vehicle in Motion / SFST / Arrest: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=d4c7108dc8714a6e9a84379186999901partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1   In Car Camera Transport: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=bb49b46a74c847de9b429d58e30a11c1partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1   Additional Trooper Body Cam: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=99e1512c71af498bb6e400a802753ffepartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1   Weather: Clear / Night   Priors: No  NARRATIVE   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1):   On 11/11/2023 at approximately 0120 hours, I, TFC Todd 6929, was at the stop light on East College Avenue at Snow hill Road when I observed a vehicle, later identified as a silver Subaru Forester bearing MD registration 9CM3638, make a left hand turn out of the parking lot of the Moose Lodge. The vehicle turned correctly, however instead of turning straight in the lane it continued turning and caused the driver side tires to go over the center double yellow lines by close to two feet before correcting and travelling correctly in the lane. As I was catching up to the vehicle in the roadway I could observe it to be swerving slightly back and forth in the lane and travelling slowly. The vehicle drove slowly until it reached South Park Drive where it activated its left turn signal to make a turn. As it did this, the driver side tires went over the double yellow lines again prior to the turn lane. Based on my observations, I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on South Park drive at Beaglin Park Drive.     PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):   I made a driver side approach and before I contacted the driver I could observe that he was looking away from me. As the driver, later identified as Joshua Neal Brooks (10/30/1992 2/M), turned his head I could observe that he did it slowly and lethargically and that his eyelids were heavy and droopy. I could also observe his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. Brooks opened his door to make contact and as he did I could immediately detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from the vehicle. I explained to him the reason I pulled him over and when he was talking I could detect that his speech was slower and jumbled and slurred. I could continue to observe Brooks stumble over his words and shaking and he stated that he has social anxiety as well as a speech impediment. I could continue to detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his vehicle as I spoke with him that would become slightly stronger when he talked. I asked him how much he had to drink that night and he said nothing at all. Based on all of my observations I asked him to exit the vehicle to conduct standardized field sobriety.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):   After Brooks exited the vehicle I asked him the standardized medical questions. I first asked if he wore glasses or contacts to which he replied no. I asked if he took any medications to which he replied no. I asked him if he had any injuries to which he replied with no. Lastly, I asked if there was anything else that he would like me to be aware of that would keep him from performing any tests and he stated no. A smooth flat surface was used for all tests that was free from any debris and well lit from my flashlight, several nearby street lamps, as well as my vehicles headlights.   I explained the first test to Brooks which was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test.   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: (Clues: 6 of 6)  After explaining the test to him I asked if he had any questions to which he responded with no. I performed the test and observed the following clues:  1  Lack of Smooth Pursuit Present in Both Eyes  2  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation Present in Eyes 3  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees Present in Both Eyes   Notes: I had to remind Brooks to keep his head still immediately after starting the test.   The national standardization of the HGN test has determined that if four or more clues were evident, it is likely the subjects BAC is at or above .10. This criterion is reliable 77% of the time.    WALK AND TURN: (Clues: 3 of 8)  The next test performed is the Walk and Turn Test. The test was performed with an imaginary line and was free from any debris or obstruction. I placed Brooks in the instructional position and after explaining the test to him I asked if he had any questions to which he replied with no. I performed the test and observed the following clues: Instructional Phase: 1  Starts Too Soon  As soon as I began explaining the test he began to walk on the line forward  Walking Phase: 2  Improper Turn  3  Raises Arms  Brooks raised his arms away from his body on the return set of steps in an attempt to regain balance  The national standardization of the walk and turn test has determined that if two or more clues are evident or the subject could not finish the test, it is likely the subjects BAC is at or above .10. This criterion is reliable 68% of the time. This test combined with four or more clues on the HGN test is reliable 80% of the time.   ONE LEG STAND: (Clues: 3 of 4)   I performed the final test with Brooks which is the One Leg Stand Test. I explained it to him and asked if he had any questions to which he replied with no. I performed the test and observed the following clues.  1  Sways 2  Raises Arms  3  Puts Foot Down   ADDITIONAL TESTS:   In addition to the standardized sobriety tests I also completed several additional divided attention tests. I first asked him to say the letters F to T without saying anything before or anything after. He stated no that he cannot do that but on a normal basis he could but not now. I asked him why that was and he stated he is just not an alphabetical person.   I then asked him to count backwards from 59 to 36. He started at 59 and went down to 31 and asked if he had passed where I asked him to stop. Throughout his counting his speech was slow and slurred.   I then asked him on a scale of 1 to 10 with 1 being sober and 10 being black out drunk where he falls on that scale. After a short pause he stated that he was only a 3 and that he only had one drink at work.  I then offered Brooks a preliminary breath test to which he refused.    ARREST:   Based on my observations of his driving and field sobriety, I placed Brooks under arrest for DUI / DWI at approximately 0136 hours. I placed him in my vehicle and retrieved his belonging from his vehicle. When I reentered my vehicle, I could detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage had filled my vehicle that had not been present before placing Brooks inside.   I arrived at the barrack at placed Brooks in the DUI room to read him his Dr-15 Advice of Rights. I read the form to him out loud and gave him a form to follow along with. After reading the form and answering any and all questions Brooks had, he refused to take the Intoximeter test at approximately 0207 hours. While answering questions and speaking to Brooks I continued to observe that his eyes were bloodshot and gassy and in several different rooms and environments I continued to detect the odor of alcohol coming from his breath. He was appropriately charged and later released to a sober driver.   Brooks was polite and respectful through my interactions with him.  I am a certified police officer in the state of Maryland with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with live donors at the Maryland State Police Academy. I have also completed an additional 16 hours of Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training through the Maryland State Police. My training, knowledge, and experience have led to several prior DUI arrests and subsequent convictions.  CASE CLOSED  TFC Todd 6929 </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6929</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 18:47:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6929</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 18:50:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Huntington</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6843</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barfield</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jacob</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7185</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Todd</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bradley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6929</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oborokumo</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tamarapreye</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4725</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Todd</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bradley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6929</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Todd</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bradley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6929</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529315</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 01:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6929</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 16:03:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6929</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 16:04:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6929</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 16:03:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6929</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 16:05:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>245762</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Brooks</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Neil</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/30/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/17/2019 05:38:27</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Brooks</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Neil</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/30/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/17/2019 05:38:27</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>710</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Beauchamp</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>H</SubNumber>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21801</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.611002</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.360826</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7184</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Parsonsburg</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Parsonsburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21849</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.468799</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.388213</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6929</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 16:05:22</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6929</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 16:05:22</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6929</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 16:03:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6929</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 16:03:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>