<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-040685</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/17/2023 07:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/17/2023 07:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/17/2023 07:35:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/17/2023 07:35:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Two vehicle collision with injuries, and one operator arrested for drug related impairment.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 07:56:25</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5932</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 12:24:37</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>W PULASKI HWY/ OLD ELK NECK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>491289</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 07:56:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/19/2023 11:25:32</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>491289</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>953</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Pulaski</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Elkton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21921</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-75.887198</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.611289</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/17/2023 07:56:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/17/2023 07:56:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/05/2023 12:23:33</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/17/2023 07:56:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:13</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reeves</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jared</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7123</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Desai</LastName>
            <FirstName>Karan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7045</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hughes</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7111</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>530153</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/17/2023 07:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/19/2023 11:26:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/19/2023 11:26:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/19/2023 11:26:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/19/2023 11:26:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/24/2023 09:31:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/24/2023 09:31:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/05/2023 12:23:33</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/24/2023 09:31:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:13</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>CASE NUMBER: 23-MSP-040685 DUI NUMBER: 23-148 DUI CITATION NUMBER: 0YB0V1W TRAFFIC CRIME: Driving Vehicle While Under the Influence of Drugs DEFENDANT: DVORAK, LISA DATE OF BIRTH: 01/11/1963 LICENSE STATE  NUMBER: (MD) D162522264032 COMMERCIAL DRIVERS LICENSE: No  VEHICLE INFORMATION: 1989 DODGE DYNASTY GRAY SEDAN (MD: 1BD1090) COMMERCIAL VEHICLE: No LOCATION OF INCIDENT: 953 PULASKI HWY (W/B), ELKTON, MARYLAND 21921 DATE  TIME OF ARREST: 11/17/2023 at 0825 hours SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER: No ACCIDENT INVOLVED: Yes ALCOHOL RESTRICTION: No WEATHER  SURFACE: Clear  Pavement  LIGHTING: Daylight TYPE OF TEST: Alcohol Concentration Test    SCENE PROCESSING: * BODY-WORN CAMERA ACTIVATED * SFSTs Offered (Completed) * Arrest for DUI/DWI  * Vehicle Tow(s) * Accident Exchange Form   BARRACK PROCESSING: * DR15 (Advice of Rights) * MSP 033 (Notification to Defendant of Result of Test) * MSP 180 (Advice of Miranda Rights)  * Traffic Citations * ACRS Report  CERTIFICATES  TRAINING: * I am trained and certified to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) and Preliminary Breath Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  * I am trained and certified to administer Advanced Roadside Impairment Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  * I am trained and certified to administer Drug Recognition Expert Evaluations (DRE) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  * I have attended and successfully completed the Advanced Driving Under the Influence training course through the Maryland State Police S.P.I.D.R.E. Team.  * I have successfully completed the Marijuana DUI Investigation online course through the Central Valley California HIDTA.  * I attended the six-month Maryland State Police Academy in Sykesville, Maryland. While there, I was also trained in the detection, identification and processing of numerous controlled dangerous substances. Prior to becoming a Maryland State Trooper, I was a prior Police Officer for approximately four years in the State of Pennsylvania working in high crime areas (Cities of Philadelphia and Chester) known for drug trafficking. During my time as a Maryland State Trooper, I was temporarily assigned for approximately six months to the Wicomico County Narcotics Task Force (WINTF) where I assisted with investigations involving Controlled Dangerous Substances. I have also attended specialized training involving the possession, sale, and processing of controlled dangerous substances, and continue to do so.  NARRATIVE:  PHASE #1  VEHICLE IN MOTION:  On Friday, November 17, 2023, at approximately 0735 hours, I, TFC. M. Hughes #7111 responded to the area of Serenity Health (a methadone clinic located at 953 West Pulaski Highway, Elkton, Maryland 21921) in reference to two vehicle collision involving injuries. Upon my arrival, I was met by assisting Troopers who identified the at fault vehicle (a gray 1989 Dodge Dynasty sedan displaying Maryland registration 1BD1090), being operated by Lisa Dvorak DOB: 01/11/1963. Witnesses on scene reported Dvorak failed to yield the right away of westbound traffic on West Pulaski Highway as she attempted to crossover to eastbound West Pulaski Highway from Serenity Health.   PHASE #2  PERSONAL CONTACT:   I made contact with Dvorak who admitted to being the driver (sole occupant) of the aforementioned vehicle during the time of the collision. Dvorak reported when she was leaving the Serenity Health parking lot, she thought traffic appeared further away (poor perception of time and distance). While speaking with Dvorak, I observed the following additional signs of impairment:    Slow, low, raspy speech.  Slurred speech (did have dentures in).  Droopy eyelids.     Due to my observations, I asked Dvorak why she was coming from the Serenity Health. Dvorak reported she is a patient there, and is prescribed to methadone (152 mg dosage). Dvorak was asked if she had just taken her methadone which she reported she did. Dvorak went on to report she was referred to the clinic by her former doctor who lost his license to practice. Dvorak admitted to over using her prescribed medications from that doctor after initially taking pain medications for a herniated disc in her bac which led to having a pinched nerve, which lead to her needing methadone; however, Dvorak said she initially started off being prescribed to 180 mgs, and is down to 152 mgs.   PHASE #3  PRE-ARREST SCREENING:    I asked Dvorak to participate in Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Dvorak then agreed to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.   PRE-SCREENING QUESTIONS:   I asked Dvorak a series of questions prior to performing Standardized Field Sobriety Tests:  * Glasses/Contacts: Yes (for driving purposes). * Injuries/Disabilities: No injuries (but shaken up) / Disabilities are a herniated disc and a pinched nerve. * Medications or Drugs: Methadone (and other medications she denied taking today (see attached medication list)). * Visual Mouth Check: Dentures.  * Miscellaneous: Denture(s) were removed for remainder of investigation until the breath test was completed.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS TEST:    I explained the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test to Dvorak. After explaining the test, I asked Dvorak if she understood the test and if she had any questions.Dvorak appeared confused by the instructions. After repeating the instructions, Dvorak stated she understood the test and I began.During this test, I had to advised Dvorak several times to not move her head, and to follow the stimulus with her eyes only.   Resting Nystagmus: No Equal Tracking: Yes Equal Pupil Size: Yes  Lack of Smooth Pursuit: Not Present Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation: Not Present Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees: Not Present Vertical Gaze Nystagmus: Not Present   Total Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Clues: 0 of 6  WALK  TURN TEST:  WEATHER: Clear. SURFACE: Pavement free of debris.  I proceeded by instructing Dvorak into the instructional stance. I next demonstrated and gave Dvorak instructions. After the instructions/demonstration, Dvorak was asked if she understood the test. Dvorak again appeared confused, so the test was demonstrated and explained again. Dvorak then advised she understood. I then advised Dvorak to begin the test.    During the instructional phase, Dvorak show great difficulties in keeping her balance as she continuously stumbled out of the instructional stance.   INSTRUCTIONAL PHASE:  BROKE HEEL-TO-TOE STANCE   WALKING STAGE 1ST NINE:  INCORRECT NUMBER OF STEPS TAKEN: eight steps (she counted her stance as step one). MISSES HEEL-TO-TOE: Step one. STEPS OFF LINE: Steps three, four, five, six, seven and eight (stumbled off line on step four). USES ARMS FOR BALANCE STOPPED WALKING: Step eight.  TURN:  Unsatisfactorily  used both feet to turn around towards her right.  WALKING STAGE 2ND NINE:  MISSES HEEL-TO-TOE: Steps six and eight. STEPS OFF LINE: Steps one, two, three, four, five, seven and nine (stumbled off line several times). USES ARMS FOR BALANCE   During the walking phase of this test, Dvorak displayed depressed reflexes, confusion, and an inability to concentrate. After she completed the first walking stage, she stopped and asked if she was done. She then waited for instructions, so I advised her to continue with her turn and complete the second stage as instructed and demonstrated.   Total Walk and Turn Clues:7 of 8  ONE LEG STAND TEST:  LEG RAISED: Left  Right  I next explained and demonstrated the One Leg Stand test to Dvorak. I then asked Dvorak if she understood the test and she stated she did. I asked Dvorak if she had any questions before beginning. Dvorak was confused, so the test was again demonstrated and the instructions were repeated. Dvorak advised she did bump her left knee during the collision. She was again advised to use either leg. Dvorak was asked if she understood the test. She advised she did, so I advised her to begin. During the test, Dvorak took several seconds to lift her legs. When she did, she almost fell over several times, which led to her switching her raised leg.   SECONDS 1-10:  PUTS FOOT DOWN USES ARMS FOR BALANCE (raised greater than six inches from her side(s)) SWAYS  SECONDS 11-20:  PUTS FOOT DOWN USES ARMS FOR BALANCE (raised greater than six inches from her side(s)) SWAYS  SECONDS 21-30:  PUTS FOOT DOWN USES ARMS FOR BALANCE (raised greater than six inches from her side(s)) SWAYS  Total One Leg Stand Clues:3 of 4  ARIDE TEST(s):  LACK OF CONVERGENCE TEST:    I explained the lack of convergence test to Dvorak. After explaining the test, I asked Dvorak if she understood the test and if she had any questions.After given the instructions, Dvorak stated she understood the test and I began.During this test, Dvoraks eyes failed to converge. She tracked the stimulus; however, she the stimulus was moved towards the bridge of her nose, she continued looking straight.    MODIFIED ROMBERG BALANCE TEST:   During the instructions of this test, Dvorak again appeared confused. The test was explained again. She then advised she understood the test. Dvorak was then advised to begin. Dvorak was observed swaying in a side to side motion which was approximately 1 inch in both directions. Dvorak estimated which was supposed to be 30 seconds; however, she thought I advised her 20 seconds. Due to the lack of concentration, Dvorak estimated her 20 seconds of time in 28 seconds (outside the DRE normal range of plus or minus five seconds). Dvorak then reattempted the test, but for 30 seconds this time. During the second attempt, Dvorak estimated her 30 seconds of time in 47 seconds (outside the DRE normal range of plus or minus five seconds), displaying a poor perception of time and distance. She also displayed an inability to concentrate during the instructions.   FINGER-TO-NOSE TEST:   During the instructions of this test, Dvorak appear confused. After given the instructions and demonstrating the test, Dvorak asked if she was to touch her eyes with her fingers. She was advised no, and instructed on what to do. When advised to start the test, Dvorak paused for several seconds, opened her eyes and asked if she was to start. She was advised yes.   width:624px"&gt;          border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:1px solid black; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Hand Told to Use     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:1px solid black; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Spot on Face Touched     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:1px solid black; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Portion of Finger Used     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:1px solid black; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;Miscellaneous           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Left     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Left Nostril     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;N/A           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Right     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Right Nostril     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;N/A           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Left     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Left Nostril     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;N/A           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Right     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Tip of Nose     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;N/A           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Right     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Right Nostril     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;N/A           border-left:1px solid black; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:142px" valign="top"&gt;Left     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Tip of Nose     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:181px" valign="top"&gt;Pad     border-left:none; border-right:1px solid black; border-top:none; padding:7px 7px 7px 7px; width:120px" valign="top"&gt;N/A         During the start of this test, Dvorak was observed peaking her eyes open to help assist with locating the tip of her nose. She was advised to keep her eyes closed.   PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST:  N/A  ARREST  TRANSPORT:    Based on the following, I had reason to believe Dvorak was driving a motor vehicle while under the influence of drugs:  * At fault driver in vehicle collision. * Droopy eyelids. * No odor of alcoholic beverages or indicators of alcohol use detected. * Dvorak having a slurred, slow, low, raspy speech. * Dvorak observed stumbling, and displaying depressed reflexes.  * Dvoraks poor perception of time and distance.  * Dvoraks inability to concentrate. * Dvoraks admission to consuming her prescribed 152 mgs of methadone just prior to driving.  * Dvorak having two additional bottles of methadone in her vehicle. * My observed signs of impairment    I placed Dvorak under arrest for the suspicion of driving vehicle while under the influence of drug at approximately 0825 hours, and was transported to the North East Barrack.  20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD:  Upon my arrival to the North East Barrack, I read Dvorak the DR-15 Advice of Rights while providing her with a copy of the DR-15 form to follow along with. While reading Dvorak the DR-15, I observed her on the nod while taking slow breaths (indicators of one under the influence of analgesic narcotics). After reading the DR-15 form, Dvorak agreed to the alcohol concentration test signing the DR-15 form at approximately 0855 hours.  ALCOHOL CONCENTRATION TEST:  INSTRUMENT SERIAL NUMBER: 011750 CERTIFIED EXPIRATION DATE: 12/31/2023 TEST TECHNICIAN: Cpl. Davis #4976     At approximately 0908 hours, Dvorak gave a breath specimen which was found to contain an alcohol concentration of .00 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath, which was expected.   DISPOSITION: After the alcohol concentration test, I explained to Dvorak that I wanted to read her the Advice of Miranda Rights, so I can ask her additional questions and possibly conduct a DRE evaluation. I then read the form to Dvorak at 0915 hours. At the conclusion of the Advice of Miranda Rights, Dvora opted to invoked her rights by requesting the assistance of an attorney. No further questions pertaining to the investigation were asked. She was then placed into a holding cell briefly, before being released to family in the North East Barracks front lobby. Dvorak was given all copies of pertinent paperwork. All times in this report are approximate. All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/26/2023 17:27:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 13:37:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kres</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hughes</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7111</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>60</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/24/2023 14:29:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7111</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/24/2023 14:29:45</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393812</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dvorak</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lisa</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/11/1963 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/24/2023 14:28:40</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D162</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dvorak</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lisa</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/11/1963 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D162</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/24/2023 14:28:40</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>813</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Nottingham</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Elkton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21921</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.882329</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.619577</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/24/2023 14:29:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/24/2023 14:29:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7111</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/24/2023 14:29:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>