<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-041499</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/22/2023 19:14:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/22/2023 19:14:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/22/2023 18:41:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/22/2023 18:41:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Single Vehicle Collision, DUI, DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/22/2023 19:14:47</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6055</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 11:38:53</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>HAUGHS CHURCH RD/ WOODSBORO PIKE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>713984</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/22/2023 19:14:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 04:01:18</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>713984</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Haughs Church</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Keymar</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>PIKE</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-77.257614</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.581072</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11500-11800 HAUGHS CHURCH RD / 12700-12798 WOODSBORO PIKE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/22/2023 19:14:44</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/22/2023 19:14:44</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/10/2023 11:38:54</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/22/2023 19:14:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP marked vehicle B-29 is equipped with an In-Car mobile recording device. Body Worn Camera was functioning and recorded entire incident for TFC. Coss #6568.  Assisting: Sgt. Gregg Lantz #1981  Body Worn Camera Functional. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Defendant: LaClair, Nikki Lynn Date of Birth: 03/30/1998 Date of Arrest: 11/22/2023 Time of Arrest: 1933 hours DUI #: 23-MSP-041499 (Frederick Barrack)  Attachments: Alcohol Influence Form DR-15 DR-15A MSP 33 LaClairs Drivers License Information LaClairs Vehicle Information Photographof LaClairs license   Certifications and Training: * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Successfully attended and completed the Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) Training Course. * Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police. * Trained and certified to operate Preliminary Breath Testing (PBT) through the Maryland State Police and the Office of the Chief Medical Examiner.  Vehicle In Motion (Phase 1):   On 11/22/2023 at approximately 1842 hours, I, TFC. Coss #6568 was dispatched to respond to a single vehicle collision in the area of Haughs Church Road and Route 194 in Frederick County, Maryland. The call came in through an auto crash notification for a vehicle. I arrived at the scene of the collision where fireboard had the intersection shut down. I observed a white Kia Sportage displaying Maryland registration 7EY5383 partially in a ditch on the southbound side of Route 194 with heavy front end damage and airbag deployment. The driver of the vehicle was talking to EMS at my arrival. The driver refused any medical treatment and fire board cleared the scene (Ambulance 169, Run #:F23036719).  Personal Contact (Phase 2): font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;   I made contact with the driver and identified her by name and date of birth as Nikki Lynn LaClair (DOB:03/30/1998). I introduced myself and advised Laclair that I would be handling the collision. LaClair said the vehicle belonged to her. I asked LaClair what happened. LaClair said she turned too soon and was heading home from her brother in laws to pick up her son. LaClair was apologetic during the interaction saying she was sorry. While standing next to LaClair, I was approximately two feet away, and I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from LaClairs breath and person. LaClair also had clear, glassy eyes. I asked LaClair how much she had to drink for the night. LaClair replied I had a drink when I was with them out at dinner, which was at, in New Market. I asked her what time she had it. She said over an hour and a half ago. I asked LaClair if she was the only one in the vehicle. She replied yes. I requested LaClairs drivers license, registration card and insurance for the vehicle. LaClair looked around inside her vehicle and couldnt find it on the scene. I had LaClair move over to the front of my patrol vehicle at northbound Route 194 just north of the intersection of the collision on the right shoulder. I asked LaClair what happened in the collision again. LaClair replied, I was leaving my brother-in-Laws home, and I decided that I could make that turn and I could not make that turn.   I asked LaClair to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. She agreed to take the test. I asked LaClair how long ago she had her one drink again. LaClair said she had one glass of wine at Linganore Winery a couple of hours ago, ate at the Derby in New Market Maryland, then went to her Brother-In-Laws residence.    font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3):  The evaluation was performed in the roadway in front of my patrol vehicle. The surface was dry, flat,and free from any obvious debris. The weather was cold. The lighting condition were my patrol vehicle lights (front lights were deactivated for tests). LaClair appeared to be in good physical condition, and did not have any signs of obvious injuries.  I asked LaClair the following questions: -Medication None -Physical Injuries  None. -Contact or Glasses None   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6 clues observed)   The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my ink pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from LaClairs eyes, just above eye level. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. LaClairs pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I asked LaClair if she understood the instructions, and she said yes.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Vertical Gaze Nystagmus - Present  Walk and Turn (6/8 clues observed)   Prior to LaClair performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. LaClair was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. She was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. LaClair was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. LaClair was to keep her hands flat at her side, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, LaClair was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. LaClair was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps, which were to be performed identical to the first series. LaClair was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her side, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked LaClair if she understood the test, and she said yes.  Instructional Stage: 1.) LaClair was not able to maintain her balance throughout the whole demonstration of the test. LaClair broke the stance from heel to toeon multiple occasions while I explained the test.  Walking Stage (1st Nine): 1.) LaClair did not touch her heel to toe on steps 4 to 5. 2,) LaClair stepped off the line on step 5. 3.) LaClair raised her arms by more than 6 inches throughout the test. 4.) LaClair took a total of 29 steps instead of 9.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): 1.) LaClair raised her arms by more than 6 inches throughout the test. 2.) LaClair did not touch heel to toe on steps 1 to 2. 3.) LaClair stopped walking on step 4 and then continued walking again up to step 6. 4.) LaClair took a total of 6 steps instead of 9.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Turn: LaClair turned Incorrectly, she did not leave her front foot planted, and lifted both feet to turn around.  One Leg Stand(1/4 clues observed)  Prior to LaClair performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. LaClair was instructed to stand with Her heels together and hands down by Her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, She was to raise the foot of Her choice off the ground approximately sixinches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked LaClair if she understood the test, and she stated Yes.LaClair balanced on her right foot.  Instructional Stage: While placing LaClair in the instructional phase, She almost fell over just by standing still.  Balance and Count Stage: 1.) LaClair put her foot down on one occasion during the entire test.  LaClair did agree to submit to a Preliminary Breath Test.Results .154 BrAC.  Arrest:  Based on the following, I had reason to believe LaClair was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol.  *LaClair was the driver involved in the single vehicle motor vehicle Collision into a ditch. * LaClair smelled like the odor of alcoholic beverages emitting from her breath and person. * LaClair admitted to drinking one glass of wine earlier at Linganore Winery. * LaClair had clear glassy eyes. * My observed signs of impairment as she performed Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.    LaClair was placed under arrest at 1933 hours. LaClair was transported to the Frederick Law Enforcement Center. LaClair was readthe DR-15 Advice of Rights form electronically with a copy of the form in front of her. The formreviewed the possible suspensions and sanctions that can be imposed by the MVA per the DR-15 form. Once the DR-15 form was completely read, LaClair Refused to submit to the Intoximeter test and agreed to sign the DR-15 indicating the same at approximately 2028 hours.LaClair added that she did not eat anything today due to stress, and that she has done some tests in Ohio in the pass to see how alcohol affects her when she eats or doesnt. LaClair said she was outrageous when she didnt eat in the past, according to her tests performed in Ohio. LaClair was provided the appropriate citations and paperwork, and released to a sober ride. LaClair was respectful and cooperative throughout the entire incident.  All Events Did Occur in Frederick County Maryland.  Case Status: Closed </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6568</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 04:08:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6568</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 00:55:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>70</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lantz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gregg</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1981</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Coss</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6568</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Freysz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6055</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Coss</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6568</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Coss</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6568</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>530969</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 04:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6568</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 04:52:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6568</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 04:53:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>25</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>C</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6568</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 04:06:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6568</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 04:55:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>394090</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>LaClair</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nikki</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/30/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/29/2023 04:05:40</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L246</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>LaClair</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nikki</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/30/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L246</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/29/2023 04:05:40</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11531</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Haughs Church</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Keymar</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21757</Zip5>
               <Zip4>8725</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.262987</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.58554</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>321</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>961</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5735</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6568</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 04:55:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6568</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 04:55:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6568</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 04:52:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6568</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 04:52:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159366</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6568</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 04:07:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6568</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 04:07:41</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>KNDPUCAF1P7036241</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2023</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>KIA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SPT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7EY5383</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>