<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-042286</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/30/2023 00:25:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/30/2023 00:25:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/29/2023 23:58:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>HANDGUN ON PERSON, PWID, CDS, DUI, DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 00:25:42</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/08/2023 15:32:21</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I83 SB,LUTHERVILLE TIMONIUM</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>714610</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 00:25:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 01:18:38</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>714610</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I83 Sb Lutherville Timonium</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.6621633333333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.4056905</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/30/2023 00:25:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/30/2023 00:25:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/06/2023 10:25:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 00:25:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>R-29 equipped with in-car camera and body-worn camera. Contact Sgt. Twardowski (joseph.twardowski@maryland.gov) for camera footage.  Case# 23-MSP-042286 Defendant: JaAli Mahire Drumgold-Walton Date of Birth: 03/19/2003  Date of Arrest: 11/30/2023 Time of Arrest: 0026 hours DUI #: 23-630 Citation #: 6GG0XD0 Breath Result: .00, refused DRE   Certificates and Training *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration  *Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) Certified  *Certified Emergency Medical Technician by the Maryland Institute of Emergency Medical Services Systems  *Certified RADAR/LIDAR operator by the Maryland State Police  *Certified License Plate Reader (LPR) operator by the Maryland State Police  *Apprehended over 180 impaired drivers while working as a Maryland State Trooper  *2023 Distinguished graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute  *2023 Ocean City DUI Conference  Vehicle In Motion (Phase 1)  On November 30th, 2023 at approximately 0000 hours I, Trooper Sigman #7376, currently assigned to the Golden Ring Barrack, was on routine patrol of the inner loop of I695 prior to 83 south in a photo enforced work zone in lane 3 when I observed a black Chevy Blazer bearing Maryland registration of 2GA4391 pass my vehicle at a high rate of speed unsafely to the right in lane 4. I then got behind the Blazer and paced it in the construction zone at 79mph in a posted 55mph zone for greater than 4/10 of a mile. My vehicle, R-29, speedometer was properly calibrated and found to be functioning properly prior to the date and time of the stop. The Blazer continued to accelerate while in lane 4. I then observed the Blazer cross the solid white line and cross onto the right shoulder with both passenger side tires. The Blazer then slowly drifted back into lane 4. The Blazer then began to drift from side to side within lane 4. As the Blazer approached the 83 south exit, it suddenly slammed on its brakes for no apparent reason. The Blazer then exited onto 83 south. I then activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the black Chevy Blazer bearing Maryland registration of 2GA4391. The Blazer then slammed on the brakes and slowly pulled to the right shoulder of I83 south prior to Ruxton Road.  Personal Contact (Phase 2)  I then made a passenger side approach of the black Chevy Blazer bearing Maryland registration of 2GA4391. Upon arriving at the passenger door I immediately detected the strong odor of burnt cannabis emanating from the vehicle. I then identified myself, the reason for the strop, and requested the drivers license. The driver then advised me that it was a rental vehicle and handed me his Maryland Provisional Drivers License which identified him as JaAli Mahire Drumgold-Walton (03/19/2003). I observed that Drumgold-Walton appeared extremely nervous while making rapid uncoordinated movements, bloodshot eyes, dilated pupils, and eyelid tremors. Drumgold-Walton then advised he was driving from his home and was traveling to a club downtown.  I then requested Drumgold-Walton to exit and walk to the front of his vehicle. I then asked Drumgold-Walton when he had last consumed cannabis. Drumgold-Walton replied I was just in the house chillin my little brothers and my cousin. We was smokin. We was chillin from like 9 all the way up until I left. I then asked Drumgold-Walton if he would consent to standardized field sobriety testing. Drumgold-Walton agreed.  Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3)  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of I83. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 31 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlights, and overhead lights, and my vehicles takedown lights. My vehicles front facing emergency lights were deactivated for the duration of the field sobriety tests. Drumgold-Walton appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries and or defects.  I asked Drumgold-Walton the following questions:  Injuries- none Medical conditions- none Medications- none Glasses or contacts- none Alcoholic beverages- denied Controlled dangerous substance- smoking cannabis from 9pm until approximately 1150pm    Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The test was explained. I then began the test. I did not observe any resting nystagmus. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit - present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - present in both eyes *Vertical Gaze Nystagmus - not present in either eye  Lack of convergence was present     Walk and Turn (6/8 clues observed)  Prior to Drumgold-Walton performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. I asked Drumgold-Walton if he had any questions. Drumgold-Walton stated that he understood the test.    Instructional Stage: Steps out of starting position Starts prior to being instructed to do so   Walking Stage (1st Nine):  Misses heel to toe Steps off line Takes 10 steps then stops walking, Takes another step and stops walking again Takes 20 total steps (the test was then concluded as it was clear that Drumgold-Walton did not remember the instructions)    Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  Not attempted      Turn: Not attempted  One Leg Stand (1/4)  Prior to Drumgold-Walton performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Drumgold-Waltonadvised that Drumgold-Walton understood the test.  Instructional Stage: Nothing observed     Balance and Count Stage  Seconds 0-10: Sways from side to side      Seconds 11-20: Sways from side to side      Seconds 21-30: Sways from side to side   During the test Drumgold-Walton exhibited an inability to remember and follow instructions. Drumgold-Walton had to be reminded to lift his foot 6 inches above the ground and to look at his toe. Drumgold-Walton also failed to continuously count by thousands.   Modified Romberg Balance Test  I instructed Drumgold-Walton to stand with his feet together and arms by his side. Drumgold-Walton was instructed to close his eyes and estimate the passage of thirty seconds. Drumgold-Walton was instructed to open his eyes and say done when thirty seconds had passed. Drumgold-Walton stated that he understood the test.  Drumgold-Walton estimated thirty seconds had passed in 25 seconds Eyelids tremors were observed    I instructed Drumgold-Walton to stand with his feet together and arms by his side. I instructed Drumgold-Walton to extend the index finger of both hands while down at his side. I advised that when I say right he was to lift his right index finger, touch the tip of his nose, then put it back down at his side. Drumgold-Walton was instructed to do the same with his left index finger when I said Left.. Drumgold-Walton stated that he understood the test.  Left- misses nose Right- misses nose Left- Right- misses nose Right- misses nose Left-    Arrest  Based on the following, I had probable cause to believe Drumgold-Walton was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of cannabis, a schedule I controlled dangerous substance:  *Passing a police car at 79mph in a construction zone *Unable to maintain a single lane of travel *Drifting from side to side within the lane *Strong odor of burnt cannabis emanating from the vehicle *Bloodshot eyes *Admission to smoking cannabis for over four hours straight *Eyelid tremors *Poor SFST     At this time Drumgold-Walton was placed under arrest for DUI. Drumgold-Waltonwas then handcuffed and searched. The search of Drumgold-Waltons person revealed a digital scale in his right pocket with green leafy residue known to be cannabis. A large amount of US Currency was located in his left pocket. The later count of the US currency was found to to be $5992. Drumgold-Walton was then placed in the front seat of R-29 and seat belted inside. Drumgold-Walton was then mirandized.  I then returned to Drumgold-Waltons vehicle and began a search incident to arrest. I then opened the center console which revealed a loaded Glock 43X handgun (Serial #BRHV929). Drumgold-Walton was under 21 years of age which prohibited him from possessing and carrying a handgun. I then requested another unit to respond to my location to standby while the remainder of my search was completed. SGT Twardowski then arrived on scene and stood by with Drumgold-Walton while I completed my search. A search was then completed, and a plastic shopping bag was then located in the back seat. The bag was found to contain 343 individual dispensary style cannabis bags. I then located a backpack in the rear passenger seat which contained multiple large plastic bags which contained a green vegetable substance know by my TKE to be cannabis, a schedule I controlled dangerous substance. I then located a black duffle bag which contained a large amount of cannabis. The search revealed a total of:  -343 cannabis dispensary style bags -a Glock 43 #BRHV929 with one round in the chamber and 8 rounds loaded in the magazine -One digital scale with cannabis residue -a combined weight of 390.5 grams of cannabis -15.0 grams of Psilocybin Mushrooms, a schedule I controlled dangerous substance -$5992 in US currency  Based on the above and based upon my training, knowledge, and experience I believed Drumgold-Walton to be distributing cannabis and Psilocybin Mushrooms. Both are schedule I controlled dangerous substances.  The Gun Center was then contacted and advised that Drumgold-Walton was prohibited from possessing a handgun based on his age.  Drumgold-Walton was then transported to the Golden Ring Barrack for processing.  Once at the Golden Ring Barrack Drumgold-Waltonwas walked inside and placed in the intoximeter room. A physical copy of the DR15 was placed in front of him and the audio version was played aloud. At the conclusion of the audio Drumgold-Walton stated that he wished to take the intoximeter test. The time was 0053 hours  20-Minute Observation Period:  Nothing observed during the observation period.     Intoximeter Result:  .00 at 0111 hours. SGT Twardowski was the intoximeter operator.  I then asked Drumgold-Walton if he would submit to a drug recognition expert evaluation. Drumgold-Walton refused. The evidence was then processed per agency policy and the currency was seized. The statement of charges and statement of probable cause was then sent to the Essex commissioner. Drumgold-Walton was then placed in front of the Essex Commissioner. Drumgold-Walton was then held without bail.  Drumgold-Walton was then transported to BCDC without incident.  All above events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/01/2023 03:48:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 13:10:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wilson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4772</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sigman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7376</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0493</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0493</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:37:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:37:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 0487</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 0487</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 5285</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 5285</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1454</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1454</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1455</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1455</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1692</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1692</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1118</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1118</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1564</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1564</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>12</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>12</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>13</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>13</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>14</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>14</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>15</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15647</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>15</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15647</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>16</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>20512</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>16</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>20512</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>17</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15550</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>17</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15550</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:43:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>18</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>18</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:44:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:44:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>19</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>19</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/29/2023 23:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:44:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:44:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>20</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:47:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 08:43:59</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>394187</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>DRUMGOLD-WALTON</LastName>
               <FirstName>JAALI</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MAHIRE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/19/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/30/2023 02:46:26</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>DRUMGOLD-WALTON</LastName>
               <FirstName>JAALI</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MAHIRE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/19/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D652</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/30/2023 02:46:26</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4950</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Lockard</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Owings Mills</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21117</Zip5>
               <Zip4>6114</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.812457</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.408337</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>667</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>308</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4541</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:47:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:47:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:47:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:47:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 02:37:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 02:37:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159405</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 04:29:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 04:29:17</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3GNKBCR40PS213423</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2023</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>BLZ</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2GA4391</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 04:32:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 04:32:50</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>MSPPI</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <SerialNumber>BRHV929</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256995</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>Glock</Make>
         <Model>43x</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 04:33:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 04:33:25</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>343 DISPENSARY STYLE BAGS</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>334</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256996</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>343</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 04:33:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 04:33:56</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256997</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>390.5</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 04:33:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 04:33:56</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256997</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>390.5</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 04:33:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 04:33:56</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256997</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>390.5</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 04:34:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 04:34:28</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Psilocybin mushroom</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>256998</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>K</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>15</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>