<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-039530</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/09/2023 01:23:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/09/2023 01:23:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/09/2023 00:44:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/09/2023 00:44:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Vehicle was stopped for moving violation. Upon contact with the driver, the odor of an alcoholic beverage was detected. SFST's was conducted and driver was placed under arrest for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 01:23:16</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0104</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/16/2023 13:58:28</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>LEONARDTOWN RD/ BILLINGSLEY RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>171244</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 01:23:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/10/2023 03:20:07</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>171244</AddressId>
         <StreetName>RT. 5 at Billingsley Road</StreetName>
         <City>Waldorf</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20601</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.861629</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.575178</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/09/2023 01:23:14</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/09/2023 01:23:14</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/16/2023 12:32:11</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 01:23:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSPQ031</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 11:32:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car camera and body worn camera operational H-13.  Defendant:Goldring, Clifton Jerome  Date of Birth:03/01/1961  Time of arrest: 0106 hours  Location:Southbound Route 5 at Billingsley Road, Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland, 20601.  Maryland identification:G-436-119-402-159  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; DUI#: 23-190  6th DUI  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING  *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police.  *Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement through Charles County Sheriffs Office. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; *Trained in Crisis Intervention Team through Calvert County Sheriffs Office.  NARRATIVE/ VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1): font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; On 11/09/2023 at approximately 0046 hours, Cpl. Manning #6421 with the Maryland State Police La Plata Barrack H stopped a vehicle for traveling over the posted 45 Mile Per Hour (MPH) posted speed limit at 67 MPH. Cpl. Manning was able to identify the driver through his Maryland identification card as, Goldring, Clifton Jerome (1/M, DOB:03/01/1961). I then responded to Cpl. Manning at 0052 hours to resume the investigation. Once I arrived on scene, I observed a blue Ford pickup truck, bearing Maryland registration 10551K. Cpl. Manning advised to me the tags are expired on 04/01/2022.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2): font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  Upon contact with the driver, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle. I asked the driver how many alcoholic beverages did he consume, he advised A couple beers. While speaking with Goldring, I observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. While speaking with Goldring, I observed his speech to be slurred. I requested Goldring to exit the vehicle to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFTSS), which he agreed to take. As Goldring approached the front of his vehicle, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):  Cpl. Manning assisted with the traffic stop. I asked Goldring if he had any medical conditions, I should be aware of, he advised No. I asked Goldring if he is a diabetic or have high blood pressure, he advised, No. I asked Goldring if he had any head injuries or concussions, he advised, No. I then asked Goldring does he wear glasses or contacts, he advised No. I asked Goldring if he can perform the Walk and Turn (WAT) and the One Leg Stand (OLS), he advised Yes. I asked Goldring if there is anything I should be aware of before conducting the test, he advised No.I then asked Goldring if he could see the pen displayed approximately 12 inches away from his eyes, he advised, Yes.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS TEST: (6/6 clues observed).  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Goldrings eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping hishead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hiseyes until told to stop. Hispupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. Hewas positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring displayed equal pupil size, equal tracking and no resting nystagmus in both eyes.  Goldring displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  Goldring displayed nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  Goldring displayed nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.  VERTICAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring did not display vertical gaze nystagmus in both eyes.  WALK AND TURN: (8/8 clues observed). font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Prior to Goldring performing the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Goldring was instructed to place hisright foot directly in front of hisleft foot and touch heel to toe. He was instructed and demonstrated to place hishands flat at hissides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Hewas advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. Hewas instructed to keep hishands flat at hissides, keep hiseyes focused on hisfeet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Goldring was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with hisrear foot to turn completely around. Goldring was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Hewas instructedonce he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep hishands down by hissides, look down at hisfeet, and count each step out loud. Goldring was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, Yes. While explaining the test, I noticed Goldring had urinated on himself.Goldring advised there is a metal rod in his right leg before starting the test.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring wore brown boots for the test. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring began the test too early. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring could not keep his balance before beginning the test. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring stepped off-line on all nine steps, on his first set nine steps. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring missed heel-to-toe on all nine steps, on his first set of nine steps. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring raised his arms on his sixth and seventh step, on his first set of nine steps.  Goldring stopped on his third, sixth, and eighth step, on his first set of nine steps.  Goldring took 19 steps instead of nine as instructed, on his first set of nine steps  Goldring performed an improper turn by performing an About face to turn around.  Goldring stepped off-line on all nine steps, on his second set nine steps. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring missed heel-to-toe on all nine steps, on his second set of nine steps. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring stopped after the improper turn and his eighth step, on his second set of nine steps. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring took 18 steps instead of nine as instructed, on his second set of nine steps.  ONE LEG STAND: (3/4 clues observed) font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Prior to Goldring performing the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Hewas instructed to stand with hisheels together and hands down by hissides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of hischoice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While hisleg was raised, he was to keep hisleg straight, watch hisraised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Goldring was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, Yes. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring raised his right foot for this test. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; 0-10 seconds font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;   Goldring swayed at five seconds and kept swaying for approximately eight seconds.  Goldring raised his arms at five seconds and kept them raised for approximately eight seconds.  Goldring kept his foot down for approximately four seconds. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; 11-20 seconds font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring swayed at 15, 18, and 19 seconds. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring raised his arms at 15, and 19 seconds. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring placed his foot down at 13 seconds. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; 21-30 seconds  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring placed his foot down at 20, 23, and 29 seconds. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Goldring was offered to take the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) and refused to take to the test.  Arrest: font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.  -Bloodshot and glassy eyes. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; -Admission to consuming an alcoholic beverage.  -Slurred speech. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  -Clues displayed from the Standardized Field Sobriety Test.  Goldring was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at 0010 hours.Goldring was Read his DR-15 Advise of Rights at 0122 hours and agreed to take the Intoximeter Test. I then transported Goldring to Maryland State Police La Plata Barrack H for further processing. While being transported, Goldring became rude until I arrived at the barrack. While at the barrack, Goldring refused to take the Intoximeter Test at 0205 hours. Goldring used racial and derogatory terms towards me at the barrack. Road Runner responded to the scene to take the vehicle.  Goldring received the following citations:  TA-21-902a1i: Driving under the influence of alcohol  TA-21-902b1i: Driving while impaired by alcohol  TA-21-901.1a: Reckless Driving  TA-21-901.1b: Negligent driving  TA-21-801.1: Exceeding posted maximum posted speed limit: 67 MPH in a posted 45 MPH zone  TA-21-801a: Driving vehicle in excess of reasonable and prudent speed on highway  TA-16-101a1: Driving motor vehicle on highway without required license and authorization  TA-16-303d: Person driving motor vehicle on highway on revoked license and privilege  TA-13-411f: Displaying expired registration plate issued by any state  TA-13-411d: Driving vehicle on highway without current registration plates and validation tabs  TA-13-936e2i: Unlawful use of historic passenger veh./truck for general daily transportation  TA-13-410e2: Failure to display tab on plates of vehicle as required by ADM.  TA-16-112c: Failure to display license on demand  TA-13-409b: Failure to display registration card on demand  Goldring was then transported to Charles County Detention Center for further processing.  Goldring was rude the entire process.  All events occurred in Charles County, Maryland.  Case closed. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/10/2023 05:49:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/10/2023 05:54:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Manning</LastName>
            <FirstName>Marcus</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6421</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alphrin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5237</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tripp</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sedrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7333</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528998</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528998</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528998</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528998</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528998</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19731</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528998</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3097</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3097</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528998</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528998</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15647</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15647</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528998</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16626</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16626</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528998</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16624</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16624</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528998</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>18876</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528998</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>12</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16619</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>12</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16619</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528998</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>13</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>13</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/09/2023 01:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>62</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:46:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/10/2023 03:20:06</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>354308</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Goldring</LastName>
               <FirstName>Clifton</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jerome</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/01/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13780781E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>09/01/2022 03:47:26</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G436</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C413</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Goldring</LastName>
               <FirstName>Clifton</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jerome</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/01/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13780781E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>G436</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C413</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/01/2022 03:47:26</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5805</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Crawford</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Bryantown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20617</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.835719</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.554566</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>13500</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Trotter</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Bryantown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20617</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.842477</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.554853</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>664</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3792</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/01/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:46:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:46:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:46:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:46:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>76</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:50:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/10/2023 03:20:06</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392509</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Crawford</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Henry</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/30/1947 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/09/2023 04:50:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C616</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Crawford</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Henry</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/30/1947 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C616</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/09/2023 04:50:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5805</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Crawford</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Bryantown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20617</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.835719</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.554566</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:50:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:41:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>143565</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 04:51:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 04:51:11</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/09/2023 04:48:12</DateOfInfo>
         <DateOfInfo>09/01/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FDKF37G7JNA57954</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>1988</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>RNG</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLU</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>10551K</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicNumber>10551K</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2022</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>4</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehConditionCode>G</VehConditionCode>
         <VehDamageCode>0</VehDamageCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>