<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008946</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/11/2023 02:49:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/11/2023 02:49:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/11/2023 02:24:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/11/2023 02:24:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>BAILEY "R" 23-143</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 02:49:40</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 10:19:20</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>24 MM BALTIMORE BELTWAY INNER LOOP EB, LUTHERVILLE TIMONIUM</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>686990</AddressId>
      <City>MDC564</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 02:49:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 13:47:19</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>686990</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>24</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm Baltimore Beltway Inner</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>LOOP</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.65285105</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.4191159833333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/11/2023 02:49:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/11/2023 02:49:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/07/2023 10:19:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 02:49:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:20</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E) TEAM* MVR Statement: The following incident was captured on in-car camera. Title: BAILEY R 23-143. ID: 223-MSP-008946 Arrested: Bailey 3RD, Ernest Lee Certification and training  -Trained in Field Sobriety Test through Maryland State Police Academy.  -Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E)  -Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  - Graduated from The Institute of Advanced Law Enforcement Studies Driving Under the Influence Institute-University of Maryland.  - I have apprehended more than 200 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)    On March 11, 2023, at approximately 0223 hours, I, TFC. I. Riba Tankari # 7058 with Maryland State Police was traveling inner loop I-695 west of I-83 South, Baltimore County, Maryland in lane #3 (right lane). My issued patrol vehicle is Maryland State Police marked unit DUI-3. At that time, I observed a gray Mazda CX-5 bearing Maryland registration 8EZ3797 traveling inner loop I695 in the I-83 South exit lane unable to stay within a single lane. I observed the Mazda had swerved from the exit lane into lane #3 by one (1) tire width on two (2) separate occasions and continued traveling partially between the two (2) lanes before swerving back into the exit lane crossing the solid white line into the right shoulder by one tire width. I observed the Mazda had changed lane into lane #3 and appeared to be traveling over the posted speed limit. I observed the Mazda had swerved from lane #3 into the right shoulder by half vehicle width on one (1) occasion. With my properly functioning patrol vehicle Golden Eagle II radar unit set activated, I obtained a speed reading of 70 in a posted 55 MPH zone. I initiated a traffic stop on the Mazda using my emergency equipment. The Mazda delayed in coming to a stop. The Mazda eventually came to a stop in the area of Inner Loop I-695 and west of I-83 North, Baltimore County, Maryland lane on the right shoulder. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the Mazda on the driver side and made contact with the driver (the sole occupant) of the vehicle. I introduced myself and explained to him the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver where he was coming from, and he stated like from east Baltimore. I asked the driver where he was heading, and he stated Reisterstown. I requested his drivers license and registration card. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I observed that the driver had glassy eyes. The driver was identified through his Maryland drivers license as Bailey 3RD, Ernest Lee. I returned to my patrol vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with. I returned to the Mazda and requested Bailey to exit his vehicle and walk to the front of his vehicle and he complied. While outside his vehicle, I noticed he had something in his mouth that I did not observe on my first approach. I asked Bailey what he had in his mouth and he stated gum. I requested him to get rid of it, and he complied. I asked Bailey how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed, and he stated, I didnt drink at all tonight. While speaking with Bailey outside his vehicle, I again detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I asked Bailey to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and he agreed.  The evaluation surface was dry, flat, and free of debris. No surface defects were observed. My patrol flashlight and his vehicle headlights lit the area. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Bailey appeared to be in good physical conditions. I asked Bailey the following questions: Medical conditions: Yes, Cholesterol, Diabetes. Medications: Yes, I asked him what kind, and he stated Simvastatin earlier today around seven oclock. Anything that will prevent you from walking on straight line or standing on one leg: inclement weather Glasses or contact: Denied wearing glasses but was wearing contacts. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: (6/6 clues observed). The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus - Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes - Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes - Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Notes: * During the HGN test, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Baileys breath. WALK AND TURN: (4/8 clues observed). The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Bailey stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage: Bailey lost his balance to the right on three (3) separate occasions and stood with his right foot next to his left. Bailey started too soon on one (1) occasion. Walking Stage (1st Nine): Missed touching heel to toe by more than half inch on counts 2 and 3 Turn: The turn was completed correctly. Walking Stage (2nd Nine): Missed touching heel to toe by more than one (1) inch on counts 6, 7, and 9 Raised his arms more than six (6) inches away from his body on count 3. One Leg Stand Test (3/4 observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Bailey stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Right foot raised during the test. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: Raised left arm more than six (6) inches from his side for balance. Seconds 11-20: Swayed body to the right and left. Raised arms more than six (6) inches from his side for balance. Seconds 21-30: Right foot hit the ground one (1) time. Swayed body to the right and left. Raised arms more than six (6) inches from his side for balance. Preliminary Breath Test:  I explained and offered a PBT to Bailey. Bailey refused to consent to the PBT. ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Bailey was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a motor vehicle safely:  -Unable to stay within a single lane/driving patterns.  - Driving over the posted speed limit (70 Mph in 55 Mph speed limit zone)  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath as he conversed with me.  -Eyes glassy.  -Observed signs of impairment as he performed the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.   Bailey was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a motor vehicle at 0249 hours and was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack. A search incident to arrest revealed no weapons or contraband. Upon arrival at the Barrack, Bailey was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and it was read to him from the MVA website in English and explain multiple times. Bailey would not make a decision to take the Intoximeter EC/IR II test. Bailey was explained that there were an instrument and operator available. Bailey stated I dont want to feel pressured to take the test, I just want to understand my rights fully, I apologize and continued asking the same questions. The test was marked as refusal at 0449 hours. A properly functioning instrument and operator were available.  Bailey was given pertinent paperwork, released from the Barrack to his friend pending an appearance in the District Court of Maryland for Baltimore County at a later date.   All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 13:53:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/22/2023 16:40:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498345</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 13:50:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 13:49:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 13:50:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 13:49:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:45</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371474</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>BAILEY</LastName>
               <FirstName>ERNEST</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LEE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/18/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>03/13/2023 13:35:15</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E652</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>BAILEY</LastName>
               <FirstName>ERNEST</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LEE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/18/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>B400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E652</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/13/2023 13:35:15</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>101</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>CROSS</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>210</SubNumber>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21230</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>615</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5851</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 13:52:05</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 13:52:05</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 13:52:05</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 13:50:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 13:50:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150837</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/13/2023 13:53:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/13/2023 13:53:21</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JM3KFBBM4N1573916</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MAZD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>STATION WAGON</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8EZ3797</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleValue>1000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>