<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-043031</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/05/2023 17:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/05/2023 17:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/05/2023 17:09:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/05/2023 17:09:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DWI, MDOP</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 17:56:13</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5938</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/23/2023 08:23:36</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>MDOP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>SNOW HILL RD/ NUTTERS CROSS RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>572010</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 17:56:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 21:05:26</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>572010</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Snow Hill</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Salisbury</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21804</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-75.55795</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.32383</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4726-4799 SNOW HILL RD / 4800-5199 NUTTERS CROSS RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4726-4799 SNOW HILL RD / 4604-4799 NUTTERS CROSS RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4800-4899 SNOW HILL RD / 4604-4799 NUTTERS CROSS RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4800-4899 SNOW HILL RD / 4800-5199 NUTTERS CROSS RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/05/2023 17:56:10</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/05/2023 17:56:10</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 18:18:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 17:56:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=d1f76f14077847fea241c583a4bace22partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=52eacb6220674402a2a2ec8859ba06abpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=56fbc3d12d8d4d62808bfef76ce00bafpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=682a9ee829c74edc8d134fd7e3341705partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=0ebcff1a3d624b4091602d723f41b85cpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=47f36771633748c5bd757600f199359fpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=0322c502db8a42369108dfd0c9fee972partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 Patrol Vehicle E-7 is MVA and BWC Equipped.  Weather: Dry and 43 degrees Defendant: Chad Michael Donoway Date of Birth: 06/01/1984 Date of Arrest: 12/05/2023 Time of Arrest: 1759 hours License #: MD D-500-115-603-412 DUI #: 23-54-237 Subsequent Offender: No Accident Involved: Yes   CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING: I am trained to administer standardized field sobriety tests (SFST) and Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  NARRATIVE  Phase #1 - Vehicle In Motion: On 12/05/2023,I was dispatched to the area of Snow Hill Road and Nutters Cross Road, Salisbury, for a traffic complaint. The caller stated the driver was asleep behind the wheel, which was identified as a black Chevrolet Colorado truck. I arrived on scene and observed a blackChevrolet Colorado truck (VA# 7062XJ) parked stationary in the grass adjacent to the roadway on Nutters Cross Road near the Snow Hill Road intersection (the vehicle was parked on the private property of 4765 Snow Hill Road).  Phase #2 - Personal Contact: At this time, I observed the vehicles driver side door to be open and a male leaned over the passenger side seat via the open passenger side door. The male would be identified as the driver and owner of the black truck, Chad Michael Donoway (W/M 06/01/1984). Donoway stated he was looking for his car keys as they were misplaced/located somewhere inside the vehicle (later on during a secondary search at the MSP Salisbury Barrack, I located the misplaced car keys in Donoways sweatshirt pocket). I then had Donoway step away from the vehicle to speak to him in regards to initial traffic complaint. Donoway appeared to be very disoriented, as well as struggled to keep his balance. Donoway stated he was exhausted as he was coming from work and was en route to his residence.  Phase #3 - Pre Arrest Screening: While speaking with Donoway, I observed him being very disoriented, displaying a lethargic demeanor and failing to maintain balance while speaking to me. When asked about why he was asleep while operating his vehicle, Donoway stated he was exhausted and needed to rest (Donoway stated later on he was stopped in the roadway at the stop sign on Nutters Cross Road/Snow Hill Road and had fallen asleep inside the vehicle, only to be woken up by a passerby). He then moved his vehicle to the adjacent grass area. I then asked Donoway if he was on any current medication or used any controlled dangerous substance, he stated no. I then asked Donoway if he had any alcoholic beverages to drink, he stated no. I then had Donoway stand on the flat roadway shoulder, facing the front of my vehicle.I then advised Donoway I was goingto perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.   Pre-Screening Questions: I asked Donoway a series of questions prior to performing Standardized Field Sobriety Tests: * Injuries: No * Medication: No * Glasses/Contacts: No  I began the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests and started with the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test as I observed him.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus: I explained the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test to Donoway and asked him if he understood the test. Donoway stated that he understood the test. I completed the following test.  Resting Nystagmus: No Equal Tracking: Yes Equal Pupil Size: Yes  No clues observed During the test, Donoway was directed not to move his head during pen movement. Donoway failed to follow these instructions and moved his head during pen movement. I also observed Donoway swaying during my pen movement, but was directed to remain stationary.  Total Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Clues: 0 of 6  Walk and Turn: Weather: Dry Surface: Level asphalt free of debris  I placed Donoway into the instructional phase. I began to explain and demonstrate the Walk and Turn test to Donoway. Donoway initially lost his balance prior to staring the test. I asked Donoway if he understood the test, and he stated he did understand. Donoway began the test stepping with the incorrect foot first (started with right step).  Instructional Phase: Could not keep balance  Walking stage 1st9: missed heel to toe steps, took improper number of steps (18), stopped walking  Turn: Completed Unsatisfactorily(improper turn, stopped walking)  Walking stage 2nd9: stepped off line, missed heel to toe steps,improper number of steps (29)    Total Walk and Turn Clues: 6of8   One Leg Stand:  I then explained and demonstrated the One Leg Stand test to Donoway.I asked Donoway if he understood the test, and he stated he did.Donoway picked up his left foot.  Seconds 1-10: Put foot down   Seconds 11-20: Put foot down Swayed Raised arms for balance  Seconds 21-30: Swayed Put foot down Hopped Raised arms for balance  Total One Leg Stand Clues: 4of 4  PBT: PBT was not offered.  ARIDE Testing: I then performed a series of additional field sobriety test (ARIDE) as suspected Donoway of being under the influence of a controlled dangerous substance. Donoway completed the Lack of Convergence Test (Donoway followed the pen tracking, but I observed his eyes not being able to come together/cross when my pen stopped at the bridge of his nose). Donoway then completed the Modified Romberg Test (Donoway was advised estimate the passage of 30 seconds in his head, approximately 69 seconds had passed during the test. Donoway appeared to have fallen asleep during the time passage). Donoway then completed the Finger To Nose Test (Donoway would fail to follow the sequence I demonstrated to him. He appeared to have fallen asleep during the test).  I then spoke to Donoway and asked again if he had used any controlled dangerous substance, he stated no. Donoway stated he was clean and in rehab, and stated he last used heroin two weeks ago (later advised he used to snort heroin).   Arrest and Transport: Based on the following, I had reason to believe Donoway was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of a controlled dangerous substance: * Disoriented, displaying a lethargic demeanor, failing to maintain balance while speaking to me * Traffic complainant for sleeping inside vehicle while stopped on roadway * My observed signs of impairment as he performed standardized field sobriety tests and ARIDE tests.   I placed Donoway under arrest for driving while under the influence of acontrolled dangerous substance at1759 hours.I thenplaced him in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. While speaking to Donoway inside my vehicle, I observed a blue/green powdery substance located on the backend of Donoways tongue. When asked about the substance on his tongue, Donoway stated it was a Starburst candy he had eaten earlier.   Observation Period: While waiting for the tow truck to remove Donoways vehicle, Donoway was played and showed a copy of MVA DR-15. During the MVA-15 Audio and Visual read, I observed Donoway nodding off and sleeping during the process. Donoway elected to take the intoxemeter test at 1809 hours. I then advised Donoway that he was most likely going to blow 0.00 as his results, as I did not suspect him of being under the influence of alcohol. I then read Donoway a copy of his Miranda Rights, Donoway elected to waive his rights at 1810 hours. I then advised Donoway that if and when his 0.00 Intoxometer Results occurred, a Drug Recognition Expert (DRE) would be requested to administer further questions and tests to Donoway in regard to controlled dangerous substance usage. Donoway stated he elected/would comply with any further questions and tests a DRE could administer to him. I transported Donoway back to the barrack. During transport, I observed Donoway nodding off and falling asleep. While at the barrack Donoways Intoxemeter Results were a 0.00. Donoway was then placed in a cell. After a few minutes inside the cell, Donoway stated he no longer wished to speak with or cooperate with a DRE and retracted his further statement he made to me. I then observed Donoway become irate and uncooperative with myself and the duty officer. Donoway began slamming on the cell door and removed his clothes, shoving his clothes down the cells toilet. I then advised Donoway to put his clothes back on and remove all clothes from the toilet. Donoway was notified that if he stuffed his clothes down the toilet again/damaged the toilet, he would be charged with Malicious Destruction of Property. The duty officer then shut off the water flow to the cell toilet, fearing Donoway would damage it. Prior to his release, Donoway began shoving his clothes down the toilet again. Donoway was then released from the cell. As he was leaving the cell I observed Donoway missing his right sock. At this time, I suspected Donoway flushed his sock down the cells toilet.  Donoway was given copies of all pertinent paperwork and citations, and was released to a sober driver around 2000 hours. Shortly after he was released, the duty officer notified me that after he turned the cells toilet water flow back on, the toilet itself was not functioning properly (it is currently out of service until it can be fixed). I suspected Donoway damaged the cells toilet by stuffing/flushing his sock down the toilet. I then located Donoway shortly after he left the barrack (Dagsboro Road and Calhoun Avenue) with his sober driver. I asked where Donoways missing sock was, Donoway stated it was somewhere in the barrack and he might have flushed it down the toilet. I then charged Donoway withMalicious Destruction of Property: Value -$1,000.00 for the damaged he caused to the barracks cell toilet, criminal citation was issued.  Attached to this report are all of Donoways correlated paperwork.  All events occurred in Wicomico County, Maryland.  I request this case be closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7218</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 20:15:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7218</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 21:42:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sosnak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7218</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bowie</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5734</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sosnak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7218</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sosnak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7218</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532505</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/05/2023 17:59:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7218</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 20:02:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7218</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 23:03:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532505</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/05/2023 17:59:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7218</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 20:02:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7218</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 23:03:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532505</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3 4025</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>11</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/05/2023 20:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3 4025</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7218</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 21:08:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7218</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 23:03:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7218</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 20:02:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7218</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 21:13:33</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>15388</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Donoway</LastName>
               <FirstName>Chad</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/01/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2014 18:54:13</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Donoway</LastName>
               <FirstName>Chad</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/01/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2014 18:54:13</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6120</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Jack</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21804</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.508857</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.359486</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>34514</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Pitts </StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Pittsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21850</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.415094</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.392561</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>859</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2362</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/17/2014 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7218</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 21:13:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7218</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 21:13:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7218</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 21:13:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7218</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 21:13:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7218</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 20:57:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7218</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 20:57:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240007659</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>MARYLAND STATE POLICE</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7218</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 21:12:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7218</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 21:12:01</UpdatorDate>
         <BusinessAddress>
            <AddressId>418448</AddressId>
            <StreetNumber>2765</StreetNumber>
            <StreetDirCode>N</StreetDirCode>
            <StreetName>Salisbury</StreetName>
            <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
            <City>Salisbury</City>
            <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
            <Zip5>21801</Zip5>
            <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            <Longitude>-75.564269</Longitude>
            <Latitude>38.420274</Latitude>
            <BusinessPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>BUS</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>749</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3101</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/11/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </BusinessPhone>
         </BusinessAddress>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7218</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/05/2023 21:16:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7218</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 21:16:11</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Toilet/Plumbing</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>835</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>100</PropertyValue>
         <Value>100</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>257143</Property_ID>
         <Make>Toilet/Plumbing</Make>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/21/2023 10:07:24</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/21/2023 10:07:24</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 18:18:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7218</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 10:07:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:28</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=c4f654536cbc4f2b85a4cb384d5a3f7dpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  On 12/21/2023, after receiving additional evidence in reference to Donoways release from the MSP Barrack on 12/05/2023, Sgt. T. Staten informed me that Donoway had littered/discarded his toilet water soaked clothes onto an MSP patrol vehicle (E-35) around 2030 hours on 12/5/2023. Please refer to Sgt. T. Statens supplement for further evidence and witness account of the incident.  Due to this new evidence, Donoway was issued and served a Civil Citation for**LITTER/DUMP: UNDER 100 LBS** on 12/21/2023 at 1000 hours. During contact with Donoway, he confessed/admitted to discarding his toilet water soaked clothes onto the MSP patrol vehicle (E-35).  Attached to this is a copy of Donoways Civil Citation and BWC footage.  This case is closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7218</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 10:09:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7218</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/21/2023 10:42:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nastvogel</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ravi</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5938</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sosnak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7218</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>