<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000588</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/05/2023 19:11:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/05/2023 19:11:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/05/2023 18:57:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/05/2023 18:57:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Maryland State Police Westminster DUI 23-002 // Rihn, Henry Tyler</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 19:11:59</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 17:19:25</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>W LIBERTY RD/ RIDGE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>564886</AddressId>
      <City>MDC196</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 19:12:00</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/21/2023 12:30:35</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>564886</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Liberty</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westminster</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-77.086972</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.457803</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2255-2526 W LIBERTY RD / 4047-4213 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>CORK AND BOTTLE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2600-2622 W LIBERTY RD / 4047-4213 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2255-2526 W LIBERTY RD / 4305-4347 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2625-2670 W LIBERTY RD / 4299-4347 RIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/05/2023 19:11:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/05/2023 19:11:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/11/2023 09:05:58</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 19:11:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/11/2023 09:06:00</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police Westminster DUI #23-002 TFC Nield #6851 Case Number: 23-MSP-000588 The incident was recorded. MSP marked unit G-23 equipped with MVR and TFC Nield is equipped with a body-worn camera.  Incident: TA 21-902(a)(1) Attempting to Drive Motor Vehicle Under the Influence of Alcohol  Certifications: - Over 80 career DUI arrests to date - Collision Reconstruction Specialist - Certified Field Training Trooper - 2018 Ocean City Impaired Driving Conference - Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) training course - National Highway Safety Transportation Administration (NHSTA) certified to conduct Standardized FieldSobriety Test (SFST) - Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator -Certified police officer in the state of Maryland with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with live donors at the Maryland State Police Academy.  Suspect: Henry Tyler Rihn W/M 11/14/1995  Attachments: DR-15 Advice of Rights DR-15A Order of Suspension METERS Printouts Copy of Traffic Citations MSP Form 67 - Chain of Custody  Location: 7/11 4213 Ridge Road, Taylorsville, Maryland  Date and Time: 01/05/2023 at approximately 1857 hours  NARRATIVE  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1): On 01/05/2023 at approximately 1857 hours, I, TFC Nield #6851, was dispatched to the Taylorsville 7/11 (4213 Ridge Road, Taylorsville, Maryland) for a call of a disorderly subject. The caller, the on-duty employee of 7/11, advised that the subject appeared heavily intoxicated and was causing a disturbance within the store. The employee also advised that the subject had arrived in a vehicle with a numeric license plate reading 5193MX. I arrived on scene and observed a silver Honda Accord bearing South Carolina registration 5193MX parked in a parking space. As I parked my patrol vehicle and approached the Honda, I observed the drivers side door of the Honda open and an empty 99 Vodka mini fall onto the ground before the door shut again. I approached the vehicle and observed that there was one occupant within the vehicle who was sitting in the drivers seat. Within the vehicle, I observed two open and empty bottles of vodka in the passenger side rear floorboard of the vehicle and one bottle of the same vodka on the drivers side floorboard of the Honda.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):  I made contact with the driver at the drivers side door. As soon as the door opened, I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from within the vehicle. I observed that the drivers eyes were dilated, as well as bloodshot, watery, and glassy. I also observed his face to be flushed. I asked the driver what was going on, and he began to stutterunintelligibly. I introduced myself and explained to the driver that everything was being audibly and visually recorded, to which he stated, I dont have my key in the ignition in a thick, slurred voice. I asked him if he had the keys on him, at which time he reached into his right front pocket and pulled out the keys to the vehicle.   I again asked the driver what was going on, to which he answered, Frankly sir this lady is freaking the fuck out. I then asked the driver how much he had to drink, to which he stated, Ive had a couple drinks sir. I probably shouldnt drive. I asked the driver for his drivers license, and I was able to positively identify him as Henry Tyler Rihn (W/M 11/14/1995) by his South Carolina drivers license. I asked Rihn how he got here, to which he answered, I drove here and I bought some drinks. I asked Rihn where he bought the drinks, to which he answered, At, down the road, theres a liquor store right down there. I asked Rihn if that is where the two empty bottles of vodka in the backseat came from, to which he answered, Yes sir. I asked Rihn if he drank them both tonight, at which time his head sank and he nodded Yes. At this time, I asked Rihn to step out of the car, to which he complied.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):    Rihn refused all Standardized Field Sobriety Tests and the Preliminary Breath Test.  ARREST:   Due to the following factors, Rihn was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol:   In care and control of the vehicle (Sitting in drivers seat, awake, keys in pocket)  Admission of consuming alcoholic beverage  Bloodshot, watery, glassy eyes  Odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the drivers breath and person  Open containers of alcohol within the vehicle  Evidence of consuming large amounts of alcohol (2 empty 750mL bottles of vodka)   Rihn was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 1911 hours. During my initial search of Rihn, I did not observe anything inside his mouth. Rihn was then placed in the front seat of my patrol vehicle. While on scene, I documented the open containers of alcohol within Rihns vehicle. The first open and empty container was mini 99 Peaches Liquer vodka that I had placed into the drivers side door pocket after it had originally fallen out of the vehicle. On the drivers side floorboard, I observed one bottle of Smirnoff Vodka. On the rear passenger side floorboard, I observed two open and empty 750ML bottles of Smirnoff Vodka bottles.    Rihn was then transported to the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack. During transport, I continued to detect the strong odor of ana acholic beverage as Rihn explained that he was in an alcohol recovery program and had relapsed.At approximately 1958 hours, Rihn was read his DR-15 Advice of Rights and was offered a decision to submit to an alcohol concentration test. At the conclusion of the form, Rihn refused to submit to the test and signed the DR-15. At the conclusion of the DR-15, Rihn was placed into the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack holding cell while I completed the paperwork, at which time Rihn began to intentionally urinate on the floor of the holding cell. Rihn was then transported to Carroll County Central Booking for his initial appearance with a District Court Commissioner.  All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland.  I request this case be closed.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 21:35:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6851</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/21/2023 12:37:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nield</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6851</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489965</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/05/2023 18:57:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 02:05:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6851</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 02:05:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 03:12:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:06</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365816</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Rihn</LastName>
               <FirstName>Henry</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Tyler</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/14/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.26757652E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>01/11/2023 03:12:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H560</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Rihn</LastName>
               <FirstName>Henry</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Tyler</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/14/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.26757652E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>R500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H560</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/11/2023 03:12:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>305</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2907</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 03:22:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:43</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/11/2023 03:22:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:43</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6851</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/09/2023 02:05:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6851</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/09/2023 02:05:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>