<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-035309</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/08/2023 01:18:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/08/2023 01:18:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/08/2023 00:38:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/08/2023 00:38:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop which resulted in DUI/DWI arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 01:19:01</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/16/2023 07:53:42</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I695 WB,LINTHICUM HEIGHTS</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>709303</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 01:19:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 00:38:15</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>709303</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I695 Wb Linthicum</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HTS</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.6575766166667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.2181604666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/08/2023 01:18:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/08/2023 01:18:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/14/2023 08:33:06</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 01:19:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack P This incident was captured by a body-worn camera    Defendant: Carlos A Fuentes Cruz (H/M DOB: 11/04/1971)  Date of Arrest: 10/08/2023  Time of Arrest: 0118 hours   DUI#: P 23-138  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement. (A.R.I.D.E). *Certified RADAR/LASER operator. *Certified Advanced Collision Investigator (ACI). *Field Training Trooper (FTT). *Trained in interdiction for uniformed Troopers. *Trained in proactive criminal enforcement (PACE). *Anne Arundel County Circuit Court reorganized HGN expert.  NARRATIVE:  VEHICLE IN MOTION: On 10/08/2023, at approximately 0038 hours. I, Trooper First Class A. J. Baldi #6907 assigned to the Maryland State Police Glen burnie Barrack P was on patrol in the area of the outer loop I-695 at I-97 in Brooklyn Anne Arundel County, Maryland. While traveling west, I observed a gray Toyota Camry bearing Maryland registration 1FD0790 weaving within lane 2.  As I approached the Toyota the left tires crossed onto the broken white line that separates lanes 1 and 2 and then immediately corrected. The vehicle continued to weave between the lane lines as we passed I-97. When we approached MD-648 the vehicle was now occupying lane 4. The Toyota then traveled onto the broken lane line for approximately 3 seconds before correcting. As we approached Camp Meade Rd, the Toyota slowly changed lanes from lane 4 to lane 3. The Toyota continued to weave within the lane and periodically traveled onto the broken white lines that divided the lanes. While approaching MD-295 the Toyotas right tires crossed over the line that divides lanes 3 and 4 into the lane my patrol vehicle was occupying. After the Toyota corrected into its lane, I positioned my patrol vehicle behind the Toyota in lane 3. While still traveling westbound the Toyota continued to rhythmically weave within lane 3.  When we arrived at MD-295, I activated my emergency equipment to conduct a traffic stop on the vehicle due to the higher volume of vehicles now traveling on I-695. The Toyota stopped on the right shoulder of the outer loop I-695 at MD-295.   PERSONAL CONTACT I exited my patrol vehicle and approached the passengers side of the Toyota. As I reached the midway point of the Toyota I observed the windows were up on the vehicle, but I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. When I reached the passenger window, I tapped on the B-pillar and the driver rolled the window down. Once he did so, the odor of alcohol became substantially stronger.  I introduced myself to the driver and advised him of the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver for his drivers license and registration card. I also asked how much alcohol he consumed prior to driving. He stated he did not speak English. While interacting with the driver, I observed his eyes to be glassy and bloodshot. When he spoke, his speech was heavily slurred. He was also slouching in the drivers seat of the vehicle. I was able to identify the driver as Carlos A Fuentes Cruz (H/M DOB: 11/04/1971) by his Maryland drivers license.  I returned to my patrol vehicle and requested for a Spanish translator to respond to the scene and an additional Trooper to assist with the traffic stop. I returned to the Toyota to ask the driver to exit his vehicle and walk to the rear of his Toyota to conduct field sobriety testing. Despite stating he didnt know how to speak English, Fuentes appeared to understand what I was saying. I asked him to exit his vehicle and walk to the rear. Once at the rear of the Toyota, I asked Fuentes if he could understand me. He stated he could a little. I then asked how much alcohol he consumed prior to driving. At this point he began to act confused as if he couldnt understand what I was saying. I told Fuentes to remain at his vehicle while I waited for a Spanish translator. A short time later, Trooper First Class N. Hitch #7051 arrived on-scene to assist.  Corporal R. Campos #2342 with the Anne Arundel County Police Department Western District arrived on-scene. I met her and briefed her on the traffic stop. She took over translation between Fuentes and I. She asked Fuentes where he was coming from and where he was going to. He stated he was traveling from work in Baltimore, and going to Hyattsville, MD. Fuentes was asked how much alcohol he consumed prior to driving. He stated 2 beers.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING The test was performed on the right shoulder of the ramp to the outer loop I-695. The surface was dry, flat, and free from any visible debris. The lighting conditions consisted of streetlights. The weather was clear.  Injuries None.  Medication None.  Past Traumatic Brain Injury or Concussion None.  Medical Conditions  Multiple.  Comfortable Footwear Yes.  Glasses/ Contacts No.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS 6/6 CLUES OBSERVED I explained the first test, Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN). I am trained and have met all requirements established by the Maryland State Police for conducting HGN. The HGN training is consistent with the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) standards. Fuentes demonstrated and confirmed that he understood the instructions to the test. HGN was conducted using the tip of an ink pen as a stimulus, and it was held at a distance of 12-15 inches and slightly above eye level. It was passed horizontally across his face. Fuentes displayed equal tracking and equal pupil size. Fuentes was asked if he understood the instructions. He confirmed that he did.  WALK AND TURN 7/8 CLUES OBSERVED Prior to Fuentes performing the test, I correctly explained and demonstrated how the test is conducted. Fuentes was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel-to-toe. Fuentes was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Fuentes was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line while touching heel-to-toe on every step.He was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, it was explained and demonstrated to him that he should keep his lead foot on the line, to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot, and to turn completely around 180 degrees. It was again explained and demonstrated to Fuentes that a second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. I instructed Fuentes, Once the test begins, youre to continue through with the entire test until you are finished. Remember to place your hands down by your sides, look down at your feet, and count each step aloud. I asked Fuentes if he understood my instructions. He confirmed he did.  Instructional Stage: -Broke position standing with his feet side-by-side.  -Starts too soon.  Walking Stage (1st nine):  -Stopped walking (Steps 1-9)  -Steps off-line (Step 1)  -Misses heel-to-toe (Steps 1-9)  Walking Stage (2nd nine):  -Misses heel-to-toe (Steps 1-6)  -Incorrect number of steps (6)  Turn:  -Improper (Turned 90 degrees toward the roadway)  ONE LEG STAND 2/4 CLUES OBSERVED  Prior to Fuentes performing the test, I explained and demonstrated the test. Fuentes was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep both legs straight, watch his raised foot, and to count the seconds out loud (one-one thousand, two-one thousand, three-one thousand), and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Fuentes if he understood the instructions. He stated she did.  Seconds 0-10:  -Swayed  -Raised arms for balance (Touched car to hold himself up)  -Hopped  -Puts foot down  Seconds 11-20:  -Puts foot down   Seconds 21-30:  -Puts foot down  Preliminary breath Test The preliminary breath test was offered to Fuentes. He declined to be tested.  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Fuentes was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  -Failing to maintain lane driving. -Rhythmically weaving within the lane. -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from within the vehicle. -Glassy eyes. -Bloodshot eyes. -Slurred speech.  Arrest:  Fuentes was taken into custody without incident. He was transported to the Glen Burnie Barrack for further processing. Fuentes DR-15 Advice of Right was played via recording through an official MVA source. Fuentes agreed to submit to a chemical breath test. The test was conducted by Sgt Natale #5415. The results indicated an alcohol concentration of .22 BRAC. Fuentes was issued the appropriate citations and paperwork. He was later released to a sober driver.   Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.  Trooper First Class A. J. Baldi #6907 Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack P 6800 Aviation Blvd, Glen Burnie, MD 21061 (410)-761-5130  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6907</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 06:46:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6907</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 08:21:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hitch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathaniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7051</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Baldi</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6907</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ricker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5861</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Baldi</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6907</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Baldi</LastName>
            <FirstName>Adam</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6907</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524769</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/08/2023 00:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6907</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 00:34:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6907</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 00:37:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>51</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6907</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 00:35:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6907</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 00:41:06</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390265</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Fuentes Cruz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Carlos</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>A</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/04/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/13/2023 00:28:04</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Fuentes Cruz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Carlos</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>A</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/04/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C642</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/13/2023 00:28:04</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7908</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>24th</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PL</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hyattsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20783</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2622</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.968469</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.985852</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6907</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 00:41:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6907</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 00:41:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6907</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 00:41:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6907</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 00:35:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6907</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/13/2023 00:35:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>