<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-044555</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/17/2023 03:02:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/17/2023 03:02:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/17/2023 02:30:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/17/2023 02:30:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop resulting in DUI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 03:02:15</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6827</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/16/2024 12:29:10</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>CRAIN,UPPER MARLBORO</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>716932</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 03:02:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/06/2024 14:47:56</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>716932</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Old Crain</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20772</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>HWY</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.781578</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.791643</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/17/2023 03:02:13</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/17/2023 03:02:13</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/16/2024 12:29:11</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 03:02:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:25</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car (L-48) and Body Worn Camera Operational.      Defendant: Kervin Donnell Johnson       Date of Birth: 09/12/1968      Date of Arrest: 12/17/2023      Time of Arrest: 0248 Hours      DUI:  23-415   Certificate and Training:  Trained in Administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) through the Maryland State Police (MSP) and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA)   Soundex:  J525465149709 // MD   Narrative:  VEHICLE IN MOTION (Phase 1):  On December 17, 2023, at approximately 0230 hours, I, Trooper S. Smalls #7676, of the Maryland State Police, currently assigned to the Forestville Barrack, was traveling northbound Robert S Crain Highway at Croom Road, Upper Marlboro, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20745 when I observed a vehicle traveling at a high rate of speed. I paced the vehicle from Croom Road to Old Crain Highway traveling at 105 miles per hour (mph) in a 55 mph zone. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the black Tesla bearing New Jersey registration of P70SVL.   PERSONAL CONTACT (Phase 2):  Upon my approach of the vehicle I advised the driver that I stopped the vehicle for driving 105 mph in a 55 mph zone. The driver advised that he stopped on the side of the road to relieve himself due to him being a diabetic. I requested the driver license and registration card. The driver was identified by his Maryland drivers license as Kervin Donnell Johnson (B/M DOB: 09/12/1968.) I asked Johnson where he was coming from and Johnson advised Tinder Box which is a cigar lounge. As I was talking to Johnson I could smell the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage. I asked Johnson if he had any alcoholic beverages at the cigar lounge, and he stated Absolutely, you drink at the cigar lounge, but not that many. I asked Johnson to clarify what he meant by Not that many, which he stated he had One drink. I asked Johnson what type of alcoholic beverage he had, and he advised A beer. I asked Johnson if he would perform the voluntary Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) which he agreed to perform. As Johnson stepped out of the vehicle I noticed that he used the door to assist in his balance.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (Phase 3):  The evaluation was performed on the shoulder area of the Robert S Crain Highway north at Old Crain Highway, Upper Marlboro, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20772. The surface was level and free from obvious debris. The weather was dry. Lighting conditions consisted of vehicle headlamps, street lights, and my flashlight. Johnson appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries, limps, and/or limb ailments. I asked Johnson if he wore glasses or contacts to which he advised just for reading. I asked Johnson if he takes any medication to which he advised he does not.   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) 4 out of 6 clues observed:  Before performing HGN, I instructed Johnson to stand with his legs and feet together and his arms down by his sides. I instructed Johnson not to move from this position until I instructed him to do so. I asked Johnson if he could see my stimulus to which he advised he could. I instructed Johnson to follow the tip of my stimulus with his eyes only, without moving his head, neck, or shoulders. Johnson exhibited equal pupil size in both eyes. Johnson showed equal tracking in both eyes while following the stimulus. Several times Johnson would look away from the stimulus and would move his head.   Lack of Smooth Pursuit:  Johnson showed a lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.   Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation:  Johnson showed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.   Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees:  I was unable to read due to Johnson looking away from the stimulus on multiple occasions.   Vertical Gaze Nystagmus:  Johnson did not show vertical gaze nystagmus in either eye.   Walk and Turn (WAT) 5 out of 8 clues observed:  Prior to performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Johnson was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Johnson was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in this position until instructed to begin. Johnson was advised to take nine (9) heel to toe steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Johnson was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes on his feet and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, Johnson was advised to conduct a turn by taking a series of small steps to the left keeping his lead foot planted. Johnson was instructed and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Johnson was instructed that once he begins the test, do not stop.   Instructional Phase:  Johnson advised that he was unable to remain in the instructional position because he has L5 in his back. I advised Johnson to do the best that he could. Johnson was still unable to remain in the instructional position for he has Neuropathy, a numbness in his right foot. I gave Johnson an alternative position and instructed him to place both feet together and his arms by his side.   Walking Stage (1st Series):  Johnson stepped off line on steps 1, 4, on step 6 Johnson almost fell over, 13, and 14. Johnson used arms for balance during the entire test. Johnson missed heel to toe during the test. Johnson did not look at his feet nor counted his steps out loud during the test. Johnson took a total of 19 steps instead of 9.  Johnson was instructed to end the test due to taking 19 steps in the direction of the roadway.   One Leg Stand (OLS) 0 out of 4 clues observed:  Prior to performing OLS, I instructed and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Johnson was instructed to stand with his legs and feet together and hands down by his sides. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot and count out loud in the manner of one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-three, and so on until instructed to stop.  Johnson did not complete the test.  Arrest:      The moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage.      Admission to consuming an alcoholic beverage.      Observed signs of impairment during SFSTs      Preliminary Breath Test:  Not offered.  At approximately 0248 hours, Johnson was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. Johnson was searched before being placed in my marked patrol vehicle to be transported to the Forestville Barrack. Johnson was provided a copy of the Advice of Rights (DR-015) from the mva.maryland.gov website to follow along with while I played the audio version of the form downloaded from the same website in its entirety.   Intoximeter Test:  .12 BrAC  After having read the DR-015, at approximately 0329 hours, Johnson agreed to submit to the Intoximeter Test.  The breath test was administered by Corporal M. York #6327, with the Maryland State Police (MSP.) The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of .12 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  Johnson was charged with DUI/DWI and other traffic related charges.  Johnson was released from the Forestville Barrack to a sober driver.  Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/16/2024 08:48:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/16/2024 08:55:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wiesemann</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5573</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smalls</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7676</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Angeli</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6827</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smalls</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7676</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smalls</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7676</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534032</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15647</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/17/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15647</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2024 17:57:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 18:30:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534032</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/17/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2024 17:57:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 18:29:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534032</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/17/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2024 17:57:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 18:29:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534032</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/17/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2024 17:57:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 18:30:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534032</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/17/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2024 17:57:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 18:28:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534032</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/17/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2024 17:57:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 18:26:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534032</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/17/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2024 17:57:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 18:28:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534032</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/17/2023 02:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17272</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2024 17:57:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 18:31:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>55</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2024 17:57:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 18:32:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>395990</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>JOHNSON</LastName>
               <FirstName>KERVIN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>DONNELL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/12/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/24/2023 06:35:32</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K615</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>JOHNSON</LastName>
               <FirstName>KERVIN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>DONNELL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/12/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K615</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/24/2023 06:35:32</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>18324</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Queen Elizabeth</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Olney</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20832</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.079448</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.157619</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>834</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4128</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/13/2024 18:32:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 18:32:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/13/2024 18:32:32</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 18:32:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2024 17:57:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 17:57:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>160138</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2024 17:57:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/13/2024 17:57:54</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>7SAYGDEE4PF899499</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2023</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TESL</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>Y</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>NJ</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>P70SVL</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2026</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>11</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>