<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009894</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/19/2023 01:46:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/19/2023 01:46:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/19/2023 01:24:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/19/2023 01:24:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect was driving the wrong way of the roadway and was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 01:46:52</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0392</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 12:24:30</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>687894</AddressId>
      <City>MDC244</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:32:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 09:37:11</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>687894</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Pennsylvania</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Upper Marlboro</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20772</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>N</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>HWY</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.758379</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.813046</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/19/2023 01:46:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/19/2023 01:46:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/07/2023 04:43:15</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 01:46:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:01</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car (L-42) and Body Worn Camera Operational.   Defendant: Lisa Wong Johnson  Date of Birth: 11/11/1963  Date of Arrest: 03/19/2023  Time of Arrest: 0146 Hours    DUI:  23-093  Certificate and Training:  Trained in Administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) through the Maryland State Police (MSP) and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA)  Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.)  Soundex:  J-525-522-907-866/Maryland  Narrative: VEHICLE IN MOTION (Phase 1):  On March 19, 2023, at approximately 0124 hours, I, Trooper J. Barlow #7186, of the Maryland State Police, currently assigned to the Forestville Barrack, was on duty in my marked patrol vehicle on a traffic stop on the right shoulder, with my rear emergency lights activated, southbound Pennsylvania Avenue north of Old Crain Highway, Upper Marlboro, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20772, when I observed a blue SUV traveling northbound in lane 1 of the southbound lanes. The blue SUV traveling the wrong way and nearly struck a vehicle head-on. I exited my vehicle to gain the attention of the driver to which they conducted a U-Turn and proceeded to travel northbound. I was able to safely and successfully get the operator to stop and pull off to the right shoulder. The vehicle was a blue Jaguar Pace bearing Maryland Registration 75684CG.   PERSONAL CONTACT (Phase 2):  Upon contact with the driver, who I identified by her Maryland drivers license as Lisa Wong Johnson (B/F DOB: 11/11/1963) and was the sole occupant of the vehicle. While talking to Johnson, I observed her eyes to be glossy. I detected the faint odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person, however, Johnson had a box of chicken and fries from Royal Farms service station on the gear shift overpowering the odor of the alcoholic beverage. I observed multiple bar/lounge/club entry bands on Johnsons right wrist. I asked Johnson if she consumed any alcoholic beverages to which she stated, Yes. I asked Johnson how much she consumed to which she advised approximately two glasses of wine. I asked Johnson how long had she consumed the wine and what kind did she have to which Johnson advised approximately 6pm or 7pm and it was Merlot. I asked Johnson where was she coming from to which she advised her friends house. I asked Johnson where she consumed the alcoholic beverages to which she advised at a concert she attended at The Anthem located in Northwest, Washington, D.C. I asked Johnson how did she end up traveling the wrong way on the roadway to which she stated, I got lost trying to get home. I asked Johnson if she had her GPS on at this time, to which she lifted her cell phone and advised she did not. Johnson stated, My friend told me to make a right after the Royal Farms and get on 4. Based off this information, I have reason to believe Johnson was traveling from Ritchie Marlboro Road. I asked Johnson if she would perform the voluntary Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) to which she agreed to perform.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (Phase 3):  Before performing the SFSTs, I requested Johnson to exit and walk to the front of her vehicle. After Johnson exited the vehicle, she closed her door and stood beside her car in the travel portion of the roadway. I advised Johnson to walk to the front of her vehicle once again. Once Johnson got to the front of her vehicle, I asked if she wore glasses, to which she advised she was currently wearing contact lenses. I asked Johnson if she took medication which would impair her judgement or coordination to which she advised she did not. I asked Johnson if she had any injuries which would hinder her from walking in a straight line or standing on one leg for any duration of time to which she advised she did not, however, Johnson advised she did have a right knee replacement. While talking to Johnson, the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath was more apparent.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) 6 out of 6 clues observed:  Before performing HGN, I instructed Johnson to stand with her legs and feet together with her arms down by her side and not to move from this position until I instructed her to do so. I asked Johnson if she could see the silver tip of my stimulus to which she advised she could. I instructed Johnson to follow the silver tip of my stimulus with her eyes only without moving her head, neck, or shoulders. I asked Johnson if she understood the instructions I gave her to which she advised she understood. Johnson exhibited equal pupil size and Resting Nystagmus was not present. Johnson did not display equal tracking as she would move her eyes ahead of the position of the stimulus. It should be noted HGN had to be performed twice as it was difficult to see her eyes due to her extended faux eye lashes. Johnson removed her faux eye lashes prior to the second time performing HGN.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit:  Johnson showed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation:  Johnson showed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation.  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees:  Johnson showed onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees.   Vertical Gaze Nystagmus:  Johnson did not show vertical gaze nystagmus.  Walk and Turn (WAT) 3 out of 8 clues observed:  Before performing WAT, I advised Johnson to imagine the solid straight white boundary line was in front of her. I instructed Johnson to stand with her right foot in front of her left foot touching heel to toe on the imaginary line with her arms down by her sides and not to move from this position until I instructed her to do so. I instructed Johnson to take nine (9) heel to toe steps down the imaginary line, looking down at her feet, and counting each step out loud. I instructed Johnson once she got to her 9th step, to leave her lead foot planted and take a series of small steps turning around to the left and take 9 more heel to toe steps back down the imaginary line. I instructed Johnson once she starts the test, do not stop until she completed the test. I asked Johnson if she understood the instructions I gave her to which she advised she understood. I demonstrated how the test should be performed, advising I would take three (3) steps simulating 9 steps. After demonstrating the test, I asked Johnson if she understood the demonstration to which she advised she understood. It should be noted, Johnson had on a long brown fur coat which covered her legs. I advised Johnson to remove the coat for this portion of the test to which she complied. After this portion of the test was completed, Johnson was given back her coat. I instructed Johnson to begin the test.   Instructional Phase:  Johnson was unable to maintain balance during instructional phase.   Walking Stage (1st Series):  Johnson took the improper number of steps totaling 8 steps.   Turn:  Johnson did not turn as instructed, as she turned around on both feet.  Walking Stage (2nd Series):  No clues were observed during the 2nd series.  One Leg Stand (OLS) 2 out of 4 clues observed:  Before performing OLS, I instructed Johnson to stand with her legs and feet together and her arms down by her sides. I instructed Johnson not to move from this position until I instructed her to do so. I instructed Johnson to lift either leg of her choosing approximately six inches off the ground. I advised Johnson since she had a right knee replacement to lift her right leg if she chose to. I instructed Johnson whichever leg she chooses to lift, look down at the toes of the raised foot and count out loud in the manner of one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-three, and so on until I instructed her to stop. I asked Johnson if she understood the instructions I gave her to which she advised she understood. I demonstrated how the test should be performed and asked if she understood the demonstration to which she advised she understood. I asked Johnson which leg would she lift off the ground to which she advised and pointed to her left leg. I instructed Johnson to begin the test. It should be noted, approximately 5 seconds into this portion of the test, Johnson had to be advised to look down at her toes.   Puts Foot Down:  Johnson put her foot down on seconds 5 and 26-30.  Uses Arms for Balance:  Johnson used her arms for balance lifting her hand approximately six inches from her sides during seconds 1-30.  Sways:  No clues were observed.  Hops:  No clues were observed.  Arrest:    Driving the wrong way on a one-way street  Glossy eyes  The odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person  The admission of consuming alcoholic beverages   margin-left:8px"&gt;The observations during the SFSTs    Preliminary Breath Test:  Refused  At approximately 0146 hours, Johnson was advised of her Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) rights and offered a PBT. Johnson refused to take the PBT. At 0146 hours, Johnson was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. It should be noted, once I informed Johnson she was under arrest she began to be passive resistant but she eventually complied to commands. There was no force used to affect the arrest. Johnson was searched prior to being placed in my marked patrol car to be transported to the Forestville Barrack. Johnsons vehicle was locked and secured on the right shoulder to be picked up by her friend. While enroute to the Barrack, Johnson was provided a digital copy of the Advice of Rights (DR-015) form from the mva.maryland.gov website to follow along while I played the audio version of the form downloaded from the website in its entirety.  Intoximeter Test:  .08BrAC  After having been read the DR-015, at approximately 0207 hours, Johnson agreed to take the Intoximeter Test. Johnson was transported to the College Park Barrack where the Intoximeter Test would be administered. The Intoximeter Test was administered by Sgt. D. Parsons #5273. At 0243 hours, Johnson took the Intoximeter Test with a result of .08BrAC.  Johnson was charged with DUI/DWI and other traffic related incidents.  Johnson was released from the Forestville Barrack to a sober driver.  Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 11:48:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 22:23:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stacey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7390</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>York</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6327</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499294</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:38:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 09:41:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499294</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15556</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15556</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:38:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 09:42:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499294</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:38:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 09:44:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499294</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>12</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:38:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 09:45:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499294</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:38:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 09:46:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499294</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:38:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 09:48:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499294</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:38:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 09:49:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499294</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:38:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 09:50:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499294</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17272</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:38:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 09:51:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>59</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:38:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:24</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372039</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lisa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wong</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/11/1963 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/20/2023 08:58:05</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lisa</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wong</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/11/1963 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/20/2023 08:58:05</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>13209</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Landsdales Hope</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Bowie</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20720</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.776415</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.955071</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:59:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:59:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:59:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 09:38:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 09:38:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151072</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/20/2023 10:00:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 10:00:39</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>SADCK2BV3HA498698</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JAGU</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>DBL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>75683CG</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>