<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-044427</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/16/2023 03:40:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/16/2023 03:40:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/16/2023 03:27:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/16/2023 03:27:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop resulting in DUI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/16/2023 03:40:21</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6827</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/16/2024 12:19:26</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>717369</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/16/2023 03:40:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/29/2023 09:53:46</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>717369</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I-495</StreetName>
         <City>Oxon Hill</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20745</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.982287</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.806822</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/16/2023 03:40:17</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/16/2023 03:40:17</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/16/2024 12:19:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/16/2023 03:40:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:19</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car (L-48) and Body Worn Camera Operational.      Defendant: Corey Torrell Collins      Date of Birth: 08/02/1985      Date of Arrest: 12/16/2023      Time of Arrest: 0341 Hours     DUI:  23-412   Certificate and Training:  Trained in Administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) through the Maryland State Police (MSP) and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA)   Soundex:  MD10274441863 // MD   Narrative:  VEHICLE IN MOTION (Phase 1):  On December 16, 2023, at approximately 0327 hours, I, Trooper S. Smalls #7676, of the Maryland State Police, currently assigned to the Forestville Barrack, was traveling northbound Capital Beltway at Saint Barnabas Road, Oxon Hill, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20745. I observed a gray dodge journey, in my rear view mirror, traveling at a speed lower than reasonable, causing a congestion of vehicles behind it. I begin to pace the dodge journey going 25 miles per hour (mph) in a 55 mph zone. As the vehicle slowly approached the passenger side of my vehicle, I noticed the drivers interior lights on as well as the driver having a hunched posture over the steering wheel. I observed the vehicle not being able to maintain its lane as the vehicle veered over the fog line twice. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the gray Dodge Journey bearing Maryland registration of 2EV2659.   PERSONAL CONTACT (Phase 2):  Upon my approach to the vehicle I advised the driver that I stopped him due to him driving below the speed limit and failing to maintain his lane. I identified the driver by his Maryland drivers license as Corey Torrell Collins Sr (B/M DOB: 08/02/1985.) I asked Collins where he was coming from and Collins advised that he was coming from a DJing job. As I was talking to Collins I noticed his eyes to be glossy and bloodshot. I asked Collins if he had anything to drink tonight, to which he advised one drink. I confirmed that Collins said one drink, and he had stated one Stella Beer. Collins advised that he was at the restaurant from 6 to 1 something. I asked Collins why he was just making his way home if the event ended at 1 a.m. and Collins advised that he had to break down equipment. As I was gathering information from Collins I could smell the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage. I asked Collins if he would perform the voluntary Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) which he agreed to perform.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (Phase 3):  The evaluation was performed on the shoulder area of the Capital Beltway north at Saint Barnabas Road, Oxon Hill, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20744. The surface was level and free from obvious debris. The weather was dry. Lighting conditions consisted of vehicle headlamps, street lights, and my flashlight. Collins appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries, limps, and/or limb ailments. I asked Collins if he wore glasses or contacts to which he advised he did not, but he had eye surgery in March for a cornea transplant. I asked Collins if he takes any medication to which he advised he takes blood pressure medication.   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) 4 out of 6 clues observed:  Before performing HGN, I instructed Collins to stand with his legs and feet together and his arms down by his sides. I instructed Collins not to move from this position until I instructed him to do so. I asked Collins if he could see my stimulus to which he advised he could. I instructed Collins to follow the tip of my stimulus with his eyes only, without moving his head, neck, or shoulders. Collins exhibited equal pupil size in both eyes. Collins showed equal tracking in both eyes while following the stimulus   Lack of Smooth Pursuit:  Collins showed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.   Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation:  Collins showed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.   Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees:  Collins did not show onset nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.   Vertical Gaze Nystagmus:  Collins did not show vertical gaze nystagmus in either eye.   Walk and Turn (WAT) 4 out of 8 clues observed:  Prior to performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Collins was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Collins was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in this position until instructed to begin. Collins was advised to take nine (9) heel to toe steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Collins was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes on his feet and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, Collins was advised to conduct a turn by taking a series of small steps to the left keeping his lead foot planted. Collins was instructed and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Collins was instructed that once he begins the test, do not stop.   Instructional Phase:  I had to remind Collins to remain in the instructional position twice.   Walking Stage (1st Series):  Collins missed heel to toe on all nine (9) steps. Collins failed to look at his feet while performing the test.   Turn:  Collins completed an improper turn.   WalkingStage (2nd Series): After Collins completed the turn he stopped. Collins missed heel to toe on all nine (9) steps.   One Leg Stand (OLS) 3 out of 4 clues observed:  Prior to performing OLS, I instructed and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Collins was instructed to stand with his legs and feet together and hands down by his sides. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot and count out loud in the manner of one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-three, and so on until instructed to stop.   Puts Foot Down:  Collins puts his foot down on the ninth (9th) second.   Uses Arms for Balance:  Collins uses his arms for balance during seconds 2-9   Sways:  Collins sways during seconds 4-8  25-30   Arrest:      The moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage.      Admission to consuming an alcoholic beverage.      Glossy and bloodshot eyes.      Observed signs of impairment during SFSTs      Preliminary Breath Test:  .11 BrAC  At approximately 0341 hours, Collins was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. Collins was searched before being placed in my marked patrol vehicle to be transported to the Forestville Barrack. Collins was provided a copy of the Advice of Rights (DR-015) from the mva.maryland.gov website to follow along with while I played the audio version of the form downloaded from the same website in its entirety.   Intoximeter Test:  .07 BrAC  After having read the DR-015, at approximately 0411 hours, Collins agreed to submit to the Intoximeter Test.  The breath test was administered by Corporal M. York #6327, with the Maryland State Police (MSP.) The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of .07 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  Collins was charged with DWI and other traffic related charges.  Collins was released from the Forestville Barrack to a sober driver.  Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.      </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/16/2024 08:41:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/16/2024 08:47:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harr</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeremy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7163</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smalls</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7676</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Angeli</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6827</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smalls</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7676</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smalls</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7676</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533904</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 03:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 20:14:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 20:32:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533904</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15570</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 03:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15570</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 20:14:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 20:29:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533904</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15657</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 03:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15657</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 20:14:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 20:22:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533904</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17317</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 03:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17317</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 20:14:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 20:23:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533904</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 03:41:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 20:14:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 20:21:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 20:14:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 20:39:34</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>396357</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Collins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Corey</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Torrell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/02/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>9.0703845E7</SSN>
               <TitleCode>SR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>12/29/2023 10:13:56</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Collins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Corey</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Torrell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/02/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>9.0703845E7</SSN>
               <TitleCode>SR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>C452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/29/2023 10:13:56</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>486</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>MOSSY GROVE</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>La Plata</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20646</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.975251</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.529287</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>468</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6065</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 20:39:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 20:39:34</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 20:39:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 20:39:34</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 20:14:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 20:14:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>160261</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7676</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/01/2024 20:14:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7676</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/01/2024 20:14:34</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3C4PDCBB8KT719134</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>JNY</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2EV2659</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>