<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008615</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/08/2023 22:46:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/08/2023 22:46:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/08/2023 22:25:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/08/2023 22:25:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI/FOA Warrant Service</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 22:46:04</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2864</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 10:12:20</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WAR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN HWY/ PEGGY NECK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>585136</AddressId>
      <City>MDC217</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 22:46:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 19:19:58</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>585136</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Princess Anne</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.66655</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.260908</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB 13 / JUST NORTH OF PEGGY NECK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13848-14120 OCEAN HWY / 31259-31279 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13647-13844 OCEAN HWY / 31298-31853 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13647-13844 OCEAN HWY / 31280-31297 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13656-13847 OCEAN HWY / 31259-31279 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13845-14111 OCEAN HWY / 31280-31297 PEGGY NECK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/08/2023 22:46:00</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/08/2023 22:46:00</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/12/2023 10:10:24</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 22:46:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:15</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police   Princess Anne Barrack X  Tpr. Bynum IBM 7345  Field Operation Bureau  (03/08/2023)  Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle: X-5 is an unmarked 2021 blue Ford Explorer equipped with MVR system.  Type of Report: DUI/FOA Warrant Service  Case Number: 23-MSP-008615  DUI Case Number: 23-95-017  Victim: Society  Driver/Suspect: Kenneth Charles Ryden  Date of Birth: 01/13/1990  License Number: T63563305  PH Number(s): N/A  Troopers Training/Experience:  * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).  * Trained and certified to operate Radar and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  * NHTSA certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E).  Narrative:  This report has been prepared based upon the observations of this trooper and/or those of other troopers relative to the offense(s). The facts contained herein are intended solely to give the prosecuting authority a basic understanding of the facts pertaining to this case. The facts contained herein are not intended to be an exhaustive recitation of the facts pertaining to pretrial or trial issues. Instead, this trooper anticipates that during the pretrial proceedings in this case, the prosecutor will take the opportunity to interview this trooper in order to ascertain any and all relevant facts which might be the subject of this troopers testimony during court proceedings.       Phase #1 - Vehicle In Motion:  On the evening of 03/08/2023, at approximately 2225 hours, I Trooper Bynum was monitoring traffic in the area of southbound US Route 13 south of Stockyard Road, in Somerset County, Maryland. At that time a vehicle passed my location with a tag light out, causing the rear registration plate to not have adequate rear registration plate illumination. This rendered the registration plate illegible from a distance of fifty feet or less. At that time I conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle identified as a 2009 tan Ford Fusion bearing Virginia registration of VXG7316.    Phase #2 - Personal Contact:   Upon running license and wanted checks on the operator identified as Kenneth Charles Ryden, it was discovered he was wanted out of Wyoming on an outstanding warrant, and his drivers license is suspended through Virginia. I requested a certified driving record. Wyoming advised they will extradite. Ryden was ultimately placed under arrest for his outstanding warrant at 2245 hours. After placing Ryden in my patrol vehicle and sitting in the patrol vehicle with him, I immediately detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage filling the inside of my patrol vehicle. Additionally, almost immediately upon entering my patrol vehicle, Ryden asked me if he could pee. Once back at the barrack and upon being asked if he had been drinking Ryden stated no. Additionally when Ryden was first asked about completing field sobriety tests, he initially refused. I explained to Ryden if he refuses field sobriety, which is my way of determining if he is DUI, he would be charged DUI based on my observations. Ryden responded Even if you didnt cha- even if you didnt test me? Thats not legal. While speaking with Ryden, at the barrack, I detected the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from his person and his breath. The barrack additionally began to smell of alcoholic beverage. Additionally looking at Ryden, his eyes were noticeably glassy/watery. After conversation, Ryden eventually agreed to submit to field sobriety tests.  Phase #3 - Pre-Arrest Screening:  The surface was dry, level and free of debris. The field sobriety tests were completed within the Maryland State Police Princess Anne barrack. Ryden was asked if he was taking any medication; to which he responded Kratom and that he smoked marijuana two days ago. He was asked if hes seeing a doctor for anything; to which he responded he was on medication for depression/anxiety; asked about injuries/recent head injuries to which he responded no, and then I dont think so. Ryden advised he had a broken finger. Ryden also mentioned something about his ankles. Ryden was asked if he had blindness in either eye and stated he was thirty percent blind in his left eye and twenty percent blind in his right eye. Ryden was asked if he wears glasses or contacts to which he responded that he does not.    Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6) clues observed  Ryden was told to stand with his feet together and hands down at his sides. Ryden was further told to follow the tip of my pen with his eyes and his eyes only. He was told to keep his head completely straight. Ryden was asked if he understands all of the instructions to which he responded I do. Ryden was asked what color the tip of the pen was to which he responded black and then when asked again he responded silver but black, correctly visualizing and describing the pens two-tone tip.  -Lack of smooth pursuit: Present in both eyes. -Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation: Present in both eyes. -Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees: Present in both eyes. -Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was not observed. -Ryden had equal pupil size as well as equal tracking.     Walk and Turn (2/8) clues observed  Prior to Ryden completing the test I explained and demonstrated the test for him. Ryden was told to stand with his right foot in front of his left foot touching heel to toe, with his hands down at his side. Ryden was instructed to stay in that position until told to start the test and not to begin the test until I told him to. Ryden was asked if he understood, and he indicated that he understood that direction.   Ryden was instructed that when I told him to begin the test he was to take nine heel to toe steps, in a straight line down the hallway imagining there is a straight line. Ryden was further instructed after his first nine heel to toe steps to turn around and take nine heel to toe steps back. He was instructed while he was taking the steps to keep his hands down at his side, make heel to toe contact on every step, stay in a straight line, stare down at his feet, and to count out loud. I demonstrated the test for Ryden. Ryden was complaining about his left ankle during the instructions. Ryden was instructed to complete a satisfactory turn he was to leave his lead foot planted and take a series of small steps with his back foot to turn himself around. Ryden was asked if he understood all of the instructions I gave him, and he responded guess so, I got it, even though I have a super weak left ankle. Ryden appeared very unsteady on his feet during the explanation of this test. On the second of the four times he stepped out of the instructional phase, Ryden swayed to his left, used his left hand on a door frame to steady himself, stumbled to his right, and stepped out of the instructional phase. Additionally, Ryden was observed using his arms for balance during the instructional phase.  -Instructional Stage- Failed to maintain starting position. (Four times) -Turn- Improper turn.        One Leg Stand (2/4) clues observed  Prior to beginning the last test I explained and demonstrated the test for Ryden in the following manner. Ryden was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands at his side. Ryden was told to remain in that position until I told him to begin. Ryden was told to raise one foot, either foot six inches off the ground; toe pointed outwards so his foot would be flat to the ground; both legs straight; and hands down at his sides. Ryden was told to count out loud in this manner; one thousand one, one thousand two, one thousand three, one thousand four and so forth while staring down at his foot, until told to stop. Ryden was asked if he understood the instructions, and he replied I understand. Ryden balanced on his right foot. Ryden counted in a different manner i.e (One one thousand, two one thousand and so forth.)  After beginning the test Ryden had to be reminded to look down at his foot. By his own count on second nine, Ryden swayed heavily to his right side and on second ten Ryden swayed to his left. By Rydens count on second thirteen he swayed again to his right. He then complained about his ankles again. On Rydens count on second fourteen Ryden was unable to maintain his balance. He put his foot down and again put his foot down on second seventeen. He then complained about his ankle again. I concluded the test at this time.  Clues Observed:  -Swayed -Put foot down   Preliminary Breath Test  Ryden was offered a PBT test and ultimately took the test, providing a breath sample for the PBT, which resulted in a reading of .172 BrAC.     Disposition andBreath Test   Due to the above facts I determined that Ryden was driving under the influence of alcohol. I placed a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights form in front of Ryden for him to read along as I read him the form in its entirety. At approximately 2334 hours, the conclusion of reading the form, Ryden refused to provide an evidentiary breath sample.The breath test was refused. After hearing the penalties for a refusal Ryden stated that doesnt sound too bad and that he was going to prison for like five years (referring to his FOA warrant.)     Charging  DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL RECKLESS DRIVING  NEGLIGENT DRIVING DRIVING MOTOR VEHICLE ON HIGHWAY WITHOUT REQUIRED LICENSE AND AUTHORIZATION PERSON DRIVING MOTOR VEH. ON HWY. ON SUSPENDED OUT OF STATE LIC.  DIRECTING AND PERMITTING HWY. VEH. OPERATION CONTRARY TO LAW  DISPLAYING SUSPENDED LIC.  POSSESSING SUSPENDED LIC. DRIVING VEH. W/O ADEQUATE REAR REG. PLATE ILLUMINATION  Ryden was given all appropriate documentation and then spoke with the commissioner regarding his outstanding FOA warrant. The commissioner held Ryden with no bond, and he was transported to SCDC without incident. Ryden was released to the custody of SCDC at approximately 0134 hours on 03/09/2023. The FOA warrant paperwork as well as DUI paperwork is attached to the report.    I request this case be closed by arrest.    All events occurred in Somerset County, Maryland.     </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:47:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 22:27:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brown</LastName>
            <FirstName>Clinton</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7569</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bynum</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7345</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498014</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 22:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:17:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 16:58:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498014</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 22:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:23:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 16:58:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498014</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 22:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:26:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 16:58:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498014</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 22:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:29:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 16:58:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498014</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17023</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 22:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17023</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:30:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 16:58:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498014</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3074</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 22:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3074</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:37:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 16:58:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498014</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21199</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 22:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21199</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:37:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 16:58:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498014</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3099</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 22:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3099</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:37:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 16:58:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498014</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 22:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17272</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:37:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 16:58:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498014</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 22:25:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19731</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 16:57:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 16:58:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:44:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:20</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371142</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ryden</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kenneth</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/13/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/09/2023 14:41:56</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R350</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K530</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ryden</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kenneth</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Charles</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/13/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R350</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K530</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/09/2023 14:41:56</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>30148</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Racetrack</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Melfa</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>23410</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:44:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:44:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:51</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7345</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 14:17:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7345</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/09/2023 14:17:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>