<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-010446</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/23/2023 16:31:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/23/2023 16:31:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/23/2023 15:43:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/23/2023 15:43:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>ACRS / DUI #23-167</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 16:31:24</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 10:09:20</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I83 / RUXTON RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>581679</AddressId>
      <City>MDC367</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 16:31:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 15:04:12</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>581679</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I83</StreetName>
         <City>Cockeysville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.66271</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.40092</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB JFX SO RUXTON RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>NB</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB 83 BTWN RUXTON AND NORTHERN PKWY</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>S/B I83 / 0-0 RUXTON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>N/B I-83 @ RUXTON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB LS AND RS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>NB MM 11</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>NB LS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB JFX @ RUXTON</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>S/B 83 PAST RUXTON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I83NB / 0-0 RUXTON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB SO RUXTON</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>N/B 83 BETWEEN EXIT 10 AND I695</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>N/B I83 / 0-0 RUXTON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>S/B I83 RUXTON-NOTHERN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I83 N BETWEEN RUXTON/695</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>N/B 83 PRIOR TO RUXTON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>S/B I-83 AT RUXTON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I83 / 0-0 RUXTON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/23/2023 16:31:22</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/23/2023 16:31:22</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/03/2023 01:02:00</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/23/2023 16:31:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP unmarked vehicle R-39, In-Car/Body Worn Camera Operational.  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING    Completed the DWI Detection and Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Course. -NHTSA  Completed the Advanced Roadside Impairment Driving Enforcement Program. -NHTSA  Completed the Cannabis Impairment Detection Workshop. -MSP CTAU  Completed the DWI Detection and Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Refresher Training. -NHTSA    VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On Thursday, March 23rd, 2023, at approximately 1543 hours, I (Trooper First Class Lora #7207) was dispatched to Jones Falls Expressway North, at Ruxton Road, Cockeysville, Maryland 21209, in reference to a two-vehicle crash between a white vehicle and a blue Volkswagen Golf.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) Soon after my arrival, I contacted the driver and sole occupant of a blue Volkswagen Golf Maryland 6FE1620. I introduced myself, provided my badge number, and informed the driver that we were being audibly and visually recorded. I asked what happened. The initial complaint I received was that a white sedan abruptly cut off the blue Volkswagen, subsequently causing the Volkswagen to run off-road left, into the ditch, and sideswiped the guardrail. As the driver explained what occurred, I observed her to appear emotional, her makeup to be ruined, and her eyes to be glassy and bloodshot. I asked for her drivers license, vehicle registration, and proof of insurance. However, she only produced her drivers license and vehicle registration. I identified the driver as Perry Elizabeth, Ryan (W/F 10-08-1997) via her Maryland license. Based on my initial investigation, I did not observe damage from another vehicle, but I did observe damage sustained from the guardrail and ditch on the left side of the Volkswagen. Soon after, I returned to Ryan to obtain the alleged witness information. As she spoke, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. I asked where she was coming from, to which she replied Baltimore Country Club. She explained she was hostess there and had consumed one alcoholic beverage. Later, Ryan called the drink Fadorade. And described it as a mix of Vodka and Gatorade. As I asked Ryan to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Testing, and Ryan agreed.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of the Jones Falls Expressway at Ruxton Road. The surface was dry and free from any obvious debris. The weather was cloudy and approximately 57 degrees Fahrenheit. Lighting conditions consisted of broad daylight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Ryan appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries.  I asked Ryan the following questions:   Injuries  No  Medication  Yes, Zoloft 100mg (Depression and Anxiety)  Medical Conditions  No  Glasses  Yes, at night to drive and watch TV.   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pointer finger was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Ryans eyes. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Ryans pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking and no resting Nystagmus was observed. She was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Ryan if she understood the instructions and she stated yes.  Ryan displayed:   Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes Vertical Nystagmus  Observed.   WALK AND TURN (8/8 clues observed) Prior to Ryan performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Ryan was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Ryan was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Ryan was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. Ryan was to keep her hands flat at her side, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Ryan was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Ryan was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Ryan was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her side, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Ryan if she understood the instructions, and she said yes.  Instructional Stage:   Started too soon. Ryan attempted to begin walking, but I stopped her.  Failed to remain in the instructional position. Ryan moved her right foot from in front of her left and placed it next to her left.     Walking Stage (1st Nine):   Missed heel to toe on step six  Stepped off-line on step six  Stopped walking on step nine   Walking Stage (2nd Nine):   Raised her arms for balance on steps one through five  Ryan took ten steps, turned around, took ten additional steps, turned around, and then took nine steps to return.   Turn:   Improper, Ryan pivoted on her left foot, simultaneously raised her arms for balance as she turned, and then stumbled   ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed) Prior to Jones performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Jones was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given during the test. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and continue the test until told to stop. I asked Jones if she understood the instructions and she stated yes.  Instructional Stage:   Nothing to report  Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10:   Used arms for balance. Ryans arms were more than 6 inches from her sides.   Seconds 11-20:   Swayed body to the left and right.                                               Seconds 21-30:    Swayed body to the left and right.     Ryan submitted to a preliminary breath test with a .13 BrAC result.  ARREST Based on the previously referenced facts, I had reason to believe Ryan was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol. I arrested Ryan for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 1655 hours. She was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. Ryan was transported to the Maryland State Police  Golden Ring Barrack for processing. Once inside the barrack, at 1756 hours, I played the English audio DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Ryan. She was given a paper copy to read along. At the conclusion of the form, Ryan verbally advised that she would submit breath samples for the intoximeter test and signed the form indicating the same.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: Ryans mouth was checked, and no foreign objects or piercings were observed. I conducted the observation period on Ryan in its entirety, starting at 1746 hours. However, to ensure enough time had passed since allowing Ryan to use the restroom, the time was again restarted commencing at 1757 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: The intoximeter test was administered within the two-hour statutory time frame. This test was administered by a certified breath technician on equipment approved by the Chief Toxicologist in the Department of State Police Forensic Science Division and resulted in a .13 BrAC per 210 liters of breath.  Ryan was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to her parents. Ryan was emotional, polite, and cooperative throughout the process. All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 18:31:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 18:44:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nolf Jr.</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gregory</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7209</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lora</LastName>
            <FirstName>Miguel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7207</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Iman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5709</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lora</LastName>
            <FirstName>Miguel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7207</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lora</LastName>
            <FirstName>Miguel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7207</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499846</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/23/2023 15:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 15:00:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 15:00:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499846</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/23/2023 15:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 15:01:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 15:01:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499846</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/23/2023 15:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 15:03:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 15:03:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499846</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/23/2023 15:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 15:03:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 15:03:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499846</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/23/2023 15:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 15:03:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 15:03:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>25</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 15:14:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372699</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ryan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Perry</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elizabeth</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/08/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 15:13:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ryan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Perry</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elizabeth</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/08/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 15:13:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>604</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5670</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 15:14:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 15:14:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 15:14:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 15:14:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 15:03:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 15:03:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151343</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7207</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 15:30:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7207</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 15:30:53</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3vw217au7gm022565</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2016</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>VOLK</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>GOLFNEW</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6fe1620</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>