<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-004379</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/04/2023 02:52:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/04/2023 02:52:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/04/2023 02:26:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/04/2023 02:26:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop led to DUI/DWI arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 02:52:21</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0392</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 16:36:17</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>682964</AddressId>
      <City>MDC113</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 02:52:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 15:58:49</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>682964</AddressId>
         <StreetName>W/B Central Avenue at Church Rd</StreetName>
         <City>Bowie</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20721</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.756158</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.902093</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/04/2023 02:52:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/04/2023 02:52:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/12/2023 12:56:40</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 02:52:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was recorded audibly and visually on BWC. L-31 is equipped with MVR.  Defendant: Peters, John Allen Jr. Date of Birth: 05/26/1971 Date of Arrest: 02/04/2023 Times of Arrest: 0251 Hours DUI # 23-041: (Forestville Barrack)  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *Trained and certified to operate the Preliminary Breath Test through the Maryland State Police.   PERSONAL CONTACT On 02/04/2023 at approximately 0225 hours, I was traveling W/B Central Avenue prior to Church Rd, Bowie, Prince Georges County, Maryland, when I observed a black Mercedes-Benz CLS bearing the Maryland Registration (5FC1934), unable to maintain in its lane and traveling at a low rate of speed.  I observed the above vehicle traveling between lanes one (1) and two (2). I also paced the vehicle for two-tenths of a mile before obtaining the speed (40/55) then the vehicle suddenly accelerated its speed from 40 to 70 within three (3) seconds. I then activated my patrol vehicles emergency equipment. The vehicle came to a stop in lane one (1). I approached the drivers side of the vehicle and made contact with the driver of a Black Mercedes-Benz CLS, who was later identified as Mr. Peters, John Allen Jr, DOB: 05/26/1971, by his Maryland Drivers License. I introduced myself as Tpr. Thienhom #7518 and informed Mr. Peters that he was being recorded. I informed Mr. Peters that I stopped him for not being able to maintain his lane and for his speed (70/50). I asked him what was going on, and he stated that someone was behind him, and he was trying to move out of their way.I asked him to provide me with his drivers license and the registration card of the vehicle. As Mr. Peters was retrieving his license and registration, I observed his head and body movements to be slow and lethargic and observed his eyes to be glassy and bloodshot. He handed his old drivers license that was expired three (3) years ago. I asked Mr. Peters where he was coming from, and he stated, Waldorf. I asked him when was the last time he had something to drink, and he stated that about two (2) hours ago. He informed me that he had a beer, a Heineken, just one can, about 16 oz. I then asked Mr. Peters where he was coming from again, and he stated that he was coming from a club in Waldorf.  Please note it was revealed later that the vehicle that was behind him was his friend following him home.  At this time, I asked Mr. Peters if he would be willing to submit to the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Mr. Peters agreed to submit to the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING The evaluation was performed on W/B Central Avenue W/O Church Rd in lane one (1). The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 15 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and my patrol vehicles lights. Mr. Peters appeared to be in good physical condition. (Reference below for further information regarding Mr. Peterss injuries and medications.)  I asked Mr. Petersthe following questions: Injuries - No. Medication - No. Medical Conditions - No. Contact lenses - No. Glasses - Yes. I asked Mr. Peters to take his glasses off for the entire the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Mr. Peterss eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Mr. Peterss pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking, and no resting Nystagmus was observed. I asked Mr. Peters if he understood the instructions, and he stated, sure.  1) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 degrees - Present in both eyes  Mr. Peters moved his head a couple of times to the direction of my pen. He also failed to keep focusing the tip of my pen more than two (2) occasions.  WALK AND TURN (5/8 clues observed) Prior to Mr. Peters performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Mr. Peters was instructed to place his left foot on the solid line, place his right foot directly in front of his left foot, and touch heel to toe. After he assumed the instructional position, He was advised to keep his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Mr. Peters was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Mr. Peters was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Mr. Peters was again explained, and I demonstrated, that the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Mr. Peters was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Mr. Peters if he understood the test, and he stated, Yes.(Footwear: Black dress shoes).  Instructional Stage: 1) Unable to maintain balance - His feet broke prior to being told to start walking multiple times. 2) Starts too soon - Observed - He started walking, and I had to tell him not to start yet on two (2) occasions.  Walking Stage (1st nine): 1) Stops while walking - Not observed. 2) Misses heel-to-toe - Observed - Missed heel to toe by more than half an inch on every step. 3) Step off the line - Observed - Stepped off the line by more than a width of foot. 4) Uses arms to balance - Observed - Raised his arms to gain balance the entire time.   5) Incorrect amount of steps - Not observed.  Walking Stage (2nd nine): 1) Stops while walking - Not observed. 2) Misses heel-to-toe - Observed - Missed heel to toe by more than half an inch on every step. 3) Step off the line - Observed - Stepped off the line by more than a width of foot. 4) Uses arms to balance - Observed - Raised his arms to gain balance the entire time. 5) Incorrect amount of steps - Not observed.  Turn: Completed properly  ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed) I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Mr. Peters was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, one thousand-three), and continue the test until told to stop. Mr. Peters was asked if he understood the test, and he stated that he understood.   1) Putting Foot down - Observed - He put his foot down the first time during the first ten (10) seconds. He put his foot down one more time, from ten (10) seconds to twenty (20) seconds.  2) Swaying - Observed - He was swaying body to the left and right after I reminded him to keep his foot off the ground.  3) Hopping - Not observed.  4) Raising Arms - Observed - He used his arms to balance himself the entire time.  After completing the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, I asked Mr. Peters if he would be willing to take the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT). I informed him that it would not be admissible in court. Mr. Peters refused to take PBT.  ARREST/ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) Based on the following, I had reason to believe Mr. Peters was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath *Eyes were glassy and bloodshot *His head and body movements to be slow and lethargic when retrieving the drivers license and the registration card. *Admission to consuming alcoholic beverages earlier prior to driving *My observed signs of impairment as he performed Standardized Field Sobriety Tests  I placed Mr. Peters under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0251 hours. Mr. Peters then was transported to the Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack. While en route to the barrack, I played the English audio DR-15 Advice of Rights form via the MVAs official law enforcement website to him in its entirety. At the conclusion of the DR-15, Mr. Peters verbally agreed to submit to the intoximeter test and later (02/04/2023 at 0330 hours) signed the form indicating the same.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the observation period on Mr. Peters in its entirety, starting with his time of the arrest. I escorted Mr. Peters into the arrest processing room and remained in his custody until the time of the test. Mr. Peterss mouth was checked and no foreign objects or piercings were observed.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: The breath test was administered by Sgt. Bolduc#4889, and two (2) samples of Mr. Peterss breath were obtained. The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of 0.12 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  CHARGES Mr. Peters was charged with the following citations: 1. DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL PER SE (0L00YJK) 2. DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL (0L10YJK) 3. DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL (0L20YK) 4. NEGLIGENT DRIVING (0L30YJK) 5. FAILED TO OBEY TRAFFIC CONTROL DEVICE (0L40YJK) 6. FAILED TO DRIVE VEHICLE ON RIGHT HALF OF ROADWAY WHEN REQUIRED (0L50YJK)  Mr. Peters was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to a sober driver. Mr. Peters was polite and cooperative throughout the process.  Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 16:33:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 20:06:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shai</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7463</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Murray</LastName>
            <FirstName>Niall</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7580</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Arioso</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7268</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bolduc</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4889</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thienhom</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bryce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7518</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493762</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/04/2023 02:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 15:55:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 15:55:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493762</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/04/2023 02:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 15:55:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 15:55:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493762</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/04/2023 02:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 15:55:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 15:55:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>51</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 16:30:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:41</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368129</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Peters</LastName>
               <FirstName>John</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Allen Jr</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/26/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/04/2023 16:18:20</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P362</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Peters</LastName>
               <FirstName>John</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Allen Jr</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/26/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P362</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/04/2023 16:18:20</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>14000</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Gadsen</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Upper Marlboro</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20774</Zip5>
               <Zip4>8512</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.764085</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.859024</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 16:30:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 16:30:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 16:30:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 16:30:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 15:55:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 15:55:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149473</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 16:31:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 16:31:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/04/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WDDLJ9BB2CA048472</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2012</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MERZ</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CLSCLASS</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5FC1934</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>