<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008491</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/08/2023 03:26:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/08/2023 03:26:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/08/2023 03:05:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/08/2023 03:05:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop. Driver was arrested for DUI / DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 03:26:51</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0104</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 09:14:10</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>659552</AddressId>
      <City>MDC574</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 03:26:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/09/2023 05:45:31</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>659552</AddressId>
         <StreetName>N/B Rt 301 S/O VFW Road</StreetName>
         <City>Waldorf</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20601</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-76.8920169666667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.6441356833333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/08/2023 03:26:49</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/08/2023 03:26:49</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/10/2023 01:32:17</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 03:26:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:20:57</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Traffic stop. In-Car Camera Operational, H-26. This incident was recorded on TFC Thomas Body-Worn Camera.  Driver:  Shannon Nicole Rison, W/F, DOB: 03/08/1992  Maryland SDX:  R-250-765-630-177   Address:  10474 Mark Dr., Waldorf, MD 20601  Vehicle: MD 3DS1887 - 2019 Mitsubishi Outlander  Location: N/B Route 301 S/O VFW Rd  Training and Certificates:   Trained and certified in administering the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Safety Administration.   Completed LIDAR and RADAR training through the Maryland State Police.  Completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E) training in June 2019.   Completed Crisis Intervention Training in September 2020.  Distinguished Graduate of the Maryland Highway Safety Office and University of Maryland DUI Institute in July 2022.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Recipient of the Maryland Highway Safety Office DUI Award for Consecutive Years (2020 and 2021).  PHASE 1  VEHICLE IN MOTION Narrative:  On 03/08/2023, at approximately 0305 hours, I, TFC Thomas #7065 of the Maryland State Police was on routine patrol in the area of northbound Route 301, south of VFW Road in Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland. At that time, I observed a white Mitsubishi Outlander bearing Maryland Registration 3DS1887 traveling in front of my patrol vehicle in lane #2. I observed the Outlanders passenger-side front and rear tires travel over the divided line into Lane #3 on three separate times. I further observed the Outlander traveling halfway in lane #2 and lane #3 and over the divided line and it appeared the driver was unable to maintain her lane. I positioned my vehicle behind the Outlander, activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop.  PHASE 2  PERSONAL CONTACT  I made contact with the driver and asked her for her license and registration. I immediately observed her pupils were glassy and bloodshot and detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath. The driver appeared disoriented. I asked the driver if she consumed any alcoholic beverages today and the driver responded by saying, Yes, I had one shot. I observed the driver having difficulties handling her registration and drivers license. I asked the driver again, Be honest with me because I smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from your breath and she responded by saying, I had drinks at dinner for my birthday. The driver was identified through her Maryland Drivers License as Shannon Nicole Rison (W/F, DOB: 03/08/1992).  PHASE 3  PRE-ARREST SCREENING  I asked Rison if she would conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests and she initially responded by saying, No, I dont have to do it. I advised Rison that I observed significant signs of impairment and that she would not be able to drive her vehicle due to the impairment. Rison then stated she would conduct the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. I asked Rison if she suffered from High Blood Pressure or diabetes and she responded by saying, No. I further asked Rison if she ever had any head trauma, brain tumors or concussions and she responded by saying, No. Rison stated she took medication for eczema that was prescribed by a doctor. I asked Rison if she suffered from any medical issues that would prevent her from completing the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests and she responded by saying, No.   The three tests administered to Rison were the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus, Walk and Turn and the One-Leg Stand tests. Rison conducted the tests in comfortable shoes and loose fitted clothing. All tests were performed on a level surface, free of debris and in a well-lit area.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)   The first test conducted was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held 12-15 inches fromRisons eyes. Rison was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping herhead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hereyes until told to stop. Risons pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking.Rison advised she understood the instructions.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in Both Eyes.  2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in Both Eyes.  3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in Both Eyes. Vertical Nystagmus  Not Present.  WALK AND TURN (3/8 clues observed)  Prior to Rison performing the test, Iproperly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Rison was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel-to-toe. Rison was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her side and to remain in that position until told to begin. Rison was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel-to-toe on every step. Rison was instructed to keep her hands flat at her side, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, it was explained and demonstrated to Rison to keep her left foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps with her right foot to turn completely around. Again, it was explained and demonstrated to Rison during the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Rison was instructed that once she began the test, she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her side, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. Rison advised she understood the instructions. When asked to stand in the position to begin the test, Rison seemed confused and could not remember the instructions that were given. I had to explain two additional times how to conduct the test.  Instructional Stage: 1.) No Observations Noted.  Walking Stage (1st Nine): 1.) Missed heel-to-toe on steps 1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8 and 9. 2.) Raised arms more than 6 inches from her side to maintain balance.  Improper turn: Rison did not complete a series of small steps as directed per the instructions.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): 1.) Missed heel-to-toe on steps 2, 5, 6 and 7. 2.) Raised arms more than 6 inches from her side to maintain balance.  ONE LEG STAND (1/4 clues observed)  Prior to Rison performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Rison was instructed to stand with her heels together and her hands down by her sides while the instructions were given, and during the test. When instructed to start, Rison was instructed to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, Rison was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop.Rison advised she understood the instructions. Rison stated the wind may cause her to become unbalanced.  Instructional Stage: Failed to Maintained Balance. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: 1.) Swayed more than 3 inches from her left to her right. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 11-20: 1.) Swayed more than 3 inches from her left to her right. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 21-30: 1.) Swayed more than 3 inches from her left to her right.   I offered Rison a Preliminary Breath Test (PBT), to which she agreed with a .15 BrAC. Based on my training, knowledge and experience as a Maryland State Trooper and in making DUI and DWI arrests, her glassy and bloodshot eyes, the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Risons breath and her inability to follow simple instructions, I believed Rison was too impaired to operate a motor vehicle. I placed Rison under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at 0326 hours.   Rison was transported to the Maryland State Police La Plata Barrack for processing.   While in the Barrack, Rison was advised of her DR-15, Advice of Rights on 03/08/2023 at 0347 hours. Rison was explained the form, and asked if she had any questions. Rison responded by saying, No. At 0354 hours, Rison signed the DR-15, Advise of Rights Form and refused to submit to an Intoximeter test.    Rison was processed for Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol and Driving While Impaired by Alcohol. Rison was released to a sober driver at the Barrack.  Charges:    TA 21-902(a1i)  Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol  TA 21-902(b1i)  Driving While Impaired by Alcohol  TA 21-901.1(b)  Negligent Driving  TA 21-901.1(a)  Reckless Driving   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;TA 21-201(a1)  Failure to Obey Properly Placed Traffic Control Device Ins.  All events occurred in Charles County, MD.  Case Closed. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/09/2023 05:30:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7065</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/09/2023 05:46:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hughes</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brant</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7578</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thomas II</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7065</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burroughs</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5968</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thomas II</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7065</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thomas II</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7065</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497890</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 03:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 04:57:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7065</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 04:58:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497890</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 03:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 04:57:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7065</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 04:58:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 04:57:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:37</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371037</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Rison</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shannon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/08/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 04:49:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S550</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Rison</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shannon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/08/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S550</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 04:49:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>10474</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mark</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Waldorf</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20601</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.945153</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.652185</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>298</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9814</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 04:59:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 04:59:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 04:59:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 04:57:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7065</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 04:57:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150657</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7065</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 04:57:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7065</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/08/2023 04:57:18</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JA4AR3AU7KU008938</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MITS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>OUT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3DS1887</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>