<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-005336</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/11/2023 02:47:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/11/2023 02:47:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/11/2023 02:46:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/11/2023 02:46:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The vehicle was stopped for a moving violation. Upon contact with the driver, the odor of an alcoholic beverage was detected. SFST's were conducted poorly, and the driver was placed under arrest for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 02:47:35</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0104</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/17/2023 08:39:27</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>ACTON LANE/TAWNY DRIVE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>683866</AddressId>
      <City>MDC574</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 02:47:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 14:05:39</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>683866</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Acton</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Waldorf</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20602</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>DR</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.90017</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.6432</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11786-11900 ACTON LN / 2472-2490 WESTERN PARK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/11/2023 02:47:32</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/11/2023 02:47:32</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/16/2023 14:24:13</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 02:47:35</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car camera and body worn camera operational.  Defendant: Cordova-Arias, Werner Danilo  Date of Birth: 04/23/1992  Time of arrest: 0246 hours  Location: Acton Lane in the area of Tawny Drive, Waldorf, Charles County Maryland, 20602.  Guatemala Identification card: 2113 28995 1712  DUI#: 23-024  1stDUI  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING  *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police.  *Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement through Charles County Sheriffs Office.  NARRATIVE/ VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1):  On 02/11/2023, at approximately 0215 hours, I, Tpr. Tripp #7333 with the Maryland State Police La Plata H Barrack, was on patrol northbound Route 925, in the area of Acton Lane, Waldorf, Charles County Maryland, in lane one when I observed a silver Mitsubishi Lancer, bearing Maryland registration, 3EV9716, in lane one, failing to drive within a single lane. I also observed the vehicle to cross the single solid yellow line by approximately one tire length. The vehicle took approximately three seconds before realigning back into lane one. Once the vehicle turned onto Acton Lane, I observed the vehicle cross over the solid white line from the right by approximately half a tire length. The vehicle took approximately two seconds before realigning back into lane one. I then observed the vehicle to cross over into the left turn lane by approximately one tire length. The vehicle took approximately two seconds before realigning back into lane one. The vehicle then stopped approximately 250 feet away from the circular red light, and took approximately five seconds before continuing forward to stop at the stop line. I activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop onActon Lane in the area of Western Parkway, Waldorf, Charles County Maryland, 20602, in the right turn lane. At the time of the stop, the light was at a steady circular red signal and as I approached the vehicle, the light then changed to a steady circular green signal. The driver then drives off at a slow steady speed, unaware that I am behind the vehicle with my emergency equipment activated. I then follow the vehicle and activated my siren (Siren use was on and off approximately four times) to get the drivers attention. The vehicle then comes to a complete stop at approximately 800 feet passed the intended stopping location at Acton Lane in the area of Tawny Drive, Waldorf, Charles County Maryland in the right turn lane.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):  Upon contact with the driver, I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle. I requested the driver for his drivers license and registration, he only displayed an identification card (ID). I was able to identify the driver through his Guatemalan ID card as, Cordova-Arias, Werner Danilo (H/M, DOB: 04/23/1992). Due to Cordova being unable to speak English, I communicated with him through Google Translate.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):  TFC Sabock #6924 assisted with the traffic stop. While standing in front of Cordovas vehicle, I asked if there were any medical conditions that I should be aware of, he advised no. I asked Cordova if he would be able to do the Walk and Turn (WAT) test and the One Leg Stand (OLS) test, he advised yes.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS TEST: (6/6 clues observed).  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Cordovas eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping hishead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hiseyes until told to stop. Hispupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. Hewas positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. While conducting HGN, Cordova was repeatedly told to keep his head straight and follow the pen with just his eyes. Cordova was also swaying back and forth throughout this test.  Cordova displayed equal pupil size, equal tracking and no resting nystagmus in both eyes.  Cordova displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  Cordova displayed nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  Cordova displayed nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.  VERTICAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS:  Cordova displayed vertical Nystagmus in both eyes.   WALK AND TURN:  Cordova refused to take the test.  ONE LEG STAND:  Cordova refused to take the test.  Cordova was offered to take the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) and refused to take to the test.  Arrest:  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person  -Bloodshot and glassy eyes  -Slurred speech   -Swaying backing and forth while standing  -Clues displayed from the Standardized Field Sobriety Test.  Cordova was arrested for Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol at 0246 hours. Cordova was transported to the Maryland State Police La Plata H barrack for processing at 0305 hours. While Cordova was being read his DR-15 Advice of Rights via the audio Motor Vehicle Administration (MVA) Spanish interpreter, Cordova began displaying signs of a possible overdose. Due to the overdose Cordova stopped breathing and began to go into shock. He was released from handcuffs and placed in the recovery position.  TFC Kreczmer #6916 conducted sternum rubs and administered Narcan on Cordova at 0322 hours. Myself and Sgt. Walker #4988 assisted with the recovery of Cordova. Emergency Medical Services (EMS) was contacted to transport Cordova to Charles Regional Medical Center (CRMC). EMS arrived on scene at 0332 hours. Cordova was breathing and conscious before being transported to the hospital. Cordova was transported to CRMC at 0354 hours.  While at CRMC, Cpl. Borroughs #5968, TFC Thomas #7065, and Tpr. Hughes #7578 assisted me with Cordova. Cordova began to become alert from the overdose. Cordova also was confused on where he was and began to tear off his Serum tubes that was placed in his arm by EMS. Cordova began to be uncooperative and intrusive throughout the entire time at CRMC. The DR-15 Advice of Rights was played again via the audio MVA Spanish interpreter. While the DR-15 audio was being played, Cordova urinated on the floor at the hospital. Cordova then refused both the intoximeter (blood test) and DRE at 0525 hours.  Cordova received the following citations:  TA-21-902 (b1i) Driving vehicle while impaired by alcohol  TA-21-902 (a1i) Driving vehicle while under the influence of alcohol  TA-21-902 (d1i) Driving vehicle while impaired by controlled dangerous substance  TA-21-902 (c1i) Driving vehicle while so far impaired by drugs  alcohol cannot drive safely  TA-16-101 (a1) Driving motor vehicle on highway without required license and authorization  TA-21-301 (a) Failure to drive vehicle on right half of roadway when required  TA-21-201(a1) Driver failure to obey properly placed traffic control device instructions  TA-21-901.1(b) Negligent driving  TA-21-901.1(a) Reckless driving  TA-16-112 (c) Fail to display license on demand of a police officer  TA-13-409 (b) Fail to display registration card on demand of a police officer  TA-21-707 (a) Driver failure to stop at stop sign line  Cordova was released to the custody of the hospital.  All events occurred in Charles County, Maryland.  Case closed. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/13/2023 08:40:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 14:04:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kreczmer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6916</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Walker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quintina</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4988</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thomas II</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7065</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hughes</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brant</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7578</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Manning</LastName>
            <FirstName>Marcus</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6421</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tripp</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sedrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7333</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494722</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:30:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 08:41:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494722</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:30:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 08:41:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494722</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:30:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 08:41:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494722</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:30:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 08:41:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494722</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:30:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 08:41:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494722</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:30:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 08:41:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494722</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:31:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 08:41:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494722</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:31:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 08:41:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494722</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19731</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:31:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 08:41:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494722</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:31:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 08:41:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494722</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16616</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16616</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:31:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 08:41:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494722</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>12</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15640</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>12</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15640</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:31:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 08:41:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>30</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:38:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:20</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368772</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cordova-Arias</LastName>
               <FirstName>Werner</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Danilo</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/23/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 06:37:13</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C631</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W656</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cordova-Arias</LastName>
               <FirstName>Werner</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Danilo</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/23/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C631</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W656</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 06:37:13</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4808</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Underwood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Waldorf</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20602</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.902554</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.589751</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:38:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:47</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:38:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:47</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:38:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:47</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:38:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:47</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 14:16:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:30</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369263</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>CORDOVA ARIAS</LastName>
               <FirstName>ENMA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ADALY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/29/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/16/2023 14:16:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C631</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>CORDOVA ARIAS</LastName>
               <FirstName>ENMA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ADALY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/29/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C631</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/16/2023 14:16:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4808</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Underwood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Waldorf</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20602</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.902554</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.589751</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 14:16:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 06:30:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 06:30:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149714</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/16/2023 14:17:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 14:17:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JA3AJ26E22U017702</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2002</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MITS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>LAN</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3EV9716</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>