<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-018711</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/26/2023 03:20:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/26/2023 03:20:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/26/2023 03:05:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/26/2023 03:05:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI with a speed of 128 MPH on N/B 97. Subject refused all testing.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/26/2023 03:20:40</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/12/2023 11:58:34</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I97 NB TO QUARTERFIELD EB / QUARTERFIELD RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>589924</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/26/2023 03:20:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 12:15:09</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>589924</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I97 Nb To Quarterfield Eb</StreetName>
         <City>Glen Burnie</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>265-293 I97 NB TO QUARTERFIELD EB / 7730-7769 QUARTERFIELD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>265-293 I97 NB TO QUARTERFIELD EB / 7770-7779 QUARTERFIELD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/26/2023 03:20:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/26/2023 03:20:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/05/2023 08:55:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/26/2023 03:20:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:54:42</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-car camera operational. Trooper #7362 BWC was functioning and in use during this incident.  DUI # P-23-056   CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING:  - National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) certified to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs)  - Certified Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator  - NHTSA Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) certified    VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On May 26, 2023, at approximately 0304 hours, I, Trooper Litz #7362 was traveling in the area of Northbound Interstate 97 and New Cut Road in my marked patrol vehicle P-9. While traveling Northbound on Interstate 97 in lane 2, South of New Cut Road, I observed a Black Kia Sportage with Temproray Maryland registration T1342978, traveling Northbound in lane 1, approach me at a high rate of speed from the rear. The vehicle remained in lane 1 while it passed me on my drivers side. The Kia Sportage passed me at a high enough rate of speed that it caused my patrol vehicle to physically shake while I continued to travel Northbound. The Kia did not attempt to slow or utilize its brakes at any point. I attempted to close the quickly expanding distance between myself and the Kia. While doing so, I observed the Kia move from lane 1 to lane 3 in an effort to pass other vehicles traveling Northbound in lanes 1 and 2. I moved into lane 3 and continued to attempt to close the distance between myself and the Kia.   The Kia then moved back into lane 2 to pass another vehicle traveling Northbound in lane 3. Still following the Kia, and having to travel at a high rate of speed to do so, I moved into lane 1 to provide the most distance possible between myself and the other vehicle we passed that was traveling in lane 3.After I passed the vehicle in lane 3 while I was in lane 1, I again attempted to close the distance between myself and the Kia. I moved into lane 2, placing me behind the Kia, without any other cars on the roadway. While I was traveling at 128 Miles Per Hour for approximately 2 seconds directly behind the Kia, it again began to accelerate away from my patrol vehicle. I reached a top speed of 137 Miles Per Hour in an effort to close the distance even more between myself and the Kia, at which point I was successful in doing so. I activated my emergency lighting system while in lane 2 directly behind the Kia, at which point it pulled over to the right shoulder area of the highway.                                       PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the Kia Sportage on the passengers side, and spoke to the driver through the passengers side window. I was able to identify the driver by his Maryland drivers license as Ricardo Palting Lagdameo (A/M, DOB: 08/12/1971). I introduced myself to Lagdameo and explained the reasons for the traffic stop. I immediately noticed Lagdameos eyes to be red and glassy and the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from the vehicle. I asked Lagdameo where he was headed, to which he gave me an address. Lagdameos speech appeared to be slow and lethargic. I asked Lagdameo for his drivers license and the vehicles registration card. Lagdameo was able to produce his drivers license and began informing me of friends of his that were in various different positions throughout the legislative, judicial and executive branches of various state and local governments. He also stated there was no excuse for his actions and that he was sorry. While attempting to retrieve the vehicles registration card, Lagdameo struggled to verbalize complete sentences and stopped in the middle of speaking. After not being able to locate the registration card, Lagdameo informed me that he had insurance on the vehicle through Geico.    I asked Lagdameo how much alcohol he had consumed prior to driving, to which he stated he had 3 drinks at the Camelot, a strip club in Washington D.C., and at another establishment called Andies. Lagdameo then informed me that his son had passed away a year ago, and that he has 5 other children from different relationships that he pays $1300 a month for. He continued on and began to talk about each child individually. He also continued to name friends of his throughout the various levels of government. While doing so, Lagdameo still appeared to be speaking with a slow and lethargic tone, and still showed signs of struggling to complete entire thought process before moving to the next. Lagdameos phone began to ring, at which point he asked me if he could answer the phone call. I informed him he could, and I returned to my patrol vehicle to perform standard checks in the METERS/NCIC systems on both Lagdameo and the Kia Sportage. I also requested another unit to my location in an effort to give Lagdameo the opportunity to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs).             At approximately 0311 hours, an Anne Arundel County Police Officer was passing through the area and stopped with me. I re-approached the Kia and asked Lagdameo to step to the front of the Kia with me. While there, I was still able to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage, this time coming from Lagdameos breath and person. I thanked Lagdameo for his honesty and for letting me know he had been previously drinking. He immediately repeated that he did, in fact, have a few drinks and quickly followed it up with more names of various people in different levels of governments and how he was related to those people. He then stated, prior to me asking him any questions regarding SFSTs, that he was not going to take any tests and that he wanted to speak to his cousin who is a district attorney in Prince Georges County. I informed him that I still wanted to explain what SFSTs were and that I wanted to provide him the opportunity to perform SFSTs due to multiple observations leading me to believe he had been driving under the influence of alcohol. Lagdameo refused the opportunity to perform SFSTs. He then continued to list names of police officers he knew and other people who worked in local governments. He also stated I know I did wrong and, again, he did not want to take any tests. I placed Lagdameo under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of alcohol at approximately 0316 hours.      PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)      Lagdameo refused all testing.     HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 Clues Observed)      Lagdameo refused all testing.      WALK AND TURN (4/8 Clues Observed)      Lagdameo refused all testing.     ONE LEG STAND (2/4 Clues Observed)      Lagdameo refused all testing.     PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)      Lagdameo refused all testing.     ARREST:  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Lagdameo was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Lagdameo traveling at a high rate of speed past my marked patrol vehicle  * The odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Lagdameos person and breath  * Lagdameo having red and glassy eyes  * Lagdameos speech being slow and lethargic  * Lagdameo informing me he consumed alcoholic beverages before driving    At approximately 0316 hours, I placed Lagdameo under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of alcohol, and sat him in the front passengers seat of my marked patrol vehicle, P-9, per agency policy. While in my vehicle, Lagdameo complained of chest pain. I requested Emergency Medical Services (EMS) to my location to look over Lagdameo. At approximately 0332 hours, EMS arrived on scene and Lagdameo refused transportation to a hospital. I then transported Lagdameo to the Glen Burnie barrack of the Maryland State Police, and arrived to the barrack with him at approximately 0340 hours.     Lagdameo was read the DR-15 Advice of Rights form in English, as well as given a copy to read for himself. Upon the completion of the DR-15 Advice of Rights being read to Lagdameo, I asked if he had any questions prior to his decision regarding the Intoximeter test. At approximately 0355 hours, Lagdameo refused the opportunity to take the Intoximeter test.     INTOXIMETER RESULT:      Lagdameo refused all testing.   Lagdameo was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to a licensed driver.  All events listed above occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.  Irequest this case be closed due to arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:46:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 14:48:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Swigert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4622</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derek</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5951</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Litz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Simon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7362</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508144</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15647</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/26/2023 03:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15647</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:32:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 12:39:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508144</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/26/2023 03:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:33:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 12:39:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508144</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/26/2023 03:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:34:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 12:39:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508144</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/26/2023 03:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:35:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 12:39:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508144</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/26/2023 03:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:35:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 12:39:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508144</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16616</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/26/2023 03:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16616</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:36:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 12:39:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508144</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/26/2023 03:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:37:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 12:39:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508144</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/26/2023 03:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:38:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 12:39:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>51</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:28:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:55</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378767</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>A</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lagdameo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Palting</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/12/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/02/2023 12:27:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L235</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R263</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lagdameo</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Palting</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/12/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L235</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R263</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/02/2023 12:27:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:39:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:39:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:39:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:39:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:39:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:37:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 12:37:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153710</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 12:41:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 12:41:58</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5XYK33AF2PG117748</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2023</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>KIA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SPT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>T1342978</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>