<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-020322</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/06/2023 19:21:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/06/2023 19:21:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/06/2023 19:04:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/06/2023 19:04:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>ACCIDENT/DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 19:21:15</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5948</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/18/2023 03:17:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>VIETNAM VETERANS MEMORIAL HWY/ SINGER RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>581846</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 19:21:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 22:09:21</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>581846</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Vietnam Veterans Memorial</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Abingdon</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>-0 VIETNAM VETERANS MEMORIAL HWY / 0-0 SINGER RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 VIETNAM VETERANS MEMORIAL HWY / 113-120 SINGER RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 VIETNAM VETERANS MEMORIAL HWY / 0-0 SINGER RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 VIETNAM VETERANS MEMORIAL HWY / 200-499 SINGER RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/06/2023 19:21:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/06/2023 19:21:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/02/2023 20:31:15</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 19:21:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police, Barrack D MarkedMSP Vehicle D-12. In-Car Camera Operational.  Defendant: Sheets, David Eugene Date of Birth: 09/19/1961 Date of Arrest: 06/06/2023 Time of Arrest: 1938hours DUI #: 23-147(Bel Air) Blood test Result: .00                                                                    REPEAT OFFENDER.  BEHAVIOR/CONDUCT:Sheets was calm, cooperative, respectful and drowsy and sleepy.   CERTIFICATION  TRAINING NHSTA Trained/certified to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Test (SFST) Preliminary breath test operator certified Certified Radar/Laser Operator  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On 06/06/2023 at approximately 1904 hours, I, Trooper Kumador #7052 of the Maryland State Police, Bel Air Barrack was dispatched to Southbound Maryland 24 in the area of Singer Road in Abingdon, Harford County, Maryland in reference of a single vehicle collision. I arrived on scene and observed a black vehicle completely buried in the Wood line. I observed a White male subject who was talking with the first responders on scene. The vehicle, a Hyundai Veloster, displayed a Maryland registration 1BP4668.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I made contact with the White male subject and asked him if he was the driver of the vehicle and he stated he was the driver. I identified him by his Maryland drivers license as Sheets, David Eugene, DOB: 09/19/1961. I asked Sheets where he was coming from, and he stated that he was traveling from the Festival Shopping Plaza in Bel Air and was heading home in Joppa. Sheets stated that he lost control of his vehicle due to the wetness of the roadway. Sheets eyes were conscripted, and he was restless and agitated. I asked Sheets if he had been consuming alcoholic beverages, and he responded confidently that he does not drink. I asked Sheets if he had consumed any drugs, and he became upset and stated why all these questions I told Sheets that the questions are standard questions I always asked drivers involved in motor vehicle accidents. Sheet later stated that he consumed Oxycodone Hydrochloride about four hours prior to the collision. He stated that he had a prescription for the Oxycodone Hydrochloride.      PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   Due to the admission of consuming a controlled dangerous substance and the condition and the appearance of Sheets, I had reasons to believe that he was driving while impaired by a controlled dangerous substance. I advised Sheet about my intention to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests to which he agreed. The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of the roadway in front of my patrol vehicle. The roadwasflat and free of any debris and the temperature was approximately 58 degrees.I asked Sheetsthe following questions: Contacts-No,Glasses-No, andAny Injuries-No.Any medication: Yes. Sheets stated that he takes other medication for Cholesterol and blood pressure medication.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (0/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the Tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Sheets eyes. Hewas instructed to look straight ahead, keeping hishead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hiseyes until told to stop. I asked himif he understood the directions, and he advised yes. His pupils were equal in size and did show equal tracking.    Lack of Smooth Pursuit-not present  The distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation  not present  The onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  not present.   WALK AND TURN (6/8) Before Sheets performed the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. He was instructed to place hisright foot directly in front of hisleft foot and touch heel-to-toe. He was instructed to place hishands flat at hisside and to remain in the position until told to begin. Hewas advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. He was to keep his hands flat at hisside, keep hiseyes focused on hisfeet, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, he was demonstrated and explained to keep hislead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around to hisleft with hisrear foot to turn completely around. He was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. He was then instructed that once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep hishands down by hisside, look down at hisfeet, and count each step out loud.  During the instructional stage:I explained and demonstrated the starting position to Sheets andplaced him in thestarting position. Hecould notstand straight in the starting position. He broke his feet and remained not in the starting position throughout the instructional period  Walking stage (1st Nine).    Raised his arms more than 6 inches throughout the test.  Missed heel-to-toe by more than an inch  Stepped offline during the teststeps.  He stopped on the 9thstep to ask a question.  Turn: The turn was unsatisfactory. Sheetsdid not plant his lead foot to turn around as instructed.  Walking stage (2nd Nine).    Raised his arms more than 6 inches throughout the test.     Missed heel-to-toe by more than an inch  Stepped offline during the teststeps.   ONE LEG STAND (3/4) Prior toSheets performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. He was instructed to stand with hisheels together and hands down by hisside, while the instructions were given and during the test. He was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of hischoice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While hisleg was raised, he was to keep hisleg straight, watch hisraised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one thousand-two), and to continue the test until told to stop.    He raised his arms during the test.  He puts his feet down during the test  He swayed side by side during the test   PRELIMINARY BREATH A preliminary breath test was not offered to Sheets  ARREST Based on the following, I havereasons to believe that Sheetswas operating his vehicle while impaired by drugs and could not operate his vehicle safely resulting in a single vehicle collision.    Admission to consuming controlled dangerous substances a few hours before operating his vehicle resulting in collision.  The negligent operation of vehicle while under the influence of drugs.  Observed signs of impairment as he performedthe Standardized Field Sobriety Testspoorly.  I arrested Sheetsat 1938hours for driving his vehicle while impaired by drugs resulting in a single vehicle collision. A search incident to arrest uncovered two pink tablets with K 56 imprints on it. There was also a light green table divided into two with the number 8 imprints on it. I identified the tablets as Oxycodone Hydrochloride using the online Pill Identifier tool. Sheets stated that the pink tablets were prescribed to his wife and he has been consuming them in addition to his prescription medications. The tablets were not in a prescription container and there was no label on the bottle to show that he was indeed the legal owner of the tablets. Sheetslistened to the Englishaudio version of DR-15 Advice of Rights in its entiretyand at the conclusion, he agreedtosubmit to the test.Itransported Sheetsto the Maryland State Police, Bel Air barrack for processing. He signed the paper copy of the DR-15 at the barrack at 2036 hours.  20-MINUTES OBSERVATION PERIOD. Sheets oral cavity was checked, and his observation started 1943 hours  INTOXIMETER RESULT:  Breath test was explained and offered to Sheets by Sgt. D Stanley #5405. The result of the test was0.00 BrAC. Sheets declined to be evaluated by a Drug Recognition Expert and was later charged with driving his vehicle while impaired by controlled dangerous substances. Hewasgiven copies of all pertinent paperwork andlater released to a sober licensed driver.  Closed by arrest.  All events occurred in HarfordCounty, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/07/2023 00:55:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 19:24:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Turner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6761</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kumador</LastName>
            <FirstName>Linford</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7052</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509757</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/06/2023 19:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:10:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 22:10:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>61</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:08:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:13</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>379164</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>SHEETS</LastName>
               <FirstName>DAVID</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>EUGENE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/19/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.19605785E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 21:50:51</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>SHEETS</LastName>
               <FirstName>DAVID</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>EUGENE</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/19/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.19605785E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S320</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 21:50:51</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1807</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Shirley</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Joppa</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21085</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.344406</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.453371</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>477</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0514</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:10:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:10:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:10:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:10:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 22:10:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 22:10:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>