<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-034507</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/01/2023 22:10:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/01/2023 22:10:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/01/2023 21:42:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/01/2023 21:42:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driving Motor Vehicle While Under the Influence of Alcohol</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/01/2023 22:10:46</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2864</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 16:23:37</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN HWY/ SPRING LN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>552738</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/01/2023 22:10:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 02:51:05</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>552738</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westover</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.695091</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.129274</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>8917-9040 OCEAN HWY / 9041-9161 SPRING LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>9041-9156 OCEAN HWY / 9041-9161 SPRING LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>9027-9099 OCEAN HWY / 0-0 SPRING LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/01/2023 22:10:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/01/2023 22:10:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/08/2023 16:22:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/01/2023 22:10:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle:X-19 is a Marked Ford Explorer equipped with an MVR system. Type of Report:DUI/DWI ARREST Victim:State of Maryland Offender: Ricky Robin Velasquez Date of Birth: 08/04/1998 Date of Incident: 10/1/2023 @ 2142 HOURS Time of Arrest:10/1/2023 @ 2208 HOURS Maryland Drivers License: Not licensed DUI Folder:23-95-053 Accident: NO Subsequent Offender: Yes, July 2023, 9/2023 This incident wasaudibly andvisually recorded. MSP marked patrol vehicle X-19 isequipped with a mobile recording device. I am also equipped with a body worn camera 00017420. Trooper Carew also recorded this incident with his MSP marked patrol vehicle X-34 and body worn camera (00017409).   VEHICLE IN MOTION: On 10/1/2023 at approximately 2142 hours, I, Senior Trooper S. Marshall and Trooper Carew were sitting stationary in the crossover in the area of Ocean Highway and Sawmill Road, Westover, Somerset County, Maryland. At that time, we were conducting a stationary Lidar Assignment and were using Laser 1 which was tested before and after our shift to make sure it was working properly. At that time, we observed a vehicle traveling northbound on Ocean Highway. Trooper Carew obtained a speed reading of 72 miles per hour in the posted 55 mile per hour zone. The vehicle was the only vehicle in the Laser beam and the only vehicle traveling northbound at that time. I then activated my emergency equipment on my Marked MSP Unit X19 and conducted a traffic stop on that vehicle. The final traffic stop location was northbound Ocean Highway in the area of the Goose Creek/Spring Lane. The vehicle was a silver four-door BMW bearing Delaware Temporary registration XQ456367. The BMW slowly came to its final resting position after it straddled the dotted white marker lines and stopped in the turn lane in front of R and W motors.   PERSONAL CONTACT: I then exited my vehicle and made my way to the front driver side window of the vehicle. I introduced myself and advised the reason for the stop to the driver. The driver would later be identified as Ricky Robin Velasquez Roblero (who will be referred to as Ricky for this report). Upon making contact with Ricky, I detected a moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I requested Ricky to provide me with his drivers license and registration to the vehicle. While attempting to locate his paperwork, I observed Rickys movements to be slow and lethargic. Ricky then advised me that he did not have a drivers license and provided me with his Mexican Identification Card. I then asked Ricky if he had anything to drink that evening, and he advised me no.  Upon returning to my patrol vehicle, I requested Trooper Carew to respond to my location. I then advised Trooper Carew that I could smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the Rickys breath and person. I then requested Trooper Carew to speak with Ricky for further investigation. Trooper Carew advised me that Ricky advised him he had tres cervezas which in Spanish means Three Beers. At that time, Trooper Carew provided Rickys information to the Princess Anne Barrack and advised that I would be conducted Standardized Field Soberity Testing on Ricky. I requested Trooper Carew assist me with the testing and translating of English to Spanish for Ricky.  I then requested Ricky exit the vehicle. It should be noted his father was in the front passenger seat and his brother was in the rear passenger seat. As Ricky exited the vehicle I continued to detect now a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I advised Ricky that he told Trooper Carew that he did have something to drink and told me that he did not. Ricky then advised me that he had three beers. I asked Ricky if he needed a full translator or if he understood what I was saying to him, and he advised he understood me. I asked Ricky if he had more than three beers and he advised me No. I then asked Ricky how long ago he had drank the beers, and he advised me three hours ago. Ricky advised me he was coming from Virginia and was headed to Salisbury.  I then advised Ricky that I would be running him through Standardized Field Sobriety Test. I then advised him if he did not understand anything I was explaining to him, that Trooper Carew and myself had a translator app that could be used to help. I asked Ricky if he had any handicaps to which he advised no. I then asked Ricky if he wore any glasses or contacts, and he advised me no. I then asked Ricky if he was taking any medication, and he advised me no. Ricky advised me that he did not use Marijuana or any other drugs that evening. I then began the testing with Ricky by starting with the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test.  Testing was completed in the turn lane to turn into R and W Motor. The roadway was free of any debris and was level. Lighting conditions were consent with my flashlight, headlights by passing cars, and artifical lighting. The weather conditions at the time of testing was clear and approximately 65 degrees.  HORIZONTALGAZE NYSTAGMUS: Inconclusive I then explained the HGN testing to Ricky. Ricky advised that he understood the test. I asked Ricky if he could see my pen, and he advised yes. I asked Ricky to touch the tip of my pen which he did not.It should be noted that my results for the clues reference HGN were found to be inconclusive. During testing, Ricky attempted to follow my pen and then began to almost attempt to fight the testing by keeping his eyes in a straight forward alignment. Ricky was not tracking the pen as he was told. Rickys eyes appeared to be following my pen but were not focused on the tip of my pen as instructed. Rickys eyes were blood shot and glassy while I was completing this test and I still detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.  WALK AND TURN: 2/8 Rickys shoes were not entirely on his feet at the time of testing. I then asked Ricky if he wanted to put his shoes on his foot correctly, and he advised yes. Ricky adjusted his shoes and I began to explain the Walk and Turn test to him. For the Walk and Turn testing, we used the white marker line located on the roadway. Ricky could not main the position for the instructional phase of the testing. Trooper Carew used the translator app to give the instruction to Ricky for the Walk and Turn Test and I also verbally instructed Ricky on how to perform the test. Ricky missed heal to toe on step 9 of the first set of 9 steps.  ONE LEG STAND: 2/4 I then explained the One Leg Stand test to Ricky. I got Ricky into instructional position and told him to stay in that position. Trooper Carew used the translator app to explain the instructions for the testing that I had verbally given Ricky. Ricky advised he understood the testing. Ricky raised his right foot and stood on his left foot. Ricky did not count out loud. Ricky did not look at his foot while doing the testing. Ricky swayed back and forth during the entire 30 seconds of testing and placed his foot down one time.  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT): I then went to my vehicle and retrieved my Preliminary Breath Test. My Preliminary Breath test was testing for accuracy on 10/1/2023 at the beginning of my shift. I explained that PBT to Ricky and asked if he wished to do the test. Ricky advised yes. As I was preparing the straw for the PBT, Trooper Carew asked Ricky to open his mouth, so he could check if he had any foreign objects in his mouth. When Ricky opened his mouth to be checked, it appeared he had coins in his mouth. Ricky advised no. Trooper Carew then instructed Ricky to spit the money out of his mouth. It took Ricky two attempts to spit all the money out of his mouth. Ricky then completed the PBT and the PBT obtained a reading of .166 BAC. It should be noted that it is false information placing pennies and other forms of currency in your mouth to attempt to throw off the PBT.  ARREST: I then placed Ricky under arrest at 2208 hours. I advised Ricky he was under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I then advised Ricky that I believed he had more than three beers and I asked how many he had. Ricky advised me he did not know how many beers he had. Trooper Carew transported Ricky to the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack to be processed according to MSP policies and procedures.  CHEMICAL BREATH TEST RESULTS: Upon arriving to the barrack, Trooper Carew played the DR15 on his computer in Spanish while Ricky followed along on the paper form of the DR15. The Spanish version of the DR15 started playing at 2228 hours and ended at 2236 hours. Ricky advised he had a question reference the DR15, so we called the Interpreter Services number, and he spoke with Karolyan. After speaking with her, Ricky advised he did not wish to submit to an alcohol concentration test at 2241 hours.  Ricky was issued the following citations: 1. Driving Vehicle While Under the Influence of Alcohol 2. Driving Vehicle While Impaired by Alcohol 3.Neglient Driving 4.Reckless Driving 5.Faiulre of Individual Driving on Highway to Display License to Uniformed Police on Demand 6. Driving Motor Vehicle on Highway without Required License and Authorization 7. Driving Vehicle Required Class C on Highway without Class C license 8. Exceeding Posted Maximum Speed Limit: 72 mph in the posted 55 mph Zone 9, Owner Knowingly Permitting Motor Vehicle to be Driven on Highway by Unauthorized Person  Ricky was released to Guillelman Edmundo Morales.  ALL EVENTS OCCURRED IN SOMERSET COUNTY, MARYLAND.  I request this case be closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:16:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6066</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 02:52:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Carew</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7074</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Marshall</LastName>
            <FirstName>Shadoe</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6066</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523965</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/01/2023 21:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:05:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6066</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 19:05:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523965</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/01/2023 21:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:06:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6066</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 19:06:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523965</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/01/2023 21:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:07:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6066</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 19:07:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523965</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/01/2023 21:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:07:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6066</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 19:07:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523965</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/01/2023 21:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:08:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6066</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 19:08:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523965</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/01/2023 21:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19731</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:09:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6066</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 19:09:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523965</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15430</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/01/2023 21:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15430</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:11:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6066</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 19:11:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>25</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:03:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 02:51:05</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383800</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Velasquez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ricky</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Robin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/08/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/29/2023 23:22:03</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>V422</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Velasquez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ricky</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Robin</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/08/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>V422</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/29/2023 23:22:03</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>36957</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Roxana</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Selbyville</City>
               <StateCode>DE</StateCode>
               <Zip5>19975</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3313</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.194459</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.475428</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:12:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:12:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:12:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:12:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:12:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:05:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6066</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 19:05:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157670</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6066</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 19:15:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6066</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 19:15:16</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WBAPH7C56BE678553</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2011</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>BMW</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>TAN</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>DE</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>XQ456367</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/01/2023 23:06:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/01/2023 23:06:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/08/2023 16:22:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7074</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/01/2023 23:06:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Narrative:    On 10/1/2023 at approximately 2142, I, Tpr. Carew #7074, responded to assist S/Tpr. Marshall with a traffic stop located northbound US Route 13 at Spring Lane. S/Tpr. Marshall requested assistance due to a language barrier with the driver as well as the driver possibly displaying signs of alcohol impairment. Upon arriving on scene I made contact with the driver who was identified by his Mexico Identification Card as Ricky Robin Velasquez Roblero (H/M DOB: 8/4/1998).  Upon speaking with Ricky I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. Rickys eyes appeared to be bloodshot and glassy, Ricky was displaying slow motor function and slowed speech. I then asked Ricky Quando Cervesas how many beers to which he replied with three beers. I relayed this information to S/Tpr. Marshall. At this time S/Tpr. Marshall asked Ricky to step out of the vehicle to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Test. I assisted with the Standardized Field Sobriety Test by utilizing Google Translate with Ricky, so he could further understand the instructions after he stated he understood them in English. Due to observations made Ricky was placed under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol.    I searched Ricky on scene and no contraband was recovered. Ricky was placed in the front seat of my patrol vehicle according to agency policy and procedure and transported to the Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack for further processing. While seated in my patrol vehicle the odor of an alcoholic beverage filled the interior of my patrol vehicle. Once at the Barrack Ricky was searched again and no contraband was recovered. Ricky was placed in the processing room where he was played his DR-15 Advise of Rights in Spanish from the MVA Website. While seated in the processing room the odor of an alcoholic beverage filled the room. While in the processing room we utilized the Language Line to assist with question in reference to the DR-15.    All events were captured audibly and visually on my Maryland State Police body worn Camera.  ALL EVENTS OCCURRED IN SOMERSET COUNTY, MARYLAND.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7074</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/01/2023 23:08:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7074</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/01/2023 23:41:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Carew</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7074</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>