<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012120</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/05/2023 10:36:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/05/2023 10:36:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/04/2023 19:29:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/04/2023 19:29:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Assist MD OSFM with wild land fire on state property.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 10:36:29</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3321</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/14/2023 09:47:46</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AOA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>689698</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 10:36:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 17:59:27</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>689698</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Soldiers Delight</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Owings Mills</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/05/2023 10:36:28</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/05/2023 10:36:28</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/14/2023 09:47:34</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 10:36:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/14/2023 09:47:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>April 4, 2023  On April 4, 2023, at approximately 1530 hours, the Baltimore County Fire Department (BCFD) responded to the area of Soldiers Delight State Park for a brush fire. Upon arrival BCFD located a large wild land fire within the park area and surrounding area. BCFD, along with multiple surrounding jurisdictions responded to aid in the extinguishing efforts.  Baltimore County Police Department (BCPD) also responded with manned aviation assets to provide over watch and support to direct ground resources. Due to the large size of the fire, the Maryland Army National Guard was requested to assist with additional manned aviation assets with air firefighting capabilities.  Due to the fire occurring in a State Park the Maryland State Police Office of the State Fire Marshal (OSFM) responded to assist the Maryland Department of Natural Resources Forest Service with investigating the cause and origin of the wildland fire. I was requested to assist the OSFM with documenting the fire scene with a small Unmanned Aircraft System (sUAS).  As the BCPD helicopter was operating, they observed a small Unmanned Aircraft System (sUAS) operating in the area of the fire near the Soldiers Delight visitor center and Baltimore Gas and Electric Power lines. BCPD located the operator sUAS on a dirt bike in the park with the controller in his hands. BCPD observed the sUAS land in the area of the power lines on a trail/access road. BCPD landed the helicopter, and Officer Al Cross made contact with the operator, who was identified as Sean Michael Kusterer. The sUAS was recovered by BCPD Officer Thompson 5497, with an Unmanned Aerial Vehicle (UAV), Ground Control Station, and a Samsung cellular telephone being recovered. As BCPD located the operator of the sUAS, the Maryland Air National Guard arrived on the scene to provide aerial firefighting assets.  I made contact with Kusterer at the Soldiers Delight visitor center. Kusterer advised that the sUAS was not registered. Kusterer said he did not have a Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) Part 107 license or an FAA Trust Certificate for recreational flyers. Kusterer stated that he was trying to get pictures of the fire. Kusterer advised that the Samsung cellular telephone was not an operational phone and was only used to operate the sUAS.  April 6, 2023  I made contact with Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) Law Enforcement Assistance Program (LEAP) Agent David Bonk, and advised him of the events of April 4.  I was directed to the Department of Transportation Office of Inspector General Special Agent Daniel Irving reference assisting with this investigation.   April 7, 2023  The BCPD later requested assistance from the MSP with this investigation. The sUAS was turned over to MSP for further investigation. The sUAS was stored at the MSP Golden Ring Barrack with a MSP Form 63 Property Record and MSP Form 67 Chain of Custody.  The sUAS was identified as a DJI Phantom with serial number PADCJ2807009X. The sUAS contained a controller, Samsung phone, associated UAS parts and a backpack.  I made contact with Kusterer via telephone to provide an update on the location of his UAS. Kusterer provided the password for the Samsung as 4139.   April 17, 2023  The 911 records were obtained from Baltimore County 911.  I made contact with Seth Clute of the Maryland Army National Guard in reference to their helicopter operations. The Helicopter on-scene registration forAutomatic Dependent Surveillance-Broadcast(ADS-B) was84-23975. Clute advised his crew did not report seeing the UAS.   April 21, 2023  The Baltimore County Police Body Worn Camera video from the contact withKusterer was obtained.   April 24, 2023  I made contact with BCPD A Cross the Tactical Flight Officer on the BCPD. The BCPD Helicopter on-scene registration for ADS-B wasN808CP. Cross advised that they located the UAS flying in the area of the fire. The UAS crashed in the area of the Baltimore Gas and Electric powerlines. Cross advised that they located the operator on a dirt bike retrieving the UAS. Cross stated that they tlandhe helicopter and made contact with the operator. Cross stated that there was no video recorded.   May 24, 2023  The sUAS was recovered by Special Agent D Irving for the execution of the Federal Search Warrant.     Definitions  Air Traffic Control  The personnel assigned to manage the controlled airspace  Control Station - interface used by the remote pilot to control the flight path of the small unmanned aircraft.  FAA  Federal Aviation Administration  Low Altitude Authorization and Notification Capability (LAANC)  provides sUAS pilots authorization to conduct operations in Controlled Airspace.  Notice to Airman (NOTAM)  Contains information for pilots regarding airspace, hazards, and other aeronautical concerns  Remote Polit in Command  The person that is manipulating the controls of the sUAS. The RPIC is directly responsible for the operation of the sUAS.  Temporary Flight Restrictions (TFR)  A NOTAM that limits operations within a specified area.  Unmanned Aircraft an aircraft operated without the possibility of direct human intervention from within or on the aircraft.  Small unmanned aircraft system (sUAS) - a small unmanned aircraft and its associated elements (including communication links and the components that control the small unmanned aircraft) that are required for the safe and efficient operation of the small unmanned aircraft in the national airspace system. Typically weighing less than 55 pounds.  Visual Observer - a person who is designated by the remote pilot in command to assist the remote pilot in command and the person manipulating the flight controls of the small UAS to see and avoid other air traffic or objects aloft or on the ground.   Airspace  Airspace is divided into two (2) categories, regulatory and non-regulatory. Within the two categories there are four (4) separate classes, Controlled, Uncontrolled, Special Use and Other.    Controlled airspace consists of Class A, B, C, D and E. Each of these types of airspace is controlled via an Air Traffic Control service or tower.     Class B - Baltimore Washington International Airport   Class D  Martin State Airport   Class D  Frederick Municipal Airport      Uncontrolled airspace consists of Class G. This type of airspace is anything that is not Class A, B, C, D, and E.      Most of Maryland is Class G airspace   Special Use Airspace is airspace where certain activities or events are conducted or confined to. Special Use Airspace consist of Prohibited Areas, Restricted Areas, Military Operation Areas among others.    Prohibited Area  P-40 Camp David      Other Airspace is everything else. These consist of Temporary Flight Restrictions parachute jump aircraft operations among others.     TFR for presidential movement      A screenshot from the FAA website visualize it of the area of operation is attached.  https://www.arcgis.com/apps/webappviewer/index.html?id=9c2e4406710048e19806ebf6a06754ad    sUAS Regulations  In the United States, UAS for civil operations are regulated by the FAA. sUAS operations are classified into two (2) categories, Recreational and Civil. Recreational sUAS are for personal enjoyment. Civil sUAS operations are conducted for compensation, public safety, or commercial operations. UAS Regulation is contained within 49 CFR Part 107.   https://www.ecfr.gov/current/title-14/chapter-I/subchapter-F/part-107   Case Status  OPEN.   Corporal James E. Lantz Maryland Department of State Police  CRASH Team - Golden Ring Office  MSP Chief UAS Pilot 8908 Kelso Drive Essex, Maryland, 21221 James.Lantz@Maryland.Gov  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 19:26:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5563</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/28/2023 13:00:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>22</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Peterson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kristie</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6074</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CT</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Menchey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3321</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CT</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lantz</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5563</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501523</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4 5399</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>50</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>A</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/04/2023 19:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>A</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4 5399</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 17:55:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5563</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 17:55:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 12:05:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:50</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373472</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>DRAKE</LastName>
               <FirstName>MARQUESE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>TIMOTHY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/03/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.74312849E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 11:20:55</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M622</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>DRAKE</LastName>
               <FirstName>MARQUESE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>TIMOTHY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/03/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.74312849E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>D620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M622</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/05/2023 11:20:55</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9717</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Branchleigh</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>201</SubNumber>
               <City>Randallstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21133</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.81576</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.383891</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>X</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 12:05:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/05/2023 12:07:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:32</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>286794</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Kusterer</LastName>
               <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/28/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13232348E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>10/21/2020 08:30:35</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K236</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Kusterer</LastName>
               <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/28/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13232348E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>K236</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/21/2020 08:30:35</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4140</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Deer Park</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Randallstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21133</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1802</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.8279703</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.3859604</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>621</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7181</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/21/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>621</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7181</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/21/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>667</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>324</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8419</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 17:57:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 12:32:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:13</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378238</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>IRVING</LastName>
               <FirstName>DANIEL</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 12:30:37</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>I615</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>IRVING</LastName>
               <FirstName>DANIEL</FirstName>
               <SLastName>I615</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 12:30:37</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1200</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>New Jersey</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>SE</StreetSuffixCode>
               <SubNumber>7th Floor</SubNumber>
               <City>Washington</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20590</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.00345</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.875942</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>405</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>523</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4888</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 12:32:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 12:36:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:14</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378239</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>U</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>BONK</LastName>
               <FirstName>DAVID</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 12:33:31</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>BONK</LastName>
               <FirstName>DAVID</FirstName>
               <SLastName>B520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 12:33:31</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>800</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Independence</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>SW</StreetSuffixCode>
               <SubNumber>300</SubNumber>
               <City>Washington</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.023046</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.886866</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>215</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>847</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6940</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 12:36:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 12:37:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5563</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 12:37:42</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>425</PropertyTypeCode>
         <SerialNumber>P5ADCJ2807009X</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>246761</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>WHI</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>BLU</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>DJI</Make>
         <Model>Phantom Standard</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 12:37:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5563</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 12:37:42</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>835</PropertyTypeCode>
         <SerialNumber>P5CDCJ2801006P</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>246762</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>WHI</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>DJI</Make>
         <Model>Controller</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 12:37:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5563</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 12:37:42</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>794</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>246763</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>WHI</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>SAMSUNG</Make>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 12:37:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5563</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 12:37:42</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>472</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>246764</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <Make>DJI</Make>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/11/2023 09:14:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/11/2023 09:14:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>CT</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/14/2023 09:47:34</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/11/2023 09:14:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/14/2023 09:47:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This investigation has been turned over to theU.S. Department of TransportationOffice of Inspector General and the United States Attorney District for Maryland. Should any additional assistance be requested by the OIG a supplement will be completed.   Case Closed.   Corporal James E. Lantz Maryland Department of State Police  CRASH Team - Golden Ring Office  MSP Chief UAS Pilot 8908 Kelso Drive Essex, Maryland, 21221 James.Lantz@Maryland.Gov  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/11/2023 09:16:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5563</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/11/2023 09:18:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CT</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Menchey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ronald</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3321</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>CT</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lantz</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5563</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501523</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>18</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4 5399</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>50</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/11/2023 09:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4 5399</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5563</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/11/2023 09:19:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5563</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/11/2023 09:20:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>