<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000120</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/01/2023 17:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/01/2023 17:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/01/2023 16:48:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/01/2023 16:48:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI ARREST OF MICHAEL DAVID MORAN</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/01/2023 17:08:14</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/17/2023 12:28:43</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>TAYLORS ISLAND RD/ DEEP POINT RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>679055</AddressId>
      <City>MDC591</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/01/2023 17:08:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/01/2023 23:34:26</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>679055</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Taylors Island</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Woolford</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21677</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.193011</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.511495</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/01/2023 17:08:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/01/2023 17:08:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/16/2023 13:15:51</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/01/2023 17:08:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:05</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>CASE NUMBER: 23-MSP-000120 INVESTIGATING TROOPER: Trooper M. Mowbray #7119 NATURE OF CALL: Motor Vehicle Collision, DUI, DWI SCENE PROCESSING: Scene processing was conducted with the following results;   Intox EC/IR Information Sheet  MSP Form 32 - Alcohol Information Report  DR-15  Advice of Rights (Alcohol Concentration Test)  MSP Form 34  Blood Sample Authorization  Copy of Automated Crash Reporting System (ACRS) Report  MVA Print Out  Copy of all Citations  One (1) digital photograph of Michael David Moran  Fourteen (14) digital photographs of the scene  uploaded to VeriPic and RMS  INCIDENT FOOTAGE: INCIDENT CAPTURED BY A MOBILE VIDEO RECORDER I-39 EQUIPPED WITH AN MVR FOOTAGE LABELED 23-MSP-000120 ON AXON EVIDENCE Dash Camera: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=609b559c26de40d48bac87e3a25578ebpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 INCIDENT CAPTURED WITH BODY WORN CAMERA Scene: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=5052ed1c7d5743fe9c70ad46ccd4e6abpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 Personal Contact (Hospital): partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=88b862446fbf43ec97fa27167aab870apartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  CAMERA SYSTEM / CAD SYSTEM The camera system is manufactured by Axon. The in-car; outward facing camera is activated when the emergency lights are activated in the patrol car or if manually activated by the user. The camera will go back in time and start the recording thirty (30) seconds before the camera is activated. This event is called a 30 second pre-record. The body worn camera (BWC); attached to the front of the Trooper, is also activated when the emergency lights are activated or manually by its user. The camera will record the previous sixty (60) seconds prior to the camera activation. The camera system does not have a date and time stamp on the video itself. The system records the date and time in the metadata. The time only records the hour and minute when the camera starts the recording. Therefore, the timeline below will start with a time that was recorded from the cameras metadata and then show the duration of the video. The in-car camera and body worn camera footage remains the best depiction of the events surrounding the traffic stop. However, in order to obtain an exact time of a specific event, the reader will have to add the length of duration from the start of the video that was recorded in the metadata. Although times are recorded by other means such as the Delta Plus system that prints a time stamp on the warning, citation or safety equipment repair order this time is only when the traffic enforcement button is activated by the Trooper. This date/time is usually started shortly after making contact with a violator and upon return to the patrol vehicle. Other programs such as Caliber RMS incident and CAD reports will show a timestamp, but this time depends on when the Police Communications Operator or Trooper activates the incident within the CAD system. The two aforementioned examples of the recording of time will almost always be different than the in-car camera system due to all of the systems utilizing different internal clocks.  DUI FOLDER NUMBER: 23-58-001 DEFENDANT:  Michael David Moran (Maryland  M-650-603-135-273) 04/07/1961 11 Woodbine Circle, Elkton, Cecil County, Maryland 21921 PRIOR DUIS: 0 DATE OF ARREST: 01/01/2023 TIME OF ARREST: 1820 hours  CERTIFICATIONS AND TRAINING:    Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration on 05/30/2019  Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police  Trained and certified to operate the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) through the Maryland State Police  Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) on 01/30/2020  Trained and certified to operate Maryland Coordination and Analysis Center License Plate Readers since August 2019  ASSIGNMENT: On Sunday, January 1, 2023, I, Trooper M. Mowbray #7119, of the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack, was assigned to road patrol duties in Dorchester County, Maryland. The Maryland State Easton Barrack is responsible for enforcing and investigating all criminal and traffic related crime within Dorchester, Talbot and Caroline counties. My duties include but are not limited to: enforcing the criminal and motor vehicle laws of the State of Maryland, issuing traffic citations and warnings, investigating traffic accidents, investigating and completing criminal investigations, interviewing witnesses, victims and suspects and writing field reports.   NARRATIVE: On January 1, 2023 at approximately 1651 hours I, Trooper M. Mowbray #7119 of the Maryland State Police, was dispatched to the area of Maryland Route 16 (Taylors Island Road) and Deep Point Road, Woolford, Dorchester County, Maryland, 21677 for a report of a motor vehicle collision.  Prior to my arrival Dorchester County Emergency Medical Services and Deputies from the Dorchester County Sheriffs Office arrived on scene and provided aid to the driver; Michael David Moran, who was the sole occupant in a black 2005 Chevrolet Silverado bearing Maryland registration 8AM5305.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) Based on my training, knowledge and experience as a Maryland State Police Trooper and as an Advanced Collision Investigator, the following events were determined to be the collision dynamics.   On January 1, 2023 around 1651 hours a black 2005 Chevrolet Silverado bearing Maryland registration 8AM5305 was travelling westbound on Maryland Route 16 (Taylors Island Road) west of Laurie Lane, Woolford Dorchester County, Maryland 21677. At that time, the Chevrolet began to drift right and failed to obey a properly placed traffic control device (solid white painted line) and entered the grass shoulder. The Chevrolet continued westbound on the grass shoulder, ultimately driving into a ditch filled with water. The Chevrolet continued through the ditch and struck a standing tree and brush where it came to rest.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) While I was on scene of the collision I made contact with Deputy First Class M. Medley #0259 of the Dorchester County Sheriffs Office. DFC Medley had made contact with the driver and noted several signs of impairment. DFC Medley also advised that the driver; identified by Maryland drivers license as Michael David Moran (DOB: 04/07/1961) [hereinafter identified as Moran], admitted to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to driving. I then made contact with Moran as he was laying on the stretcher within Dorchester County Emergency Medical Services Paramedic 500. Moran was being treated for minor injuries to his face as a result of the motor vehicle collision. As I entered the ambulance I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the area of Moran. I then requested Moran to provide his drivers license to which he complied. I then made contact with a witness of the collision; identified by Maryland drivers license as Kevin Bryan Cook Jr. (DOB: 02/13/1983)[hereinafter identified as Cook]. Cook provided a written statement on an MSP Form 76. The following is the statement of Cook; I, Kevin Cook, was behind the truck that went in the ditch on Rt. 16 about 200 yards behind him. He rode the ditch for a good 100 yards before he came to a stop. I was first to him. He said Im going to jail right! I ask him if he been drinking he said yes. (Cook)  I relayed all pertinent information to the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack.  Moran was transported to the University of Maryland Shore Medical Center at Cambridge; located at 715 Cambridge Marketplace Boulevard, Cambridge, Maryland 21613, for treatment of his injuries. (EMS Run #: Z23000159)  METERS/NCIC CHECKS: I relayed Moran and the Chevrolets information to the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack Emergency Dispatcher. After conducting checks of Stokes via the National Crime Information Center (NCIC) and Maryland Electronic Telecommunications Resource System (METERS); it was learned that his Maryland drivers license was valid.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) Upon my arrival at the University of Maryland Shore Medical Center at Cambridge, I made contact with Moran as he was in a bed within the Emergency Department. I began to speak with Moran and ask about his condition and the facts surrounding the collision. Moran immediately stated that he had been drinking alcohol prior to the collision. Moran advised that he stopped at the Goose Creek (Snows Turn, 1801 Race Street, Cambridge, Maryland) and purchased alcohol. Moran stated that he consumed two Jim Beam shots and two Yuengling Lagers while he sat in his Chevrolet within the parking lot. I immediately informed Moran that I intended to reactivate my body worn camera; which was off due to HIPAA concerns, and requested his consent to record him to which he stated yes. I again recounted where he consumed the alcoholic beverages. Moran advised that he had a disagreement with his wife while at home in Elkton and decided to leave and travel towards Taylors Island where they share a travel trailer.  Due to Morans injuries and the potential for causing further harm, I elected to only perform the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test as he remained seated and within a cervical collar. While speaking with Moran I observed his speech to be slurred and his eyes to be glassy and bloodshot. I also continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Morans breath and person.  The test was performed as Moran sat within a bed in the emergency department. Lighting consisted of overhead. Moran was wearing and a yellow shirt. The first test administered was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test. I held an ink pen 12-15 inches in front of Morans face and slightly above eye level. Moran was checked to ensure that his eyes could track the pens movement equally. Additionally, I ensured there was no resting nystagmus and that his pupils were equal in size.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6 of 6 Clues) (EYE COLOR: Hazel) 1.) LACK OF SMOOTH PURSUIT - Present in both left and right eyes - 2 clues 2.) DISTINCT AND SUSTAINED NYSTAGMUS AT MAXIMUM DEVIATION - Present in both left and right eyes - 2 clues 3.) ONSET OF NYSTAGMUS PRIOR TO 45 DEGREES - Present in both left and right eyes - 2 clues VERTICAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS - Not present  WALK AND TURN (0 of 8 Clues) Not offered.  ONE LEG STAND (0 of 4 Clues) Not offered.  ALPHABET TEST (F-T): Moran was asked if he was familiar with the alphabet. Moran was asked to recite the alphabet starting with the letter F and ending with the letter T. Moran replied; Yes. and agreed to perform the Alphabet Test with the following results: WELL THATS KIND OF CRAZY YOU START AT THAT, E, F, T, G, H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, P  NUMBERS TEST (59-36):  Moran was asked if he was familiar and comfortable with counting numbers backwards. He was instructed to count backwards from 59 to 36. Moran agreed to perform the test with the following results: 58, 57, 56, 55, 54, 53, 52, 51, 50, 49, 48, 47, 46, UH, 45, 44, 43, 42, 41, WAS I CLOSE THERE?, 40, START AT 40?, I DONT REMEMBER WHAT THE LAST NUMBERS WERE, 39, 38, 37, 36  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST RESULTS: The Preliminary Breath Test was not offered to Moran at the scene. I advised Moran of the State of Maryland Preliminary Breath Test Advisement of Rights prior to the test. Result: NOT OFFERED  ARREST/ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) Based on the following, I had reason to believe Moran was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: - Driver failing to maintain a lane - Driver failing to control vehicle to avoid a collision - Eyes glassy and bloodshot - Admission to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to operating a motor vehicle  - Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person  - My observed signs of impairment as she performed field sobriety tests (HGN)   I played the DR-15 Advice of Rights (Alcohol Concentration Test) English Audio provided by the State of Maryland at 1803 hours within room 18 of the Emergency Department. The DR-15 audio had to be stopped due to medical intervention. I replayed the DR-15 Audio at 1810 hours. Moran agreed to submit to the chemical alcohol concentration test at 1820 hours. At 1828 hours Heidi VanWinkle, RN of the University of Maryland Shore Medical Center at Cambridge performed a blood draw from Morans left arm. (MSP Blood Kit #: I-364). As VanWinkle collected the blood, I maintained visual contact with the procedure and confirmed that the sample was obtained properly.  Due to Morans poor performance on the horizontal gaze nystagmus test portion of the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and my observed signs of impairment I charged Moran with driving under the influence at 1828 hours. Moran was released to the care and custody of the hospital staff after receiving copies of the appropriate paperwork.  ALCOHOL CONCENTRATION TEST RESULT: PENDING LABORATORY ANALYSIS Michael David Moran was charged with the following offenses; TA 21-902 (A)(1)(II): DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL PER SE (4BD0V1Z TA 21-902 (A)(1)(I): DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL (4BF0V1Z) TA 21-902 (B)(1)(I): DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL (4BG0V1Z) TA 21-902 (C)(1)(I): DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE SO FAR IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL CANNOT DRIVE SAFELY (4BH0V1Z) TA 21-901.1 (A): RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OF PERSONS AND PROPERTY (4BJ0V1Z) TA 26-102 (B): DIRECTING AND PERMITTING HIGHWAY VEHICLE OPERATION CONTRARY TO LAW (4BK0V1Z) TA 21-901.1 (B): NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON (4BL0V1Z) TA 20-105.1: FAILURE OF VEHICLE DRIVER INVOLVED IN ACCIDENT TO GIVE INSURANCE POLICY INFORMATION (4150V1Z) TA 21-801 (B): FAILURE TO CONTROL VEHICLE SPEED ON HIGHWAY TO AVOID COLLISION (4BM0V1Z) TA 21-201 (A)(1): DRIVER FAILURE TO OBEY PROPERLY PLACED TRAFFIC CONTROL DEVICE INSTRUCTIONS (4BN0V1Z)  I respectfully request the case remain open pending laboratory analysis.  All events occurred in Dorchester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 23:26:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/10/2023 15:08:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Del Vecchio</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mowbray</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7119</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/01/2023 16:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4BD0V1Z</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:40:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2023 23:40:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/01/2023 16:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4BF0V1Z</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/01/2023 16:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4BG0V1Z</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/01/2023 16:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4BH0V1Z</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/01/2023 16:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4BJ0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/01/2023 16:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4BK0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17272</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/01/2023 16:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4BL0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/01/2023 16:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4BM0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489497</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/01/2023 16:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>CITATION #: 4BN0V1Z</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>61</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:42:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>364992</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Moran</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>David</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/07/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/01/2023 22:56:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M650</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Moran</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>David</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/07/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M650</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/01/2023 22:56:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Woodbine</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Elkton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21921</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2078</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.797471</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.712732</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>302</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>521</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6595</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:42:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:34</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:42:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:34</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:42:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:34</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:42:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:34</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 23:41:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:18</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366642</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cook</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Bryan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/13/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>01/19/2023 23:41:02</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cook</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Bryan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/13/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/19/2023 23:41:02</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3620</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Bonnie</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Linkwood</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21835</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.962641</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.542816</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>477</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4670</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 23:41:24</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/02/2023 23:41:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148139</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 12:23:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/19/2023 12:23:21</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1GCHK29U55E315370</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2005</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SLV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8AM5305</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>