<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-030451</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/29/2023 17:07:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/29/2023 17:07:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/29/2023 17:06:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/29/2023 17:06:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Police information.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 17:07:12</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0392</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/06/2023 13:36:48</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>34690</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 17:07:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 23:27:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>34690</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>10251</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Central</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Upper Marlboro</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20774</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.82874</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.896889</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MVA LARGO</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MVA - LARGO</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/29/2023 17:07:09</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/29/2023 17:07:09</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/06/2023 13:36:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 17:07:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP0392</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/06/2023 13:36:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>THIS INCIDENT WAS CAPTURED ON BODY WORN CAMERA ONLY. L-20 is equipped with a camera but due to the nature of the incident, it was not operating during this incident.  SCENE PROCESSING: -Sgt. Zarzecki # 6202 requested surveillance camera video from the Largo MVA Supervisor, Ms. Whitley. A preservation notice has been sent for the videos of the related areas and time of the incident. -Enterprise rental car was contacted for further information on the missing vehicle with negative results at this time.  NEIGHBORHOOD CHECK: Responded to the Kettering Shopping center located directly east of the MVA (the last know direction the vehicle traveled) to attempt to locate the vehicle with negative results. During this time, I spoke with a security guard, advised him of the incident and asked him to call the Forestville Barack if he observed a suspicious vehicle meeting the description of the vehicle reported taken.  ATTACHMENT: A copy of the written statement from the complainant is attached to this report.   NARRATIVE: On August 29, 2023, at approximately 1615 hours, I, Cpl. York # 6327 of the Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack was dispatched to the Largo Motor Vehicle Administration (MVA) located at 10251 Central Ave. Upper Marlboro, MD in reference to a motor vehicle theft. Upon my arrival, I was immediately contacted by the complainant who identified himself as Daniel Edmunson Ezikel Phillip (B/M, DOB 10/17/76) through his Maryland drivers license. Phillip advised he was homeless and lost his job due to his truck being stolen (previous to today), further advised his phone was in his stolen truck, and he could only be reached through his email, Dannp007@gmail.com. Phillip advised he rented a black Nissan Altima with Minnesota registration plates through Enterprise rental car company on Annapolis Rd. due to his truck being stolen. Phillip did not have any documentation of the rental agreement with him or on his phone. Phillip advised two subjects were in the rental car while he was in the MVA and the vehicle was now missing. Phillips story of the missing rental car was hard to follow and I had to keep him on task to get the required information from him. On the keyless vehicle fob still in Phillips possession was written the following: (2022 Black Nissan Altima 7WTMWC, 1N4BL4BV1, NN353055).  Phillip gave a written statement and advised the following:  -He was at the Largo MVA to obtain a duplicate title for his stolen truck to claim a total lose and that vehicle was insured through Geico. Phillip could not provide a case number for his stolen truck but advised it was reported through Bowie Police Dept.He needed the duplicate title to get paid for his stolen truck.  -He drove the above stated rental car to the MVA and brought two subjects with him who he only knew as a black male named Rick (5 3 - 5 4 tall and slim), and a black female named Tia (55- 5 6 tall and thicker build). Phillip further advised he knew these two subjects through a friend who he also only knew as Bay-Bay (phone number 202-967-8146). I attempted to contact Bay-Bay by the phone number provided with negative results. He advised the friends were with him to get food as they stopped at McDonalds before heading to the MVA. Phillip also advised he had no money which contradicting his story.  -He picked up Rick and Tia at an apartment building located at Eastern Ave. and Nash as they were at that location in Bay-Bays truck.  -He arrived at the MVA at approximately 11am.  -He was in and out of the MVA twice due to a long wait time and had moved his car to a different parking spot but kept it in the same northern parking lot. Due to the hot weather, the two subjects who were waiting in his rental car requested he turn on the car for A/C. After turning on the A/C, Phillip advised he did not leave the keyless fob with the two subjects.  -When he returned outside at approximately 1300 hours, his rental vehicle was gone and he assumed they would return, but they did not. Phillip was in contact with Sgt. Zarzecki who was working security at the MVA during the incident but Phillip hoped the subject would return with th vehicle.  -At approximately 1600 hours, it was apparent the subjects were not returning the vehicle. Phillip stressed he did not want to get anyone in trouble.  After listening to Phillips story,I spoke with Sgt. Zarecki who was able to review surveillance video of the incident. Sgt. Zarzecki advised he witnessed on the surveillance video the female subject got in the car after walking around the parking lot, drove the vehicle in a northern direction, and merged onto eastbound Central Ave. as the vehicle made a right-hand turn.While Phillip was filling out a written statement form per my request, he seemed more interested in catching the bus that was on scene than to finish the form completely. I spoke with the bus driver who advised he was not leaving for another eight minutes and Phillip finished with his written statement. I instructed Phillip to report the vehicle stolen through Enterprise rental car company and provided him with an index card containing my contact information and the case number before he left.  A search of the information on the keyless fob produced negative results for any registration through Minnesota for a Nissan Altima. I then contacted Enterprise rental car company and requested to speak with their law enforcement liaison division. I was instructed to send an email to get further information on the missing vehicle. As the time of writing this report, I have not received a response.  On August 30, 2023, at approximately 1449 hours, I sent a follow-up email to the complainant, Phillips. I was inquiring if he had located the vehicle and if not, had he reported it stolen to Enterprise as I requested. At the time of writing this report, I have not received a response from the complainant Phillip.  On August 30, 2023 at approximately 1506 hours, I responded to the Enterprise Rental Company location at 5201 Auth Rd. Suitland, MD to request more information on the alleged stolen vehicle. After speaking with the store manager, I was directed to contact a Jenna Thompson at 571-241-1004 for the information I requested. When I called that number twive, she did not answer, her mailbox was full and I was unable to leave a message.  I request this case be SUSPENDED due to the lack of assistance from the complainant and the rental car company. This case may be reopened if further information is obtained.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6327</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 21:00:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6327</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/30/2023 15:57:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bowling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0392</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>York</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6327</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>46</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6327</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 20:51:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 23:27:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386458</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Phillip</LastName>
               <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Edmunson Ezikel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/17/1976 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/29/2023 20:50:59</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P410</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Phillip</LastName>
               <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Edmunson Ezikel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/17/1976 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P410</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/29/2023 20:50:59</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6327</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 20:59:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP6327</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 20:58:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 23:27:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386459</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/29/2023 20:58:43</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <DateOfInfo>08/29/2023 20:58:43</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6327</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 20:58:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP6327</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 20:58:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 23:27:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386460</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/29/2023 20:58:43</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <DateOfInfo>08/29/2023 20:58:43</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6327</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 20:58:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240016419</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>ENTERPRISE</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6327</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 20:52:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6327</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/29/2023 20:52:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156593</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>ST</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6327</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 22:26:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6327</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/29/2023 22:26:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>7</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ALT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleValue>23000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>