<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-045045</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/21/2023 08:38:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/21/2023 08:38:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/21/2023 07:43:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/21/2023 07:43:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DWI, CDS POSSESSION, FALSE STATEMENT TO PEACE OFFICER. SUSPECT PASSED OUT AT PANTRY 1 GAS PUMP.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 08:38:41</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2637</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 13:02:57</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>238465</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 08:38:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/21/2023 12:55:03</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>238465</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1897</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Conowingo</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Rising Sun</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.10240205793937</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.6939609602476</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>PANTRY 1</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/21/2023 08:38:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/21/2023 08:38:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/15/2024 10:25:32</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 08:38:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>SCENE PROCESSING:   Copies of the relevant paperwork can be found in Attachments, along with photographs.    I, Trooper First Class Scott (#7217) of the Maryland State Police, am equipped with a body-worn camera, which was recording during this investigation.    A vehicle search report was completed on Delta Plus.    PROPERTY RECORD P-345493 - ONE (1) CLEAR PLASTIC BAG CONTAINING AN ORANGE CONTAINER WITH ELEVEN (11) BLUE WAX FOLDS CONTAINING SUSPECTED HEROIN AND FENTANYL. TOTAL WEIGHT INCLUDING PACKAGING: 15.9 GRAMS - ONE (1) CLEAR PLASTIC BAG CONTAINING TWO (2) SEPARATE PLASTIC BAGGIES WITH EACH CONTAINING A WHITE CRYSTALLINE ROCK-TYPE SUBSTANCE, SUSPECTED METHAMPHETAMINE. TOTAL WEIGHT INCLUDING PACKAGING: 21.6 GRAMS. - ONE (1) CLEAR PLASTIC BAG CONTAINING ONE (1) GLASS SMOKING DEVICE WITH METHAMPHETAMINE RESIDUE.  CRIMINAL CITATION TRACKING NUMBERS:  - 192001919303 - 192001919292 - 192001919281 - 192001919270 - 192001919314  TRAINING AND CERTIFICATION:  - Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests (SFSTs) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.   - Enhanced DUI Enforcement course through Maryland Police and Correctional Training Commissions.   - Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) Training.  SUSPECT:   NAME: PHILIP JASON MITCHELL (W/M)   DATE OF BIRTH: NOVEMBER 22, 1983   MD SOUNDEX:MD10272563238   ADDRESS: 459 BASIN RUN ROAD, CONOWINGO, MD 21918   DWI#: 23-155   DATE/TIME OF ARREST: DECEMBER 21, 2023 @ 0837 HOURS    VEHICLE REGISTRATION: PENNSYLVANIAJZK8641   VEHICLE IDENTIFICATION NUMBER:3VWRF81K86M660410   VEHICLE YEAR/MAKE/MODEL: 2006 VOLKSWAGEN JETTA  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE ONE):   On December 21, 2023, at approximately 0746 hours, I, Trooper First Class Scott (#7217) of the Maryland State Police, was dispatched to the Pantry 1 gas station located at 1897 Conowingo Road, Rising Sun, Maryland 21911 in response to an impaired driver.The suspect vehicle was described during dispatch as a gray Volkswagen parked at a gas pump with the operator passed out behind the wheel.I arrived on scene at approximately 0814 hours.    Upon arrival, I observed the vehicle described during dispatch, a gray 2006 Volkswagen Jetta bearing Pennsylvania registrationJZK8641 (see SUSPECT). Upon approach, I observed the operator was slumped in the drivers seat of the vehicle. I observed he was alone. I felt the vehicles hood and noted it was cool to the touch. However, the vehicles ignition key was very clearly in the ignition as the operator sat in the drivers seat, still unaware of my presence. I also observed a glass smoking device with burnt residue sitting about the center console of the vehicle. I know through training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper that such glass smoking devices are commonly used in the administration of controlled dangerous substances, such as crack cocaine and methamphetamine. I immediately recognized the glass smoking device to be drug paraphernalia.    As a result, I requested another unit as back-up and attempted contact with the operator. Eventually, Trooper First Class Bachu (#7184) and Master Trooper Proctor (#4999) arrived on scene as my back-up.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE TWO):  Upon knocking on the drivers window, I was able to wake the operator and speak to him. He promptly opened his door and I ordered him out of the vehicle. As he opened the drivers door, I noticed several indicator lights activated on the drivers display of the vehicle. I also could hear an audible chime (i.e. such as a chime that would warn a driver their key is still in the ignition). The operator initially had a pack of cigarettes in his hand, which I asked that he place in his vehicle. However, he then started to reach around the passenger seat of his vehicle. I ordered him to stop doing that and demanded he step out of the drivers seat.    The operator complied, and he consented to a pat down of his person upon my asking. I did not detect a weapon on him upon a pat down of his person.    I asked the operator when the last time he used illicit substances was (considering I found him slumped at the wheel and observed paraphernalia in plain view in his car). He denied using illicit substances.He told me he stopped at the Pantry 1 to get gasoline.    I asked the operator for his name/identification. The operator told me his name was Michael Shane Mitchell (W/M; DOB: 12/31/1977) and failed to display identification when I asked if he had his identification card on him. However, I would later discover upon a search of his person (search incident to arrest) that he indeed had his Maryland identification card and his social security card in his wallet. I identified the operator then via the social security card and the Maryland identification card as Philip Jason Mitchell (see SUSPECT). I would later learn that Michael Mitchell is actually Philips brother.    I noticed as I spoke to Philip that his speech was heavily mumbled and slurred. I also observed lethargic behaviors throughout our interaction (to include testing).    I asked Philip to participate in Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) for the following reasons:      - I was dispatched to the associated gas station in response to the operator of a gray Volkswagen passed out behind the wheel.     - Upon arrival, I observed a gray Volkswagen at a gas pump with its operator slumped at the wheel. I would later positively identify this person as Philip Mitchell.     - I observed the vehicles key was in the ignition as Philip sat slumped in the drivers seat, unaware I was on scene.     - Philip did not wake and become alerted to my presence until I physically knocked on his window.     - I observed a glass smoking device that I immediately recognized to be drug paraphernalia. The device was located about the center console of the vehicle, within easy reach of Philip.     - Philips speech was mumbled and slurred.    Philip consented to SFSTs.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE THREE):  The ground used for testing was level and clear of any debris that would reasonably interfere with testing. I positioned Philip in front of my vehicle for testing. The emergency lights of my vehicle were not activated at the time of testing. I asked Philip a series of questions before testing. His responses are as follows:    ALCOHOL: NO   DRUGS: METHADONE, GABAPENTIN, ZOLOFT.   EYE ISSUES: MAY NEED EYEGLASSES. LATER MENTIONED HE HAS PARTIAL VISION LOSS.   ISSUES WALKING/BALANCING: PRIOR SPINAL INJURIES.   EPILEPTIC/DIABETIC: NO   MEDICAL CONDITIONS: NONE (ASIDE FROM SPINAL INJURIES).    Additionally, during testing, I observed Philips nose appeared to be somewhat runny. I know through training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper that some controlled dangerous substances can cause a runny nose, in addition to lethargic behaviors and other indicators.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS TEST (HGN): 2/6    I instructed Philip to stand with his feet together and arms at his sides. I had him remove his hat for this portion of testing. I instructed him to hold his head/chin level and track the tip of my pen (silver in color; the stimulus) with only his eyes, keeping his head still in the process. I held my pen approximately twelve to fifteen inches from his face, just above eye level. Philip said he could see the tip of my pen clearly. Philip advised he understood my instructions and had no questions.    I had to pause and restart testing for certain clues at some points of this test because Philip stopped tracking my pen.    I noted Philip had equal pupil size, equal tracking, and no resting nystagmus in either eye. He also did not have vertical gaze nystagmus.    I observed the following two out of six validated clues of impairment during this test (one clue per eye):      - LACK OF SMOOTH PURSUIT (BOTH EYES).  WALK AND TURN TEST (WAT): 6/8    During this portion, I had Philip assume the starting position (right foot heel-to-toe in front of the left foot, arms at the sides). I demonstrated and explained the test for him. I told him to hold the starting position while I explained the test, and told him not to start until told to do so. I told him not to stop either once the test is started. I demonstrated the test by holding the starting position myself and taking three heel-to-toe steps along an imaginary line. I then executed the turn by planting my lead foot and making short choppy steps with my following foot to turn around. I then made three steps back along the line from whence I came. I iterated to Philip that he was taking a total of nine heel-to-toe steps each way. I told Philip he would keep his arms at his sides for the duration of testing, that he would count each step out loud, and keep watch of his feet as he walked. Philip told me he had no questions regarding the test instructions.    I observed the following six out of eight validated clues of impairment during this test:      - FAILURE TO MAINTAIN BALANCE IN STARTING POSITION     - MISSES HEEL-TO-TOE STEP     - STOPS     - STEPS OFF LINE     - RAISES ARMS     - IMPROPER TURN    Phillip briefly left the starting position before starting the test. I instructed him to return to the proper position. Phillip also did not walk heel-to-toe for a few of his steps throughout testing, and he stepped off-line a number of times (there were some steps were he would place his following foot roughly adjacent to his lead foot before adjusting the following foot to be heel-to-toe with the leading foot). Phillip also stopped a few times during testing. He also failed to keep his arms pinned to his sides, and raised his arms a few times. He also executed the turn improperly (i.e. he failed to plant the lead foot and make choppy steps around it with the following foot).  ONE LEG STAND TEST (OLS): 3/4    For this test, I had Philip stand with his feet together and arms at his sides. Considering his reported back issues, I asked if he thought he could conduct this test without putting his foot down. He said maybe, and consented to participating in this test. I explained and demonstrated the test for his understanding. I demonstrated/explained he would be raising the foot of his choosing approximately six inches above the ground, using the height of a dollar bill standing upright as reference. I told him he would raise his chosen foot, and lock his eyes on the raised foot, keeping his arms at his sides while doing so. I told him to lock the raised legs knee straight, and demonstrated the proper way to extend his foot and leg. I told him not to put his foot down for any reason. I told him to count out loud by one-thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two, etc.) until told to stop. I clarified the test before he told me he had no further questions regarding instructions. I timed him for thirty seconds.    I observed the following three out of four validated clues of impairment during this test:      - PUTS FOOT DOWN     - SWAYS     - USES ARMS FOR BALANCE    Phillip put his foot down part of the way through testing. Upon being told to pick it up again, Phillip picked it up. However, he then raised each of his arms out from his sides a minimum of six inches and his upper body started to sway slightly from side to side. He also put his foot down again just before the end of the test.  LACK OF CONVERGENCE TEST: CONVERGENCE PRESENT    For this test, I had Philip remove his hat again and stand with his feet together, arms at his sides. I told Philip I would use my pen to trace a couple of circles around his face before drawing the pen in close to the tip of his nose without touching it. I told him to let his eyes cross naturally during the test. I asked him if the test sounded easy. He initially said it did not. Then I asked if it wasnt easy to track a pen. He then said he could track a pen. I asked if he had any questions before starting the test, and he said he did not.    In completing the test, I observed Philips eyes converged normally.  MODIFIED ROMBERG BALANCE TEST: 33 SECONDS    I had Philip stand with his feet together and his arms at his sides. I instructed him to leave his hat off. I demonstrated and explained that he would tilt his head back and close his eyes. I told him while doing so that he was to estimate the passage of time for thirty seconds in his head (counting by one-thousands again). I told him that, when finished, he was to return his head forward, open his eyes, and say done. Philip had me repeat my instructions. After repeating my instructions, he said he had no questions. I timed Philip while he estimated the passage of time.    Philip estimated thirty seconds in the passage of approximately thirty-three seconds. On scene, I noted thirty-five seconds as I was slightly delayed in marking the time. This was because Phillip mumbled significantly when he advised he was finished counting. I reviewed the relevant footage to better pinpoint when he said he was finished. Philip started to try to announce that he was done counting at approximately thirty-three seconds.  FINGER TO NOSE TEST:  I demonstrated and explained the test for Philip. I told him to stand with his feet together, arms extended from his sides. I told him he would have the index finger of each hand extended. I told him he would be tilting his head back and closing his eyes for testing. I told him to raise the index finger of the hand I call to the tip of his nose. I told him that upon touching his index finger to the tip of his nose, he is to bring that hand back down and continue raising the corresponding hand I call in the same fashion. Philip advised he had no questions/understood instructions.    I observed Philip demonstrate the test himself while I explained it (he did this on his own, not at my request). I noticed when he raised his hand up he failed to touch his nose doing this (he raised his hand up and his finger stopped well ahead of the tip of his nose).    I called Philips hands in the following order: left, right, left, right, right, left. I noticed on the first left call out, Philip raised his left hand and brought his index finger just to his right of the tip of his nose before adjusting its position to the tip of his nose. When I made the first right call out, Philip raised his right hand extremely slowly to his face. He stopped his hand just above his upper lip and it took a few seconds for him to find his finger to his nose. I observed Philips movements throughout this test were notably slow, lethargic, and uncoordinated. Each call out I made resulted in the same sort of difficulty and slowed movements I already described. It took Philip several seconds to raise each hand I called to actually touch the tip of his nose. I noticed his hand at times would hover near the tip of his nose, as if he was having difficulty completing the movement and finding the tip of his own nose. He would eventually make adjustments and touch the tip of his nose.    Overall, the observations I gathered during this portion of testing further indicated to me that Philip was significantly impaired. His performance struck me as obviously abnormal. I know through training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper that certain controlled dangerous substances, such as narcotic analgesics like heroin, can cause significant lethargic behaviors to display.  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST: NOT OFFERED/NOT AVAILABLE  ARREST:  At approximately 0837 hours, I placed Philip under arrest. I did so based upon the following facts:      - I was dispatched to the associated gas station in response to the operator of a gray Volkswagen passed out behind the wheel.     - Upon arrival, I observed a gray Volkswagen at a gas pump with its operator slumped at the wheel. I would later positively identify this person as Philip Mitchell.     - I observed the vehicles key was in the ignition as Philip sat slumped in the drivers seat, unaware I was on scene.     - I observed a glass smoking device that I immediately recognized to be drug paraphernalia. The device was located about the center console of the vehicle, within easy reach of Philip.     - Philip did not wake or become alerted to my presence until I knocked on his window.     - Aside from the obvious drug paraphernalia, Philip also advised he takes Gabapentin, Zoloft, and Methadone, which I know through training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper can also cause impaired driving.     - Philips speech was mumbled and slurred.     - Phillips nose appeared somewhat runny.     - Philip appeared lethargic. As our interaction and testing progressed, he also appeared off-balance.     - Philip consented to SFSTs. His performance indicated impairment.     - Philips finger-to-nose test performance was so slow, lethargic, and uncoordinated that it was specifically notable.    Based on the totality of the above circumstances, and my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, there is probable cause to believe Philip was driving while impaired by a controlled dangerous substance.    Upon arresting Philip, I conducted a search of his person. A mouth check was conducted at 0839 hours, and Philips mouth was found to be free of any foreign substances.    During the search incident to arrest of Philips person, I discovered a small orange plastic container in one of Philips pockets. The orange plastic container was transparent, and I could see it contained several (discovered to be eleven total) blue wax paper folds with various stamps on them. I know through training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper that such folds are commonly used for the packaging and abuse of controlled substances such as heroin and fentanyl. I immediately recognized the folds as such.    Philips wallet was also retrieved, which I previously mentioned contained his Maryland identification card and his social security card. This allowed for photographic identification and proved that Philip was not Michael as he claimed to be. Philip admitted he assumed his brothers name.    Additionally, it was discovered Philip had an active felony arrest warrant. A check of the warrant on Maryland Judiciary Case Search (case numberD-032-CR-23-002285) revealed he was charged in that case with Assault - First Degree, Assault - Second Degree, Trespass: Private Property, Burglary - 4th Degree Theft, and Robbery. The warrant was through the Cecil County Sheriffs Office.    Following a search of his person, I placed Philip into my patrol vehicle and the DR-15 Advice of Rights English audio was played for him. Trooper First Class Bachu stood watch over Philip as he listened to the form. Meanwhile, I conducted a probable cause search of his vehicle. Philip would consent to a breath test for alcohol at approximately 0907 hours.  PROBABLE CAUSE SEARCH OF VEHICLE:  Based on Philips impaired state, the fact that I found him in the drivers seat of the gray Volkswagen, and the glass smoking device (illicit drug paraphernalia) I observed in plain view within the vehicle, I had reason to believe Philips vehicle contained not only evidence of impairment, but also additional drug-related offenses. I initiated a probable cause search of the vehicle at approximately 0849 hours. The only area of the vehicle that was searched was the passenger compartment (i.e. the areas Philip would have had within his wingspan).    During the course of the search, I collected the glass smoking device I observed about the center console. The smoking device contained controlled dangerous substance residue. I also located a torch lighter on the front passenger floorboard, underneath the seat.    Philip also had a book bag in the front passenger seat next to where he sat. I searched that as well considering it was within arms reach of Philip when I encountered him. I discovered a small weight scale inside the bag, with what seemed to be small trace amounts of a white powder substance. I know through training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper that such scales are used in relation to the abuse of controlled dangerous substances. Considering the scale did not present a significant degree of evidence to be processed, I simply photographed it for documentation purposes. The scale was otherwise left in the vehicle.    Aside from the glass smoking device, nothing else was seized from Philips vehicle.  MARYLAND STATE POLICE NORTH EAST BARRACK:  Upon the completion of the probable cause search, I placed Philips wallet, the glass smoking device, and the container of wax folds in my vehicles trunk for safe transport. I then transported Philip to the Maryland State Police North East Barrack. I read Philip his Miranda Rights during transport to the Maryland State Police North East Barrack. Philip advised he understood his rights as I explained them, and he consented to me questioning him.    In questioning, Philip told me the glass smoking device was his methamphetamine pipe. Also, when asked why he lied about his name, Philip tried to tell me he was simply so tired that he forgot his name and used his brothers. Philip insisted this was the case even when I strongly pointed out how unbelievable that explanation was. Philip also claimed to not have any additional contraband on his person.    While at the Maryland State Police North East Barrack, Philip provided a breath sample of 0.00 BAC. He declined to speak to a drug recognition expert when offered.    A strip search was authorized by Corporal Mingle (#6742) considering the controlled dangerous substance contraband discovered in Philips possession (which created a reasonable likelihood he could be hiding additional contraband under his clothing). My body-worn camera was deactivated during the strip search for Philips dignity. The strip search was conducted in one of the holding cells of the Maryland State Police North East Barrack, which covered Philip from the observation of others while I conducted the strip search. The strip search was authorized at approximately 1007 hours.  The strip search revealed Philip had a plastic baggie in one of his socks, which contained two other separate plastic baggies, with those baggies containing a crystalline, rock-like substance. Through my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, I recognized this substance to be methamphetamine. No further contraband was discovered in Philips possession.    Philip was charged on several criminal citations based on the following facts:      - Philips vehicle contained a glass smoking device that I recognized to be drug paraphernalia. After I read him his Miranda Rights, Philip admitted the smoking device was a methamphetamine pipe.     - Philip was found in possession of several blue wax folds, which I recognized to be packaging commonly used for heroin/fentanyl.     - Philip had a crystalline, rock-like substance in one of his socks. This was discovered upon a strip search, and I recognized said substance to be methamphetamine.     - Through my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, I am familiar with heroin, fentanyl, and methamphetamine and know them to be controlled dangerous substances. I am also more than capable of recognizing those substances and their paraphernalia.     - The Drug Enforcement Administration lists heroin as a Schedule I controlled dangerous substance. They also list fentanyl and methamphetamine as Schedule II controlled dangerous substances.     - Philip was caught lying about his identity, having claimed he was his brother, Michael. His Maryland identification card and social security card in his wallet proved he was not Michael.     - The warrant for Philips arrest and the variety of contraband I recovered from him, as well as his faulty explanation that he was so tired he forgot his own name, give reason to believe he deliberately attempted to conceal his identity from me during a lawful investigation.    Based on the totality of the above circumstances, there is also probable cause to believe Philip was in possession of three separate controlled dangerous substances: methamphetamine, heroin, and fentanyl. There is also probable cause to believe he gave a false statement to a peace officer (i.e. myself), namely by lying and saying he was his brother, Michael, to deter a lawful investigation and avoid apprehension.  CLOSING REMARKS:    The related criminal citation numbers can be located in SCENE PROCESSING.    In addition to the criminal citations, I also issued Philip twelve traffic citations related to his unregistered motor vehicle, his lack of a valid drivers license, and his driving while impaired.    I would note here that Philip became frustrated when signing the criminal citations and refused to continue signing them. He relented when I warned him he would be charged with failure to obey a lawful order. That being said, he signed one of his citations (tracking number192001919314) Scott Sucks Dick.    Philip was issued all the appropriate copies of his paperwork. A deputy from Cecil County Sheriffs Office arrived at the barrack and took custody of Philip for warrant service at approximately 1212 hours. A check of the related warrant case lists that Philip was held without bond following his initial appearance.    Case cleared by arrest.    All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 12:59:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/15/2024 09:50:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bachu</LastName>
            <FirstName>Farhan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7184</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Proctor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4999</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Spayd</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5369</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Scott</LastName>
            <FirstName>Conor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7217</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534522</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>5 3550</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>18</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/21/2023 08:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>5 3550</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 12:55:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/21/2023 12:56:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534522</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>18</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/21/2023 08:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 12:55:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/21/2023 12:57:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534522</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>18</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/21/2023 07:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2024 00:52:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/07/2024 00:52:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 12:55:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/21/2023 13:45:57</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>98488</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>mitchell</LastName>
               <FirstName>phillip</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>jason</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/22/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/22/2017 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M324</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P410</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mitchell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shane</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/31/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M324</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mitchell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Philip</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jason</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/22/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.18177078E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/26/2016 10:20:27</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M324</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P410</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>mitchell</LastName>
               <FirstName>phillip</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>jason</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/22/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M324</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P410</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/22/2017 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mitchell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Shane</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/31/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M324</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mitchell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Philip</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jason</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/22/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.18177078E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>M324</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P410</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/26/2016 10:20:27</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>228</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Edgevale</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Brooklyn Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21225</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.616822</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.235326</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>459</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Basin Run</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21918</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.134635</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.656182</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>251</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5927</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>466</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0030</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/26/2016 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 12:58:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/21/2023 12:58:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 12:58:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/21/2023 12:58:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/21/2023 12:55:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/21/2023 12:55:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>160726</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/15/2024 09:52:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/15/2024 09:52:39</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/15/2024 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3VWRF81K86M660410</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2006</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>VOLK</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>JET</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>PA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>JZK8641</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2024 00:55:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/07/2024 00:55:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/07/2024 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>ORANGE CONTAINER W/11 BLUE WAX FOLDS CONTAINING SUSPECTED HEROIN/FENTANYL</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>258166</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>D</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>15.9</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2024 00:55:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/07/2024 00:55:10</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/07/2024 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>TWO SEPARATE PLASTIC BAGGIES CONTAINING WHITE CRYSTALLINE SUBSTANCE, SUSPECTED METHAMPHETAMINE</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>258167</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>L</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>21.6</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2024 00:56:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/07/2024 00:56:07</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/07/2024 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>GLASS SMOKING DEVICE WITH METHAMPHETAMINE RESIDUE.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>100</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>258168</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>