<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000554</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/05/2023 15:07:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/05/2023 15:07:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/05/2023 13:27:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/05/2023 13:27:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>JUVENILE ASSAULTS MOTHER AND GRANDFATHER. JUVENILE BREAKS MOTHER'S MUG.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 15:07:29</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2637</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/13/2023 11:52:05</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>MDOP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>679424</AddressId>
      <City>MDC221</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 15:07:34</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/05/2023 15:57:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>679424</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>331</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Slicers Mill</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Rising Sun</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.092192</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.709002</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/05/2023 15:07:27</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/05/2023 15:07:27</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/07/2023 09:49:10</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 15:07:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:29</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>SCENE PROCESSING:   Photographs of injuries and damaged items can be found in Attachments with a copy of the juvenile referral form.    A domestic violence supplement was not completed considering the victims and the suspect share a grandparent/grandchild and parent/child relationship among the three of them.    DAMAGES: ONE (1) BUTTERFLY MUG VALUED AT $2.00  NEIGHBORHOOD CHECK:  A neighborhood check was not conducted.  JUVENILE SUSPECT:  NAME: ASHLYN SPROUT (W/F) DATE OF BIRTH: NOVEMBER 18, 2006   AGE DURING INCIDENT: 16 YEARS   ADDRESS: 331 SLICERS MILL ROAD, RISING SUN, MD 21911   GUARDIAN: SHONA L. SPROUT  VICTIM NUMBER ONE:   NAME: SHONA SPROUT (W/F)   DATE OF BIRTH: NOVEMBER 13, 1977   ADDRESS: 331 SLICERS MILL ROAD, RISING SUN, MD 21911   TELEPHONE: 443-553-6855  VICTIM NUMBER TWO:  NAME: GARY L. PIERCE (W/M)   DATE OF BIRTH: MAY 13, 1949   ADDRESS 331 SLICERS MILL ROAD, RISING SUN, MD 21911  WITNESS:   NAME: GERALDINE WHEATLEY (W/F)   DATE OF BIRTH: JANUARY 5, 1949   ADDRESS: 331 SLICERS MILL ROAD, RISING SUN, MD 21911  NARRATIVE:  On January 5, 2023 at approximately 1328 hours, I, Trooper First Class Scott (#7217) of the Maryland State Police, was dispatched to 331 Slicers Mill Road, Rising Sun, Maryland 21911 for a domestic dispute involving a juvenile suspect, her mother, and her grandfather. I was advised leading into dispatch that the juvenile assaulted her mother and grandfather. During my response, I also overheard radio traffic from Cecil County Sheriffs Office, advising they received notification from the juvenile that she was assaulted by her mother. I arrived on scene at approximately 1348 hours.    Upon arrival, I made contact with Ashlyn Sprout (see Suspect), Shona Sprout (see Victim One), Gary Pierce (see Victim Two), and Geraldine Wheatley (see Witness). Ashlyn, Shona, and Gary were separated for interview purposes.    Ashlyn claimed that she and her mother had a dispute, leading to her mother assaulting her. During investigation, I observed faint scratches on the side of Ashlyns neck. She also claimed someone pulled her hair, but I did not have physical evidence to collect for this.    However, when I spoke to Shona, Gary, and Geraldine, I gathered that Ashlyn was actually the aggressor in the situation, and I am led to believe the scratches on her neck resulted from her assaulting Shona and Gary, and then attempting to flee. For purposes of clarifying, I gathered the following insights:    - Gary witnessed Ashlyn assaulting Shona.   - Geraldine witnessed Ashlyn assaulting Gary and breaking a mug belonging to Shona. - Ashlyn and Gary personally gave an account of the assaults that happened to them personally.    As a result of interviewing Shona, Gary, and Geraldine, I gathered the following events occurred regarding the assault on Shona:      - Ashlyn was recently suspended from school.     - Ashlyn was asked to help clean the kitchen. She had her laptop with her.     - Ashlyn started to eat some breakfast sandwiches in the kitchen. Shona told her to stop eating them, and Ashlyn walked to the bathroom.     - Due to Ashlyns behaviors, Shona took Ashlyns laptop and gave it to Gary (to confiscate it from Ashlyn).     - Ashlyn returned, discovering her laptop was confiscated. She became upset and knocked Shonas glasses from her face with her hand.     - Ashlyn proceeded to assault Shona, swinging her hands at her.     - Ashlyn broke contact with Shona. She grabbed a butter knife and used it to pick a lock on a door leading to a bedroom in the home.     - Ashlyn locked herself in the bedroom.    Shona initially did not believe she had injuries. However, she came to realize she had a scratch under her left arm, near her armpit.    Following the assault on Shona, I was told the following occurred:      - Shona attempted to gain entry to the bedroom. She was concerned about medications she stores there and thought Ashlyn may access them.     - Shona could not effectively get in, so she broke the door open. She then ordered Ashlyn out of the bedroom.     - Ashlyn proceeded back to the kitchen, where she confronted her grandfather at the kitchen table.     - Ashlyn physically tugged back and forth with her grandfather on the laptop before pushing him away from the laptop.     - Ashlyn knocked over a butterfly mug belonging to Shona.     - Ashlyn attempted to run outside with the laptop. Gary attempted to grab her, but Ashlyn was able to break free and run outside.    It seems the hair grabbing Ashlyn complained of may have come from Gary attempting to stop her.    During my investigation, I gathered that Ashlyn has previously made suicidal statements and made attempts to run away from home. Her family expressed concern over her well-being, which would explain why her grandfather attempted to stop her from leaving.    From speaking with Geraldine, she seemed positive that Ashlyn purposefully knocked over Shonas mug. Shona told me she personally owns the mug and collects butterfly-related items (such as the mug). I was told the mug was the only thing knocked off the table, which was very cluttered. This makes it likely that Ashlyn broke the mug intentionally as a means of upsetting her mother, Shona.    Ashlyn also communicated that she does not desire to reside at 331 Slicers Mill (which coincides with what I was told regarding her attempts to run away).    Additionally, Shona told me Ashlyn previously broke Shonas glasses. I observed Shonas glasses were clearly held together by glue, leading me to believe Ashlyn has a history of aggression toward her mother.    Based on the following facts, I completed a juvenile referral for Ashlyn:      - Ashlyns mother, grandmother, and grandfather all pointed to her as the aggressor in this incident.     - Shona and Gary claim Ashlyn assaulted them.     - Gary witnessed the assault on Shona and Geraldine witnessed the assault on Gary.     - Shona was able to point to a scratch that she claimed was from Ashlyns assault.     - Shona showed me her glasses, which were damaged. She claims they were glued together due to a prior assault from Ashlyn.     - I personally observed Shonas broken butterfly mug.     - Geraldine witnessed Ashlyn breaking the butterfly mug. Shona and Geraldine believe it was intentional destruction of property.     - I was told the mug was the only thing knocked off of what was otherwise a very cluttered table, making it likely intentional.    Based on the totality of the above circumstances, there is probable cause to believe Ashlyn assaulted Shona and Gary in the second degree, and she committed malicious destruction of property valued under $1,000. Their residential status also makes this an instance of domestic violence.    I decided to conduct the juvenile referral for Ashlyn at approximately 1459 hours. The referral was completed at approximately 1515 hours. Ashlyn was appropriately left in the care of her mother, Shona. Shona was provided a copy of the juvenile referral upon completion.    I asked Ashlyn if she had thoughts of harming herself. She advised me she did not desire to harm herself. She also declined any medical attention when offered. I also encouraged Ashlyn to behave and attempt to get along with her family.    Shona also wanted to document that she has previously confiscated marijuana-related item(s) from Ashlyn. She believes Ashlyn has been telling people that she receives marijuana from Shona, which Shona denied being true.    I advised Shona to keep in touch with Juvenile Services and recommended she contact Social Services. I also recommended she file for an emergency petition herself, considering her claims regarding Ashlyns prior statements on self-harm/suicide. To reiterate, Ashlyn denied having such feelings when I interviewed her, and she declined medical treatment when offered.    Shona and Gary did not appear to have any injuries requiring medical attention. Shona appeared to have a minor scratch on her arm, and did not make any other injuries known. Gary did not make any injuries known. I did not observe any other injuries to the two of them.    I provided Shona with my name/rank/identification number and the case number, all written on her copy of the juvenile referral form.    Copies of the juvenile referral were promptly delivered to the Maryland State Police North East Barrack after I cleared the scene.    Case cleared by juvenile referral.    All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 15:58:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/05/2023 17:15:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Roland</LastName>
            <FirstName>Trevor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6698</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Spayd</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5369</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Scott</LastName>
            <FirstName>Conor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7217</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489931</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>19</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/05/2023 15:15:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 17:04:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/05/2023 17:05:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489931</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>19</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3 4025</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/05/2023 15:15:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 17:04:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/05/2023 17:06:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>16</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 17:04:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:12</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>350857</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sprout</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ashlyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Angela</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/18/2006 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/29/2022 15:24:23</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S163</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A245</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sprout</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ashlyn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Angela</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/18/2006 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S163</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A245</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/29/2022 15:24:23</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>331</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Slicer</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Rising Sun</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21911</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.0627266</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.6978871</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>945</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5922</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/29/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 17:08:05</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:37</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 17:08:05</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:37</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 17:09:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365293</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>SPROUT</LastName>
               <FirstName>SHONA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LYNN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/13/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 17:09:19</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S163</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>SPROUT</LastName>
               <FirstName>SHONA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LYNN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/13/1977 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S163</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 17:09:19</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>331</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Slicers Mill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Rising Sun</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.092192</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.709002</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>553</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6855</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 17:11:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:40</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>73</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 17:10:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:40</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365294</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>PIERCE</LastName>
               <FirstName>GARY</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/13/1949 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 17:10:27</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>PIERCE</LastName>
               <FirstName>GARY</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/13/1949 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 17:10:27</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>331</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Slicers Mill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Rising Sun</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.092192</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.709002</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 17:16:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:35</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>74</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 17:13:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:46</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365295</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>WHEATLEY</LastName>
               <FirstName>GERALDINE</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/05/1949 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 17:13:14</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W340</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G643</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>WHEATLEY</LastName>
               <FirstName>GERALDINE</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/05/1949 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W340</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G643</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 17:13:14</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>331</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Slicers Mill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Rising Sun</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.092192</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.709002</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 17:13:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:42</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>4</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/05/2023 17:14:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/05/2023 17:14:13</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>ONE (1) BUTTERFLY MUG.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>313</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>2</PropertyValue>
         <Value>2</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>240891</Property_ID>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>