<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-003434</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/27/2023 17:04:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/27/2023 17:04:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/27/2023 16:28:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/27/2023 16:28:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>TRAFFIC STOP, MTA</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 17:04:31</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6039</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/01/2023 11:35:25</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>16 MM I695 NB, GWYNN OAK</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>682020</AddressId>
      <City>MDC586</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 17:04:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/27/2023 17:50:27</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>682020</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>16</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I695 Nb Gwynn Oak</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.74673205</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.3588677833333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/27/2023 17:04:28</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/27/2023 17:04:28</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>03/01/2023 11:35:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 17:04:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6039</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/01/2023 11:35:25</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>I trooper Pezold #7512 with the Maryland State Police, assigned to Golden Ring Barracks Baltimore MD, was on routine patrol on O/L I-695. I was parked on the O/L I-695 @ Milford Mill Road over pass on the right shoulder. I observed a silver passenger vehicle later identified as a Silver Chrysler PT Cruiser bearing a Delaware Temporary registration of XR931802, drive to the end of the merge lane from south bound I-795. It appeared to have partially merged over but then began passing vehicles on its left. I observed more than half of the vehicle driving on the shoulder of the roadway (the PT cruiser was straddling the rumble strip). I observed the PT Cruiser pass approximately 4 vehicles in this manor before merging into lane 4 of the travel portion of the highway just prior to where I was parked.  I made contact with the driver, Boyd CHRISCOE, identified by his Maryland Drivers license as C-620-095-738-893. I explained the reason for the stop was for passing vehicles while using the shoulder of the roadway, at which time he stated he didnt have time to merge. I explained that I watched him attempt to merge then accelerating past vehicles while straddling the rumble strips. I asked him to provide his Drivers License and Vehicle registration. CHRISCOE provided a MD drivers license and a registration card that did not look or feel normal. It appeared to be thick poster board or plastic card stock.  I ran the information CHRISCOE provided at which time I discovered a valid drivers license but no valid information coming from the registration number. This registration number appeared to have been stopped 15 times prior all showing different vehicles and drivers listed on the traffic stops.  I returned to the vehicle and asked CHRISCOE to provide insurance information on the vehicle. He supplied an Allstate Insurance card but it was expired and not for the PT Cruiser. CHRISCOE explained that the insurance was for his other vehicle. I returned to my patrol vehicle and ran the PT Cruisers VIN, at which time I discovered the vehicle had not been registered in Maryland. I returned back to the PT Cruiser and asked CHRISCOE to be honest about the situation. He stated he was being honest and that he bought the vehicle from his boss and that his boss registered the vehicle for CHRISCOE. At this time I issued the citations and confiscated for destruction the Delaware registration tag and card. I explained to CHRISCOE he could not drive the vehicle any further and that he would need to figure out how to get it to where he needed without driving it.  All events Occurred in Baltimore County MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7512</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/27/2023 17:51:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7512</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/27/2023 17:51:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Burton</LastName>
            <FirstName>Graham</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>PEZOLD</LastName>
            <FirstName>JONATHAN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7512</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>