<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-033682</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/24/2023 21:53:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/24/2023 21:53:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/24/2023 20:28:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/24/2023 20:28:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The driver on a traffic stop displayed signs of mental crisis and was transported to the hospital for a voluntary evaluation.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/24/2023 21:54:00</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5635</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 18:04:29</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>707944</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/24/2023 21:54:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 17:20:13</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>707944</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Leonardtown</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Waldorf</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20601</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.870518</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.596655</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/24/2023 21:53:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/24/2023 21:53:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>09/25/2023 18:04:29</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/24/2023 21:54:00</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5635</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 18:04:29</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was recorded on a body worn camera. The initial approach was not recorded due to the camera charging.  Attachments: None  Narrative: On September 24, 2023 at approximately 2027 hours, I, Cpl. B. Meurrens #6372, was operating marked patrol vehicle H-15 in the area of Leonardtown Road and Renner Road, Waldorf, Charles County, MD. I was conducting stationary radar enforcement facing south in the center turn lane. I observed a gray Jeep Compass traveling south on Leonardtown Road and utilized my rear antenna to obtain a steady speed on 68 mph in a posted 45 mph speed zone. I conducted a traffic stop on the gray Jeep and identified the driver as Paul Kean Kyles (W/M 7/15/1989). During my initial approach, I recognized numerous indicators that made me concerned for the safety and mental health of the Kyles. I noticed Kyles had a Military Identification Card, and he advised he was active duty Navy and currently stationed in PatuxentRiver Naval Air Station in Lexington Park, MD. Kyles advised he was, just driving around, and that he currently lived at the Lexington Park, MD address listed on his registration card. Kyles appeared visibly distressed and had a depressed and melancholy demeanor. It was extremely difficult to understand him due to the low volume which he was speaking. It also appeared as though Kyles may have also recently been crying. I noticed that Kyles was wearing pajama pants and a tee shirt during the evening hours which was also atypical attire for the time of night and distance from his residence in Great Mills, MD (approximately 45 minutes).  I returned to my patrol vehicle and issued Kyles a warning for the speeding violation. I returned to the vehicle to gather more information and inquire on the mental health status of Kyles. I discussed his current military assignment and checked with Kyles to see if he was feeling ok. Kyles advised he just got out of a three-year relationship approximately one week ago. I continued speaking with Kyles, and he displayed visible signs of mental distress with by leaning forward in his seat with his head leaned forward into his hand. Kyles was asked if he was having any suicidal thoughts, and initially he was evasive and did not provide a direct answer other than stating that he would be ok. Kyles stated that he had been suicidal in the last week due to his relationship issues, but was not currently having suicidal thoughts. I explained my concerns to Kyles and the ability to receive help at a hospital, and Kyles advised that he was intending on going to a military medical unit the next day. Based on my training and experience gained through Crisis Intervention Training (CIT), I recognized his overall demeanor, evasive answering and admissions of recent thoughts as concern for his well-being. I also recognized the enhanced risk of military suicide and was concerned that he may act on recent thoughts if not provided with mental health services.  I continued to speak with Kyles out of the vehicle and requested for Kyles to contact someone in his military chain of command to notify and ascertain if they wanted to handle the mental health screening through the military or civilian hospital. Kyles contacted Chief Tukes and I advised him of the situation.After speaking further with Kyles and Chief Tukes, Kyles agreed to allow me to transport him to Charles Regional Medical Center to be admitted for a Voluntary Emergency Petition. I secured Kyles vehicle on the shoulder and transported him to CRMC. I waited with Kyles in the hospital room until Chief Kyles arrived at approximately 2345 to sit with him until the evaluation was completed.  Case Closed, non-criminal.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6372</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 15:53:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6372</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 16:40:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Howard</LastName>
            <FirstName>Travis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6842</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Esh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5635</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Meurrens</LastName>
            <FirstName>Blake</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6372</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6372</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 16:38:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/25/2023 17:20:13</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388740</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Kyles</LastName>
               <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kean</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/15/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/25/2023 16:38:17</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Kyles</LastName>
               <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kean</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/15/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>K420</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>P400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/25/2023 16:38:17</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>45511</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Westmeath</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>UNIT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>D11</SubNumber>
               <City>Great Mills</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20634</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3476</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.502077</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.287996</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>747</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>251</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8580</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6372</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/25/2023 16:38:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>