<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-014503</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40L</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/24/2023 10:18:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/24/2023 10:18:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/21/2023 23:10:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/21/2023 23:10:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Bones located in a wooded area determined to be Whitetail Deer.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 10:18:54</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1897</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/01/2023 13:14:17</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>OTH</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>12750 Naves Cross Road, NE, Cumberland MD 21502</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>691779</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 10:18:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/01/2023 13:05:50</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>691779</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Naves</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>XRDS</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>PARK AND RIDE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/24/2023 10:18:50</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/24/2023 10:18:50</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>Y</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40L</SuppAgencyCode>
      <DsIcrDate>05/01/2023 13:12:39</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 10:18:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP1897</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/01/2023 13:14:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>   On April 21, 2023, I was contacted by Sgt. Bryan Willetts, the Allegany County Combined Criminal Investigative Unit (C3I) Administrative Supervisor. Willetts informed me of a Cumberland Barracks case that his unit was assisting with. Willetts advised that a local family was participating in a Geo Treasure Hunt which led them to a wooded area off of Naves Crossroad near a park-and-ride when they located two bones. The family had taken photographs of the bones, which appeared to be vertebrae and a femur. Upon inspection of the photographs, it was unsure to investigators if the bones could be human remains. Sgt. Willetts stated that he and other investigators were currently attempting access to the area where the bones were located, but were having difficulties due to the growth of brush. Sgt. Willetts determine that the search for the remains would have to be conducted another time with coordination with the State Highway Administration for the use of equipment to clear a path.      On April 24, 2023, I et with Sgt. Willetts and discussed this case further. He provided me with a copy of a report authored by Detective Mazzone that details the discovery of the bones and the prior efforts made to recover them. The report reads as follows:     On 04/21/2023, at 2230 hours, I was contacted by C3I Administrative Sergeant Bryan Willetts to respond to the Park-And-Ride on Naves Crossroads for possible human bones located in the wooded area. Upon arrival, I met with Sgt Willetts and County Investigator Jon Dudiak, along with Troopers from the Maryland State Police. With Troopers were Jake Snurr and Gracie Smith. Both advised they were with Snurrs mother and friends doing a Geo Treasure Hunt and looking for an old headstone located in the area. After going through the brush, they located the headstone for Jacob Hoblitzell, who died in 1830. Near the headstone were two bones which they took photographs of. When they returned home, Snurr showed the photographs to his father, who thought the bones were suspicious and wished to report it to police. Snurr displayed the photographs, which appeared to be a vertebra and a leg bone, but could not determine if the bones were human or animal just from the photos. Snurr and Smith showed us the general area where the bones were located and displayed the Geo Treasure Hunt map, which showed the location of the headstone. The location was almost directly in the middle between Interstate-68 westbound and Naves Crossroads. Both advised the brush and trees in this area were extremely difficult to navigate through and took several hours to enter and exit the area. Snurr then provided his phone so I could monitor the GPS. Sgt Willetts, Invest. Dudiak, and I then attempted to enter the brush, but after an hour of searching, we had too much difficulty navigating through the extremely thick brush in the dark. At several points, we were no longer able to advance and had to try other areas for access. At one point, Invest. Dudiak was approximately 10-15 yards from me and I could not see his flashlight. Due to the complexity of the search, darkness, and logistics, we exited the brush and decided that the area would be extremely difficult for anyone else to attempt to access until daylight. Plans for other resources to help clear out the brush for better access will be made as soon as possible. Snurr provided copies of his photographs and I took a photograph of the GPS location of the headstone. A Google search of Jacob Hoblitzell Allegany County Maryland revealed a link to www.waymarking.com, where I observed the Hoblitzell Family Cemetery, with a GPS location of N 39 40.447 W 078 43.740 After entering the GPS into Google Maps, I observed the same area where the headstone was located. The description read, This was located thanks to the Geocache (visit link). We found it hard to navigate through the brush to locate the stones. We only noticed one standing stone, Jacob Hoblitzell. After some searching and kicking dirt off we found about eight pieces of headstones. All were very hard to read. Some had small script engraving. A family plot that has had the access cut off by the Interstate and ramps. Photographs were attached to the website.     After speaking with Sgt. Willetts, I made telephone contact with Joan an investigator at the Office of Chief Medical Examiners Office (OCME). I explained the situation to Joan and asked if they could be of assistance and view the photographs. I was advised that a Forensic Anthropologist could view the photographs and make a determination of the origins of the bone.     Several minutes later, Joan called me back from the OCME Office. Joan advised that Dr. Rodriquez the Forensic Anthropologist viewed the photographs and determined the bone to be of a Whitetail Deer.    Sgt. Willetts was made aware of the determination and this case was closed. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP2841</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/01/2023 12:37:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP2841</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/01/2023 13:02:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lechliter</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2387</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>King</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2549</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Doll</LastName>
            <FirstName>Henry</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0870</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brinkman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5328</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40L</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Knight</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1897</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40L</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schramm</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2841</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>