<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000675</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/06/2023 13:59:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/06/2023 13:59:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/06/2023 13:19:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/06/2023 13:19:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/06/2023 13:59:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6505</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/27/2023 12:06:13</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>W/B I-70 P/T MD RT 85 (BUCKEYSTOWN PIKE)</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>679549</AddressId>
      <City>MDC151</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/06/2023 13:59:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 18:22:09</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>679549</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>54</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I70 Wb</StreetName>
         <City>Frederick</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.41794</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.39805</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/06/2023 13:59:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/06/2023 13:59:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/27/2023 12:06:17</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/06/2023 13:59:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP marked vehicle TIM6 is equipped with a mobile recording device   My Axon Body worn camera was also operational and recording during this incident   ACRS: 23MSP000675  Defendant: Tyler Christian Miller Scuderi Date of Birth: 10/29/1996 Date of Arrest: 01/06/2023 Times of Arrest: 1359 Hours Frederick Barrack  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING  * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.   *Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Recognition through Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration   *EC/IR II IntoximeterOperator certified through the Maryland State Police and the Maryland State Toxicologist Office   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)   On 01/06/2023 at approximately 1321 hours, I (Master/Tpr J Ekani #5038) was on duty operating my marked MSP vehicle TIM6 when Maryland State Police dispatched me to respond to an overturned multi vehicle collision W/B I-70 P/T MD RT 85 (Buckeystown Pike) in Frederick County Maryland.   Upon my arrival, I contacted was contacted by an off duty Prince Georges County Police Officer who observed the driver of the overturned vehicle make multiple attempts to get back in to the vehicle. I approached the scene and observed multiple vehicles on the right shoulder and a red Mazda 3, bearing Maryland registration 9EJ2029, overturned on its roof blocking lane #4. The temperature was 45 degrees at the time of this incident.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I contacted a Caucasian male who was receiving medical attention on an ambulance. Upon entering the ambulance, I smelled a potent and strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on board. I contact the individual of receiving medical attention and I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath as he spoke. I observed his blue eyes to be glassy and bloodshot with a glazed look and the drivers speech was slurred. The driver was identified by his State of Maryland drivers license as Tyler Christian MillerScuderi (Caucasian/M/DOB 10/29/1996).    Scuderi was checked out by the Frederick County Fire Department (FCFD) and heREFUSEDmedical treatment. I asked Scuderi how much alcohol he had to drink and he advised 2 beers. He further advised that his boss supplied the beer he was drinking at work a work function. I asked Scuderi what he was drinking and he stated Rollin rock and Blue Moon beer. Scuderi was dressed for the weather I informed Scuderi that I wanted him to perform field sobriety tests, to which he consented.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed on the asphalt on I-70. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions were optimal due to the daylight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Scuderi appeared to be in good physical condition.  I asked Scuderi the following questions: Injuries-Scuderi stated he hit his head in the accident and had dry blood on his right hand Medication  None Medical Conditions  None Glasses- No Contact Lenses- Scuderi was wearing contact lenses   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Scuderis blue eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Scuderis pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. He was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Scuderi if he understood the instructions and he stated yes.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3.) The onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes   Vertical Gaze Nystagmus (VGN) was NOT present  WALK AND TURN (1/8)  Prior to Scuderi performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Scuderi was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Scuderi was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Scuderi was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Scuderi was told to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, Scuderi was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Scuderi was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Scuderi was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Scuderi if he understood the test and he stated, Yes.  Instructional Stage: 1.) Lost balance  Nothing to report 2.) Starts too soon- Nothing to report  Walking Stage (1st Nine):  Nothing to report   Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  Nothing to report  Turn: 1.) He did not turn as instructed. Scuderi executed a military style about face movement.  ONE LEG STAND (0/4)  Prior to Scuderiperforming the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Scuderi was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and I demonstrated the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his foot was raised he was to keep his leg straight, and look at his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Scuderiif he understood the test and he stated yes. Scuderi used his right leg for the One Leg Stand test.  Instructional Stage:   Scuderiwas offered a preliminary breath test which indicated a .28BrAC  ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Scuderiwas driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his body. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot with a gazed look. * Reckless vehicle operation (Accident) * Stating he was coming from a work party where he consumed alcoholic beverages * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath. * My observed signs of impairment as he performed sobriety tests.  I arrested Scuderi for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 1359 hours, and he was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Maryland State Police Frederick Barrack for processing. Once inside my vehicle, the strong and overwhelming odor of an alcoholic beverage filled the interior with my vehicle as I transported Scuderi to the Barrack. At the Barrack, I advised Scuderi of his MVA DR-15 Advice of Rights. Scuderi AGREED to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the DR-15 indicating the same at approximately 1437 hours.Sgt Hill administered the intoximeter test and the specimen was collected at 1511 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT:  ***.09 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath***  Scuderi was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released his friend from the barrack.  All events occurred in Frederick County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5038</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 18:22:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5038</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/27/2023 09:28:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Holland</LastName>
            <FirstName>Marcus</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6059</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ekani</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5038</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sorenson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6505</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ekani</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5038</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ekani</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5038</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490052</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/06/2023 13:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>N/A</Remarks>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5038</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 18:11:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5038</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 18:15:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490052</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/06/2023 13:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>N/A</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5038</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 18:11:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5038</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 18:17:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490052</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/06/2023 13:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>N/A</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5038</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 18:11:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5038</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 18:16:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490052</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/06/2023 13:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>N/A</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5038</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 18:11:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5038</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 18:16:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5038</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 18:11:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:15</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>145098</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Scuderi</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christian Miller</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/29/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/30/2017 05:10:46</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S360</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T460</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Scuderi</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christian Miller</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/29/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S360</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T460</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/30/2017 05:10:46</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1049</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Long Corner</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Mount Airy</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21771</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.143843</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.339578</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>732</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9430</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/30/2017 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5038</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 18:19:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5038</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 18:19:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5038</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 18:19:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5038</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 18:11:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5038</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 18:11:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148299</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5038</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 18:11:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5038</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 18:11:22</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3MZBN1W30JM187494</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2018</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MAZD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>RED</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>RED</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9EJ2029</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>