<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009898</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/19/2023 02:01:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/19/2023 02:01:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/19/2023 01:38:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/19/2023 01:38:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>-Conducted a traffic stop on the above vehicle due to failing to maintain a single lane.-While making contact with the female operator, I immediately observed signs of impairment.-The operator was placed through SFST'S, ending with DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 02:01:49</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4783</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/29/2023 14:41:08</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>687781</AddressId>
      <City>MDC302</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 02:01:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 23:18:23</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>687781</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>25618</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Garrett</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Mc Henry</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-79.370355</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.571384</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/19/2023 02:01:45</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/19/2023 02:01:45</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/29/2023 14:40:22</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 02:01:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:15</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Marked Unit W-13 is NOT equipped with a camera. Axon Body Camera footage was recorded.  Case # 23-MSP-009898 Defendant: Stephanie Elizabeth Siix Date of Birth: 03/03/1994 Date of Arrest: 03/19/2023 Time of Arrest: 0156 Hours DUI#: 23-015   CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING:  *I am trained to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside ImpairedDrivingEnforcement (ARIDE) training in May of 2021. *I am trained and certified to conduct preliminary breathalyzer tests by the Maryland State Police.    Phase #1 - Vehicle in Motion On Sunday, March 19th, 2023 at approximately 0138 hours, I, TFC Kline (#7112), currently assigned to the Maryland State Police McHenry Barrack was on patrol, operating marked patrol vehicle W-13, in the area of Garrett Highway (US 219) and Pinewood Drive, McHenry, Garrett County, Maryland 21541. At that time, I observed a white Subaru Legacy failing to maintain a single lane, while traveling northbound on US 219, in lane 1. While following the white Subaru Legacy, I observed that vehicle swerve back and forth from lane 1 to lane 2, on 4 separate occasions. More than a tires width was observed crossing the white dotted marker line as the vehicle crossed from lane 1 to lane 2 on each occasion. A turn signal was not utilized while traveling back and forth each lane. As the white Subaru Legacy continued northbound, that vehicle was observed braking excessively. No other vehicles and/or traffic caused the white Subaru Legacy to travel in that manner. I activated my emergency equipment to initiate a traffic stop on the white Subaru Legacy, which the vehicle came to a complete stop on the right shoulder of the roadway, in the area of US 219 and Friendsville Road.I then advised the McHenry Barrack of the traffic stop via radio, and identified the suspects vehicle as a 2006 Subaru Legacy displaying a Maryland registration 35U975 and noted that it was occupied one time.    Phase #2 - Personal Contact Upon initial contact with the operator, I immediately detected an overwhelming odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from inside the vehicle. I then introduced myself and the reasoning for the traffic stop, noting, she was failing to maintain a single lane while traveling north on US 219. The female operators eyes were observed bloodshot and glassy while speaking with her. I immediately asked the female operator if she was ok, which she advised that she was fine. I asked the female operator if I could see her drivers license, however, she stated, I had an inconvenience earlier this evening, and advised she did not have her license on her. At this time, the females movements were observed as slow and lethargic and her voice slurred at times while she was speaking. I asked her again if she was ok, which she advised she wasnt necessarily ok, but she is ok as of right now. The female did advise she is the registered owner of the vehicle, which I was then able to identify her as Stephanie ElizabethSiix (W/F, DOB: 03/03/1994). I then advised Siix how much alcohol she had consumed prior to driving. Siix advised about 3 1/2 hours ago was when her incident happened. Siix then stated she had consumed 2 beers around 3 1/2 hours ago. Siix provided little to no information regarding the incident she had dealt with around 3 1/2 hours prior to the stop.I requested for Siix to exit her vehicle for voluntary standardized field sobriety tests, which she consented to. While speaking with Siix in front of her vehicle, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage not only emanating from her person, but also from her breath. Her eyes were bloodshot and glassy at that time. While she was speaking, she continued to slur her words at times. Siix then advised she was placed through this same test by the Frostburg Police Department around an hour and half ago. I asked Siix if she had consumed any alcoholic beverages after she was stopped by the Frostburg Police Department, which she advised she had not. I then reiterated that she was stopped by Frostburg earlier and that she was placed through a Standardized Field Sobriety Test, which she advised that she was and that the results were fine. I could tell Siix was hiding something based on her demeanor towards me. Siix then advised she has to be in Accident, Maryland in 10 minutes, due to her meeting her boss named Brenda. Siix advised she is going on vacation with her boss to Memphis and does not want to be late.  While investigating the nature of incident that occurred between Siix and the Frostburg Police Department earlier, it was later revealed that Siix was placed under arrest for suspicion of driving under the influence of alcohol by Sergeant Curry (7764) at approximately 2122 hours on 03/18/2023. The case number for that incident is as follows: (#F2023-01645).   Phase #3 - Pre-Arrest Screening  The tests were conducted on the right shoulder of the roadway, in the area of northbound US 219 and Friendsville Road. The surface was dry, level, and free from obvious debris. Siix displayed no visible injuries. The front facing emergency lights of all patrol vehicles were deactivated during all phases of testing.   I asked Siix the following questions:  Daily/Regular Medications  YES. Thyroid, Anti-Seizure, Lexapro, Adderall, Aripiprazole, Hydroxyzine Medication. Glasses - NONE. Contacts - NONE. Injuries  Siix advised she had a seizure on 03/18/2023 and fell down the stairs.   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS TEST (6/6 clues displayed) I used my pen as a stimulus and held it approximately 12 to 15 inches from Siix eyes. Her eyes displayed no resting nystagmus and her pupils were equal in size. Her eyes also showed equal tracking. Siix advised to stand with her feet together and her hands down at her sides during the instruction/demonstration and throughout the test. I asked Siix if she could see the tip of my stimulus, and she stated that she could. I observed her eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. Siix was instructed to follow the stimulus with her eyes only, keeping her head still. After stating that she understood the instructions, Siix attempted the test with the following results:  1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes. 2. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes. 3. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 degrees - Present in both eyes.   WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues displayed) Prior to Siix performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test is conducted. Siix was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel-to-toe. Siix was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Siix was instructed to take a series of nine (9) heel-to-toe steps in a straight line. Siix was advised to keep her hands flat at her side, keep her eyes focused on her feet and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, it was explained and demonstrated, to keep her lead foot on the line, to take a series of small steps around, and to completely turn around 180 degrees. It was explained and demonstrated to Siix that a second series of nine (9) heel-to-toe steps were to be performed, identical to the first series. I instructed Siix, that once the test begins to continue until instructed to stop. I then reminded Siix to place her hands down by her sides, look down at her feet, and to count each step aloud. I asked Siix if she understood the test, she confirmed that she understood.  Instructional Stage -Stepped out the instructional stage due to not able to keep balance (Siix stepped off the line when told to keep her left and right foot heel-to-toe and stood in a normal manner). -Siix attempted the test early by starting to walk. Siix was asked to stop and wait until I advised for her to begin.  Walking Stage (1st Nine Steps) -Missed heel-to-toe on steps 4-9. -Siix did keep her hands flat to her sides, however, her hands were inside her jean pants pockets for the duration of the test.  The Turn -Not completed properly, Siix took multiple steps with both feet to turn around.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine Steps) -Missed heel-to-toe on all steps. -Siix did keep her hands flat to her sides, however, her hands were inside her jean pants pockets for the duration of the test.    ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues displayed) Siix was instructed to stand with her feet together and her hands flat to her sides while the test instructions and demonstration were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground in front of her approximately 6 inches, keeping her legs straight and her toes pointed out in front of her parallel to the ground. While her leg was raised, she was to count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand two, one thousand three...) and to continue counting until told to stop. After demonstrating the test, Siix advised she understood. Siix was advised to begin the test. At that time, Siix raised her right foot off the ground to begin the test.  Balancing and Counting Stage  0-10 Seconds: -Hopped from side to side. -Siix placed her right foot back onto the surface.  10-20 Seconds: -Siix placed her right foot back onto the surface.  20-30 Seconds: -Hopped from side to side. -Siix placed her right foot back onto the surface.   While roadside, I asked Siix again how much alcohol she had consumed, which she advised she had 2 Miller Lights around 2-3 hours ago. I then asked her if she would submit to a Preliminary Breath Test roadside, which she consented to take. The results are as follows: .12  Siix was placed under arrest forDUI/DWI at approximately 0156 hours. I then placed Siix in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. At that time, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage that was not present prior to placing Siix inside my patrol vehicle.   ARREST: Based on the following, I had reason to believe Siix wasdrivinga motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol. -Glassy, bloodshot eyes. -Slurred Speech. -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. -HGN: 6/6 clues displayed. -Walk and Turn: 4/8 clues displayed. -One Leg Stand: 2/4 clues displayed. -Admitted to consuming alcoholic beverages prior todriving. -Failing to maintain a single lane. -Negligentdriving. -Preliminary Breath Test: .12 -Opened alcoholic beverage located inside of vehicle (Mixed drink).   20 Minute Observation Period While at the Maryland State Police McHenry Barrack W, Siix was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, so she could follow along as the DR-15 Advice of Rights audio was played out loud in English. The English version audio can be found onmva.maryland.gov. Siix signed the DR-15 at approximately 0217 hours acknowledging her consent to take the test. Corporal Davis (#5223), a certified Intoximeter technician, instructed the test for Siix. Siix breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of.14 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. Siix was issued all pertinent documentations regarding the incident. While speaking with Siix at the barrack, Siix advised she was involved in a motor vehicle collision in Frostburg, Maryland earlier in the night. Siix then advised the police showed up and placed her through a Standardized Field Sobritety Test. Siix advised she failed the test, and they transported her to jail. Siix advised she was released and traveled to Garrett County to hang out with friends. Siix advised she did drink alcohol with friends at a local bar called Black Bear. Siix was very apologetic for her actions this evening. Siix advised she works at Brendas pizza in Oakland, Maryland, and she advised she is doing everything she can to be a good person. Siix was released at approximately 0251 hours from the Maryland State Police McHenry Barrack.  All events occurred in Garrett County, Maryland.  I request this case to be closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:44:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7112</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/29/2023 14:10:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Poland</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kurt</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7213</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bittinger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Blair</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0199</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sigmund</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4783</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kline</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7112</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499298</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7112</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499298</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7112</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499298</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7112</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499298</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7112</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499298</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7112</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499298</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>12630</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 01:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>12630</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7112</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>C</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:27:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:26</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372009</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Siix</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stephanie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elizabeth</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/03/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 23:26:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Siix</LastName>
               <FirstName>Stephanie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Elizabeth</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/03/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 23:26:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetName>12413 Bowling Street</StreetName>
               <City>Cresaptown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21502</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:43:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:43:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:43:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:43:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7112</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 23:32:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151059</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7112</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 23:20:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7112</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 23:20:55</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2006</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>SUBA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>LEG</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>35U975</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>