<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009923</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/19/2023 07:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/19/2023 07:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/19/2023 05:56:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/19/2023 05:56:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI / DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 07:08:28</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/16/2023 10:40:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OLD WASHINGTON RD/ HOODS MILL RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>547954</AddressId>
      <City>MDC589</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 07:08:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 12:55:26</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>547954</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Old Washington</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Woodbine</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-77.017423</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.361403</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>7501-7638 OLD WASHINGTON RD / 340-532 HOODS MILL RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>7513-7641 OLD WASHINGTON RD / 115-538 HOODS MILL RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>7501-7638 OLD WASHINGTON RD / 611-611 HOODS MILL RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 OLD WASHINGTON RD / 400-599 HOODS MILL RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/19/2023 07:08:25</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/19/2023 07:08:25</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/13/2023 09:55:22</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 07:08:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:27</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>THIS INCIDENT WAS AUDIBLY AND VISUALLY RECORDED  Defendant: Yasheeda Kaylia Seville  Date of Birth: 08/29/1991  Date of Arrest: 03/19/2023  Time of Arrest: 0705  MD License #: S140947461673  Westminster DUI #: 23-045  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES      Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, July 2019.      Certified to administer Preliminary Breath Test, July 2019         Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement through the Baltimore County Police Department, February 2021      Graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute, August 2021.      Completed Cannabis Impairment Detection Workshop training through the Maryland State Police, September 2021.      Drug Recognition Expert, December 2022.     VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On March 19, 2023, at approximately 0556 hours, I, Trooper First Class Mills #6784, currently assigned to the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack, was operating marked Maryland State Police vehicle G-31 when I was dispatched to Old Washington Road at Hoods Mill Road, Woodbine, Carroll County, Maryland, in attempt to locate a vehicle disabled in the roadway which had no tags displayed.  At approximately 0632, I located the disabled vehicle and observed a marked Maryland State Police vehicle, A-13, parked behind it with the rear emergency equipment activated to warn approaching motorists of the traffic hazard. I then positioned my patrol vehicle directly behind the marked patrol vehicle and activated my rear emergency equipment to assist with traffic control. After I placed my patrol vehicles transmission in park, I exited and approached the disabled vehicle.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the drivers side of the gray Nissan Pathfinder bearing temporary Georgia registration S1423629. I made contact with the female operator of the vehicle, who was sitting in the drivers seat. I also contacted Senior Trooper Allen #5820 who was in uniform and already at the drivers door speaking with the female (See S/T Allens attached supplement report for his observations). I checked on the drivers welfare and immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from within the vehicle. I also noted that there was damage to the front left fender and that the rear glass windshield was shattered.  I asked the driver how she was, and she responded, Good. I asked the female what happened to inquire why her vehicle was stopped in the roadway, and she stated, So the um, well, I was coming from Baltimore. I was going to go toto ato another spot, and he told me that I had my tail light out. I was transitioning from Atlanta to Baltimore. He was like your tail light is out. You cant drive like that. So I, I was like forget it, I was just going to drive straight home. So I didnt stop at where I was originally was going to stop. So I was going home, and you guys stopped me. And thats the paperwork I have here today (turning to her right, facing the passenger seat). So Long story short, was my original stop that has my tail light out isI was on Milford Mill Road in Pikesville. Milford Mill Road, and Pike 21208. I was making a R Left turn And I was stopping to make my left turn, and he stopped me. Instead of him stopping, he then stopped and hit me and drove around me and kept going. While speaking with the female, I observed glassy and bloodshot eyes. Her movements and speech were slow. I confirmed that the vehicle collision happened in Baltimore, and the female stated, Yes, this happened in Baltimore, Maryland. So he didnt stop. There was no cameras there. Called the police, and they were like they are no cameras on this road. So I was like, alright forget it. I submitted my papers, which I have here today. I submitted my papers, and they were just like, well, its on me because. I then confirmed that it happened the current day in Baltimore, and she replied, No, no, not today. Not today. Uh, it happened onmaybe a week ago? I asked the female if the rear glass was broken and the damage to the front left fender was caused a week ago, and the female paused and stated, Yes, fromfrom the accident. They took pictures, and I submitted everything to Baltimore County. Yes, sir. Due to the vehicle being disabled in the roadway, I asked her if she wanted a tow truck, and she replied, No, so today I just stopped like 30 minutes ago. He told me (incomprehensible) my tail light, he was like no you cant drive it Park. So thats what I was heading home to donow. Due to her statement not making sense of driving to park the vehicle, I asked her why she was driving the vehicle. She stated, Thats what he told me. I have my papers right here. This is what he just stopped me. Thirty minutes (30) minutes ago. And I wrote everything downand everything. And I told him everything that just happened was a week ago, and he was like all right. Well, with the incident, he said, Was you transitioning from Atlanta to Baltimore, me too. I requested to see the paperwork that she claimed to have and she displayed a 8.5 by 11 inch piece of white paper folded in half and stated,  this is everything he wrote down for me. And this is everything he told me I needed to file. Due to the text on the document being handwritten, I asked the female if it was written by a police officer, and she stated, No, it was a police officer. I advised the driver the paper she had was not an official document, and she stated, No, this is what he wrote down there I was like a random piece of paper need to file. And this is what he said that(the driver did not finish her sentence). I asked the driver where the paperwork was for the light that was out, and she stated, He just said it was a warning. I advised the driver she would have received a piece of paperwork for the light being out, and she stated, Im gonna be honest, Ive never been pulled over before (the drivers speech was slurred) Im just telling you what he told me. He, I wrote down everything he told me, this was that. The driver showed me a piece of paper with writing on it to me. I attempted to confirm with the driver that she had not been pulled over before, and she stated, I was pulled over today. Yes, sir. about 30 minutes ago. I asked the driver to step out of the vehicle and walk to the front of her vehicle; the driver stated, Yes, sir.  I requested her drivers license, and she stated, Of course. (incoherent). As the driver was looking for her drivers license, she stated, He didnt give it back. I explained the other trooper on the scene had her identification with him, and she stated, Yeah, yeah, I gave it to him. This is my ID. The driver was identified by her Maryland drivers license as Yasheeda Kaylia Seville (08/29/1991 B/F.) I asked the driver where she was coming from if she was coming from Baltimore, and she stated, Yes, sir. So I went to a baby shower. I asked what time that was, and she said, Uh, maybe eight or nine? And then he took. He pulled me over, so. I was going home, so I never stopped at the, I never stopped at the baby shower, basically cause he said that my tail light was out, so he said I was not in compliance. So he said I had to go home, so what I did was I rerouted. Ill show you my GPS; hold on. So I rerouted myself in my GPS, so I didnt stop, so to, to get home. I asked Seville if she stopped anywhere, and she stated, Yes, sir. I asked the driver where she stopped, and she stated, I didnt stop; I was trying to stop at, they said it was... (Seville never finished her sentence.). I asked Seville to confirm her trip, that the baby shower was at eight oclock in the evening, and she made a round trip, and it was now almost six thirty the next morning. Seville stated, Yeah, so what he told, I was trying to make the stop toooo, hold on. Yeah, I was trying to, oh, hold on. I was trying to go here. (Seville pulled up the GPS on her cell phone and pointed to an address) but when I. I confirmed the address with Seville, 8644 Washington Boulevard, and she stated, Yes, so that was the venue. Yes, that was the venue for the shower and the gender reveal so, when he pulled my tail light, he said no, this is not in compliance, you, you cannot be on the road like this, so Im trying to I was rerouted trying to go home now because he said you cant be compliant like this and everything else. I asked Seville to exit her vehicle, to which she complied, stating, Yes, sir.  I attempted to confirm with Seville that she was trying to get home and asked why she was parked in the roadway, and she stated, Yeah, my battery went out on me. I asked Seville to walk to the front of her vehicle, and she stated, Yes, sir.  I informed Seville that I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage, and she interrupted me, stating, I did have wine earlier on today at last officer; I talk to him, I told him the same thing. Um, about nine or 8 PM, I did have wine I had to teleport, and I told him the same thing, and he said that again you need to go home, but my back light was out, and it wasnt in compliance with the Maryland state because I had temporary tags Im telling you everything he told me, I had temporary tags, and I wasnt in compliance. I asked Seville if she knew the officers name, and she stated, No sir, I cant remember Im a liar if I said it, but I did get I might have paperwork I dont, he, he handed me everything that I just gave you he handed it back to me, and I wrote everything down, he told me everything to write down. He was like you cant go to, my second base where I was supposed to go to for my gender reveal, is, was my goal, but he said I couldnt, I, he said dont do that and he and I wrote that down thats what I gave you earlier. I confirmed with Seville that she had wine earlier, and she stated, Yeah, I had teleport wine, I did tell him that, and he was like, he told me, he pulled me out the car drove me around the car, he said that my tail light which is on my pas, my drivers passenger side he talked me through that, he asked me what happened, and I told him about that I was on Milford Mill Road, and I was turning into my mothers driveway, and someone hit me, and I was in a dispute with that with my current (Seville did not finish her sentence). I asked Seville if she was on any medication, and she stated, No, sir.  A check through the Maryland Department of Motor Vehicles revealed that Sevilles license was valid. She had no open warrants. A further check of the vehicle revealed that the registration of the vehicle was expired.  As I communicated with Seville outside of the vehicle, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person.  I asked Seville to perform standardized field sobriety tests (a battery of tests developed by the National Highway Transportation Safety Administration (NHTSA) used to determine impairment by alcohol or drugs), to confirm that she was okay to drive, and she agreed, stating, Of course. Yeah yeah yeah, I understand.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed in lane one of Old Washington Road north of the Carroll County line, Woodbine, Carroll County, Maryland, in front of the suspects vehicle in accordance with Maryland State Police Operations Directive 04.01(D)(3)(b). The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and natural sunlight. Seville appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. Prior to beginning the test, I ensured that the front emergency lights remained off to prevent optokinetic nystagmus.  I asked Seville the following questions:  Glasses or Contacts  Seville advised, I do wear glasses. I asked Seville if she needed her glasses to see me, and she stated, No. I asked Seville if she needed her glasses to drive, and she stated, Not permanent, I wear them, but I dont need them to have to drive, if that makes sense. I asked if she wore reading glasses, and she stated, Yeah yeah yeah, like reading glasses, like I would say computer because if Im computering for a long period of time, I need them.  Medical Conditions  None  Injuries  None  Medication  None  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus. It was held approximately 12-15 inches from Sevilles eyes, slightly above her eye level. Seville was instructed to look straight ahead, keep her head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with her eyes. Seville was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. Sevilles pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking.      Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes      Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes      Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes     As the test began, Seville started to keep her eyes on the light from my flashlight; I repeated the instruction to follow the stimulus, my pen, and Seville stated, Not the light, the pen. Gotchu. Prior to checking for vertical nystagmus, I informed Seville she was doing well and that this process takes time, and she stated, Yeah, no, I know, you gotta do your job, its Yeah, I know. I informed Seville the stimulus would be moving straight up this time, and she interrupted me and stated, Okay sir, I gotchu. As I finished my explanation, Seville stated, Yes sir. I asked Seville if she understood my instructions, and she stated, Yes sir. I reminded Seville to keep her head still, and she stated, Okay sir.  RESTING NYSTAGMUS NOT PRESENT. VERTICAL NYSTAGMUS NOT PRESENT.  As I was taking notes after the test, Seville stated, Im, Im anemic as hell, so. I advised Seville there were two (2) more tests to go through and asked if she would be okay to go through them; Seville stated,  I am anemic. Im extremely anemic. I just I just been through this with the last officer, so Im confused as to why Im doing this again because he, I went through this he asked me how much if I drank or whatever else, and I said no, I had a cup of wine I had to teleport for, and I told him that. I asked Seville if she had done all these tests, and she stated, Yeah, I said my last officer, I said I said, I had to teleport, and he said because of my my headlight he said you cant be on the road with this car. I explained that I could not make any exceptions, and she said, I understand, Im just saying, Im just saying, youre right. Yeah, I understand, Im just saying, Im just anemic.  WALK AND TURN (7/8 clues observed)  The test was explained and demonstrated. Seville was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe on the solid white fog line on the right side of the road. I explained I needed her to listen to the instructions, place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe on the solid white fog line. Seville followed the instruction and stated, Oh, sorry, like this? Im so clumsy. Seville was then instructed to place her hands flat at her sides, and she stated, Im so cold, Im just anemic so... and remain in that position until told to begin. Seville was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Seville then began to walk, taking two (2) steps, and stated, So like this, like this til you instruct me too? Im just asking. I explained to Seville that I would demonstrate the test for her after I finished my instructions. I instructed Seville to place her feet back in the instructional position, and she stated, Um, all confused, what? Like this til you instructed me to? Seville was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, she was instructed to keep her lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Seville was instructed to complete the second series of nine (9) steps in the same heel-to-toe fashion. Seville was instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and count every step aloud, Seville interrupted my instructions again, and stated, So walk forward and walk back, is what you want me to do? I informed Seville she was correct and that I would answer her questions when I finished the instructions. Seville was instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and count every step aloud, and once she began the test, she was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Seville if she understood the test, and she confirmed that she did and that she did not have any questions, stating, No, Im just freezing, haha, I just did this; this is so.  Instructional Stage:      Could not maintain balance. Just before beginning the test, I instructed Seville to put her feet back in the starting position, with her heel touching her toe, she moved her feet, and asked, Thats how we do it? I again instructed Seville to place her hands down by her side, and she grabbed her jacket, stating, No use trying to zip my jacket up. Im just cold. I informed Seville she was making the process more difficult for herself, and she stated, Im just freezing, Im jus sorry. Not intentally. I inform Seville her feet were not in the starting position, again, and she stated, Alright, show me one more time. I instructed Seville to start with her heel touching her toe, and she stated, thats impossible Im just so cold.      Started too soon. Seville began the test too soon and stated, Oh, sorry, I didnt know what you wanted me to do, sorry sir.     Walking Stage (1st Nine)      Missed heel to toe on steps 2, 5, 6, 8, 9, and 10      Stopped while walking      Incorrect number of steps taken, taking thirteen (13) steps      Began using her arms for balance on step 5     While walking, Seville stated, Let me know when you want me to turn around. Seville then stopped walking, and stated, Turn around or no? I asked Seville if she was completed the test, and she advised, I dont, I really, I didnt count. You said nine and then turn around? I instructed Seville to complete the test as instructed. Seville then took one additional step, and she stated, OK, so do that.  Turn: Seville completed the turn unsatisfactorily, and stated, Turn around.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine)  As Seville began the second series of nine steps, she stated, Im freezing.      Missed heel to toe on all fourteen (14) steps      Incorrect number of steps taken, fourteen (14) steps      Used arms for balance on all fourteen steps.     As Seville was walking, she stated, Said turn around.  On step eleven (11), Seville began counting out loud, stating, Seven, eight, nine. Seville then attempted to turn around, turning to the right. When doing so, Seville lost her balance and nearly fell over, taking a step to the left with her right foot to maintain her balance, and stated, Oh, Im so cold, Im just so freezing. Nah, Im OK, Im OK. Im just cold. The other trooper and I went to assist her to keep her from falling to the ground. Seville continued to state, Yeah yeah yeah, Im good Im just so cold Im ane. Im already anemic. Yeah, Im anemic really bad. Im already anemic, really, really bad. And I just did this. Its like repetitive. He told me about my tail light, and he told me where to go to the center and everything. Im so freezing. Its like repetitive. Cause he told me he was like, if I get pulled over again, just show my card, and I know I have to go to the center; within, he said I had a week, to do it cause he said if I dont fix it, if I dont fix the repair. in a week, he said, then I would be penalized.  ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)  The test was explained and demonstrated. Seville was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, watch the raised foot, and count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, etc.), Seville then began counting out loud, stating, One thousand-one, one thousand-two, one thousand-three, k. I continued with my instructions and informed Seville she would count in that fashion until told to stop, and not put her foot down until the end of the test. I asked Seville if she had any questions about the instructions for the test, and she stated, So you want me to be like this? (Seville lifted her right foot off the ground and began counting) one thousand-one, one thousand-two, one thousand-three until Im comfortable? (Seville then put her foot down). I informed Seville she was correct in her demonstration, and that she would continue to count until told to stop. I asked Seville if she understood the test, and she confirmed that she did. Seville stated, Imma try; Im anemic.  Instructional Stage:  I asked Seville which foot she wanted to raise, and she stated, I think Ill do Ill do this, Ill, it doesnt matter (Seville then mumbled incoherently). I advised Seville the choice was hers, and she stated, Ill do this one (pointing at her left leg). Im my left. As I attempted to confirm her choice, Seville stated, Im so cold. Yes sir, thats fine. Seville chose to raise her left foot. Seville then asked, Can I do four? Im so freezing, Im jus, I jus, my anemia is so bad. I offered Seville the opportunity to sit in her vehicle to warm up, and she stated, No, I dont have to have a seat I just wanna just get it over with because I did this I told you I did this just a second ago my officer told me he gave me my paperwork and everything. I advised Seville that because she did not want to sit in her car to warm up, we would continue with the test, and she stated, Yeah, Im so cold. I asked Seville to take one step away from her vehicle, and as she complied, she stated, Of course!  Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10:  Seville began to state, One thou-, so step (Seville then put her foot down) I instructed Seville to keep her foot raised off the ground. Seville raised her foot off the ground, and stated, One thousand-one, one oh, one thousand-one (Seville then began to sway to the right and took one step backward with her left foot to maintain her balance) and stated, Im so clumsy.      Put foot down      Used arms for balance      Swayed     Seconds 11-20:      Used arms for balance      Put foot down     On her count of One thousand-seven, Seville put her foot down, and stated, One thousand-, oh, I cant. (Seville raised her foot back off the ground and continued to count) one thousand-eight, nine, ten. Seville then put her foot down and stated, No, I have to keep it up? I explained to Seville she needed to raise her foot back up and continue the test until told to stop, and she stated, I never until. Seville then raised her foot back off the ground, and stated, One thousand-one, one thousand-two, one thousand-three, one thousand-four (Seville then put her foot down again and raised her foot back up off the ground).  Seconds 21-30:      Used arms for balance      Sways     PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST  While on scene, I informed Seville of her Preliminary Breath Test Rights. I advised Seville that she told me earlier that she had consumed an alcoholic beverage, and she stated, I did teleport. Seville was offered a PBT. I asked Seville if she had ever blown up a balloon before, and she stated, So, no, not today, no. I again asked Seville if she had ever blown up a balloon, and she stated, No hahaha, no, I havent. I again offered Seville the PBT, and Seville stated, And is that something that I will be have to do today, because once again I just got stopped 20 minutes ago, and he told me, to, he gave me my rules, he gave me everything else, so? And Ive been compliance the whole time. I again explained the PBT to Seville, and she stated, At this time I am, I am literally freezing. I just wanna go home, so I would not be in compliance with everything else because Im not, I am, Ive been in compliance with everything else you have my car, I havent been out of line of anything else, I am freezing, I didnt hit anything I didnt do anything wrong and I literally, he gave me my paperwork literally 20 minutes before you pulled me over and he said to me he pulled me over not because I did anything wrong. Yeah, no, I dont want to do anything else, sir; I, I am freezing. I confirmed with Seville that she did not want to take the PBT, and she stated, No, Im freezing, Im freezing. I, I did everything else. Ive been compliance. I didnt do nothing wrong. And I did everything with the last officer too. I instructed Seville to face the front of her vehicle, and while she complied, she stated, OK, I didnt do anything else like, everything you told me I did.  ARREST  Based on the totality of circumstances, I had reason to believe Seville was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:      Vehicle disabled in roadway      Sevilles own statements      A strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle, breath, and person.      Clues during Standardized Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (6/6), WAT (7/8), OLS (4/4).      Unable to operate a vehicle safely     Due to the number of observations, I concluded Seville was driving under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a vehicle safely.  I gave Seville the instruction to bring her right hand back to the sound of my voice, and she stated, Ugh, k, what else do you (incoherent mumbling) me to do? I repeated my instructions and asked Seville if she could do that, Seville stated, Of course, anything you ask (incoherent mumbling), Im I then demonstrated to Seville what I was asking her to do, and she stated, Yes, over. I then instructed Seville to touch her wrist together, behind her back, to which she complied, and stated, Nk.   At approximately 0705 hours, I placed Seville under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. As I placed Seville under arrest, she stated, I am being arrested for what? I explained she was being placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol, and Seville stated, For what though? Under the influ, under the influence of what? I informed Seville she was being placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol, and she stated, No, cant be. I just got pulled over 20 minutes ago, and he told me everything I needed to do. This cannot be real, its not real; its cant be. Can I ask a question? Can you saying Im under the influence of alcohol? When I just got pulled over 20 minutes ago. And he told me the same thing.  I informed Seville her vehicle was going to be towed to a safe location because we could not leave it in the middle of the road, and she asked, But can I move it out the way I dont want it to get towed? I informed Seville the vehicle was going to be towed because it was in the middle of the road, and I did not want her vehicle to be involved in a collision, and she stated, Got that, but can I ask you a question? So, I just got pulled over. He gave me my my paperwork. The same thing. And he was like, I didnt even stop, he told me. I explained to Seville I can not vouch for what the other officer did because I was not there, and she stated, And this is based on what? I explained the arrest was based on the totality of the circumstances.  I explained the process to Seville, and she asked, Can you, but can you, can we uncuffed me cause its not, Im not gonna anything you say Im gonna do, Im gonna do. It was explained that it is policy she remains in handcuffs throughout the rest of the process; Seville asked, But can you, all right? Can you put it in front of me because Im I cannot Im not gonna be able to walk properly like this. I explained to Seville I would be right beside her to assist her in walking, and she asked, I dont know, where are you taking me? I explained she was being taken to the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack on Maryland Route 140, and she stated, Westminster he said. As I walked Seville to my patrol vehicle, she stated, I cant like this, Im very clumsy, I dont I assured Seville I was there to help walk her back to my patrol vehicle, and she continued to state, No, can you do it in front of me, if you can put em in front of me, thats fine. I, anything you go-me to do, I can do, but its not in front of me. I explained to Seville I had to follow policy, and I could not move the handcuffs to the front. Seville then stated, Im just tryin figure out, the best way (incoherent mumbling) cause Im, this is not me. I immediately notified the barrack, and searched her person for weapons and contraband, both with negative results.  While walking Seville to the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle, she continued to explain that she was clumsy and did not know how to sit down. I informed her that I would give her instructions on how to sit in the seat without falling down. As Seville turned to face me and sit in the vehicle, as I instructed her, she stated, And theres no way you can like this, like, haha. I uh oh my god. As Seville sat on the seat, her shirt was pulled lower on her left side. I asked Seville to swing her feet into the vehicle, and she stated, But Im I am undressed like. Can we? I asked Seville if she wanted me to help her by zipping up her jacket, and she stated, OK, so can I just be, I I am in compliance theres no reason to cuff me. Is that a, is that a I asked Seville if she wanted me to lift her shirt, and she stated, All right, so so my question to you is for the cuffs, compliance or not, thats what you have to do? It was explained to Seville, again, that it was policy for her to be in handcuffs, and she stated, OK. I asked Seville if I could fix her shirt, and she said, Thank you. Thats what I have to do. Thank you. I attempted to explain to Seville how to sit in the seat so as not to sit on the handcuffs, and she stated, I cant, this is as good as its gonna get. I continued to explain to Seville how best to sit in the seat, and she stated, This is still going to get from me, I cant this is not it; it is what it is, I have to just deal with it. I attempted to explain to Seville that if she listened to me, the seat may be more comfortable, and she stated, This is as good as its gonna get for me. Thank you. I explained to Seville I was trying to help her, and she stated, No, absolutely. Understood, but you cant uncuff me, so so this is as good as its gonna get for me. I again explained it was policy for her to remain in handcuffs, and she stated, Yeah, no, its a compliance, Im not worried about that, it is what it is. I informed Seville I was going to adjust the seat belt to ensure it was properly restraining her, and she stated, Do whatchu gotta do.  TRANSPORT  While transporting Seville to the barrack, I observed her begin to fall asleep, I asked her if she was okay, and she stated, Yeah, Im fine.  Once at the Maryland State Police Westminster barrack, Seville was read her DR-15 Advice of Rights in English. While reading the DR-15 Advice of Rights to Seville, it appeared as though Seville had fallen asleep. I paused from reading the DR-15 Advice of Rights and asked Saville if she was awake and listening, and she stated, No, Im with you. Ha ha ha ha ha, Im here with you for sure. It again appeared as though Seville had fallen asleep, and I asked if she was listening, and she stated, Yeah. Attempting to be.  After reading the DR-15 Advice of Rights in its entirety to Seville, I asked if she was willing to submit to the intoximeter test, and she stated, OK, so this is about the test and any suspension that would be. I explained the form was asking if she wanted to submit to the intoximeter test, and I pointed to the intoximeter on the counter behind her. Seville then stated, Got it. Got that. Yeah, I got that, I read through that, OK, got it. So this is my right to waive or not do, my right to waive or do it? I explained that she was correct, and Seville stated, N, K, yeah, I read that. OK. I advised Seville I just needed to know what her decision was, and she stated, Give me one second here. Let me read through one this last part here that I did not look through. Yeah, since Im by myself. Im gonna, Im going to waive it. For clarification, I asked Seville if that meant she did not want to take the test, and she stated, No, since Im by myself, I dont have my lawyer, or nothing like that, Im going to waive it. After I signed the DR-15 Advice of Rights indicating that I had read the form to Seville, I explained that the top box indicated Yes and the bottom box indicated No, and that she was to mark her response, Seville stated, Gotchu. As Seville was signing the form, she asked, And todays the 18th? I informed Seville it was the 19th, and she stated, I am a day short. At approximately 0754 hours, Seville refused to take an alcohol concentration test. I informed Seville that everything she signed I would provide her with a copy, and she stated, Thank you so much.  I continued to process Seville according to policy and advised her she could call someone to pick her up from the barrack. With her cell phone in her hand, Seville looked up and asked, Yeah, from what is the address? The address was pointed out to her, printed on a piece of paper directly above Sevilles head, to her left. Seville saw the paper, and stated, Thank youuu. OK, so its the one, 1100 Baltimore Boulevard. She was informed that was correct and continued looking at her phone. Seville then stated, No, its 1100 Baltimore Blvd., Westminster, MD 211157. Im about to send it to you. Nope. Mhm. Okay. Because Im about to send it to you right now. Im about to send it to you right now; hold on. All right, I just sent it to you. Right? All right, so I just sent my location to you. Could you see it? OK, Thank you. Thank you. Seville then put her cell phone down on the table and stated, Im sorry, I have carpal tunnel in my hands do that from time to time. OK, thank you again.  As I was filling out the paperwork, I asked Seville where she consumed that alcoholic beverage and she stated, Yeah, um, teleport. I asked her to repeat her answer, and she stated, Teleport. I asked her where she consumed the alcoholic beverage, and she said, Oh, no, it was a venue. What was the name of the venue? Um, oh Jesus, um, it was. At. It was it wasnt like a bar or anything. It was like a venue, so I dont know, I, Im trying to remember the name it was, you know when you like rent a hall, Im trying to remember the name of this hall, but I cant remember the name of the hall. I asked her, while she was thinking about the name of the hall, how old she was, and she stated, Im 31. Yeah, I cant remember. I cant remember the name of the hall, to be honest. Because I didnt rent it, so I dont remember the name of the hall, to be honest. We were at the baby shower. And then we were we were supposed to go to the gender reveal to the next venue. It was a baby shower spot one. And the gender reveal spot two is how it shouldve went.  I explained the DR-15A Order of Suspension to Seville, and she asked, All right, so how long is my license is going to be suspended? And for what? I again explained the DR-15A Order of Suspension, and she stated, OK, then its correct, so I should be taking action through the courts too? I advised Seville not to wait till the last minute, and she stated, Yeah, Im not, so what I should be doing is taking action through the courts for a, what do you, what, what was I being here for today? I informed Seville again she was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol, and she stated, Thats crazy. And this was for your original reason for sus; your original reason for pulling me over was what? I explained to Seville I was called out to the scene because she was disabled in the roadway and that the arrest was based on the totality of the circumstances, and she stated, Understood.  Seville was released on citations pending an appearance in the District Court of Maryland for Carroll County at a later date. Seville was released to the custody of her brother from the barracks.   She was issued the following citations:  CITATIONS:      TA 13-411(F) Displaying Expired Registration Plates Issued By Any State      TA 21-902(a)(1)(i) Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol      TA 21-902(b)(1)(i) Driving Vehicle While Impaired By Alcohol      TA 21-901.1(a) Reckless Driving In Wanton or Willful Disregard For The Safety of Persons or Property      TA 21-901.1(b) Negligent Driving Vehicle In Careless And Imprudent Manner Endangering Property, Life And Person     The defendant was issued copies of the following documents:      Citations (listed above)      DR-15 Advice of Rights      DR-15a Order of Suspension     All documents were forwarded to the Carroll County States Attorneys Office.  The vehicle was towed from the scene by JT Collision.  All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland.  CASE CLOSED BY ARREST. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 16:29:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 13:46:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dale</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2927</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mills</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryder</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6784</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499323</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 05:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 13:00:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 13:00:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499323</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 05:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 13:00:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 13:00:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499323</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 05:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 13:00:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 13:00:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499323</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 05:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 13:00:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 13:00:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499323</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16626</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 05:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 13:00:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 13:00:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 13:22:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371962</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>SEVILLE</LastName>
               <FirstName>YASHEEDA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>KAYLIA</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/29/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 13:07:47</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S140</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Y230</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>SEVILLE</LastName>
               <FirstName>YASHEEDA</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>KAYLIA</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/29/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S140</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Y230</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 13:07:47</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>926</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Milford Mill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Pikesville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21208</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4616</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.741701</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.360301</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 13:22:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 13:22:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 13:22:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 13:22:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 13:22:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 13:00:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 13:00:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151039</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6784</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 13:24:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6784</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/19/2023 13:24:03</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5N1AR2MM5EC675802</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>PATHFINDER</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>GA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>S1423629</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/19/2023 14:33:55</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/19/2023 14:33:55</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>50</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/13/2023 09:55:22</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5820</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 14:33:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:27</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was audibly and visually recorded.  On Sunday, March 19, 2023, at approximately 0600 hours, I was in my marked patrol car A-13 traveling north on MD Rt 97 in the area of Hoods Mill Rd in Carroll County, Maryland. At that time, I observed a Gray Nissan Pathfinder, bearing Georgia registration, S1423629, stopped in the northbound lane of Rt. 97. The Nissan had damage on the rear and front drivers side of the vehicle and a broken rear window that appeared to be from a collision. I activated my rear emergency lights and walked up to the drivers side of the vehicle, where I observed the female driver slumped over the steering wheel asleep. I knocked on the window and the driver woke up and opened the door. She appeared confused and disoriented, and I was able to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. When I asked the driver why she was stopped and what happened, she was unable to form a complete sentence and began making incoherent statements that made no sense. She provided me with her Maryland drivers license and was identified as Yasheeda Kaylia Seville, African American female, DOB 08/29/1991. While speaking with Seville, I observed that her speech was slurred and her eyes were red and glassy. After getting her information, I realized that I had conducted a traffic stop earlier in the morning at approximately 0100 hours on this same vehicle and driver. That stopped occurred in Howard County, Maryland on southbound I-95 in the area of MD Rt 100. During that stop, I did not observe and signs of impairment or abnormal behavior. The only damage to her vehicle that I observed was the broken passenger side taillight that was the probable cause for my traffic stop. TFC Mills #6784 from the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack responded to the scene and took over the investigation. I stayed on scene while TFC Mills performed standardized field sobriety testing and subsequently arrested Seville for DUI.  All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5820</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 14:35:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5820</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/13/2023 09:53:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gailor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zinnah</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1086</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Allen</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thaddeus</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5820</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>