<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011589</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/01/2023 02:22:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/01/2023 02:22:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/01/2023 02:01:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/01/2023 02:01:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop leads to the arrest of an intoxicated driver.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 02:22:06</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 15:08:06</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I695 / I83</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>689445</AddressId>
      <City>MDC508</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 02:22:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 04:24:30</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>689445</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I/L I-695</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Pikesville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21208</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>AVE</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.69172</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.39516</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/01/2023 02:22:01</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/01/2023 02:22:01</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/27/2023 20:41:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 02:22:06</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP MARKED VEHICLE R-42 NOT EQUIPPED WITH MVR // INCIDENT CAPTRURED ON TROOPERS BWC  Defendant: Jourdan Jakina Moore Date of Birth: 10/09/2000 Date of Arrest: 04/01/2023 Time of Arrest: 0214 hours DUI #: 23-181  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Certified Preliminary Breath Test Operator. * Successful completion of the Advanced Roadside Impairment Driving Enforcement Program. * Successful completion of the Maryland coordination analysis center for License plate recognition. * Successful completion of Advanced Interview for Law Enforcement Investigators Training program.   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On Saturday, April 1st, 2023, at approximately 0155 hours, I, TFC Howard #7278, of the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack, was working in an official capacity in full uniform operating my marked Ford Explorer police vehicle. I was driving on the inner loop I-695 from Stevenson Road in lane #3. I observed a silver Acura TLX bearing Maryland registration (5EE8221) in lane #4. Traveling above the posted 55mph speed limit at approximately 74 mph. I then observed the Acura drift left and right inside of its lane for about 4 seconds then finally drifted out of its lane onto the right shoulder by half of a tires width on two occasions then corrected themselves. The Acura was then passing Greenspring Avenue. The Acura drifted into the Gore area and continued driving through it without correction until we were past the exit. Moments later the Acura veered amongst the right shoulder again with the solid white line which separates the right shoulder and the travel lanes was now evenly splitting the center of the Acura. This action continued for approximately 2 seconds prior to I-83 south. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop upon the vehicle. The Acura came to an abrupt stop on the right shoulder.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I immediately made contact with the operator of the Acura TLX via passenger side of the vehicle who I identified as Jourdan Jakina Moore, DOB: 10/09/2000, B/F. I introduced myself to her and informed her the reason for the stop. Moore was the sole occupant of the vehicle. I requested the drivers license and vehicle registration of Moore and questioned her whereabouts. Moore stated she was on the way to pick up her daughter and coming from a dinner party at a friends house. Moore surrendered a Maryland ID card and registration.While speaking with Moore. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle. I observed her eyes were bloodshot red, glassy with a glazed look. I asked her how much alcohol had she consumed earlier in the night she stated she had nothing to drink. I requested her to exit the vehicle, to which he complied. I informed Moore of all of my observations of her vehicle while she was driving and informed her I would like her to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, she agreed. Moore informed me she has to use the facilities, real bad which was a potential reason for her swerving.  While outside of the vehicle and still having a conversation with Moore, I detected an overwhelming odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Moores breath and person.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of the Baltimore Beltway. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear skies, dry road and approximately 57 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of street lights and my flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Moore appeared to be in good physical condition. She did not exhibit any visible injuries or did not appear to be in any sort of pain.  I asked Moore the following questions: Glasses or contacts- Contacts in both eyes Injuries- No. Medications- Albuterol. Medical conditions- Asthma  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12-15 inches from Moores eyes. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes only until told to stop. Moore pupils were equal in size and displayed equal tracking. No resting nystagmus was observed. I asked Moore if he understood the instructions and she stated, Yes.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes  -VERTICAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS PRESENT IN BOTH EYES-   WALK AND TURN (2/8 CLUES OBSERVED) Prior to Moore performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Moore was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Moore was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Moore was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Moore was to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Moore was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Moore was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Moore was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keeping her hands down by her side, looking down at her feet, and count each step aloud. I asked Moore if she understood the test and she stated, Yeah Instructional Stage:  Walking Stage (1st Nine):    margin-left:8px"&gt;Missed heel to toe by more than half an inch on every step   Turn: Completed properly  Walking Stage (2nd Nine)    Missed heel to toe by more than half an inch on every step.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Raised arms greater than 6 inches on steps 3  4   ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)  Prior to Moore performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Moore was instructed to stand with her heels  toes together with her hands down by her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count aloud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Moore if she understood the instructions of the test and she stated, Yes, I am not a balanced person. It must be noted Moore did not display any unbalanced coordination when exiting her vehicle performing normal day-to-day functions.  *Moore Chose to raise her left foot, balancing on her right foot*  Instructional Stage: Nothing observed.  Balance and Count Stage:  1-10 seconds used arms for balance  11-20 seconds: Uses arms for balance Puts foot down Hopping  21-30 seconds: Hopping Puts foot down  Used arms for balance   *Moore submitted to PBT Results: .14  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Moore was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Eyes glassy, bloodshot with a glazed look. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. * My observed signs of impairment as he poorly performed Standardized Field Sobriety test * Unable to maintain a single lane. * Admission to consuming alcohol prior to driving. * Inconsistent speeds while driving  I arrested Moore for driving under the influence of alcohol and at approximately 0214 hours. She was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle.  MOUTH CHECK: Moores oral cavity was checked and clear of fluids and any edible materials at0244 hours.  Moore was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack R for processing. Once at the Barrack, I played the English DR-15 Advice of Rights recording to Moorein its entirety at 0239 hours. Moorewas handcuffed to the front and given the form to follow along. At the conclusion, Moore verbally advised she would submit to the intoximeter test, and signed her signature in the required location on the DR-15 Advice of Rights Form indicating the same at approximately 0250 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT:  **.13 BrAC per 210 liters of breath** Test administered by Sgt. Iman #5709 / INTOX ID # 0030   Charges 1. TA 21-201(a1) 2. TA 21-902(a1i) 3. TA 21-902 (a1ii) 4. TA 21-902(b1i) 5 TA 21-902(c1i) 6 TA 21-901.1(a) 7 TA 21-901.1(b)  Mooreremained polite and cooperative throughout the entire process. Shewas given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to a sober driver.   All above events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/21/2023 12:15:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 23:54:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Forrester</LastName>
            <FirstName>Douglas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1174</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Howard</LastName>
            <FirstName>Charles </FirstName>
            <InternalID>7278</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500992</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/01/2023 02:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 04:26:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 04:26:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500992</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/01/2023 02:01:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 04:27:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 04:27:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 05:08:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:27</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373273</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Moore</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jourdan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jakina</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/09/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 05:07:44</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J635</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Moore</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jourdan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jakina</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/09/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J635</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 05:07:44</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>424</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4400</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>960</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1320</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/21/2023 12:13:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/21/2023 12:13:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/21/2023 12:13:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/03/2023 04:26:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/03/2023 04:26:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151586</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7278</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/21/2023 12:15:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7278</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/21/2023 12:15:05</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>19UUB1F59GA010679</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2016</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>ACUR</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>0</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5ee8221</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>5</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>