<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009622</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/17/2023 02:46:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/17/2023 02:46:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/17/2023 02:29:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/17/2023 02:29:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>23-152 "R" COLEY</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 02:46:37</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6354</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 16:45:32</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I695 / YORK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>582484</AddressId>
      <City>MDC564</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 02:46:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 03:35:54</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>582484</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I695</StreetName>
         <City>Curtis Bay</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.6133</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.41525</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L 695 @ YORK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 IL  / 0-0 YORK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IL @ YORK</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 0-0 YORK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/17/2023 02:46:35</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/17/2023 02:46:35</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/24/2023 16:45:34</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 02:46:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E.) TEAM* The following incident was captured on in-car and body camera Defendant: Torrez Latone Coley  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: * I am trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (March 2013 SFST NHTSA Manual). * I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor as of February 2016. * I am a Certified Breath Test Operator by the Toxicologist of the State of Maryland as of March 2016. * I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of March 2016. * I am a distinguished graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute as of June 2015 * I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of May 2014. * I am a Preliminary Breath Test Instructor as of May 2019. * I am a RADAR and LIDAR Instructor as of October 2019. * I have apprehended more than 1,000 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On March 17, at approximately 0229 hours, I (Cpl. Wallace #6323) was on patrol in unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle DUI-1 on northbound Dulaney Valley Road prior to I-695, Baltimore County, Maryland. I observed a white Volkswagen Jetta on northbound Dulaney Valley Road at what appeared to be above the posted speed limit. As I was accelerating to catch up to the Volkswagen I observed it to approach a steady red arrow at I-695. The Volkswagen slowed, but did not stop as it proceeded through the steady red arrow onto the O/L I-695. The Volkswagen accelerated as it was getting onto I-695 at what appeared to be above the posted 55 MPH speed limit. I activated the front antenna of my Golden Eagle II Radar (S/N: EG-02387), which is a directional radar, in the moving mode (same). I heard a Doppler tone indicative of the estimated speed and obtained a speeding reading of 80 MPH in a posted 55 MPH zone (my radar unit was checked before and after my shift and was functioning properly).I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the Volkswagen. The Volkswagen moved onto the right shoulder, into the grass area and jerked left. The Volkswagen bearing Maryland registration 8EW1402.  The above referenced RADAR was calibrated before and after my shift and was functioning properly. I am a certified RADAR operator. Training certificates and calibration records will be made available upon request. This RADAR is specifically assigned to my vehicle.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Volkswagen on the passenger side and made contact with the male operator of the vehicle, who was the only occupant in the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop and requested his drivers license and vehicle registration. He was identified by his Tennessee drivers license as Torrez Latone Coley. While speaking with Coley, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I deliberately observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. He stated that he did not run a red light. I returned to my patrol vehicle to notify the barrack who I was out with.  I returned to the Volkswagen and requested Coley to exit his vehicle and walk to the front. He complied and exited his vehicle. While speaking with Coley outside the vehicle, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. When asked about alcohol consumption prior to driving, he stated that he had a 1  beers. Stated that he was at dinner with his people, then went to Backyard and his last drink was at 9:30. I informed Coley that I wanted him to perform standardized field sobriety tests, to which he agreed to the tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. He was wearing a colorful green hat, button up, white pants, white Jordan shoes (tied).  I asked Coley the following questions:  Glasses or contacts  No Head Injuries - No Medication No Problems with knees or ankles  Toenail removed 13 or 4 months ago, grew back and cutting into tissue  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus   Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes     Looked away when instructed to follow the stimulus.  Now stated that he had a shot of Tequila.   He missed the window as he was attempting to put his hoodie in the open driver window.  WALK AND TURN (6/8 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage:    Lost balance offline to the right 6 times and stumbled left 1 time.   Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Stepped completely offline on steps 2 and 4.  Took 8 steps when instructed to take 9, counted 9.  Turn: Spun left in one motion, lost balance stopped Walking Stage (2nd Nine):    Stepped completely offline on steps 8 and 9.  Missed touching heel to toe by more than  inch on step 9.  Stopped to regain balance after step 8.   ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. -Left foot raised. Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10:    Swayed body to the left and right.  Hopped on left foot.  Seconds 11-20:     Swayed body to the left and right.  Left foot hit the ground 2 times.  Seconds 21-30:    Swayed body to the left and right.  Hopped on right foot.  Left foot hit the ground     You can arrest me.   PBT refused I deny it  ARREST Due to the number of observations, I concluded Coley was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0246 hours, I placed Coley under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. He was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack for processing.     margin-left:8px"&gt;Asked if he could take a snap chat  Upon arrival at the barrack, I provided Coley with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Coley listened to the DR-15 Advice of Rights from the MVA website. At 0328 hours, Coley agreed to take a breath test.  20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Coley beginning at 0245. A search revealed that he had grills on his teeth that he could not remove. Coley was observed from that time until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by Sgt. Twardowski of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Coley had a result of .14 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 0340 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: ****.14 grams of alcohol****  Coley was polite and cooperative during the encounter. Coley was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 03:38:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 16:35:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499021</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/17/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 03:36:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 03:36:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 03:36:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:28</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371789</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Coley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Torrez</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Latone</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/04/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 03:20:09</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Coley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Torrez</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Latone</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/04/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 03:20:09</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3800</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hampton</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Knoxville</City>
               <StateCode>TN</StateCode>
               <Zip5>37914</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3924</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-83.877135</Longitude>
               <Latitude>36.000887</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 03:37:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 03:37:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 03:36:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 03:36:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150954</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/17/2023 03:38:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/17/2023 03:38:12</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/17/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>VOLK</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>JET</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8EW1401</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>