<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-001557</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/13/2023 17:02:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/13/2023 17:02:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/13/2023 17:01:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/13/2023 17:01:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>3 VEHICLE MVC WHERE THE OPERATOR OF V1 WAS FOUND TO HAVE JUST COMMITTED A HIT AND RUN MINUTES PRIOR. V1 CONTINUED N/B ON MD-152 WHERE IT CAUSED THIS SECOND COLLISION. THE OPERATOR OF V1 SHOWED SIGNS OF IMPAIRMENT AND WAS PLACED UNDER ARREST FOR DUI/DWI: DUI#23-012 LEARY, RYAN P</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 17:02:23</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 08:40:27</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MOUNTAIN RD/ DUNWOOD LN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>606781</AddressId>
      <City>MDC446</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 17:02:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/15/2023 20:57:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>606781</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Mountain</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Joppa</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.38696</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.4819</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>900-912 MOUNTAIN RD / 2290-2318 DUNWOOD LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/13/2023 17:02:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/13/2023 17:02:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/23/2023 01:38:17</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 17:02:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:30</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack D-30 is equipped with mobile recording device Incident was captured on mobile recording device and BWC  Defendant: Ryan Patrick Leary Date of Birth: 12/05/1996 Date of Arrest: 01/13/2023 Time of Arrest: 1750 hours MD OLN: L-600-755-676-927 DUI # 23-012 (Bel Air)  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:   I am trained by the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration to administer standardized field sobriety test.  I am a NHTSA certified SFST Instructor.  I am trained by the Maryland State Police and NHTSA in ARIDE.  I am certified by the NHTSA/IACP as a Drug Recognition Expert (DRE).  I am certified by the IACP as a DRE Instructor  I attended the 2019 DUI Conference in Ocean City, Maryland.  I attended the 2022 Maryland DRE Conference in Ocean City, Maryland.  I have completed the Cannabis intoxication/impairment workshop hosted by Montgomery County Police Department.  I have been a guest instructor at the Cannabis intoxication/impairment workshop hosted by Montgomery County Police for States Attorneys.  I am a certified LIDAR/RADAR operator through the Maryland State Police.  I am certified as a Preliminary Breath Test Operator through the Maryland State Police.  I am certified by the Maryland State Police as a License Plate Recognition operator.   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On 01/13/2023 at approximately 1702 hours, I (TFC Mott #6918) was on-duty operating unmarked patrol vehicle D-30 when I was dispatched to the area of MD-152 and Dunwood Ln for a multiple vehicle collision with injuries. As I was in route to the scene, several off-duty Troopers called out on the radio that multiple vehicles were involved with a head on collision also occurring. As I approached the scene, I observed several vehicles disabled in the middle of the roadway with Police vehicles providing traffic control of the scene. Traffic on S/B MD-152 was at a complete stop.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) As I arrived on scene, I observed a white passenger car and a black Nissan passenger car disabled in the continuous turn lane on MD-152. The vehicles both had heavy front end damage with airbag deployment, indicating a head on collision. The vehicles had come to rest inches from each other. I also observed a Blue Dot further down the roadway, which was partially off the roadway into a ditch. I spoke to Lt. Forchion #1561, Commander of the Maryland State Police Annapolis Barrack, who was on scene. In a witness statement Lt. Forchion provided me, Lt. Forchion stated that she was traveling N/B on MD-152 when a white vehicle in front of her motioned for her to go around the vehicle. Lt. Forchion stated this occurred several times. Lt. Forchion had utilized the center continuous turn lane to pass the vehicles. In doing so, Lt. Forchion was able to observe a black Nissan with it turn signal activated swerve and enter the center turn lane. Lt. Forchion activated her emergency equipment and attempted to catch up to the vehicle in order to make a traffic stop. Before Lt. Forchion was able to initiate a traffic stop and call the stop out to the Bel Air Barrack, the black Nissan crossed into oncoming traffic and struck a Blue Dot van traveling S/B on MD-152. The Nissan bounced off the van and proceeded to hit the vehicle behind the van head on. The Bel Air Barrack was immediately contacted and additional Trooper and Fire/EMS was dispatched to the scene. Lt. Forchion remained on scene for the entire incident, assisting responding Troopers.  As I finished speaking with Lt. Forchion, I observed witnesses were on scene waiting to speak with Law Enforcement. One of the witnesses was identified as Bridget Merryman (01/29/1987 W/F). Merryman observed the entire incident and provided a written statement to Troopers. Merryman stated in her statement that she observed a black Nissan sedan swerving in the lane of travel. Merryman stated that she observed Police lights activated and the Police vehicle move into the center lane. Merryman then stated that Nissan then immediately swerved into oncoming traffic. The Nissan first struck the Blue Dot van and then the second vehicle, a white Hyundai sedan. This occurred right in front of Merryman.  As second individual was Shawn White Jr (02/11/1991 B/M) who was identified as by his Maryland drivers license. White stated that the black Nissan had struck his vehicle at the intersection of MD-152 and Old Joppa prior to this collision occurring. White also provided a witness statement detailing that incident. Due to this first crash being a separate incident, the ACRS report for the hit and run would be captured on 23-MSP-001556. As I continued to process the scene, I spoke with Benjamin Turner (01/25/1992 W/M) who was operating the Blue Dot van, bearing Maryland registration 3EL2891. While speaking with Turner during the incident, he stated that the van is equipped with a camera, which may have recorded the incident.  I proceeded to walk over to the black Nissan, bearing Maryland registration 8CZ6402. The driver of the vehicle was still sitting in the driver seat. The driver of the vehicle would be identified as Ryan Patrick Leary (12/05/1996 W/M) by his Maryland drivers license. As I initially spoke with Leary, he appeared very disoriented and confused. Leary had droopy eyelids and just from the brief conversation I had with him, his speech was slurred. Leary had slow deliberate movements as he was moving in the vehicle and attempting to exit. Once Leary was out of the vehicle I continued to speak with him regarding the collision, I immediately observed Learys pupils were very constricted. As I continued speaking with Leary, it became darker as night time approached. Leary stated that he had vehicle issues causing the collision. Leary stated that he felt the vehicle rumble as he hit his brakes. Leary mentioned that he had vehicle issues before, but continued to operate the vehicle none the less. Leary claimed his engine light was on but stated that vehicle had never done that before. I asked Leary about the first collision that he fled from, involving Shawn White. Leary advised he had no idea he was involved in a separate collision. As Leary continued speaking with me, I observed his movements to be very slow and deliberate. I asked Leary if he took any drugs or medications, he stated no. I asked Leary if he had any medical conditions, specifically regarding his constricted pupils. Leary did not advise that he any and conditions that affected his eyes. Leary stated that he passed out the other day. Leary then stated that it was actually a couple months before hand. Leary stated that he did not have any other conditions. I asked Leary if he was evaluated by medics and he stated yes, he was fine physically. I proceeded to return to my patrol vehicle and complete processing the collision scene. After I finished processing, I relocated my patrol vehicle to the parking lot of Reckord Park and requested Leary to walk over with me. As I walked over to Leary, he stumbled standing up and began limping on his left leg. I asked Leary if he wanted EMS to respond back to the scene and he declined.  Once in the parking lot, I requested Leary to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, Leary agreed.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation took place in the parking lot of Reckord Park. The surface where the evaluation took place was level, dry and free from obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of patrol vehicle head lamps, spotlight and my flash light. Leary appeared to be in good health and did not have any visible signs of injury. It should be noted that as I was completing the medical screening with Leary, I asked Leary about any medical issues. Leary stated that he told one of my coworkers about that earlier. Leary did not realize that he actually provided that information to myself. Leary would now state that the incident where he passed out months prior was possible stress related.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (0/6 clues observed) The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST manual. Learys pupils were equal in size and displayed equal tracking. Resting Nystagmus was not observed. Learys pupils were very constricted. It should be noted that Leary was swaying during this test.    Lack of smooth pursuit  not present in either eye.  Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation  not present in either eye.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees  not present in either eye.  Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was not observed.  Walk and Turn (Not Attempted) I attempted to administer the Walk and Turn test. As I was attempting to place Leary into the instructional position, he immediately lost his balance and then slowly went and grabbed his right thigh. Leary would state he was fine but then was not able to be placed into the instructional position. Leary was asked if he wanted medics and he replied maybe. Leary did not wish for medics to respond back to the scene. I attempted to have Leary placed into the instructional position, but he was unable to do so. The test was not attempted.  One Leg Turn (4/4 clues observed) The test was explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST manual. Leary stated that he understood the test and how the test was to be completed. Due to the leg issue with his right leg, Leary raised his right (injured) leg and balanced with his left leg, which Leary had never stated had any issues.  Seconds 01-10    Puts foot down   margin-left:8px"&gt;Uses arms for balance  Seconds 11-20    Uses arms for balance  Puts foot down  Sways    margin-left:8px"&gt;Hops   Seconds 21-30     margin-left:8px"&gt;Put foot down complained of a calf issue.  Lack of Convergence The Lack of Convergence test was administered to Leary. As the stimulus approached the bridge of Learys nose, he was unable to follow the stimulus. Learys would follow the stimulus and then remain looking straight as the stimulus came to the bridge of his nose.  Modified Romberg For this test, Leary was asked to think about the passing of 30 seconds and to say when 30 seconds had passed. Leary exhibited 4 inch sway front to back and stumbled at one point. Leary also had a 2 inch sway side to side. During the 30 second test, Leary took 64 seconds to compete the 30 second test.  Arrest Based on the following, I had reason to believe that Leary was operating a vehicle while impaired drugs.    Being involved in two collisions, not recalling one within minutes  Glassy, bloodshot eyes  Slurred speech  Constricted pupils  Inability to concentrate  Confused  Disoriented   Drowsy   margin-left:8px"&gt;Clues during SFSTs  Due to my observations and based on my training, knowledge and experience as a certified Drug Recognition Expert, I concluded that Leary was operating a vehicle while impaired by drugs and unable to do so safely. At approximately 1750 hours, I placed Leary under arrest for DUI/DWI. A preliminary search of Leary was conducted on scene and he was placed in the front seat of my patrol vehicle per department policy. Leary was transported to the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack for processing. During the very short drive from the collision scene to the Bel Air Barrack, Leary fell asleep in the front seat of my patrol vehicle. At approximately 1817 hours, Leary was advised of his DR-15 Advice of Rights. Leary agreed to submit to the breath test for alcohol. Cpl Brown #4758 successful administered the test at approximately 1835 hours. The result of the test was .00 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. At this time I explained the DRE process to Leary and explained that I would contact a DRE to respond to the Barrack. When Leary learned that the process included a blood draw, he was not interested in speaking to a DRE. Maryland DRE SOPs require an arresting DRE to first attempt to find a different DRE to conduct an evaluation prior to conducting an evaluation for their own arrest, which Leary did not wish for.  Blue Dot was able to provide dash cam footage of the collision.  Leary was polite and cooperative.  Learys vehicle was towed from scene by Carriers Towing.  Leary was released from the Bel Air Barrack to his wife.  A MVA Driver re-evaluation was completed in DELTA PLUS for Leary.  ACRS reports were completed in DELTA PLUS for both collisions.  All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 19:50:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6918</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/23/2023 00:24:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>22</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>English</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samantha</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7049</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Forchion</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicole</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1561</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7015</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mott</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6918</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brown</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4758</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mott</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6918</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mott</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6918</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490938</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3222</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/13/2023 17:50:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3222</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 09:47:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6918</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/15/2023 21:01:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490938</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3224</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/13/2023 17:50:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3224</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 09:47:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6918</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/15/2023 21:02:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490938</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/13/2023 17:50:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 09:47:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6918</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/15/2023 21:03:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490938</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/13/2023 17:50:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 09:47:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6918</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/15/2023 21:03:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>C</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 09:47:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:47</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366163</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Leary</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Patrick</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/05/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13491431E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>01/15/2023 09:16:50</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Leary</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Patrick</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/05/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13491431E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>L600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/15/2023 09:16:50</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>8200</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Featherhill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Perry Hall</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21128</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.45402</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.380779</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>844</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2143</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 21:06:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:37</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 21:06:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:37</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 21:06:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:37</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 21:08:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366200</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Merryman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Bridget</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/29/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/15/2023 21:08:04</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B632</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Merryman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Bridget</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/29/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B632</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/15/2023 21:08:04</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1609</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Fallston</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Fallston</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21047</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.432514</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.526938</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>608</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2721</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 21:08:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 21:08:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 20:59:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6918</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/15/2023 20:59:45</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148640</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6918</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/15/2023 21:17:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6918</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/15/2023 21:17:14</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3N1AB6AP7BL669890</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2011</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8CZ6402</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>