<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-006392</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/18/2023 22:02:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/18/2023 22:02:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/18/2023 21:46:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/18/2023 21:46:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 22:02:47</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/25/2023 17:19:25</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY/ SAMUEL BOWEN BLVD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>584958</AddressId>
      <City>MDC108</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 22:02:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 19:52:59</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>584958</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>BLVD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.164904</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.34502</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>50 WB / WALMART</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 / SAMUEL BOWEN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50 / SAMUEL BOWEN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>IN FRONT OF MCDONALDS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>7-ELEVEN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11266-11314 OCEAN GTWY / 11001-11299 SAMUEL BOWEN BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11224-11264 OCEAN GTWY / 11001-11299 SAMUEL BOWEN BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>11316-11542 OCEAN GTWY / 11329-11599 SAMUEL BOWEN BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>7-11</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/18/2023 22:02:43</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/18/2023 22:02:43</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/25/2023 00:04:50</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 22:02:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Zachary Joseph Rishkofski Pennsylvania SOUNDEX: 31165482 Breath Test Result: .10 DUI Citation # 5RX0T5Y DUI Tape #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-006392 (Axon View XL Software)   CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. * Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.). * Completed and graduated from the DUI Institute. * Completed and graduated from the SFST Instructor school  NARRATIVE -PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION- On February 18, 2023 at approximately 2146 hours, I (TFC. S. Shubert #6944), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating unmarked MSP vehicle V-08 in the area of westbound US 50 at Racetrack Road, Berlin, Worcester County, Maryland.   At that time, I observed a black Ford F-450 traveling southbound on Racetrack Road and was approaching the intersection of westbound US 50. I observed the black Ford F-450 traveling at a high rate of speed and stopped abruptly at the steady red signal on Racetrack Road at the intersection of US 50. I observed the front two tires cross the solid white line by approximately seven feet.   Once the traffic light displayed a green signal, I observed the black Ford F-450 make a right turn onto eastbound US 50. I positioned my patrol vehicle and conducted a traffic stop.   While the black Ford F-450 was stopping. I observed the rear passenger side tires scrape the right curb.   -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT- I exited my patrol vehicle and made contact with the driver via the driver side door. I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle. I informed the driver the reason for the traffic stop and requested his drivers license and registration card. I asked the driver where he was traveling from, and he replied: The casino. I also observed the driver to display a dazed/expression looks on his face. The driver was identified through his Pennsylvania drivers license as Zachary Joseph Rishkofski. I asked Rishkofski how many alcoholic beverages he consumed prior to operating his motor vehicle and Rishkofski stated I had two beers. I observed Rishkofskis movements to be lethargic. As Rishkofski spoke, I observed his eyes to be glassy and bloodshot. I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Rishkofski.   I then returned to the black Ford F-450 and asked Rishkofski to step out of his vehicle and walk to the front of it. Which he complied. I then asked Rishkofski where he was coming from and Rishkofski stated The casino. I asked Rishkofski if he consumed any alcoholic beverages prior to operating his motor vehicle and Rishkofski stated I had two beers at the casino. I then asked Rishkofski if he wanted to submit to standardized field sobriety tests to insure he was not impaired and Rishkofski agreed to submit to the tests.   -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING- STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs) The evaluation was performed on the roadway near the right shoulder area. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of overhead lights, headlights and flashlight. Rishkofski appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any limps or any limb ailments. Rishkofski was wearing blue jeans and a bluish pullover shirt.   **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**  1. Rishkofski displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  2. Rishkofski displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes. 3. Rishkofski displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.   **WALK AND TURN: 3 of 8 clues** First nine steps: -Missed heel to toe by approximately two inches on step 9 -Stepped off line by approximately three inches on step 8 -Took 11 steps when instructed to take 9 steps Turn: Completed satisfactory Second nine steps: -Stepped off line by approximately three inches on step 4  **ONE LEG STAND: 3 of 4 clues** -Placed left foot down two times during the test. -Swayed one time during the test -Raised arms from sides by approximately twelve to fourteen inches one time during the test.   I asked Rishkofski if he could read and recite the English alphabet and Rishkofski stated Yes. I then asked if he could recite the English alphabet starting at the letter H ending at the letter T Rishkofski stated he understood and recited the following:  H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P-Q-R-S-T  After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Rishkofski the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Rishkofski agreed to submit to the Preliminary breath test, which resulted in .12 BrAC. ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Rishkofski was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.  * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests.  *lethargic movements   I placed Rishkofski under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 2200 hours on February 18, 2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Rishkofskis mouth for any foreign objects and none were found.   ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) Rishkofski was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Rishkofski was given his Advice of Rights via the audio version of the DR-15 Form. I placed a copy of the DR-15 in front of Rishkofski. Once the DR-15 was completed being played Rishkofski stated that he understood his Advice of Rights. At approximately 2219 hours, Rishkofski agreed to submit to the Intoximeter test. I then transferred Rishkofski back to the Maryland State Police Berlin barrack for processing.  Intoximeter: Cpl. Lenz and myself checked Rishkofskis mouth for any foreign objects. Rishkofski did not have any foreign objects or liquid located in his mouth. Rishkofski gave two valid breath samples, which resulted on .10 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.   PROCESSING During all aspects of processing (mugshot, completion and explanation of the DR-15A Form, issuance and explanation of citations), the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Rishkofski continued to be strong.  CHARGES  Rishkofski was charged with the following citations: 1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (5RX0T5Y) 2. Driving While Impaired By Alcohol (5RY0T5Y) 3. Negligent driving (5S00T5Y) 4. Driving under the influence of alcohol per se (5RZ0T5Y) 5. Failure to stop at stop line (5S10T5Y) Case closed by arrest. All events occurred in Worcester County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 20:03:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 20:04:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>495788</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/18/2023 22:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 20:00:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 20:01:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 20:00:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:26</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369945</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Rishkofski</LastName>
               <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Joseph</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/30/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/23/2023 19:55:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R221</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Z260</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Rishkofski</LastName>
               <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Joseph</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/30/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R221</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Z260</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/23/2023 19:55:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 20:02:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:44</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 20:02:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:44</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 20:00:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 20:00:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150164</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 20:03:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 20:03:15</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2023</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>F45</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>PA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>ZRE4029</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>