<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-010799</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/26/2023 01:48:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/26/2023 01:48:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/26/2023 01:08:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/26/2023 01:08:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Subject was involved in a collision and taken into custody for DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/26/2023 01:48:24</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0266</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 13:11:39</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>BARCLAY RD/ DIXON TAVERN RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>578125</AddressId>
      <City>MDC104</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/26/2023 01:48:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 02:56:30</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>578125</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Barclay</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Barclay</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.834396</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.144996</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2201-2209 BARCLAY RD / 700-999 DIXON TAVERN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2209-2499 BARCLAY RD / 700-999 DIXON TAVERN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2200-2208 BARCLAY RD / 700-999 DIXON TAVERN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2101-2199 BARCLAY RD / 700-999 DIXON TAVERN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/26/2023 01:48:21</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/26/2023 01:48:21</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>80</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/06/2023 12:41:41</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/26/2023 01:48:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:11</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>INCIDENT CAPTURED ON BODY AND IN CAR CAMERA  DUI FOLDER #: S-23-035  ATTACHMENTS:  DR-15  DR-15A  TRAFFIC CITATIONS  MUST APPEAR COMMISSIONER NOTICE   NARRATIVE:    On Saturday March 26th at approximately 0109 hours, I was dispatched to respond to a vehicle off of the roadway Rt. 302 in the area of Dixon Tavern Rd. Upon arrival I observed a maroon pick up truck East of Dixon Tavern Rd off of the Westbound side of the roadway facing Eastbound. The vehicle was approximately 5 feet from the roadway. The headlights, and brake lights of the vehicle were illuminated, and I observed a male subject wearing a dark colored hoodie, and blue jeans standing behind the vehicle with a flashlight. When I exited my vehicle, I approached the subject and asked if he was the driver. The subject stated yes. I asked the driver if he was injured or needed an ambulance to which he replied no. The subject advised he had been traveling Eastbound when several deer ran into the roadway. He had swerved to avoid striking the deer, went off of the roadway, struck a tree, then came to rest in the ditch. The vehicle sustained damaged along the drivers side from the middle of the front quarter panel to the rear bumper. While speaking with the subject, I detected the odor of an acholic beverage emitting from his person.   I requested the subjects drivers license and registration. He presented a Delaware drivers license identifying him as Abelardo Trejo-Martinez (Trejo). Trejo produced his license from his wallet in his pocket. He advised the vehicle was not his. Trejo sat in the drivers seat of the vehicle with the drivers side door open while looking for the registration. I stood next to Trejo as he was seated. Trejo advised there were a lot of papers in the vehicle as he continued looking for the registration. He handed me his flashlight as he was looking. I asked Trejo where he had been coming from and I was unable to understand what Trejo had said. When asked again Trejo stated he had been coming from Elkton and was en route to Hartly, Delaware. Trejo attempted twice to contact the owner of the vehicle to ask about a tow for the vehicle and the calls went to voicemail. Trejo did not leave a message. As Trejo was speaking, the odor of an alcoholic beverage came more prevalent.   I asked Trejo if he had been drinking to which he initially stated no, then he stated not too much. When asked how much he had consumed he stated 3 or 4 beers with the last drink being around 9 PM. Trejo stated he left Elkton at approximately midnight and when asked what the current time was Trejo stated approximately 0100 hours. The time was 0133. Once a secondary police unit arrived, I advised Trejo to walk towards the roadway to which he complied. As we were walking Trejo mentioned tests and laughed. I asked Trejo if he had ever been through the tests before to which he replied no.   All field sobriety tests were conducted on the shoulder of the roadway which was a flat, level surface clear of loose debris. All of the tests were explained and demonstrated prior to Trejos attempting the tests. Trejo was asked prior to each test if the understood the instructions and questions were answered.   Prior to conducting field sobriety tests I asked Trejo if he had any problems with his eyes or head injuries to which he replied no.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS   I first checked Trejos eyes for equal pupil size and dilation and tracking of the visual stimulus. Trejos pupils were of equal size and dilation and tracked the visual stimulus equally. I observed a lack of smooth pursuit, the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees, and a distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes. Trejo had to be reminded three times during the test to not move his head. Trejo also returned his eyes to center ahead of the pen twice. Vertical nystagmus was not observed.  WALK AND TURN    I explained and demonstrated the instructional stance to Trejo. When Trejo attempted the instructional stance he placed his left foot in front of his right, contrary to the instructions. I advised Trejo again Right foot directly in front of your left. When I asked Trejo which foot was his right foot, he correctly placed his feet according to the instructions. During the instructional phase, Trejo raised his arms greater than 6 inches from his sides once. Prior to beginning the test, Trejo broke the instructional stance and motioned with his arms forward and backward asking to walk up and walk back. I advised Trejo to perform the test as demonstrated.   During his first 9 steps, Trejo completed a total of 10 steps. To complete the turn, Trejo did not leave his front foot in place according to the instructions, moved his front foot from in front of his left, and turned around in place in small steps.   During his second 9 steps, no clues were observed.  ONE LEG STAND   After the instructions and demonstration, Trejo advised his English was not good but that he understood the test. I advised Trejo he could count in Spanish if it made him more comfortable. When Trejo began the test he had to be reminded multiple times to keep his leg straight. He raised his left foot from the ground by bending his knee. Trejos right (back) leg was also bent. Trejo put his foot down on count 18 and looked at me as if he completed the test. Trejo had counted to 18 in 18 seconds. During his second attempt at the test, Trejo counted to 20 and put his foot down, again looking at me as if he had completed the test. This action was contrary to the instructions of to continue counting until he was advised to stop.   Trejo was then offered a preliminary breath test. Prior to me be able to advise Trejo to continue exhaling until told to stop, he blew a puff of air through the PBT straw. The read button had been pressed and the PBT displayed a digital reading indicating alcohol present in Trejos breath. Since I had not completed the instructions for the test, I reset the PBT to all zeros to conduct the test again which took several reset attempts. Once reset to all zeros, the PBT was conducted again with a result of .17. A secondary PBT from Queen Annes County Deputy Bradley was also utilized with the same result of .17. Trejo was asked again during this testing period when he had consumed his last drink. He answered 4 or 5 PM, which differed from his previous answer of 9 PM  Trejo was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol and placed in my patrol vehicle. Trejo advised he was having difficulty with the handcuff on his left wrist. Trejo then revealed scars from a previous wrist injury, and the handcuffs were placed in the front. Trejo was then placed in my patrol vehicle again. Utilizing the Maryland MVA website, audio of the DR-15 in Spanish was played for Trejo. Near the end of the audio, Trejo stated no. I asked Trejo if he wished to take the test. Trejo then stated what I believed to be no entiende (do not understand) I asked Trejo if he had understood the audio and he replied yes. I asked Trejo if he wished to take the breath test and he stated no.  I was seated in my patrol vehicle next to Trejo as I completed paperwork. The odor of an alcoholic beverage was now present in my vehicle.   When Trejo was issued his paperwork, he requested that his wife translate for him. His wife had arrived on scene prior to field sobriety testing. With the assistance of his wife, signatures were completed and Trejo was issued his paperwork. Trejo and his wife were asked if they had questions regarding the incident. Trejo, through his wife translating stated so I am drunk? I advised Trejo that he was under the influence of alcohol to the point he could not operate a motor vehicle safely. I advised Trejo he would have a court date regarding the incident and that I would not argue the point on the side of the road.  Trejo was released to his wife.                                                                             ALL OF THE ABOVE EVENTS OCCURRED IN QUEEN ANNES COUNTY.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 04:01:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4349</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 23:54:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nickerson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tanner</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5702</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wiley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6097</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joyce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4349</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500202</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 01:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 03:01:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4349</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 03:01:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500202</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 01:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 03:44:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4349</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 03:44:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500202</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 01:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 03:45:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4349</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 03:45:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500202</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 01:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 03:57:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4349</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 03:57:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500202</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/26/2023 01:08:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 03:57:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4349</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 03:57:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 02:58:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:39</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372578</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Trejo  Martinez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Abelardo</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/10/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/26/2023 02:26:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A146</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Trejo  Martinez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Abelardo</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/10/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A146</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/26/2023 02:26:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2020</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Halltown</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hartly</City>
               <StateCode>DE</StateCode>
               <Zip5>19953</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>302</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>415</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1706</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 03:59:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 03:59:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 03:59:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 03:59:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4349</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/27/2023 03:01:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4349</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/27/2023 03:01:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>