<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-003501</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/28/2023 02:01:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/28/2023 02:01:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/28/2023 01:16:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/28/2023 01:16:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Check for welfare resulting in D.U.I arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/28/2023 02:01:23</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5932</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/02/2023 13:23:43</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>WFC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>ELKTON RD/ FLETCHWOOD RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>62400</AddressId>
      <City>MDC146</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/28/2023 02:01:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/28/2023 23:13:47</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>62400</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Elkton</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Elkton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21921</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.78953</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.6537</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1473-1751 ELKTON RD / 1-199 FLETCHWOOD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>ELKTON WAWA</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1752-1755 ELKTON RD / 1-200 FLETCHWOOD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1473-1751 ELKTON RD / 0-200 FLETCHWOOD RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/28/2023 02:01:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/28/2023 02:01:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/15/2023 16:34:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/28/2023 02:01:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:01</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI Case # 23-MSP-003501 TRAINING: STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TEST TRAINED ADVANCED ROADSIDE IMPAIRED DRIVING ENFORCEMENT  DEFENDANT: Jason Thomas Hoffman DOB: 03/24/1971 300 West Creek Village Apt D1, Elkton, MD 21921  Phase #1 - Vehicle in Motion On January 28, 2023, at approximately 0117 hours, I, Trooper Williams #7381 was dispatched for a check the welfare at northbound route 279 at Fletchwood Rd, Elkton, Maryland. I arrived on scene at approximately 0127 hours with Trooper First Class Hughes #7110. I observed multiple vehicles in the turning lane for Fletchwood Road waiting to make a left-hand turn. I activated my in-car camera and notified the Maryland State Police North East Barrack via agency radio and advised I would make contact if the vehicle did not move once the light changed. When we arrived at the intersection the light was red. The traffic light remained red for 12 seconds then turning green and stayed green for 33 seconds which was the first cycle. The light then turned red again after 43 seconds during the second cycle of the traffic lights, at which time myself and TFC. Hughes went to make contact with the driver of a black Audi Q5 bearing Maryland registration CR18129.   Phase # 2 - Personal Contact I made a driver side approach on the vehicle and observed the driver who appeared to be unconscious in the driver seat with the vehicle still running with the brake lights engaged. I knocked on the window one time in a normal fashion. Once I observed no response from the driver I then made more than five (5) attempts of hard pounding knocks on the window while yelling multiple times to try and get the driver to wake up. Once the driver finally woke up he rolled the window down and yelled at me hold on a fucking minute god-damn. While speaking with the driver I immediately detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from within the vehicle from the drivers breath and person. I asked the driver for his license and he started looking for it. I asked the driver if he knew where he was located, the driver stated Newport Delaware. The driver then reached to retrieve his wallet and pulled out multiple cards, I observed the drivers license on top of the stack of cards. As I watched the driver shuffle through the stack of cards his movements were delayed as he was trying to sort through the cards. After going through the stack the driver attempted to hand me a debit card. I asked the driver where was he headed the driver stated Im not headed anywhere. The driver then picked his foot up off the brake and the vehicle started to roll forward, the driver put his foot back on the brake and put the vehicle in park. While speaking with the driver I detected the drivers speech was slurred. I asked the driver for his license again, and he began shuffling through the stack of cards once he was done looking he advised he did not have his license with him. I then told the driver where the license was located in the stack, he then handed me his Maryland drivers license which identified the driver as Jason Thomas Hoffman, DOB: 03/24/1971, Soundex: H-155-373-792-237, 2/M, phone number: 443-309-4557. I asked Hoffman where was he coming from he stated Im coming from a buddys house. Hoffman then advised he was on his way to work. Due to how late it was, I asked Hoffman where he works, and he began to give an address. While speaking with Hoffman I observed that his eyes were red. Hoffman advised that he was chopping firewood at his buddys home. I advised Hoffman to exit the vehicle, once he was out I observed he was moving slowly as he followed me to the front of the vehicle. Hoffman grabbed onto the front of his vehicle to keep himself balanced. TFC Hughes advised he would remain with Hoffman while I moved my vehicle out of the travel lane. I put Hoffmans information on the card and then returned to ask Hoffman if he would be willing to submit to field sobriety. While speaking with Hoffman the odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath was stronger than during my first approach. I asked him if he would be willing to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Test. Hoffman stated yes.  Phase # 3 - Pre-Arrest Screening Do you have any injuries I need to be made aware of? Neck and back. Glasses/Contacts: Yes Do you take any medication? Yes, nine medications. Hoffman could only remember Fluoxetine. I am trained by the Maryland State Police in performing Standard Field Sobriety Tests. The test was performed on the shoulder of the roadway the ground was free of debris and the surface was level.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus - 6 of 6 clues  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) test. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Hoffmans eyes and slightly above his eye level. Hoffman was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while focusing on and following the stimulus with his eyes, and his eyes only, and keep his hands down at his side until told to stop. Hoffmans pupils were equal in size and displayed equal tracking. Hoffman was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. While I moved the stimulus, Hoffman had to be reminded not to turn or move his head he moved his head (2) times. 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present. 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present. 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Before 45 Degrees - Present.  Walk and Turn - 3 of 8 clues  Before Hoffman performed the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Hoffman was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot, touch heel to toe, and place his hands down at his side. He was instructed to stand in this manner until told to begin. Hoffman was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching hell to toe on each step. Hoffman was advised to keep his hands down at his side, keep his eyes focused on his lead foot on the ground and take a series of small steps around his foot that was pivoted while turning. Hoffman was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Hoffman was told once he began the test not to stop and to walk until the test was completed, to keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. After stating that he understood the instructions and had no questions about the test then the test was administered.  *INSTRUCTIONAL PHASE*  Walking Stage (1st nine): Missed heel to toe on steps 5,6,7,8,9, walks off-line on steps 5,6,7,8,9 Walking Stage (2nd nine): Missed heel to toe on all steps, walks off-line on all steps Turn: Completed. *Additional Observation* During the Walk and Turn I observed that Hoffman was taking small steps throughout the test which is abnormal. Hoffman started the test too soon.   One Leg Stand - 2 of 4 clues Before Hoffman performed the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Hoffman was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his legs straight, look at his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand two), and continue the test until told to stop. After he indicated understanding the instructions, the test was administered.  *INSTRUCTIONAL PHASE* Puts foot down: 4 times Swayed: 1 time  *Additional Observation* Hoffman was counting very quickly during the test showing his perception of time was altered. Hoffman advised he would stand on his right leg but he used his left leg. It was noted that the call for service was received at approximately 0116 hours with callers reporting the vehicle stopped in the turn lane. The vehicle was still stopped in the turn lane at 0127 hours, a minimum of 11 minutes had elapsed while Hoffmans vehicle was stopped in the lane.  PRELIMINARY BREATH TESTS PBT not given.  ARREST:  Because of the above observations, I determined Hoffman was unable to operate a vehicle safely, and he was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at 0148 hours. Hoffman was taken to the barracks and a secondary search was conducted. At the barrack Hoffman was provided a copy and read the DR 15 Advice of Rights Form. Hoffman refused the Alcohol Concentration Test at 0258 hours.  Intoximeter Results: N/A  Hoffman was charged with driving under the influence of alcohol while operating a vehicle. Hoffman was ultimately released to the custody of his Lieutenant and given a ride home.  At this time, I request the case be closed. All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7381</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 01:08:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7381</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/15/2023 16:31:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hughes</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7110</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Parisan</LastName>
            <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4741</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quran</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7381</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492884</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/28/2023 01:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7381</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/28/2023 23:17:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7381</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/28/2023 23:17:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492884</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/28/2023 01:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7381</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/28/2023 23:23:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7381</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/28/2023 23:23:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492884</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/28/2023 01:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7381</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/28/2023 23:24:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7381</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/28/2023 23:24:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>51</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7381</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/28/2023 23:25:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:36</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>367470</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hoffman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Thomas</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/24/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/28/2023 22:54:13</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H155</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hoffman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Thomas</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/24/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H155</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/28/2023 22:54:13</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>309</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4557</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7381</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 16:27:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7381</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/15/2023 16:27:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7381</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/28/2023 23:17:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7381</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/28/2023 23:17:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149188</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7381</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/28/2023 23:27:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7381</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/28/2023 23:27:45</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/28/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WA1DKAFP4CA122312</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2012</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>AUDI</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>Q5</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>CR18129</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>