<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-014586</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/24/2023 21:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/24/2023 21:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/24/2023 21:27:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/24/2023 21:27:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop resulting in the arrest of the operator for DUI. Search incident to arrest revealed two cigarettes dipped in suspected CDS.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 21:57:01</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2864</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 12:31:59</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SR</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>CRISFIELD HWY/ LOVERS LN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>561506</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 21:57:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 09:12:52</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>561506</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Crisfield</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westover</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.736837</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.062409</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>6593-7035 CRISFIELD HWY / 29011-29362 LOVERS LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>7006-7981 CRISFIELD HWY / 29100-29375 LOVERS LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/24/2023 21:56:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/24/2023 21:56:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 12:32:01</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 21:57:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack X Tpr. J. D. Revel III, IBM 7146 Field Operation Bureau April 23rd, 2023  Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle:X-11 is a maroon unmarked 2021 Ford Explorer equipped with MVR system. Type of Report:DUI // DWI DUI Case Number:23-95-027 Driver/Suspect:Shamone Dekuron Price Date of Birth:2/26/1992 Subsequent Offender:No Accident Involved:No MVR Recordings:  Serial:X60A67491 Model: Axon Body 3 Link: https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=96f7693ee50c432f83aa86a646a955ddpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=54e6f3a6b828441e96453380049b5d30partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  Troopers Training/Experience:  * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).  * Trained and certified to operate Radar and LiDAR through the Maryland State Police.  * NHTSA certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E).  * Attended numerousNHTSA certified cannabis impairment detection workshops.  * Federal Motor Carrier Safety Administration (FMCSA) certified commercial vehicle weights officer.  * FMCSA certified North American Standard (NAS) Level III Commercial Vehicle Inspector.  * Attended the 2021 Middle Atlantic-Great Lakes Organized Crime Law Enforcement Network (MAGLOCLEN) Conference.  * Certified At-Scene (Level I) Crash Reconstructionist through the Baltimore County Police Department and Maryland Crash Reconstruction Committee (MCRC).  * Certified in Advanced (Level II) Crash Investigation through the Montgomery County Police Department and Maryland Crash Reconstruction Committee (MCRC).  * Attended the 2022 Maryland Impaired Driving Conference hosted by the Maryland Department of Transportation and Zero Deaths Maryland.  * Trained in Human Trafficking investigation and recovery through the Federal Bureau of Investigation and the Maryland State Police.  * Certified Standardized Field Sobriety Instructor through the Maryland State Police.   Narrative:  This report has been prepared based upon the observations of this trooper and/or those of other troopers relative to the offense(s). The facts contained herein are intended solely to give the prosecuting authority a basic understanding of the facts pertaining to this case. The facts contained herein are not intended to be an exhaustive recitation of the facts pertaining to pretrial or trial issues. Instead, this trooper anticipates that during the pretrial proceedings in this case, the prosecutor will take the opportunity to interview this trooper in order to ascertain any and all relevant facts which might be the subject of this troopers testimony during court proceedings.  Phase #1 - Vehicle in Motion: On the evening of April 24th, 2023, I was on proactive patrol along U.S. Route 13 in Westover, Somerset County, Maryland. At approximately 2129 hours, an off-duty Maryland State Trooper called the barrack and advised that he was behind a vehicle that was being operated by a possible intoxicated driver on MD Route 413 heading towards US Route 13. The caller advised that the vehicle, a maroon Nissan Maxima bearing MD registration 8EM0151, was all over the road, crossing both the center line and the fog line. I started to head over that way and positioned my vehicle on the side of the road on MD Route 413 @ Tawes Campus Rd. At 2131 hours, the caller advised that he could see me, and they were both approaching my location. As they passed me, the caller slowed down and allowed room for me to pass him and get behind the Maxima.  The Maxima started off at a speed of 44 miles per hour in the posted 55 mile per hour zone. The Maxima was all over the road, crossing both the shoulder and center line by half of the vehicles width multiple times. Before we entered the 45 mile per hour zone, the Maxima Accelerated to 76 miles per hour, dropped to 45, and then accelerated back to 73 miles per hour. Right as we approached Wedda Scott Rd, I activated my lights and siren to perform a traffic stop. The vehicle reduced its speed to approximately 30 miles per hour and continued driving for another 2,779.4 feet. Because the vehicle was approaching US Route 13, I drove around the vehicle and slowed down. The Maxima had another trooper behind him, so when I slowed down, it effectively boxed him in and brought him to a stop.  Phase #2 - Personal Contact: I exited my patrol vehicle and contacted the driver, later identified asShamone Dekuron Price(DOB: 2/26/1992). I approached the window, identified myself, and advised the reason for the stop. I also noticed that his car was not in park. I asked Price where he was coming from, and he just looked at me. I would continue to ask him a few questions, and he would blankly stare at me and not reply. While at the window, I detected a strong and distinct odor of an alcoholic beverage, as well as a strong chemical odor regressing from the passenger compartment of the vehicle. He had a glossy, glazed over look in his eye that seemed like he understood what I was saying but just wasnt answering. I asked him to step out of the car. He reached over and put the car in park. I had to ask Price to step out of the car three times before he did so. After Price stepped out, I asked him if there was anything on his person I should know about and to step to the front of his car. He just stared at me and did not move. I asked if he needed medical attention, he still did not answer. I asked him again to move to the front of his car and he just stood there at the door until I gestured for him to move. Price began walking across the street towards the guardrail contrary to my instruction. I told him to walk towards the front of his car. He turned around and walked straight past the front of his car and towards the other guardrail until I corrected him again.  Phase #3 - Pre-Arrest Screening: At the front of his vehicle, I asked Price what he had that night, whether it was any form of drugs or alcohol. I asked Price multiple other questions that he just refused to answer. I also asked if he had a drivers license, he just turned around and pointed at his car. I asked Price to remove his glasses and he refused. I asked him if he would like to participate in field sobriety, and if he wanted to I needed him to remove his glasses. He then took the glasses off. I asked him again if he wanted to participate in field sobriety testing. Price did not answer and just stuck his tongue out. As I stood in front of Price, I could still detect the strong and distinct odor of an alcoholic beverage, as well as a strong chemical odor. I asked two more times if he wanted to participate in field tests, and he shook his head no both times. I shined my flashlight more towards Prices face, so I could see his eyes. Prices eyes were very glassy and bloodshot. See the attached image for a depiction of Prices appearance at the time of his arrest.  Arrest and Transport Price was placed in the front seat of my patrol vehicle. After I placed him in my vehicle, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage that was not present in my vehicle prior to Price sitting down.  A probable cause search of the vehicles wingspan incident to arrest revealed a 200mL bottle of Absolut Vodka on the passenger seat that was a fifth full. It was also found next to a black grocery-style plastic bag that had multiple cigarette butts inside. Inside the center console, I located two cigarettes that had a strong chemical odor to them. They were soaking wet and likely dipped in CDS, suspected PCP. The aroma given off by the cigarettes match the chemical odor that I could smell on Prices person. See the attached image labeled IMG_8111 for a depiction of the cigarettes found, which clearly do not resemble normal Newport 100s.  Back at the barrack, I performed a secondary search and checked Prices mouth for foreign objects. I did not locate any foreign objects. I then pulled up a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, sat it in front of Price, and I played the DR-15 audio directly from the MVA website, having Price follow along. After the reading was complete, Price refused to take the intoximeter test. He repeatedly stated Im not drunk bro, while slurring his speech to the point of where it was almost unintelligible. When I mentioned the bottle of vodka and the dipped cigarettes found, he had nothing to say. Price also asked, on multiple different occasions, why he was arrested, despite my shift partner and I notifying him multiple times. The CDS was packaged per MSP policy and procedure, labeled, and forwarded to the lab for analysis.  Breath Test  Refused.  Charging  Price was charged with the following:   DRIVINGVEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL  DRIVINGVEHICLE WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL  DIRECTING AND PERMITTING VEHICLE OPERATION CONTRARY TO LAW  RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OF PERSONS AND PROPERTY  NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON  SPEED - 76/55  SPEED - 73/45  FAILURE TO DRIVE RIGHT OF CENTER  FAILURE TO OBEY A TRAFFIC CONTROL DEVICE  Price was given all appropriate documentation and released to a sober driver, Ebene Jackson.  I request this case be left OPEN, pending laboratory analysis.  All events did occur in Somerset County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 09:32:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 15:41:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Heun</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mason </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6661</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Revel</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7146</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504005</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/24/2023 21:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 09:19:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 09:19:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504005</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/24/2023 21:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 09:19:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 09:19:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504005</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>08</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/24/2023 21:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 09:19:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 09:19:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 09:23:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:17</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>100994</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Price</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shamone</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dekuron</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/26/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/16/2016 11:07:46</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S550</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Price</LastName>
               <FirstName>Shamone</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dekuron</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/26/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S550</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/16/2016 11:07:46</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>800</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>CHESTNUT</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>DELMAR</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.5678016374961</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.45322738034609</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1209</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Pocahontas</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21801</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.614102</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.384262</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>859</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4382</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 15:38:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 15:40:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 15:40:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 09:19:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 09:19:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 09:28:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 09:28:01</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/12/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Two (2) cigarettes dipped in suspected CDS, PCP</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>561</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>248592</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>J</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>2</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/17/2023 15:38:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/17/2023 15:38:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 12:32:01</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 15:38:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Added FAR</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/17/2023 19:55:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/17/2023 19:55:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Revel</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7146</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/18/2023 21:19:26</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/18/2023 21:19:26</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 12:32:01</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 21:19:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 10/16/2023, Shamone Price was placed under arrest for DUI (Drugs) under the same circumstances. At that time, I served him with the lab results indicating that the cigarettes seized from his vehicle contained approximately 1.8 Grams of Phenylcyclohexyl Piperidine.  The results are attached to this supplemental report.  I request this case be closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/18/2023 21:20:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/18/2023 21:25:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Revel</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7146</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/20/2023 12:24:32</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/20/2023 12:24:32</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/20/2023 12:32:01</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/20/2023 12:24:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:12</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Added copy of criminal citation that was served on 10/13/2023 after Prices second DUI arrest in an unrelated case. A copy of the test results were also provided.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/20/2023 12:25:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 12:25:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Revel</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7146</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>