<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-021280</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/13/2023 23:37:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/13/2023 23:37:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/13/2023 23:24:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/13/2023 23:24:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop leading to dui arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 23:37:22</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 10:47:33</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>CLOVERDALE RD/ MCWILLIAMS RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>697623</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 23:37:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 08:03:56</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>697623</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Cloverdale</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Rhodesdale</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21659</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.857194</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.574532</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4700-4799 CLOVERDALE RD / 5600-5699 MCWILLIAMS RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/13/2023 23:37:18</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/13/2023 23:37:18</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/18/2023 14:35:00</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 23:37:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> padding:0in 0in 0in 0in"&gt;TROOPER D. Walker- ID #7010 MARYLAND STATE POLICE  EASTON BARRACK I CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING: -NHTSA CERTIFIED TO CONDUCT STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFST) -CERTIFIED PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT) OPERATOR - I attended and successfully completed A.R.I.D.E (Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement) training  March, 2022.  DESCRIPTION OF VIOLATION / INCIDENT / TRAFFIC STOP (VEHICLE IN MOTION)- On 06/14/2023 at approximately 2324 hours, I Trooper Walker, was traveling on MD RT- 14 in the area of Centennial Road East New Market, Maryland when I observed a vehicle traveling on Centennial Road. I noticed a gray Toyota pick-up traveling off the right side of Centennial Road in the grass and then back to the center of the road way. As I followed the Toyota truck down Centennial Road the vehicle still failed to maintain a single lane. As we approached Cloverdale road the vehicle turned its right blinker on to stay on Centennial road but made a slight left turn onto Cloverdale Road. As I continued to follow the vehicle down Cloverdale Road, the vehicle was still unable to drive on the roadway, the vehicle went off the roadway by half a truck length four times before we approached Mcwilliams Road. I then activated my emergency lights, The vehicle stopped just before Mcwilliams Road, I identified the vehicle as a Gray Toyota Pick-up (MD/A370141) INITIAL CONTACT WITH DEFENDANT (PERSONAL CONTACT)- As I approached the driver side of the vehicle I made contact with the driver and soul occupant of the vehicle. I identified the driver as Wilbert Thomas Cole 2/M DOB (10/07/1987) who I identified by his Maryland Drivers license. I asked Cole where he was coming from and Cole stated Im just riding around. In speaking with Cole I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I noticed Coles eyes were bloodshot, watery and glassy. I then asked Cole if he had anything to drink, Cole Stated A couple beers I then went back to my patrol vehicle to relay Coles information to the barrack. When I returned back to the vehicle I asked to step out of the vehicle. As Cole stepped out of the vehicle he stated seriously. While speaking with Cole I asked him how much he really had to drink and he stated maybe a six pack. I asked Cole if he would be willing to perform in standardized field and sobriety test, Cole willingly agreed. Prior to taking the test, I asked Cole if he had any medical conditions that would interrupt his performance on the test, Cole advised he did not.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The first test I explained to Cole was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. Cole then stated he understood the test. As I began the test, I observed Coles pupils were of equal size and his eyes tracked equally. During the test, I observed Cole lacked smooth pursuit in both his right and left eye. I then observed Cole had distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both his right and left eye. I also observed Cole had onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both his right and left eye.(Clues:6/6) Note: I advised Cole multiple times to follow my finger and not to move his head.  The next test I conducted with Cole was the Walk and Turn test. This test was conducted using the paved portion of the roadway that was level and clear of debris. For the instructional portion of the test, Cole was asked to stand with his right foot in front of his left in a straight line. After Cole was placed it the starting position placing his right foot in front of his left, I advised him not to move until I instructed him to start. Cole was having a difficult time remaining in the starting position of the test. On the first set of 9 steps Cole did not remain in the starting position, stepped off line, missed heel to toe and used his arms for balance. As Cole approached his final step he completed an improper turn. Cole took 13 steps when he was instructed to take 9 steps. On the second set of 9 steps Cole again missed heel to toe and stepped off line. As Cole was walking on his second set of 9 steps Cole stopped and looked at me, I asked Cole how many steps he took Cole stated 5. Actual steps taken 7. (Clues 6/8)  Next I explained and demonstrated the One Leg Stand test to Cole. Upon completion of my demonstration, Cole advised he understood the test and began by raising his right foot. Cole began to sway, placed his foot down and raised his arms for balance as he counted. Cole had a difficult time counting correctly. Cole was told multiple time to stop putting his foot down.(Clues:3/4)   I then had my shift partner Tpr. Cooper retrieve my PBT from my patrol vehicle ( I-46). I explained to Cole the reason for using a PBT. Cole submitted a breath sample of .210.  Cole was then taken into custody at 2337 hours. At that time I placed Cole in my vehicle. Cole was then advised of his DR-15 Advice Of Rights by MVA recording and paper copy.  After hearing the recording, Cole refused to submit to the breath test at 2347 hours. I then transported Cole to the Hurlock Police Department where he received all of his paper work. Cole was later released to a sober driver.  All events did occur in Dorchester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7010</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 11:14:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7010</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 06:03:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cooper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Connor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7501</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Moore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2269</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dadds</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5551</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Walker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Drew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7010</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510715</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/13/2023 23:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7010</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 10:18:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7010</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 10:18:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7010</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 10:21:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:54</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>380512</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Cole</LastName>
               <FirstName>Wilbert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Thomas</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/07/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/22/2023 10:21:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W416</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Cole</LastName>
               <FirstName>Wilbert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Thomas</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/07/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W416</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/22/2023 10:21:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7010</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 14:29:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7010</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 14:29:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7010</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 14:29:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7010</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 10:18:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7010</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 10:18:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>