<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-004506</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/05/2023 03:35:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/05/2023 03:35:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/05/2023 03:11:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/05/2023 03:11:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/05/2023 03:35:35</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/19/2023 17:17:05</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY/ OLD BRIDGE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>532392</AddressId>
      <City>MDC208</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/05/2023 03:35:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/08/2023 20:39:27</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>532392</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.126391</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.339479</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12217-12319 OCEAN GTWY / 12295-12298 OLD BRIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50 / OLD BRIDGE (IN FRONT OF ATLANTIC GENERAL MED CENTER)</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50 E/O OLD BRIDGE (GRAND PRIX)</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12321-12325 OCEAN GTWY / 12295-12298 OLD BRIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 / OLD BRIDGE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12312-12320 OCEAN GTWY / 12295-12298 OLD BRIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12312-12320 OCEAN GTWY / 12299-12303 OLD BRIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12322-12324 OCEAN GTWY / 12295-12298 OLD BRIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12401-12409 OCEAN GTWY / 0-0 OLD BRIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 OCEAN GTWY / 12300-12311 OLD BRIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 OCEAN GTWY / 0-0 OLD BRIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12400-12418 OCEAN GTWY / 12300-12311 OLD BRIDGE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/05/2023 03:35:33</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/05/2023 03:35:33</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/16/2023 16:58:13</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/05/2023 03:35:35</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Walter Nieto-Silva Delaware SOUNDEX: 2197451 Breath Test Result: .10 DUI Citation # 5R20T5Y DUI Tape #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-004506 (Axon View XL Software)  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. * Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.). * Completed and graduated from the DUI Institute. * Completed and graduated from the SFST Instructor school  NARRATIVE -PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION- On February 05, 2023 at approximately 0311 hours, I (TFC. S. Shubert #6944), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating unmarked MSP vehicle V-08 in the area of eastbound US 50 at Samuel Bowen Blvd, Worcester County, Maryland.   At that time, I observed a white Chevrolet Silverado bearing Delaware registration (C73010) traveling eastbound US 50 at Samuel Bowen Blvd in lane two. I observed the white Chevrolet Silverado drive in the following manner:    Driver side tires cross the center dotted white line by approximately three feet and then drift back into lane two.  Driver side tires cross the center dotted white line by approximately one foot then drift back into lane two.   I observed the driver side tires cross the center dotted white line by approximately three feet then drift back into lane two  I observed the driver side tires cross the center dotted white line by approximately two feet then drift back into lane two.   I positioned my patrol vehicle directly beside the white Chevrolet Silverado. I observed from approximately eight feet the operator unrestrained and the seatbelt buckle resting against the b pillar of the white Chevrolet Silverado.   I activated my emergency equipment on eastbound US 50 at Old Bridge Road. I observed the white Chevrolet Silverado make a right turn onto Old Bridge Road and continue to travel eastbound bound on Old Bridge Road. I observed the white Chevrolet driver side tires cross the center solid yellow line by approximately one foot then then drift back into the eastbound lane. I then observed the white Chevrolet Silverado make a right turn onto Green Ridge lane and continue southbound. I observed the white Chevrolet Silverado make a right turn into 12309 Green Ridge Lane and come to a complete stop.  -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT- I exited my patrol vehicle and made contact with the driver via the driver side door. I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle. I requested his drivers license and registration card. I also observed the driver to display a dazed/expression looks on his face. The driver was later identified through his Delaware ID card as Walter Nieto-Silva. I asked Nieto how many alcoholic beverages he consumed prior to operating his motor vehicle and Nieto stated None. I observed Nietos movements to be lethargic and his speech to be slurred. As Niesto spoke, I observed his eyes to be glassy and bloodshot. I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Niesto. I also asked for a Spanish speaking officer to respond to the scene to translate.  I then asked Niesto to step out of his vehicle and walk to the rear of it. Which he complied. Ofc. Murillo #8384 from the Ocean City Police Department responded to the scene to translate. I asked Nieto if he wanted to submit to standardized field sobriety tests to insure he was not impaired and Nieto agreed to submit to the tests.   -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING- STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs) The evaluation was performed in the driveway of where the stop was located at. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of headlights and flashlight. Nieto appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any limps or any limb ailments.  Nieto was wearing black pants and a red long sleeve shirt.  Standardized Field Sobriety tests were instructed by myself and translated by Ofc. Murillo with the Ocean City Police Department.   **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**  1. Nieto displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  2. Nieto displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes. 3. Nieto displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes. ^^^I observed vertical nystagmus during the test^^^  **WALK AND TURN: 5 of 8 clues** Cannot keep balance during instructed position First nine steps: -Messed heel-to-toe by approximately two inches on steps 2,4,6,7,8 -Stepped off line by approximately three inches on step 3,5 -Took 10 steps when instructed to take 9 steps Turn: Completed satisfactory  Second nine steps: -Messed heel-to-toe by approximately two inches on steps 1,3,5 -Stepped off line by approximately three inches on step 2,4 -Took 6 steps when instructed to take 9 steps -Stopped on step 6  **ONE LEG STAND: 1 of 4 clues** -Placed right foot down one time during the test.  After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Nieto the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Nieto agreed to submit to the preliminary breath test, which resulted in .11 BrAC.  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Nieto was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot.  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.  * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests.  *lethargic movements  *Slurred speech  I placed Nieto under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0334 hours on February 05, 2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Nietos mouth for any foreign objects and none were found.   ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) Nieto was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Nieto was given his Advice of Rights via the audio version in Spanish of the DR-15 Form. I placed a copy of the DR-15 in front of Nieto. Once the DR-15 was completed being played Nieto stated that he understood his Advice of Rights. At approximately 0350 hours, Nieto advised he wanted to submit to the Intoximeter Test. I then transported Nieto back to the Maryland State Police Berlin barrack for processing. Ofc. Murillo also responded to the barrack to assist in translating.  Intoximeter: Cpl. Snell and myself checked Nietos mouth for any foreign objects. Nieto did not have any foreign objects or liquid located in his mouth. Nieto gave two valid breath samples, which resulted on .10 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.   PROCESSING During all aspects of processing (mugshot, completion and explanation of the DR-15A Form, issuance and explanation of citations), the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Nieto continued to be strong.  CHARGES Nieto was charged with the following citations: 1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (5R20T5Y) 2. Driving While Impaired By Alcohol (5R30T5Y) 3. Negligent driving (5R40T5Y) 4. Driver failure to obey designated lane directions (5R50T5Y) 5. Operator unrestrained (5R60T5Y) 6. Failure to display registration on demand (5R70T5Y) 7. Displaying expired registration plates (5R80T5Y) 8. Failure of individual to display drivers license (5R90T5Y) 9. Driving attempting to driver motor vehicle on highway w/o authorization (5RB0T5Y) 10. Directing permitting contrary to law (5RC0T5Y) 11. Driving under the influence of alcohol per se (5RD0T5Y) Case closed by arrest. All events occurred in Worcester County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/10/2023 18:36:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 15:56:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Benjamin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7043</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jenkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7357</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493889</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/05/2023 03:34:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 20:52:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/08/2023 20:53:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>36</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 20:52:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:19</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368557</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Nieto Silva</LastName>
               <FirstName>Walter</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>J</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/20/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/08/2023 20:47:34</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N324</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W436</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Nieto Silva</LastName>
               <FirstName>Walter</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>J</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/20/1986 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>N324</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W436</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/08/2023 20:47:34</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 20:54:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:48</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 20:54:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:48</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/08/2023 20:52:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/08/2023 20:52:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149657</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6944</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/09/2023 18:54:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6944</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/09/2023 18:54:32</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2001</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SLV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>DE</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>C73010</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>