<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-026263</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/23/2023 17:48:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/23/2023 17:48:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/23/2023 17:05:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/23/2023 17:05:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The operator was involved in a motor vehicle collision and under the influence of alcohol.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 17:48:55</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0266</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 07:23:02</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>BARCLAY RD/ BUSIC CHURCH RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>320820</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 17:49:00</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/23/2023 22:31:11</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>320820</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Barclay</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Barclay</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21607</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.81959</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.14416</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2211-2499 BARCLAY RD / 100-499 BUSIC CHURCH RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2210-2498 BARCLAY RD / 100-499 BUSIC CHURCH RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2208-2498 BARCLAY RD / 0-0 BUSIC CHURCH RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2211-2499 BARCLAY RD / 500-506 BUSIC CHURCH RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/23/2023 17:48:53</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/23/2023 17:48:53</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>80</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/05/2023 10:59:05</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 17:48:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:56</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was captured on an In-Car Camera, S-27.  Body Worn Camera (BWC) utilized.  SCENE PROCESSING:  All appropriate DUI paperwork.  PHYSICAL EVIDENCE:   DR-15 (Advice of Rights)  DR-15A (Officers Certification and Order of Suspension)  TROOPERS TRAINING AND EXPERIANCE:   *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (2014).  *Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) (2017).  *Maryland State Highway DUI Conference (Maryland Impaired Driving Conference) (2019).  NARRATIVE:    Defendant (DUI): Delfino Ramirez Tomas  Date of Birth: 01/12/1994  Date of Arrest: 07/23/2023  Time of Arrest: 1814 Hours  License #: None  DUI #: S-23-096 Centreville  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On July 23, 2023 at approximately 1705 hours, I responded to MD Rt. 302 at the intersection of Busic Church Road, Barclay, Queen Annes County, Maryland for the report of a Motor Vehicle Collision. I arrived on scene and observed two vehicles, one vehicle on the right shoulder of MD Rt. 302 and one vehicle on Busic Church Road. The first vehicle was a White Chevrolet Express box truck bearing Maryland registration A344719 and the second was a Black Jeep Cherokee bearing Maryland registration A279503. Refer to the ACRS report for further information.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)   I made contact with the operators of both vehicles. The operator of the black Jeep, identified himself as Francis Wayne Baker (W/M, 07/01/1994) who advised he was attempted to make a left turn onto Busic Church Road when he was struck in the rear end by the operator of the white Chevrolet and the operator of the white Chevrolet, identified himself by word of mouth as Delfino Ramires Tomas (H/M, 12/12/1999). Tomas could not provide any identification but advised he did not have a drivers license. I later learned from Tomas nephew, Rudibel Ociel Sales Ramirez (H/M, 12/26/2004) the correct spelling was Delfino Ramirez Tomas (H/M, 01/12/1994). While speaking with Tomas, I observed his eyes to be red, glassy, and his speech was slurred. I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. I asked Roberto for the registration and insurance to the vehicle, while attempting to reenter the vehicle, Tomas almost fell out of the vehicle attempting to get back into it. There was also a language barrier. I utilized the Language line with an interrupter to assist attempting to gather further information from Tomas. Tomas reactions were very slow. I asked Tomas how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed and he stated, None. At this time, I made contact with Tomas nephew, Rudibel to assist with translating for me. While speaking with Rudibel he asked what was next and I explained to him, I needed to run Tomas through the Field Sobriety to make sure he hadnt had too much to drink and Rudibel said, yeah when I opened the door I could smell it. I provided Baker all the appropriate information in regards to the Motor Vehicle Collision.. I asked Tomas to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety test to which he agreed.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   The Standardized Field Sobriety Tests were performed in front of Tomas white Chevrolet on the right shoulder of the roadway.The surface was flat, dry and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of daylight.    Tomas struggled to follow the directions due to his level of intoxication.   The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Tomas eyes, slightly above eye level. Tomas was instructed to position his head so that it was facing me, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Tomas pupils were equal in size, and showed equal tracking. I observed there was no resting nystagmus. While giving the instructions, I observed Tomas swaying back and forth. Tomas stated he didnt take any medications, or hit his head in the accident. Tomas stated he was just scared. When asked if he understood the instructions Roberto stated, Yes.  HORIZONTALGAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)   (No resting Nystagmus observed.)  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present  2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present  3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present   Vertical Nystagmus  Present   Several times I had to tell Tomas to use just his eyes and not move his head. Tomas struggled to follow simple direction.  WALK AND TURN (7/8 clues observed)   Prior to Tomas performing this test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Tomas was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot, touching heel to toe. Tomas was instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Tomas stated he understood. Tomas was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step. Tomas was told to keep his hands flat at his sides, keeping his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Tomas was advised to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Tomas was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. I advised Tomas I was taking three (3) steps for instructional purposes but he was to take nine (9) steps. Tomas was instructed once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keeping his hands down by his sides, looking down at his feet, and to count every step out loud. When asked if he understood the instructions, Tomas stated, Yes.  Instructional Stage:   Tomas was unable to keep his balance during the instructional stage. Stepping off line and utilizing his arms to aide in his balance.  Tomas started the test before being instructed to do so twice.  Walking Stage (1st Nine):    1) Missed heel to toe by more than 1/2 inch on step one.    2) Took a total of 8 steps.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  1)Stopped walking after completing the turn.  2)Stepped off line on step five.  3)Took a total of 8 steps.  Turn:   Improper - did not turn as instructed, pivoting on both toes.  ONE LEG STAND (4/4 clues observed)   Prior to Tomas performing this test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Tomas was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watching his raised foot, keeping his toe pointed straight forward, keeping both arms at his sides, to count out loud by thousands (one-one thousand, two- one thousand), and to continue the test until told to stop. When asked if he understood the instructions Tomas stated, Yes, Yes, Yes.  Instructional Stage:   Tomas swayed back and forth.  Balance and Count Stage:   Tomas began the test with his rightfoot raised.  Seconds 0 - 30:   Swayed left to right and back and forth.  Put his foot down and restarted the test.   Used his arms to aide in his balance by extending them more than approximately 6 inches from his side.  For information purposes: Tomas began the test before being instructed to do so.  PRELIMINARYBREATH TEST:   Tomas was offered a Preliminary Breath test and submitted with a test result of 0.239 BrAC. A mouth check was conducted at 1814 hours and was learned Tomas had removable teeth, I had him remove the teeth and place them into his pocket.  ARREST:   Based on the following totality of circumstances, I had reason to believe Tomaswas driving a motor vehicle under the influence of Alcohol:    * Eyes red and glassy.    *Stong Odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath.   * Driver continuously swaying for balance, while standing.   * Slow movements.   * Speech slurred and mumbled.   * Involved in a Motor Vehicle Collision.   *Could not follow simple directions.   *Almost falling out of his vehicle when attempting to get back into the vehicle.   *HGN: 6/6 W/T: 7/8 OLS: 3/4    Due to the number of observations, I concluded Tomas was driving under the influence of Alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At 1814 hours, I advised Tomas he was under arrest for Driving While Under the Influence of Alcohol. Tomas was read his DR-15, Advice of Rights, in Spanish. Upon completion, I asked Tomas if he wished to submit to the intoximeter test. At 1832 hours, Tomas agreed to submit to take an intoximeter test, to measure his breath alcohol concentration per 210 liters of breath. At 1844 hours, Cpl. Turpin attempted to conduct the intoximeter test, Tomas was instructed several times to blow into the tub. Tomas refused to cooperate resulting in the test being a refusal due to insufficient samples.    Tomas was charged with Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol and issued all the appropriate paperwork. Tomas was released to a sober adult.    Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Queen Annes County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6494</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/27/2023 02:04:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6494</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/30/2023 05:22:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wiley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6097</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mulhearn</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6494</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515708</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/23/2023 17:05:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6494</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 22:32:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6494</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/23/2023 22:32:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6494</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 22:54:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:09</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383301</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Tomas</LastName>
               <FirstName>Delfino</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ramirez</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/12/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/23/2023 22:39:24</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D415</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Tomas</LastName>
               <FirstName>Delfino</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ramirez</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/12/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D415</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/23/2023 22:39:24</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1217</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Dudley corners</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Millington</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21651</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.912367</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.211175</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>988</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2709</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6494</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 05:20:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6494</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 05:20:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6494</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 05:20:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:11</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6494</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 22:57:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383305</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Baker</LastName>
               <FirstName>Francis</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/01/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/23/2023 22:57:32</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F652</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Baker</LastName>
               <FirstName>Francis</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/01/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F652</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/23/2023 22:57:32</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>104</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Vickers</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>STE</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>B</SubNumber>
               <City>Chestertown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21620</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3327</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.089294</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.223666</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>778</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2279</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6494</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 22:57:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6494</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 22:57:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6494</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 22:32:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6494</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/23/2023 22:32:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155404</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6494</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 23:01:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6494</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/23/2023 23:01:16</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1GB3G2AG4A1154193</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2010</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>EXPRESS1500CGO</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>VN</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>A344719</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>FM</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>