<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-035038</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/06/2023 01:19:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/06/2023 01:19:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/06/2023 01:02:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/06/2023 01:02:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop that led to a DUI arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 01:19:37</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5660</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/21/2023 19:01:11</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>709219</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 01:19:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 02:15:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>709219</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Marlboro Pike / Donnell Drive</StreetName>
         <City>District Heights</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20747</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.88604</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.84895</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/06/2023 01:19:35</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/06/2023 01:19:35</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/21/2023 19:01:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/06/2023 01:19:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:55</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>L-41 is equipped with an MVR this incident was also recorded with my body-worn camera.  Defendant: Dannie Henry Michelle Sylla Date of Birth: 05/03/1994 Date of Arrest: 10/06/2023 Time of Arrest: 0114 MD License #: MD10272378756 DUI #: 23-315  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES   Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration on December 5th-8th, 2022.  Trained in administering Preliminary Breath Tests through the Maryland State Police Forensics Science Division on December 9, 2022.  Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement through the Baltimore County Police DepartmentsTraffic Training Team on May 15-16, 2023.  Vehicle in Motion (Phase 1):   On 10/06/2023, at approximately 0102 hours, I, Trooper Stacey #7390 of the Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack was conducting traffic enforcement on Marlboro Pike near Donnell Drive in Prince Georges County, Maryland. At this time I observed a gray Dodge Durango bearing Maryland registration 1FG2835, two traffic signals ahead of my vehicle. I observed the Dodge Durango fail to stop at the steadily red traffic signal at the intersection of Marlboro Pike and Kipling Parkway. Once I was approximately 2 car lengths behind the Durango it began to fail to drive right of center on Marlboro Pike, straddling two lanes of the roadway. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle at Marlboro Pike and Donnell Drive.  Personal Contact (Phase 2):   Upon my drivers side approach of the vehicle I witnessed the driver reaching in the back seat and I heard a glass bottle hit the floorboard. The driver was later identified by his Maryland Drivers License as Dannie Henry Michelle Sylla (B/M, DOB: 05/03/1994). I asked Sylla to retrieve the bottle that he just placed into the backseat, and he showed me a glass liquor bottle that was empty. Sylla advised he had drank it with his friends, who he just dropped off. Sylla was coming from a Washington Commanders football game and was on his way home. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. Syllas eyes were glassy and bloodshot. I asked Sylla to hand me his license and registration, at which time he handed me a red visa credit card. I told Sylla I needed his license and he began to continue searching for it. At this time I asked Sylla to exit the vehicle to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, to which he agreed.  Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3): The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of the road. The weather was clear and approximately 80 degrees. Lighting conditions were dark with lighting. The ground was level and free of any debris. My patrol vehicles overhead emergency lights in the front were deactivated prior to field sobriety tests as well as the vehicles spotlight. Sylla was wearing flat heeled shoes. Sylla appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible signs of injuries. I asked Sylla the following questions: Medical Conditions: None Glasses or contacts: No  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from his eyes. SUBJECT was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. SUBJECT pupils were of equal size and showed equal tracking. Sylla displayed the following clues:    Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eye  WALK AND TURN TEST (5/8 clues observed) Prior to Sylla performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Sylla was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and to touch heel to toe on an imaginary line. Sylla was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat as his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Sylla was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. Sylla was instructed to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Sylla was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to the left to turn completely around. Sylla was again explained and demonstrated the series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series, Sylla was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. Sylla advised he understood the test. Instructional Stage:    Cannot keep balance during instructions  Walking Stage (1st set of nine steps):     margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Misses heel to toe   margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Uses arms for balance   margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Steps off line on step 5 to 6  Walking Stage (2nd set of nine steps):     margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Misses heel to toe   margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Uses arms for balance   margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Improper turn  ***Sylla did not turn around after completing 9 heel to toe steps. Sylla instead, took 9 heel to toe steps backwards after agreeing he understood my instructions and demonstrations.***  ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed) Prior to Sylla performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. He was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands down by his side while the instructions were given. During the test he was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start, once the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Sylla advised he understood the instructions given.  Sylla displayed the following clues: Puts foot down:    0 to 10  11 to 20  Use arms for balance:    0 to 10  11 to 20  21 to 30  Sways:    0 to 10  ***First 5 seconds into OLS, Sylla fell backwards, catching himself on his vehicle***  Sylla was offered a Preliminary Breath Test to which he refused  ARREST: Based off of the following, I had reason to believe Sylla was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:    Odor of an alcoholic beverage on hisbreath  Eyes glassy and bloodshot  Admission of consuming alcoholic beverages  Open container of liquor in the vehicle  Clued observed during field sobriety  Sylla was arrested at 0114 hours and transported to the Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack. At approximately 0128 hours, Sylla was read the DR15 Advice of Rights played aloud via the MVA website English audio recording. Sylla refused to take the intoximeter examination test at 0201 hours. Sylla was given the appropriate citations and all pertinent paperwork and released to his wife at 0219 hours.  All of the above events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 02:27:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/17/2023 14:34:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6931</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Reily</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7338</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rogers</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dominique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5660</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stacey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7390</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524496</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/06/2023 01:02:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 02:16:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 02:16:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 02:21:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 02:22:52</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389777</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sylla</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dannie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Henry Michelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/03/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/07/2023 02:20:17</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sylla</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dannie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Henry Michelle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/03/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/07/2023 02:20:17</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7169</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Cross</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>101</SubNumber>
               <City>District Heights</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20747</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4317</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.8814822</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.8439892</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 02:22:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 02:22:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 02:22:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 02:16:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 02:16:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157816</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 02:26:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 02:26:33</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C4SDJCT8MC609740</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2021</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>DUR</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1FG2835</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>