<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-016263</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/07/2023 04:12:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/07/2023 04:12:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/07/2023 04:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/07/2023 04:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Accident that resulted in two DUI arrests</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/07/2023 04:12:57</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0392</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/17/2023 22:40:23</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>255746</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/09/2023 03:55:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/09/2023 03:55:21</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>255746</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>N</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Capital beltway</StreetName>
         <City>Hyattsville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>N</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>DR</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.8501591682434</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.9008024705708</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 CAPITAL BELTWAY / 0-0 ARENA DR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/07/2023 04:12:54</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/07/2023 04:12:54</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/17/2023 22:40:24</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/07/2023 04:12:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:27</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>L-8 is equipped with a mobile recording device, this incident was recorded. This incident was also recorded with my body-worn camera. Defandent: Fabrice Nji Date of Birth: 04/18/1999 Date of Arrest: 05/07/2023 Time of Arrest: 0429 hours MD License #:N200244002300 DUI #: 23-083  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES    Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration on December 5th-8th, 2022.  Trained in administering Preliminary Breath Tests through the Maryland State Police Forensics Science Division on December 9, 2022.  Vehicle in Motion (Phase 1):  There was no vehicle in motion as this was a motor vehicle collision. On May 7, 2023 at approximately 0401 hours, Fabrice Nji (B/M, DOB:04/18/1999) was operating a gray Infiniti G37 bearing WI registration WH2350A Southbound I-495 prior to exit 16A (Arena Dr). Nji explained to me when he was driving he suddenly felt a bump from behind and noticed he was struck by another motor vehicle. The other vehicle was a gray Jeep Limited bearing MD registration 89178HT by Eric Latimore (B/M, DOB: 09/06/1980). Both Nji and Latimore were identified by their Maryland Drivers Licenses.  Personal Contact (Phase 2): Upon my arrival I observed the gray Jeep in the left shoulder and the gray Infiniti blocking the exit ramp. I made contact with the driver of the Infiniti who was Nji. Nji explained he was driving at the time of the collision and was struck from the rear. Nji refused medical treatment from PG County Fire and EMS personnel. I immeditaly detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Nji breath and person, while he was standing outside his vehicle as well as glassy and bloodshot eyes. At this time I asked Nji to retrieve his license, insurance, and registration cards. After providing me with these documents, I asked Nji if he consumed any alcoholic beverages prior to driving, to which he replied with one beer, a budlight. Nji advised that he was coming from a party in Germantown MD and headed to Riverdale MD. At this time I asked Nji to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests to which he agreed.  Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3): The evaluation was performed on the left shoulder of the highway. The weather was clear and approximately 50 degrees. Lighting conditions were dark. The ground was on a minor slant and free of any debris. My patrol vehicles overhead emergency lights in the front were deactivated prior to field sobriety tests as well as the vehicles spotlight. Nji was wearing a winter jacket. Nji was wearing flat heeled shoes. Nji appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible signs of injuries.  I asked Nji the following questions: Medical Conditions: None Glasses or contacts: No  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from his eyes. Nji was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. Nji pupils were of equal size and showed equal tracking.  Nji displayed the following clues:    Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes   WALK AND TURN TEST (3/8 clues observed)  Prior to Nji performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Nji was instructed to place hisright foot directly in front of hisleft foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary line. Nji was instructed and demonstrated to place hishands flat at hissides and to remain in that position until told to begin.Nji was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Nji was instructed to keep hishands flat at his sides, keep hiseyes focused on hisfeet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Nji was explained and demonstrated to keep hislead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with hisrear foot to the left to turn completely around. Nji was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Nji was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep hishands down by hissides, look down at hisfeet, and count each step out loud.  Instructional Stage:    No clues presented   Walking Stage (1st set of nine steps):      Does not touch heel to toe      Improper turn      Uses arms for balance for steps 8 and 9     Walking Stage (2nd set of nine steps):    Does not touch heel to toe   ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)  Prior to Aji performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. He was instructed to stand with his feettogether and hands down by his side while the instructions were given. During the test he was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start, once the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Nji advised he understood the instructions given.  Nji displayed the following clues:  Raises arms for balance:    0 to 10  11 to 20  21 to 30   Sways:    11 to 20   Nji was offered a Preliminary Breath Test to which he agreed to take. Results: .15  ARREST:  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Nji was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:    Odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting fromhis breath  Eyes glassy and bloodshot  Clues observed during field sobriety  Admission of consuming alcoholic beverage    Nji was arrested at 0429 hours. Nji was transported to the Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack. At approximately 0440 hours, Nji was read the DR15 advice of rights, which was played in English via the MVA website. Nji refused to take the intoximeter examination test at 0452 hours. Nji was given the appropriate citations and was released to his brother at 0551 hours.    All of the above events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.    </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 19:24:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 20:06:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Reily</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7338</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rogers</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dominique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5660</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stacey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7390</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505682</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/07/2023 04:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 19:18:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 19:18:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 19:14:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377474</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>NJI</LastName>
               <FirstName>FABRICE</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/18/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/19/2023 19:06:37</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F162</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>NJI</LastName>
               <FirstName>FABRICE</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/18/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>N200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F162</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/19/2023 19:06:37</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 19:19:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 19:19:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 19:19:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 19:18:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 19:18:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/16/2023 11:08:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/16/2023 11:08:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/17/2023 22:40:24</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7229</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/16/2023 11:08:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:27</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This report has been expunged per District Court of Maryland.  Petitioner: Fabrice Nji  Date expunged: 8/16/2023</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7229</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/16/2023 11:09:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7229</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/16/2023 11:09:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bowling</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0392</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Matthews</LastName>
            <FirstName>Monica</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7229</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>