<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025106</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/14/2023 01:21:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/14/2023 01:21:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/14/2023 01:07:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/14/2023 01:07:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI arrest of Kerrie Anne Bunting.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 01:22:01</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/25/2023 00:27:09</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN EXPY/ RACETRACK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 01:22:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 02:55:49</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>EXPY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.170578</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.38053</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 E/O 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB/ 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 PRIOR 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MERGING OFF OF 90 INTO OCEAN PINES</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB BETWEEN BRIDGE AND OCEAN PINES EXIT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB PAST 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11083-11086 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1296-1352 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/14/2023 01:21:58</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/14/2023 01:21:58</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/23/2023 11:47:18</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 01:22:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:29:37</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Kerrie Anne Bunting [SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER] Maryland SOUNDEX: MD-10272219276 Breath Test Result: 0.14 DWI Citation #: 4QK0J79 DWI MVR/Body Cam #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-025106 (Axon View XL Software).   TROOPER CERTIFICATES / TRAINING / SPECIAL ASSIGNMENTS  1. Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. 2. Certified SFST Instructor. 3. Chemical Breath Test Operator. 4. Graduate of the University of Marylands DUI Institute. 5. Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. 6. Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.). 7. Trained in Cannabis Impairment Detection (Maryland State Police). 8. Assigned to the Berlin Barrack V Special Enforcement Team (focusing exclusively on DUI enforcement) from October 2017 - June 2022.   NARRATIVE   -PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION-  On 07-14-2023 at approximately 0107 hours, I (Corporal J. Ruiz #6312), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating marked MSP vehicle V-15 in the area of Maryland Route 90 near Mile Marker 8 at the base of the St. Martin River Bridge (Ocean Pines). I was stationary on the right shoulder area, monitoring all westbound traffic. At that time, I observed a sport utility vehicle traveling westbound pass my location. I made the following observations on the same vehicle:  NEAR MILE MARKER 8  1. The vehicles right tires were directly on top of the solid white shoulder line on one (1) occasion. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane.  2. Approximately 150 feet further westbound, the vehicles right tires crossed (1 tire width) the solid white shoulder line. I could hear the sound of the tires striking the rumble strips.  I safely entered the roadway and closed in on the same vehicle near Mile Marker 7.  BETWEEN MILE MARKER 7 AND THE MARYLAND ROUTE 589 EXIT  3. The vehicles right tires crossed the solid white shoulder line on one (1) occasion. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane.  4. The vehicles right tires were directly on top of the solid white shoulder line on one (1) occasion. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane.  ADDITIONAL OBSERVATIONS   5. The vehicle failed to maintain proper lane position due to pronounced and excessive weaving (alternately moving toward one side of the lane and then the other) during the entire duration of my observations.  6. Total distance traveled was approximately 1.88 miles.   DWI INDICATORS / REASON FOR STOP  The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHSTA) published a The Visual Detection of DWI Motorists booklet in March 2010. The research revealed that DWI cues related to problems in maintaining proper lane position include:  1. Weaving across lane lines 2. Drifting 3. Weaving  All of the above DWI indicators were exhibited by the SUV prior to my initiating a traffic stop on the same vehicle.   TRAFFIC STOP  I activated the emergency lights to my patrol vehicle, initiating a traffic stop on MD Route 90 westbound at the MD Route 589 exit. The vehicle was a black 2015 Ford Escape bearing Maryland Registration SU0068.   -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT-  I made contact with the driver via the driver side door, and I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop and requested the drivers license and the registration card to the vehicle. The driver was identified as Kerrie Anne Bunting by her Maryland drivers license. I asked Bunting where she was traveling from, and she responded: I am leaving work and heading home. I asked Bunting where she was employed at, and she replied: I work at Seacrets, and I live in Snow Hill.    As Bunting spoke, I made the following observations:  1. I intentionally observed her eyes to be glassy and bloodshot.  2. When asked how much she had to drink earlier in the evening, Bunting advised: Not much.   I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Bunting.   I later returned to the Ford and requested Bunting exit the vehicle and walk to the front of it, to which she complied. While at the front of the vehicle, I continued to speak with Bunting. I asked Bunting again where she was traveling from, and she stated: I have been in Ocean City for the evening, and I did work at Seacrets. And Im heading home to Snow Hill. I run the Ocean Pines Chamber of Commerce.   During my second interaction with Bunting, she advised the following:  1. Bunting had consumed: Maybe 3 drinks while in Ocean City. Bunting stated that the kind of drinks were all: Liquor.  2. When asked how much time had passed since she consumed her last drink prior to driving, Bunting advised: Oh, I havent had a drink in at least 2 hours.  3. As Bunting spoke, I smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person.   I informed Bunting that I wanted her to perform field sobriety tests which she agreed to submit to.    -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING-  STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder area. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and vehicle headlamps. Weather was clear and approximately 78 degrees. I asked Bunting if she had any significant medical issues with her eyes, arms, or legs which would prevent her from performing the field sobriety tests or if she had taken any medication prior to driving. Bunting responded: No. Bunting appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries, limps, or any limb ailments.  Bunting was wearing an orange flower design shirt, white capri style pants, and white strap sandals.  **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**   1. Bunting displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.   2. Bunting displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  3. Bunting displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.  **WALK AND TURN: 4 of 8 clues**  1. Bunting could not maintain her balance during the Instruction Phase. Buntings feet broke from the start position on two (2) occasions, and she stumbled to her right each time.  2. Bunting missed heel-to-toe on steps 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 9 during the first series. Bunting missed heel-to-toe on all steps during the second series. All misses were of more than half an inch.  3. Bunting did not complete the turn in a satisfactory manner, simultaneously pivoting both feet to her left which was contrary to my instructions.  4. Bunting was unable to maintain a straight line and stepped off the line on step 8 during the first series and steps 1 and 9 during the second series.   **ONE LEG STAND: 2 of 4 clues**  1. Buntings body swayed to the left and right on counts 5, 7, and 11.  2. Bunting put her right foot down on count 11.   ADDITIONAL ANNOTATIONS REFERENCE FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS // ADDITIONAL TESTING  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN):  A. Bunting displayed vertical nystagmus. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus is an involuntary jerking of the eyes (up and down) which occurs when the eyes gaze upward at maximum elevation. The presence of this type of nystagmus is associated with high doses of alcohol for that individual and certain other drugs.  Walk And Turn (WAT):  A. The solid white shoulder line was used for this test.  One Leg Stand (OLS):  A. At no point during the test did Bunting look down at her raised right foot as instructed. Instead, she looked out directly in front of her.  **ALPHABET TEST**:  Bunting advised that she was a high school graduate and that she was capable of reciting the English alphabet and numbers. I instructed Bunting to recite from the letter F to the letter S.   -Bunting recited from A to S.   **COUNT TEST**:  I instructed Bunting to count backwards from 36-19.  -Bunting counted in the following manner: 36-35-34-33-32-31-30-29-28-27-26-25-24-23-22-21-20-19-18-20-19-18-17-16-15-14-13. Bunting then stopped and asked at what number she needed to stop at. When asked if she could remember at what number she had been instructed to stop at, Bunting replied: I dont.   PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)  After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Bunting the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Bunting submitted to a PBT with a reading of 0.158 BrAC.    ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Bunting was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Driving vehicle in a negligent manner which caused it to commit 4 lane violations in addition to excessive weaving  DRIVING SKILLS IMPAIRED. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot. * Admission to consuming at least one (1) alcoholic beverage prior to operating a motor vehicle.  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. * My observed signs of impairment as she performed field sobriety tests.  * PBT reading of 0.158 BrAC.  I determined that Bunting was impaired by the presence of an alcoholic beverage in her system that adversely affected her ability to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests properly can also adversely affect the persons ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. I placed Bunting under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0121 hours on 07-14-2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Buntings mouth for any foreign objects and none were found.   ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)  Bunting was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Bunting was given her Advice of Rights via the audio version of the DR-15 Form (played through the patrol vehicles laptop speakers). A copy of the DR-15 Form was placed directly in front of Bunting, attached to the sun visor. At the conclusion of the audio version, I verbally re-explained the drivers license sanctions and penalties (section printed in red) to Bunting. Bunting stated that she understood her Advice of Rights and agreed to submit to a breath test at approximately 0136 hours on 07-14-2023.   TRANSPORT  Bunting was subsequently transported to the Berlin Barrack for processing. During transport, the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Bunting continued to be strong.   **INTOXIMETER RESULT**:  Prior to the breath test, I observed Sergeant D. Harper #1464 visually check the inside of Buntings mouth for any foreign objects. None were found.  The breath test was administered by SGT Harper at approximately 0155 hours on 07-14-2023, and two (2) sufficient samples of Buntings breath were obtained. The breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of 0.14 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.   RELEASE  Bunting was released to a sober driver at approximately 0223 hours on 07-14-2023.   SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER DETAILS  A check of the E-tix system revealed that Bunting was previously charged with DUI on one (1) occasion:  1. 2017 (Wicomico County)   CHARGES  Bunting was charged with the following citations:  1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (4QK0J79) 2. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol Per Se (4QL0J79) 3. Driving Vehicle While Impaired By Alcohol (4QM0J79) 4. Failure To Obey Traffic Control Device (4QN0J79) 5. Negligent Driving (4QP0J79)   Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 05:24:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 22:29:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Furness</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7275</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jonischek</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4794</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514548</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/19/2023 02:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 02:55:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 02:58:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514548</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/19/2023 02:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 02:55:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 02:56:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514548</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/19/2023 02:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 02:55:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 02:56:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>52</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 02:55:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382876</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bunting</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kerrie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/31/1970 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 22:42:52</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B535</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bunting</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kerrie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/31/1970 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B535</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 22:42:52</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>307</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Market</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Snow Hill</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21863</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1021</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.400218</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.173165</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>251</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2237</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 03:00:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 03:00:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 02:55:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 02:55:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155261</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 03:01:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/19/2023 03:01:06</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FMCU9GXXFUA34940</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ECP</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>SU0068</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>4</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>