<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-030027</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/25/2023 18:40:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/25/2023 18:40:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/25/2023 18:18:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI, DWOL, False Name</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/25/2023 18:40:04</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2650</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/03/2023 03:41:05</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>704994</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/25/2023 18:40:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:20:07</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>704994</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>93</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm Us-301 Sb</StreetName>
         <City>Centreville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21617</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.02155</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.03295</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/25/2023 18:40:01</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/25/2023 18:40:01</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>80</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/03/2023 03:41:07</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/25/2023 18:40:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On August 25, 2023 at approximately 1815 hours, I TFC Daigle was on duty in uniform operating my un-marked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle S-33. I was positioned in the center median crossover from northbound US Route 301 to W/B MD Route 305 monitoring the flow of southbound traffic. At the above stated date and time I observed a silver passenger vehicle traveling in lane #1 at what appeared to be traveling above the posted speed limit of 55 miles per hour. I utilized my Pro-Laser 3 handheld Lidar unit, placed the devices reticle on the violators vehicle and obtained a speed reading of 70 miles per hour in a posted 55 mph zone. Once the vehicle passed my location I observed a Hispanic male operator with long black hair, I also observed that the passenger vehicle was a silver Ford passenger car bearing Pennsylvania registration MGH3450. I pulled out onto southbound 301 in lane number 1 to conduct a traffic stop on the vehicle. Due to heavy traffic I was unable to pull out directly behind the vehicle. While closing the distance on the vehicle, I observed the violators car on the right shoulder of the roadway just prior to the Maryland State Police Centreville barrack crossover. I observed the driver and passenger get out of the vehicle and switch seats. The violator driver was now seated in the passenger side seat. I was positioned in the left turn lane for the barrack cross over, I activated my emergency equipment of my patrol vehicle and got the attention of the violator car, I waved them to move up the shoulder, which they did and I pulled behind them to conduct my traffic stop.  I conducted a passenger side approach on the vehicle to greet the original violator. I introduced myself and reason for the stop, during this interaction I detected the overwhelming odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from inside the passenger compartment of the vehicle. I deliberately observed the violators eyes to be, glassy, bloodshot, and his speech to be slurred. I asked him how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed which he informed he consumed three margaritas. Due to him informing me that he did not have his drivers license with him I asked what his name was which he replied Jonaton Velasquez. I then asked him to write down his name date of birth and address. He wrote Jonaton Mendez with a DOB: 10-05-2003. (Hereinafter referred to as Jonaton) I had reason to believe that he did not have a drivers license and that he was given a false name. I asked the current driver for his drivers license which I was informed that he did not have a drivers license either. I handed him my notepad and pen and asked him to write down his name. He identified himself as Martin Perez Morales ( Hereinafter referred to as Martin). I requested Jonaton to exit the vehicle, which he agreed and opened the door and stepped out. While Jonaton stepped out I noticed the alcoholic beverage bottle on the passenger side floorboard of the vehicle. Once outside the vehicle I could smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. Jonaton and Martin were both placed under arrest for driving without a license and providing false names. I asked Jonaton what his name was again and he informed me Jonaton when asked for his last name he replied Sanchez.  A search incident to arrest was conducted on the vehicle to locate any pertinent documents, drivers licenses, passports that may contain the pairs true identity. While attempting to locate information related to the identities of the pair my attention was caught to a lone cigarette in front of the vehicle gear shifter. In my experience as a Maryland State Trooper I have located cigarettes that look and smell identical to the one located inside the vehicle. The tobacco portion of the cigarette was dipped and saturated in a brownish liquid, which from knowledge training and experience I believe to be Phencyclidine (PCP). I know from knowledge training and experience that Phencyclidine to be a Schedule 1 narcotic and that it is a common trend to dip cigarettes into the PCP and smoke the saturated cigarette and a way to introduce the drug into the body in the form of smoking it, this type of tactic and referred to as Dippers. I searched Martins person and located two Pennsylvania identification cards and two Social Security Cards. Immediately by looking at them I was able to determine they were fraudulent. The first PA identification card was identified as Elber Velasquez Zunun (H/M, DOB: 05/02/2001, IDN: 32159583, Address: 3559 Jasper St Philadelphia, PA). The IDN# 32159583 comes back to a Frenjy L Jaquez Fabian (H/M, DOB:06/09/1995) and an address of 2400 Market St Apt A53 Harrisburg, PA. The second identification card was identified as Martin Perez Moralez (H/M, DOB: 05/02/2002, IDN: 32583941, Address: 1637 S 22nd St Philadelphia, PA. The IDN: 32583941 came back to a Abdul Raman Sesay (B/M, DOB: 12/24/1967 with an address of 1100 W Chester Pike Apt K13, West Chester, PA. Due to the proximity to the Maryland State Police Centreville barrack and the pair already placed under arrest that standardized field sobriety would be conducted at the Centreville barrack. I transported Jonaton to the Maryland State Centreville barrack for processing and Trooper Pettitt transported Martin to the barrack. Once at the barrack Jonaton was placed into the processing room inside the barrack, I requested him to perform a series of standardized field sobriety tests, which he agreed to submit. Prior to beginning any of the field sobriety tests I asked Jonaton two separate times if he had any medical conditions or vision impairments with his eyes which he stated no. I also asked if he had any medical issues that would hinder his ability to perform walking/balancing testing which he stated no.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: (6/6 Clues Observed) The first test that was given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test. The evaluation was conducted in the hallway inside the Maryland State Police Centreville barracks. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Jonatons eyes and I confirmed with him that he could in fact the stimulus clearly. Jonaton was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Jontatons pupils showed equal tracking and did opt have resting nystagmus. RESULTS: 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit-Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation-Present in both eyes 3.) Onset Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees-Present in both eyes  VGN: Observed. WALK AND TURN:  Prior to Jonaton performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Jonaton was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Jonaton was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position unit told to begin. Jonaton was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Jonaton was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Jonaton was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around by taking small choppy steps. Jonaton was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first. Jonaton was instructed that once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side and look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. Jonaton was asked if he understood the tests and he stated yes. Prior to the demonstration I confirmed with Jonaton that he did not have any medical problems or existing injuries that would hinder his ability to perform the test. The test was demonstrated and explained in the hallway at the barrack. INSTRUCTIONAL STAGE:    margin-left:8px"&gt;Started Too Soon.  WALKING STAGE (1ST NINE):    Missed Heel-to-Toe: (Steps 2, 7).  Stepped Off Line: (Steps, 2, 3, 7).   margin-left:8px"&gt;Stopped Walking: (Step 7).  Actual Steps: 7 Turn: Did not turn as demonstrated, turned around stopped, bent over, spit in hands rubbed them together, rubbed knees.  WALKING STAGE (2nd NINE):    Raises Arms for Balance: (Steps 4,5)   Missed Heel-to-Toe: (Steps 1, 2)   margin-left:8px"&gt;Stepped Off Line: (Step 2)  Actual Steps: 17 ONE LEG STAND: Prior to Jonaton performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Jonaton was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he would raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Jonaton was asked if he understood the instruction and stated yes. When instructed he could begin Jonaton squatted down and wiggled side to side.    Foot Down: 3, 19 seconds  Arms for balance: 6 second.  Hops: 10 second.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Sway: 10 second.  Jonaton was offered to submit to a preliminary breath test which he refused to submit. Jonaton was played the DR-15 Advice of Rights Spanish Audio version on my laptop and was provided a Spanish copy of the DR-15 to follow along with. At the conclusion of the reading Jonaton refused to submit to the breath test at 1929 hours.  I asked Jonaton to write his name and date of birth on a piece of paper which he wrote Edison Mendes with a DOB of 01/19/1995.  Both Jonaton and Martin were finger printed and sent off for identification. At the conclusion of attempting to locate their identities from fingerprints was unsuccessful and was unable to identify them.  Jonaton was transported to the Queen Annes County Commissioners office for his initial appearance. He provided a name of Edison Mendez DOB: 01/19/1995 to the commissioner. At the conclusion of the hearing he requested the assistance of an attorney and was temporally held at the Queen Annes County Detention Center. Martin was transported to the Queen Annes County Commissioners office for his initial appearance, whichhe requested the assistance of an attorney and was temporally held at the Queen Annes County Detention Center. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 22:39:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/03/2023 02:32:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pettitt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Julia</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7174</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Daigle</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6425</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Resh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2650</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Daigle</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6425</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>80</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Daigle</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6425</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:19:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:23:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:31:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15408</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:23:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:23:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21457</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:23:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3075</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:23:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:29:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:29:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:29:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:29:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:29:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>12</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:29:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>13</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>12</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:29:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>14</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>13</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:29:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519476</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>15</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>14</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/25/2023 18:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:29:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:23:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/03/2023 02:27:52</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386304</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Perez-Morales</LastName>
               <FirstName>Martin</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/02/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M635</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mendez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jonaton</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/05/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J535</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Perez Morales</LastName>
               <FirstName>Martin</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/02/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/27/2023 17:58:51</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M635</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Morales Velasquez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Josue</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/02/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M642</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>T</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Perez-Morales</LastName>
               <FirstName>Martin</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/02/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M635</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mendez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jonaton</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/05/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J535</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Perez Morales</LastName>
               <FirstName>Martin</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/02/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M635</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/27/2023 17:58:51</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Morales Velasquez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Josue</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/02/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M642</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>210</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Davis</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Easton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.070047</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.769747</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/03/2023 02:27:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/03/2023 02:27:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>20</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:29:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:46:51</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386207</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mendez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Edison</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/19/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E325</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mendez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jonaton</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/10/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/26/2023 18:25:07</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J535</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>A</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mendez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Edison</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/19/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E325</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mendez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jonaton</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/10/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J535</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/26/2023 18:25:07</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:46:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:46:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:23:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:23:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156518</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:49:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:49:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/27/2023 10:49:40</DateOfInfo>
         <DateOfInfo>08/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FAHP3FN2AW204578</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2010</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FOC</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>PA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>PA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>MGH3450</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicNumber>MGH3450</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehConditionCode>G</VehConditionCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:44:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:53</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>557</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>253411</Property_ID>
         <Make>Pennslyvania</Make>
         <Model>ID</Model>
         <Quantity>2</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6425</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6425</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/27/2023 18:45:16</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>253412</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>J</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>DU</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>