<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-030480</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/29/2023 23:01:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/29/2023 23:01:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/29/2023 22:42:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/29/2023 22:42:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI, DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 23:01:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/06/2023 10:54:26</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>705383</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 23:01:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/01/2023 21:12:40</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>705383</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>7400</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Ritchie</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Glen Burnie</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.62205</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.16747</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/29/2023 23:01:40</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/29/2023 23:01:40</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/06/2023 02:22:11</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 23:01:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:06:42</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Case # 23-MSP-030480 This incident was recorded. Body warn camera operational. In-car camera not equipped. SCENE PROCESSING:  - A visual inspection of the vehicle revealed a clear solo cup located in the center console with at green/ brown liquid inside. A further investigation of the clear cup revealed that it was a long island ice tea mixed alcoholic beverage inside. NEIGHBORHOOD CHECK:  - Due to the location of the crime, a neighborhood check was not conducted. NARRATIVE: DUI#: P-23-109 (Glen Burnie Barrack) Lakevious Antwone Griffin (DOB:04-17-1988) Date/time of arrest: 08/29/2023 @ 2336 hours  CERTIFICATION AND TRAINING *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Test through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * National Highway Traffic Safety Administration in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.)  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On Aug 23, 2023 at approximately 2242 hours, I, Tpr.Tenney (#7378) of the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack, was on route patrol Ritchie Highway in the area Georgia Ave. At that time, I observed a black BMW 328I displaying Maryland Registration plate 21DV21 parked in the CVS parking lot located at 7400, Ritchie Highway, Glen Burnie, Maryland after hours. I positioned my patrol car, MSP marked unit P-15 behind the BWI and activated my emergency equipment. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I exited my vehicle wearing my full Maryland State Police issued Class-C uniform, complete with brass breast badge. I approached the BWI on the drivers side of the vehicle. On my approach, I observed the tail lights and head light to be activated, exhaust exiting the tail pipe of the vehicle. Once at the drivers side window I observed the keys in the ignition and the driver unconscious in the drivers seat of the vehicle. I began to knock on the window multiple times with no reaction from the driver. A few minutes later I then opened the drivers side door. At that time, the driver woke up and acknowledged my presence and began speaking with me. At that time, I observed his eyes to be blood shot and glassy, his speech appeared to be slurred and a strong odor of alcoholic beverage was emanating from the inside of the vehicle. I asked the driver to turn off the vehicle and step to the rear of his car for further investigation. Once at the rear of his vehicle, I was the driver what was going on. The driver stated ya I was drinking and trying to sleep it off. At that time, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I asked the driver where he was drinking and how much he had to drink. The driver could not recall the place or the amount he had at the time. I asked the driver if he had a drivers license on him. The driver then reached into his pocket and provided me with his Maryland drivers license which identified him as Lakevious Antwone Griffin (DOB:04-17-1988). The drivers appearance matched the photograph on the drivers license. I asked Griffin if he was willing to preform standardized field sobriety testing. Griffin stated yes,sir   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  I asked Griffin the following questions:  Do you have any medical conditions? Griffin stated he had chronic headaches.   Do you have any pre-existing injuries? Griffin Griffin stated he has a trauma brain injury in 2019, reconstruction on his right foot  Do you take any medications? Griffin answered No.  Do you wear glasses or contacts? Griffin answered No.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) Test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Griffins eyes. Griffin was instructed to keep his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Griffins pupils appeared to be equal in size and showed equal tracking. I asked Griffin if he understood the direction and had any questions prior to the test he stated he understood and did not have any questions. The results were as follows:   1. Lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  2. Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  3. Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.  WALK AND TURN (5/8 clues observed)  Prior to Griffin performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Griffin was instructed to place his left foot on the parking space line and place he right foot on the same line in front of he left foot with the heel of his right foot touching the toes of he left foot. Griffin was to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in his position until he was told to begin. Griffin was instructed to take nine (9) steps on the straight-line touching heel to toe on each step. Griffin was told to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step out loud. After completing his ninth step Griffin was demonstrated and explained to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around his lead foot with his rear foot to turn completely around. Griffin was then explained and demonstrated to take nine more heel to toe steps on the same line in the opposite direction of the first nine steps. The second nine steps were to be performed identical to the first nine steps. Griffin was instructed that once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was complete. Griffin was again instructed to keep his hands down at his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. After explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked Griffin if he completely understood the instructions and asked if he has any questions. Griffin stated he understood and does not have any question. The results were as follows:  Instruction stage: 1. Cannot keep balance/ breaks feet apart. Griffin broke his feet from the starting position on one occasion.  Walking Stage (first nine): 1. Missed heel to toe on steps 2,3,5,6,7,8,9, and 10 2. Incorrect number of steps. Griffin was instructed to take nine heel to toe steps and Griffin took a total of 11 steps. 3. Steps off line on steps 2,4, and 6  The turn:  Completed unsatisfactory. Griffin completed the turn with his lead and follow foot planted while using his momentum to swing his body around.  Walking Stage (second nine): 1. Missed heel to toe on steps 2,3,5,6,7,8,9, and 10 2. Steps of line on step 2 and 4  ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed) Prior to Griffin performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Griffin was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. Griffin was instructed not to begin the test until told to do so and after it had been demonstrated. When instructed to start he was to keep his hands down by his sides, and raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his foot was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Griffin was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated Yes. The results were as follows: 1. Put foot down from seconds 01 and 18  2. Sways to the right to left throughout the test  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST Preliminary breath test was offered and refused ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe that Griffin was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Observations during standardized Field Sobriety testing.  * Observations during personal contact while speaking with the driver. I advised Griffin that he was under arrest for driving under the influence of Alcohol. A search incident to arrest was conducted and revealed no contraband was on his person, and nothing was in his mouth. Nothing was introduced to his mouth while he was in my custody. Griffin was read the DR-15 at 2330 hours on August 29, 2023 and refused to take the test.  Griffin was issued all necessary paperwork before being released into the custody of his wife All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland. Case closed by arrest.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/01/2023 21:14:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7378</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/01/2023 23:36:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lema</LastName>
            <FirstName>Carlos</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7659</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ricker</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5861</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tenney</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7378</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519929</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>18</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/29/2023 22:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 16:00:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7378</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 16:02:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 16:02:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/01/2023 21:12:40</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386611</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Griffin</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lakevious</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>antwone</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/17/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/31/2023 15:23:59</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G615</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L212</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Griffin</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lakevious</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>antwone</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/17/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G615</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L212</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/31/2023 15:23:59</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7810</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Contee</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>407</SubNumber>
               <City>Laurel</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20707</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.872366</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.078367</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 16:02:05</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 16:02:05</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 16:02:05</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/31/2023 16:00:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7378</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 16:00:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>