<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025249</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/15/2023 00:45:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/15/2023 00:45:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/15/2023 00:29:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/15/2023 00:29:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>23-085 "P" WATKINS</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 00:45:36</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6354</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 16:51:17</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>REECE RD/ PIONEER DR</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>700949</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 00:45:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 15:29:35</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>700949</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Reece</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Severn</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>DR</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.70909</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.12105</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1146-1179 REECE RD / 8142-8167 PIONEER DR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/15/2023 00:45:32</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/15/2023 00:45:32</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/01/2023 16:51:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 00:45:36</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:29:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E.) TEAM* The following incident was captured on in-car and body camera Defendant: Samantha Jane Watkins ****Under 21 years old****  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:  * I am trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (March 2013 SFST NHTSA Manual). * I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor as of February 2016. * I am a Certified Breath Test Operator by the Toxicologist of the State of Maryland as of March 2016. * I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of March 2016. * I am a distinguished graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute as of June 2015 * I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of May 2014. * I am a Preliminary Breath Test Instructor as of May 2019. * I am a RADAR and LIDAR Instructor as of October 2019. * I have apprehended more than 1,000 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On July 15, 2023 at approximately 0026 hours, I (Cpl. Wallace #6323) was on patrol in unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle DUI-1 in Anne Arundel, County Maryland. I observed a silver GMC SUV on eastbound MD 175 at Reece Road stopped past the white stop line at an angle in the intersection. When the light turned green the GMC made a left onto Reece Road. The GMC was unable to drive within a single lane and appeared to be traveling above the posted 45 MPH speed limit. I activated the front antenna of my Golden Eagle II Radar (S/N: EG-02387), which is a directional radar, in the moving mode (same). I heard a Doppler tone indicative of the estimated speed and obtained a speeding reading of 64 MPH in a posted 45 MPH zone (my radar unit was checked before and after my shift and was functioning properly. The GMC swerved left over the solid double yellow line with both driver side tires and immediately right. The GMC swerved left onto the solid double yellow line and right over the solid white line. I activated my emergency lights and conducted a traffic stop on the GMC bearing Georgia registration TDX3180 prior to Pioneer Drive.   The above referenced RADAR was calibrated before and after my shift and was functioning properly. I am a certified RADAR operator. Training certificates and calibration records will be made available upon request. This RADAR is specifically assigned to my vehicle.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the GMC on the driver side and made contact with the female operator of the vehicle, who was the only occupant in the vehicle. I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop and requested her drivers license. She was identified by her Georgia drivers license as Samantha Jane Watkins. While speaking with Watkins, I deliberately observed her eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I returned to my patrol vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with. Her license showed that she was under 21 years old and had an alcohol restriction.  I returned to the GMC and requested Watkins to exit her vehicle. She asked why, then complied and exited her vehicle. As I communicated with Watkins outside the vehicle, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. When asked about alcohol consumption she stated that she did not drink. She stated that she was coming from work and going home. I explained to her what I observed and that I detected an odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. She continued to tell me that she did not drink. I explained to Watkins based on what I have scene, I would like to ensure she was safe to drive home and she complied.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The weather was clear. Lighting conditions consisted of patrol vehicle headlights, spotlight, and flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests.   I asked Watkins the following questions:  Glasses or Contact  No Head injuries  No Medication  Yes, nothing that is going to impair ability to drive Problems with knees or ankles  No   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual.  - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus.    Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes     Moved head when instructed to keep head still.   Now stated she did not consent to the tests.  I explained that I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and why I wanted her to do the tests. She then stated she would do the tests.   WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed) The test was properly demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual, but not demonstrated. Watkins stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed.   Instructional Stage:  Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Stepped completely offline on step 2.  Stopped after step 1, 3 (regain balance), 9.  Turn: Turned left using both feet, one motion  Walking Stage (2nd Nine):    Took 10 steps when instructed to take 9.  ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual.  Watkins stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed.  Balance and Count Stage:    Swayed body to the left and right (all)  Raised arms more than 6 inches from side for balance (11-20 seconds)  Right foot hit the ground 1 time (11-20 seconds)     Skipped counting 1013.   PBT refused.   ARREST Due to the number of observations, I concluded Watkins was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0045 hours, I placed Watkins under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. Watkins was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and was transported to the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack for processing.  Upon arrival at the barrack, Watkins was provided with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Watkins listened to the DR-15 Advice of Rights from the MVA website. At 0123 hours, Watkins refused to take a breath test.   20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: Not applicable.  INTOXIMETER RESULT:  ****Refusal****  Watkins was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released.  All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/20/2023 12:05:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 16:41:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514691</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/15/2023 00:45:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/01/2023 16:37:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 16:38:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>19</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/01/2023 16:37:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 16:39:12</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>384011</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Samantha</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jane</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/30/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/01/2023 16:33:06</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W325</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S553</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Watkins</LastName>
               <FirstName>Samantha</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jane</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/30/2003 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W325</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S553</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/01/2023 16:33:06</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>337</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Osprey</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Richmond Hill</City>
               <StateCode>GA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>31324</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3467</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-81.324792</Longitude>
               <Latitude>31.922286</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/01/2023 16:39:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/01/2023 16:39:12</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/01/2023 16:37:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 16:37:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155648</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/01/2023 16:40:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 16:40:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2011</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ACA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>GA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>TDX3180</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>