<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-019413</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/30/2023 23:55:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/30/2023 23:55:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/30/2023 23:40:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/30/2023 23:40:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Hit-and-run collision leads to DUI arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/30/2023 23:55:31</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5364</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 13:08:00</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>W 495 TO N 650 RAMP / NEW HAMPSHIRE AVE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>695926</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/30/2023 23:55:32</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 04:31:23</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>695926</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>I-495</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Silver Spring</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20903</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>AVE</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.9834599</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.019961</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/30/2023 23:55:29</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/30/2023 23:55:29</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/03/2023 05:27:21</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/30/2023 23:55:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:52:05</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>N-20 is equipped with a mobile recording device, body worn camera operational. Body worn camera did not activate with front lights, initial contact with Siria and Standardized Field Sobriety Tests were not captured on BWC. Defendant: Abraham Siria 5/M  DOB: 08/30/1960 Date of Arrest: 05/31/2023  Time of Arrest: 0028 hours DUI#: 23-126  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING: * Successfully completed (6) month Maryland State Police Academy (6/2020).  * Trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (4/2022)   AUDIO VISUAL RECORDING: MSP unmarked patrol vehicle N-20 is equipped with audio visual recording equipment. Body worn camera also equipped.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1): On May 30,2023 at approximately 2349 hours, I, Trooper First Class Emerick #6888, was dispatched to the Outer Loop of I-495 in the area of Maryland Route 650 (New Hampshire Avenue), Silver Spring, Montgomery County, Maryland to make contact with a complainant of a hit and run collision. On the Outer Loop of I-495 west of MD RT 650 I made contact with the driver of a gray Jeep Cherokee who was identified by his Maryland drivers license as Jon Martin Vega. Vega told me that he was traveling in lane 2, when a white Ford truck bearing Maryland registration 5EE2489 approached his vehicle from behind. Vega told me that the Ford truck was driving in between lane 1 and lane 2 and struck the side of his Jeep and kept driving. Vega told me the driver of the ford was a white or Hispanic male.  Sergeant Landis #5082 stopped out with me. The collision occurred at the start of the construction zone of the beltway. I asked SGT Landis if he could make his way through the construction zone and attempt to locate the striking vehicle. A short time later SGT Landis radioed to me and advised he had the striking vehicle stopped approximately one half mile west of my location. I made my way with Vega to SGT Landis location. I observed the vehicle SGT Landis had stopped to be a white Ford Ranger bearing Maryland registration 5EE2489. The Ford Ranger had passenger side damage, and the passenger side mirror was broken off of the Ranger. The damage was consistent with the damage on Vegas Jeep.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2): I made contact with the driver of the Ford Ranger via the passenger side of his vehicle. I advised him my name, agency I work for, ID number, and that he was being audibly and visually recorded. I requested his drivers license, vehicle registration, and proof of insurance. I asked the driver why he did not stop when he hit another vehicle. The driver advised me that he did not know that he hit another vehicle.  At this time I observed his passenger side mirror was in the cab of the Ranger. As the driver spoke to me I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I also observed his eyes to be glassy and speech to be extremely mumbled.  The driver was unable to locate his vehicle registration and kept handing me different receipts to include Jiffy Lube receipts. The driver then handed me the title for the truck. The driver was unable to locate a current proof of insurance, and produced an expired insurance card. SGT Landis was able to get the operators Maryland drivers license. The driver was identified by his Maryland drivers license as Abraham Siria (Hispanic/Male DOB 08/30/1960). I then returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct an MVA check. The check revealed that Siria had a valid Maryland drivers license. I deactivated my patrol vehicles forward facing emergency equipment. I then requested Siria to step to the front of his vehicle to which he complied. As Siria was exiting his vehicle he was stumbling. I advised Siria that I wanted him to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests to which he consented.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3): The evaluation was performed on the Outer Loop of I-495 west of MD RT 650 in the construction lane closure, in lane 4 and the right shoulder. The surface was dry, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear, the lighting conditions were dark. I observed Siria to be in decent physical condition. I asked Siria the following questions: Glasses or contacts  Neither. Medications  Stated he takes a pill, asked him what kind of pill and he said he could not remember. Medical conditions  Stated that he could not remember. How much has he had to drink  two beers approximately 4 hours prior.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 CLUES OBSERVED) The first test given was the horizontal gaze nystagmus test. The tip of my right pointer finger was used as the stimulus and was held approximately 12 inches from Sirias eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following the tip of the stimulus with his eyes only until told to stop. Sirias pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking, and no resting nystagmus was observed.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes. 2.) Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes. 3.) Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes.  WALK AND TURN (7/8 CLUES OBSERVED) Prior to Siria performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Siria was instructed to place his left foot on the white fog line out in front of him with his right foot directly in front and touching heel to toe. Siria was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Siria was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step. Siria was instructed to keep his hands down at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count each step out loud. Siria was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to the left to turn completely around. Siria was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Siria was instructed that once he began the test he was to keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud, and to not stop until the test is complete. Siria was asked if he had any questions, he had no questions.  Instructional Stage: 1.) Broke from starting position on 2 occasions 2.) Started walking before instructed to do so on 6 occasions.  Walking Stage (1st Nine): 1.) Stepped off line. 2.) Missed heel to toe. 3.) Incorrect number of steps (33 steps).    Turn: Completed unsatisfactorily.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): 1.) Stopped walking after turn. 2.) Stepped offline. 3.) Missed heel to toe. 4.) Incorrect number of steps (43 steps).  I asked Siria how many steps he was supposed to take and he replied 9 steps. I asked him how many steps he took and he stated he took 9 steps.  ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)  Prior to Siria performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed Siria was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, and so on) and to continue the test until told to stop. Siria was asked if he had any questions about the test, to which he did not. Siria initially balanced on his right foot.   Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: 1.) Left foot hit the ground. 2.) Swayed side to side. Seconds 11-20: Siria was walking. Second 21-30: Siria was walking.   Preliminary Breath Test (PBT): While on scene, Siria submited to a preliminary breath test. The results were .15 BrAC   ARREST: Based on the following, I had reason to believe Siria was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol. * Being involved in a hit and run collision. * Glassy eyes. * Odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath. *Admission of drinking. * Clues during standardized field sobriety testing. *PBT results.  Siria was placed under arrest at approximately 0028 hours on May 31,2023. A preliminary search of Siria was conducted on scene. Siria was transported to the Rockville City Police Station for processing. Upon arrival at the station, I provided Siria with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Siria was also played the MVA recording of the DR-15 Advice of Rights in Spanish at his request. Siria elected to submit to an evidentiary breath test. The results of the intoximeter test were .19 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  Siria was transported to the Maryland State Police Rockville Barracks to wait for a family member to pick him up. Siria was charged with DUI, and released to a sober family member.  Case closed by arrest.   All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:48:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 04:44:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Emerick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6888</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Butler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andre</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0452</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Emerick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6888</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Emerick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6888</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508847</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16615</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16615</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 04:37:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508847</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3222</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3222</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 04:37:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508847</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3224</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3224</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 04:37:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508847</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 04:37:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508847</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15558</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15558</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 04:37:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508847</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 04:37:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508847</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 04:37:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508847</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 04:37:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508847</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 04:37:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508847</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:28:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17272</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 04:37:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>62</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378532</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Siria</LastName>
               <FirstName>Abraham</FirstName>
               <DOB>08/30/1960 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 07:17:47</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A165</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Siria</LastName>
               <FirstName>Abraham</FirstName>
               <DOB>08/30/1960 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A165</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 07:17:47</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9013</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Miles</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Silver Spring</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20901</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3753</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.990385</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.003916</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>855</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2084</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 04:38:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 04:38:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 04:38:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 04:38:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 04:38:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153621</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6888</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6888</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/01/2023 02:53:23</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FTYR10U03TA40437</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2003</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>RNG</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5EE2489</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>