<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013836</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/19/2023 02:30:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/19/2023 02:30:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/19/2023 02:12:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/19/2023 02:12:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop led to DUI arrest</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 02:30:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0392</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/04/2023 04:24:02</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>4 MM CAPITAL BELTWAY NB, OXON HILL</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>691227</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 02:30:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 07:25:43</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>691227</AddressId>
         <StreetName>N/B Capital Beltway</StreetName>
         <City>Oxon Hill</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20745</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.98107</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.806843</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/19/2023 02:30:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/19/2023 02:30:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/29/2023 09:24:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 02:30:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:31</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was recorded audibly and visually on BWC. L-23 is equipped with MVR. Defendant: Markos, Yohanes Negatu Date of Birth: 08/07/1990 Date of Arrest: 04/19/2023 Times of Arrest: 0230 Hours DUI # 23-126: (Forestville Barrack)  *REPEAT OFFENDER*  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *Trained and certified to operate the Preliminary Breath Test through the Maryland State Police.  SCENE PROCESSING A search incident to arrest resulted in the recovery of suspected raw Cannabis.  PHYSICAL EVIDENCE The physical evidence, in this case, is the suspected Cannabis recovered from the defendants pants pocket. The total weight was verified by Sgt. Sorenson #5368. Through my training, knowledge, and experience while at the Maryland State Police Academy, I identified the suspected Cannabis. The suspected cannabis was seized and processed according to agency policy and regulations. The Cannabis was stored on MSP Form 67 Chain of Custody under the Property Held P-339189.   VEHICLE IN MOTION On 04/19/2023 at approximately 0210 hours, I was on a routine patrol operating a marked Maryland State Police Ford Explorer L-23 in the area of N/B Capital Beltway in the area of Indian Head Highway and St. Barnabas Road, in Oxon Hill, Prince Geroges County. I observed a Silver Chevrolet Cruze bearing Virginia registration (1JON44) unable to maintain in its lane in lane four (4). Before I activated my patrol vehicles emergency equipment, the vehicle was driving between lane four (4) and the right shoulder. I then conducted a traffic stop on the right shoulder.  PERSONAL CONTACT I approached the passengerrs side of the vehicle. I already detected an odor of an alcoholic beverage from inside the vehicle. I also observed the drivers eyes to be glassy and bloodshot. I then introduced myself as Tpr. Thienhom#7518 and informed him that I stopped him for failure to maintain a single lane. The driver was later identified as Markos, Yohanes Negatu, 1/M, DOB: 08/07/1990, by his Virginia drivers license. I asked the driver where he was coming from and he stated, my brothers house. I also questioned Markos if he had anything to drink tonight, to which he denied it. Due to Markos exhibiting signs of impairment, I requested him to step outside the vehicle to conduct the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Markos stepped out of his vehicle and walked towards me. Immediately, I detected an odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Markoss breath and on his person as he was getting closer to me.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING The evaluation was performed on N/B Capital Beltway, prior to St. Barnabas Road on the right shoulder. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 48 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight, surrounding pole lights and my patrol vehicles lights. Markos appeared to be in good physical condition. (Reference below for further information regarding Markoss injuries and medications).  I questioned Mr. Markos the following questions: Injuries - Markos stated that his left ankle hurt from playing basketball in the past. Medication - No. Medical Conditions - No. Contact lenses - No. Glasses - No.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Markoss eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Markoss pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking and no resting Nystagmus was observed. I asked Markos if he understood the instructions and he stated, Yes.  1) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 degrees - Present in both eyes  Vertical Nystagmus - Not Observed.  WALK AND TURN (2/8 clues observed) Prior to Markos performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Markos was instructed to imagine a straight line and put his left foot on the imaginary line, place his right foot directly in front of his left foot, and touch heel to toe. After he assumed the instructional position, he was advised to keep his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Markos was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Markos was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step out loud. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Markos was again explained and I demonstrated that the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Markos was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Markos if he understood the test and he stated, Yes.(Footwear: White and Black sneakers).  Instructional Stage: 1) Unable to maintain balance - His feet broke prior to being told to start walking. 2) Starts too soon - Observed - Not observed.  Walking Stage (1st nine): 1) Stops while walking - Not observed. 2) Misses heel-to-toe - Observed - Missed the first three (3) steps 3) Step off the line - Not observed. 4) Uses arms to balance - Not observed.   5) Incorrect amount of steps - Not observed.  Walking Stage (2nd nine): 1) Stops while walking - Not observed. 2) Misses heel-to-toe - Not observed. 3) Step off the line - Not observed. 4) Uses arms to balance - Not observed. 5) Incorrect amount of steps - Not observed.  Turn: Completed properly.  ONE LEG STAND (0/4 clues observed) I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Markos was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, one thousand-three), and continue the test until told to stop. Markos was asked if he understood the test and he stated that he understood.   1) Putting foot down - Not observed.  2) Swaying - Not observed.  3) Hopping - Not observed.  4) Raising Arms - Not observed.  After completing the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, I asked Markos if he would be willing to take the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT). Markos refused to submit to the PBT.  ARREST/ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) Based on the following, I had reason to believe Mr. Markos was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: *Unable to maintain in his lane *An odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and on the person *Eyes were glassy and bloodshot  I arrested Markos for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0230 hours.Markos was then transported to the Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack. While en route to the barrack, I played the English audio DR-15 Advice of Rights form via the MVAs official law enforcement website to him in its entirety. At the conclusion of the DR-15, Markos verbally refused to submit to the intoximeter test and later (04/19/2023 at 0255 hours) signed the form indicating the same.While conducting a secondary search on Markos in front of my supervisor at the Forestville Barrack, I located a ziplock bag containing suspected raw Cannabis from Markoss pants pocket. Based on my knowledge, training, and experience in the Maryland State Police Academy, I identified the smell and greenish vegetable-like matter to be Cannabis.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the observation period on Markos in its entirety, starting with his time of arrest. I escorted Markos into the arrest processing room and remained in his custody until the time of the test. Markoss mouth was checked and no foreign objects or piercings were observed.  CHARGES Markos was charged with the following citations: 1. DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL (0TK0YJK) 2. DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL (0TL0YJK) 3. FAILURE TO OBEY PROPERLY PLACED TRAFFIC CONTROL DEVICE INSTRUCTIONS (0TM0YJK) 4. FAILURE TO DRIVE VEHICLE ON RIGHT HALF OF ROADWAY WHEN REQUIRED (0TN0YJK) 5. NEGLIGENT DRIVING (0TP0YJK)  Mr. Markos was charged accordingly on Civil Citation (5Z46647487) for possessing Cannabis in the amount of less than 1.5 ounces. Hewas also given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to a sober driver. Mr. Markoswas polite and cooperative throughout the process.  The total amount of cannabis was 3.04 grams, verified by Sgt. Sorenson#5368.  Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:15:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/29/2023 06:35:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Arioso</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7268</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sorenson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5368</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thienhom</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bryce</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7518</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503250</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/19/2023 02:12:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:18:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 05:18:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503250</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>CIVIL 5-601</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/19/2023 02:12:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>CIVIL 5-601</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:18:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 05:18:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 17:58:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:17</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374798</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Markos</LastName>
               <FirstName>Yohanes</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Negatu</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/07/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.30931574E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/20/2023 03:37:44</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Y520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Markos</LastName>
               <FirstName>Yohanes</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Negatu</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/07/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.30931574E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>M622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Y520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/20/2023 03:37:44</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5413</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sheffield</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>152</SubNumber>
               <City>Alexandria</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>22311</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.126379</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.825194</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>934</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9310</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>934</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9310</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 17:58:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 17:58:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 17:58:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 17:58:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/19/2023 05:18:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 05:18:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152164</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 17:59:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 17:59:34</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1G1BC5SM2J7184095</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2018</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CRUZE</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1JON44</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7518</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 18:00:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7518</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 18:00:50</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>247715</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>E</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>3.04</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>