<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-019107</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/28/2023 20:41:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/28/2023 20:41:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/28/2023 20:15:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/28/2023 20:15:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was stopped for speeding. The driver showed signs of impairment. The driver was placed on SFST's and arrested.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 20:41:10</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/20/2023 20:56:30</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>3467 BALTIMORE,FINKSBURG</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>695626</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 20:41:12</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/29/2023 19:26:14</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>695626</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>3467</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Baltimore Finksburg</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.8696745</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.4891833333333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/28/2023 20:41:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/28/2023 20:41:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/12/2023 12:12:05</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/28/2023 20:41:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:54:29</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI Case #23-087 This stop was captured on Axon body worn camera and in-car camera.  TRAINING: STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY CERTIFIED A.R.I.D.E (Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement) CERTIFIED STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY CERTIFIED INSTRUCTOR  DEFENDANT: Mervin Purnell Purdie B/M DOB: 04/07/1975 3565 Shannon Dr. Baltimore, MD 21213 443-800-3564  Phase #1  Vehicle in Motion On May 28, 2023, at approximately 8:15 pm I, TFC Adle of the Maryland State Police was on duty and operating MSP unmarked Unit G-07 in a stationary LASER assignment in the area of eastbound Route 140 west of the Baltimore County line when I observed a white Nissan Maxima bearing Maryland registration 8CC7533 approaching my location at what appeared to be a high rate of speed. I then began to track the vehicle with the Kustom Pro Laser III set 7. I am certified by the Maryland State Police as a LASER operator. All of the records are kept on file at the Westminster Barrack. On the date in question an accuracy test verification was made both before and after the stop on the Kustom Pro Laser III and it was found to be in proper working order. I operated the LASER per MSP policy. A LASER speed measurement was obtained on that vehicle which registered an actual speed of 70 miles per hour in a 50 mile per hour posted speed limit. The speed of that vehicle was acquired at a distance of 875.5 feet.  I activated my emergency equipment to conduct a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle stopped on the right shoulder just inside Baltimore County.   Phase #2  Personal Contact I made a passenger side approach on the vehicle and made contact with the operator and sole occupant of the vehicle. The driver was later identified as Mervin Purdie by his name and date of birth. I advised Purdie who I was and the reason for the traffic stop. I asked for Purdies license and registration. At this time, I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from Purdies breath. Purdie advised that he lost his wallet two days ago and did not have his license or registration. I then asked Purdie where he was coming from while I gathered my pen and paper to collect his information. Purdie advised he was coming from the Carroll County farm museum and then began mumbling and saying he was sorry as he began to get emotional. I asked Purdie if he was okay or if he was having a hard time with something in his life. As Purdie began to cry I continued to talk with him to determine what was wrong. Purdie advised that he just found out that his friend was diagnosed with an illness. Purdie collected his emotions and provided me with his information. I asked Purdie how many alcoholic beverages he has consumed tonight and he stated none as he motioned to a Gatorade bottle on the passenger seat. I then returned to my vehicle.  I made a second approach to his vehicle to collect his insurance information to verify his name and date of birth. I asked Purdie to exit the vehicle where I reviewed his insurance information. While we were standing outside the vehicle I again detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his breath. I asked Purdie how many alcoholic beverages he consumed and he stated I had a couple drinks. I asked Purdie if he would complete Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and he stated yes.  Phase #3  Pre-Arrest Screening I asked Purdie about the following questions:  Medications  No Contacts  No Eyeglasses  No Injuries  No Head Trauma- No  I am trained through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Transportation Safety Administration in administrating Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Weather conditions were clear and the tests were performed on a smooth surface free of any debris. Purdie chose to wear a pair of sneakers.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus  6 of 6 clues  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. Purdie was turned away from my patrol lights. My pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Purdies eyes. Purdie was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Purdies pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I asked Purdie if he understood my instructions and he acknowledged he did.  - Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes - Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes - Onset of Nystagmus Prior to Reaching 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes.  After looking at Purdies eyes, I asked Purdie how many alcoholic beverages he consumed tonight. Purdie stated one beer. I asked what kind of beer did he have and he stated a Heineken, no alcoholic in it, one shot of Vodka and one Natural Light. I asked Purdie where he was headed too and he stated Baltimore. I asked Purdie on a scale of zero to ten, zero being sober and ten being the drunkest hes been where he thought he was at. Purdie replied a two.  Walk and Turn  3 of 8 clues  Before Purdie started performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Purdie was instructed to place his left foot on an imaginary line and to put his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Purdie was instructed to place his hands down at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Purdie was advised to take nine (9) steps on an imaginary straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. He was to keep his hands down at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Purdie was demonstrated and explained to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Purdie was again explained and demonstrated the second series of steps to be performed identically to the first series. Purdie was advised once he started the test, he was not to stop until the test was finished. I asked Purdie if he understood all of my instructions in which he acknowledges he did.  *INSTRUCTIONAL POSITION * None  *WALKING PHASE* First 9 Steps - Stepped offline on steps 1 and 7 - Missed heel to toe on steps 2,3,4,5,6 and 9  -Turn was completed incorrectly  Second 9 Steps -Missed heel to toe on steps 1,2,3,4,7,8, and 9  One Leg Stand  2 of 4 clues  Before Purdie started performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Purdie was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands down to his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. He was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start, and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately six (6) inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, keep his toe pointed forward, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand two, one thousand three...) and to continue the test until told to stop (30 seconds). Purdie was asked if he understood the test and the instructions given in which he acknowledged that he did. Purdie chose to perform the test with his left foot.  *BALANCE AND COUNTING STAGE* Seconds 0-10 Used arms for balance Swayed Seconds 11-20 None Seconds 21-30 Used arms for balance Swayed  I offered Purdie the preliminary breath test in which he accepted. The results were .12. I reiterated to Purdie what he previously told me which was that he consumed one shot of Vodka, one Heineken beer, and one Natural Light. I asked him what else he had to drink in which Purdie replied thats it. I explained to him that I believed he consumed more than he was telling me and I asked him again. Purdie stated that there was no alcohol in the Heineken beer.Based on my observations I believed Purdie was unable to operate the vehicle safely, and he was placed under arrest for driving under the influence at 2035 hours. Purdies vehicle was moved with his permission farther over on right shoulder. Purdie was transported to the Westminster Barrack. While en route to the Barrack my patrol vehicle filled with the odor of an alcoholic beverage. At the Barrack, Purdie was provided and read the DR15 Advice of Rights Form in its entirety. Purdie stated he understood the form and refused to take the alcohol concentration test at 2058 hours. Purdie was issued citations and other appropriate paper and released to a sober driver. Purdie was respectful and polite the entire time.  Case CLOSED by arrest.     </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/29/2023 19:48:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6906</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 03:52:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reid</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7215</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Karas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5562</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Adle</LastName>
            <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6906</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508541</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/28/2023 20:15:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/29/2023 19:31:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6906</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/29/2023 19:31:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508541</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/28/2023 20:15:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/29/2023 19:32:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6906</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/29/2023 19:32:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>48</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/29/2023 19:36:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378375</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Purdie</LastName>
               <FirstName>Mervin</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/07/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/29/2023 19:35:04</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M615</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Purdie</LastName>
               <FirstName>Mervin</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/07/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M615</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/29/2023 19:35:04</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3565</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Shannon</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21213</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>800</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3564</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/29/2023 19:36:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/29/2023 19:36:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/29/2023 19:36:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/29/2023 19:31:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6906</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/29/2023 19:31:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153565</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6906</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/29/2023 19:47:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6906</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/29/2023 19:47:50</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2018</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MAX</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8CC7533</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>