<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-026093</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/21/2023 23:39:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/21/2023 23:39:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/21/2023 23:23:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/21/2023 23:23:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/21/2023 23:39:49</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 14:36:24</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>612 ROCK SPRING,BEL AIR</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>701659</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/21/2023 23:39:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 01:08:17</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>701659</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>612</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Rock</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>SPG</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.3593007333333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.5428239666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/21/2023 23:39:46</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/21/2023 23:39:46</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/09/2023 21:43:50</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/21/2023 23:39:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:27:58</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP Unmarked Vehicle, D-08: In-Car/Body Camera Operational  Case # : 23-MSP-026093  Arrestee Information:      Defendant: Howser, Matthew William      Date of Birth: 10/25/1991      Date of Arrest: July 21, 2023      Time of Arrest: 2338 hours     CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING      Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration      Certified in A.R.I.D.E(Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement) to enhance skills to observe, identify, and articulate the signs of impairment related to drugs, alcohol, or a combination of both      A distinguished graduate of Marylands DUI Institute, a rigorous 40-hour program that provides specialized training on enforcing laws related to driving under the influence.      Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police      I have apprehended more than 75 impaired drivers during my tenure as a Law Enforcement Officer to date.     VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On July 21, 2023, at approximately 1120 hours, I was in the parking lot of the Harford County Government Administrative Offices with my cruise lights on, working on reports. I observed a white male stumble across the parking lot from the direction of Looneys Pub located at 312 S Main St, Bel Air, Maryland. The white male was walking toward a black truck, parked in the parking lot of the administrative offices. I observed the white male enter the vehicle, which I later observed to be a black GMC truck with Maryland registration 7EC5049.  The white male had started the GMC and sat in the parking lot for a few minutes before leaving. I followed the GMC as he entered a public roadway, and began to drive northbound out of downtown Bel Air, I observed the operator struggle to maintain its lanethe GMC swerved onto the shoulder then back into the lane, and drove with one-half of the GMC on the shoulder, almost striking the curb.  I activated my emergency equipment to initiate a traffic stop on the GMC. The vehicle slowly came to a stop on the shoulder, blocking a private residences driveway.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I made initial contact with the operator, who was later identified as Matthew William Howser(2/M 10/25/1991) via the drivers side window, I introduced myself, provided the operator with the reason for the stop, informed him that he was being audible, and visually recorded, and requested his drivers license and registration. I observed the operators eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. Howser began small talk with me, asking how I was doing tonight. I could hear Howsers speech was slurred when he spoke.  I confronted the Howser regarding him coming from Looneys, to which Howser replied that he wasnt going to lie to me, it was his buddys 32nd birthday and he was about to tell me how far he lived away from where I stopped him before I cut him off, asking how many drinks of alcoholic beverages did he consume. Howser replied, Im not going to lie to you, two drinks. I replied, asking specifically what drinks did Howser have Howser took a moment, smirking and putting his head down before he replied Two orange crushes.  I asked Howser if hed hand me the car keys to his vehicle, which he did, and I returned to my patrol vehicle to call out Howsers information to the Bel Air barrack. I observed a Bel Air police officer had stopped out to assist me, I informed him that Id be asking Howser if hed want to perform field sobriety testing.  I returned to Howsers vehicle, and I asked that he step out of the GMC, Howser complied and stepped out. I asked if Howser would be willing to submit to field sobriety testing and Howser agreed to complete testing.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was completed out of the roadway, on a driveway. The surface was dry, level, and free from any visible debris. The weather was clear and approximately 75 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of natural moonlight.   I asked Howser the following questions before proceeding with Standard Field Sobriety Testing:   Physical Ailments/Medical Conditions/Medications  None.  Contacts/Glasses - No.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 CLUES OBSERVED WHICH INDICATE IMPAIRMENT)  The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and demonstrated to Howser before he had begun the test. I asked Howser if he understood the tests and he agreed. The following clues and observations were made during this test.        Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes      Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes      The onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes     *Vertical Gaze Nystagmus  Present in both eyes  NOTE: Before testing Howser made a comment that it didnt matter what he did while testing, and that his buddy was a police officer, as if he knew what was going to happen.  WALK AND TURN (3/8 CLUES OBSERVED WHICH INDICATE IMPAIRMENT)  The walk and turn test was explained and demonstrated to Howser before he had begun the test. I asked Howser if he understood the tests and he agreed. The following clues were observed:  Instructional Stage:      Started too soon      Failure to maintain balance/position     I was unable to fully conduct the standardized tests because during my explanation and demonstration of the Walk  Turn Test Howser became increasingly irate, and would not listen to my instructions. Instead, Howser continued to complain and try to instruct me to conduct the test in its entirety.  ARREST:  Based on the following, I had probable cause to arrest Howser for driving while impaired:      My observed signs of impairment as Howser performed field sobriety tests      My observed signs of impairment as Howser operated the motor vehicle      Howsers slurred speech      Howsers bloodshot and glassy eyes      Howsers admittance to consuming alcoholic beverages before operating the vehicle     Howser was placed under arrest at 2338 hours. A search of Howserss person was conducted in front of my patrol vehicle, and nothing of evidentiary value was found.  Howser was placed inside of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Bel Air barrack for further processing. Throughout the remainder of the night Howser was extremely irate and belligerent, threatening me multiple times and calling me expletives.  Howser was read a DR15 but declined to complete a breath test.  Howser was transported to the Harford County IPC to see a court commissioner regarding his charges.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD:  Nothing to report.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: REFUSED  I request the case be closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7208</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/05/2023 16:34:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5037</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/09/2023 21:42:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dudek</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5037</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Montgomery</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7208</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515538</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/21/2023 23:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7208</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 01:08:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7208</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/23/2023 20:19:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515538</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/21/2023 23:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7208</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 01:08:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7208</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/23/2023 20:19:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7208</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 01:08:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:16</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>10574</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Howser</LastName>
               <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>William</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/25/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.18542177E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>03/02/2014 07:55:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Howser</LastName>
               <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>William</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/25/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.18542177E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>H260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/02/2014 07:55:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3865</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Colwyn</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Jarrettsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21084</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.505933</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.609428</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>807</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2483</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/02/2014 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7208</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 20:21:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:17</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7208</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 20:21:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:17</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7208</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/22/2023 01:08:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7208</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/22/2023 01:08:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>