<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-032351</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/14/2023 21:15:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/14/2023 21:15:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/14/2023 20:38:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/14/2023 20:38:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>ACRS/DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/14/2023 21:15:26</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3033</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 14:37:04</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>72258</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>515</SubBeat>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/14/2023 21:15:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 18:10:50</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>72258</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2860</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>JEFFERSON</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PIKE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>JEFFERSON</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>515</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-77.57035904765056</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.358256015842066</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/14/2023 21:15:21</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/14/2023 21:15:21</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/02/2023 12:16:58</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/14/2023 21:15:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP1652</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/27/2023 19:27:24</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>CAR- B33 // Body worn Camera available // In Car Camera not available. Assisting TFC Oyola Body worn Camera available/ In Car Camera not available  Attachments: -METERS -ACRS -DR 15 - Photo of Drivers License - MSP 034  Defendant: Zachary Taylor Geiser   Date of Birth: 12/19/2001 Date of Arrest: 09/14/2023 Time of Arrest: 2215 hours MD License # MD-10272547481  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES   Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, June 2020.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On 09/14/2023 at approximately 2115 hours I, TFC Breakall #7145, currently assigned to the Maryland State Police Frederick Barrack and was operating marked Maryland State Police vehicle B33, when I was dispatched to a single vehicle collision on Jefferson Pike in the area of Gene Hemp Rd, Frederick, Maryland.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) When I arrived on scene, I made contact with the driver, who was sitting against the guardrail on the left shoulder. The driver was identified by his Maryland Drivers License as Zachary Taylor Geiser. While speaking with Geiser, I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Geisers breath. Geiser advised he had just left the Brookeside Inn in Jefferson. Geiser advised he punched it too fast as he was coming around the curve and lost control of his motorcycle. At this time, I noticed Geiser had thrown up on the ground beside where he was sitting. Geiser advised he had 3 beers at Brookeside Inn. Geiser advised the last beer he had was approximately 15 minutes before the collision. At this time, EMS arrived on scene and transported Geiser to Frederick Health.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed in room 10 of the Frederick Health Hospital. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. Geiser had two lacerations to his right leg and thigh. Geiser also advised me his left ankle was in pain. Before starting the test, I asked Geiser multiple times if he felt okay to take it, and he advised I will do my best.  I asked Geiser the following questions:  Glasses or Contacts  None Medical Conditions  None Injuries  Leg lacerations and Ankle injury Medication  None  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus. It was held approximately 12-15 inches from Geisers eyes, slightly above his eye level. Geiser was instructed to look straight ahead, keep his head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. Geisers pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking.   Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes  RESTING NYSTAGMUS NOT PRESENT. VERTICAL NYSTAGMUS PRESENT.  WALK AND TURN (2/8 clues observed)  The test was explained and demonstrated. Geiser was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Geiser was then instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and remain in that position until told to begin. Geiser was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Geiser was instructed to complete the second series of nine (9) steps in the same heel to toe fashion. Geiser was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keeping his eyes focused on his feet, count every step aloud, and once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Geiser if he understood the test and he confirmed that he did.  Geiser performed this test wearing socks.  Instructional Stage: - No clues  Walking Stage (1st Nine) - Misses heel to toe (steps 2, 3, 4, 5 and 7) - Steps offline (step 6)   Turn: Preformed correctly  Walking Stage (2nd Nine)  - Misses heel to toe (steps 3 and 5) - Steps offline (steps 4 and 6)   ONE LEG STAND (0/4 clues observed)  The test was explained and demonstrated. Geiser was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch the raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, etc) and to not put his foot down until the end of the test. I asked Geiser if he understood the test, and he confirmed that he did. Geiser advised me prior to starting he was going to use his left foot.  Balance and Count Stage:  - No clues                                                                               While on scene, I informed Geiser of his Preliminary Breath Test Rights. Geiser was offered a PBT, to which he agreed. Geiser results were .14  ARREST  Based on the totality of circumstances, I had reason to believe Geiser was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: - Single vehicle collision  - Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. - Clues during Standardized Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (6/6), WAT (2/8), OLS (0/4).  Due to the number of observations, I concluded Geiser was driving under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a vehicle safely.  At approximately 2215 hours, I advised Geiser of his DR15 rights. Geiser advised he wanted to take the alcohol concentration blood test. During approximately 2220 and 2258 hours, my body worn camera was not recording. At Approximately 2259 hours, Nurse Dane Palmer took Geisers blood sample and signed the MSP 034, agreeing that he was a qualified medical personnel.    I processed Geiser and released him to Frederick Health.   The defendant was issued copies of the following documents: - Case number/ Tow Information - DR-15  The vehicle was towed by Bussards towing and recovery.  All events occurred in Frederick County, Maryland.  I request this case remain open, pending blood results.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7145</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/15/2023 21:58:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7145</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 03:55:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oyola</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cristian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7028</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1652</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Breakall</LastName>
            <FirstName>Abram</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7145</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>521804</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/14/2023 20:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7145</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/15/2023 18:11:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7145</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 18:11:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7145</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/15/2023 18:19:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7145</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 18:19:01</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>387915</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>GEISER</LastName>
               <FirstName>ZACHARY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>TAYLOR</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/19/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/15/2023 18:15:41</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Z260</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>GEISER</LastName>
               <FirstName>ZACHARY</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>TAYLOR</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/19/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>Z260</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/15/2023 18:15:41</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Walnut Pond</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Middletown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21769</Zip5>
               <Zip4>7962</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.542932</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.437137</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>357</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5418</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7145</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/15/2023 18:19:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7145</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/15/2023 18:19:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7145</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/15/2023 18:19:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7145</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/15/2023 18:19:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7145</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/15/2023 18:11:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7145</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 18:11:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157113</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7145</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/15/2023 18:22:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7145</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 18:22:29</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1HD1CGP10TY221170</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>1996</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>CY</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>05425ND</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/21/2023 15:16:15</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/21/2023 15:16:15</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/27/2023 19:27:24</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7145</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/21/2023 15:16:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/27/2023 19:27:25</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 11/19/2023 at approximately 0814 hours, I responded to 5 Walnut Pond Ct, Middletown, Maryland. Once at the residence, I made contact with Geiser. Geiser was issued copies of the blood kit results, as well as charged for Driving under the influence. A DR-15A was completed on scene.  Case Status: I request this case be closed by arrest  All events occurred in Frederick County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7145</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/21/2023 15:20:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7145</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/21/2023 15:27:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hill</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1652</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Breakall</LastName>
            <FirstName>Abram</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7145</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>