<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025786</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP9800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/19/2023 14:46:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/19/2023 14:46:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/19/2023 14:07:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/19/2023 14:07:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>SEE NARRATIVE</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 14:46:25</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3267</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/27/2023 12:47:40</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>701412</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 14:46:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 12:09:16</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>701412</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>244</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Frederick</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Hagerstown</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.71808</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.635957</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/19/2023 14:46:22</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/19/2023 14:46:22</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40J</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/15/2023 14:09:53</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/19/2023 14:46:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 20:22:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>-THIS TRAFFIC STOP WAS CAPTURED BY A BODY-WORN CAMERA-   On 7/19/2023 at 1400hrs, Investigators from the Criminal Enforcement Division  Strategic Operations Group  Western Region were conducting criminal enforcement in Hagerstown, (Washington County) Maryland.   At that time, ST Deaner alerted MT Talbert and Sgt Smith to the area of Mulberry Street and East Avenue. ST Deaner observed a White 2017 Hyundai Tucson SUV bearing MD registration 2EM2950, which was exhibiting drug seeking behavior while traveling in a well-known drug area of the City of Hagerstown. The driver parked in a parking lot just off of Mulberry Street and walked out of sight momentarily down an adjacent alley.    MT Talbert and Sgt Smith positioned themselves in an advantageous area to observe the Hyundai and its driver and sole occupant, a white male wearing black shorts and a black t-shirt. Once the driver reentered his vehicle and left the area, MT Talbert and Sgt Smith followed close behind.    While following the Hyundai, both MT Talbert and Sgt Smith observed that the vehicles passenger side brake lamp was inoperative. Additionally, a standard check of the Hyundais registration revealed it was suspended for failing to comply to Marylands Vehicle Emissions Program (VEIP) and was also expired (March of 2023). MT Talbert activated his emergency equipment including audible siren and conducted the traffic stop in the area of the 200 Block of Frederick Street.    MT Talbert approached the drivers side of the Hyundai with Sgt Smiths passenger side approach. MT Talbert identified the driver via his MD-issued drivers license (B-100-887-067-911) as William Anthony Beebe (DOB: 11/29/1990  W/M).   Including the initial observations of drug-seeking behavior, a number of criminal indicators were observed during the initial contact, which resulted in the request of ST Deaner to conduct a K-9 scan. ST Deaners partner, Captain conducted the free-air scan, which resulted in a POSITIVE ALERT. The subsequent search revealed the following item on Beebes person, more specifically in his right sock:  -One (1) yellow traschcan containing a white rock substance; suspected CDS: Crack Cocaine (Schedule II)  Total Weight: 0.6 grams  -CERTIFICATIONS, KNOWLEDGE, TRAINING,  EXPERIENCE-  MT Talbert was able to identify the above-listed contraband based upon his nineteen-plus (19+) years of knowledge, training, and experience in the field of enforcing Marylands laws concerning controlled dangerous substances (CDS). MT Talbert graduated from the 122nd class of the Maryland State Police Academy and has successfully completed numerous courses accounting for thousands of hours of training in Maryland, West Virginia, Virginia, Pennsylvania, and New Mexico. During this time, MT Talbert attained several certifications that assist him in investigating the origins, production, manufacturing, distribution, and use of illicit street drugs and prescription medications. MT Talbert has also identified numerous controlled dangerous substances during his career based upon appearance, texture, and odor.    During his tenure as a Maryland State Trooper in both an overt and covert capacity, MT Talbert has conducted countless drug-related investigations resulting in hundreds of arrests with subsequent criminal convictions for possession, manufacturing, possession with the intent to distribute, and other crimes peripheral to the possession and trafficking of narcotics. MT Talbert also has extensive knowledge, training, and experience as it relates to the methods of administration for all seven (7) categories of drugs (inhalation, smoking, insufflation, injection, transdermal, etc.).   MT Talbert has also been identified as an expert witness numerous times in both the District  Circuit Courts of Maryland as it relates to controlled dangerous substances. MT Talbert is also currently certified by the International Association of Chiefs of Police (IACP) as a Drug Recognition Expert  DRE Instructor.   Beebe was released from the scene pending criminal charges. The suspected CDS was transported to the MSP Hagerstown Barrack where it was heat sealed in a clear evidence bag and all information was captured on an MSP Chain of Custody Log and an MSP Property Record.   Criminal charges were later preferred in this case by the Washington County Court Commissioners Office for the following criminal charge:  1.) Possession of CDS: Not Marijuana (Crack Cocaine - Schedule II) (Case #D-112-CR-23-003535 - Tracking #231001422831)   Based upon the above-listed information, this case is considered CLOSED BY ARREST / issuance of the criminal charge on the suspect, William Anthony Beebe.  -ALL EVENTS DID OCCUR IN WASHINGTON COUNTY, MARYLAND-</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4777</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 11:59:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4777</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/13/2023 12:27:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Deaner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Douglas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5830</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeremy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4780</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40J</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Talbert</LastName>
            <FirstName>William</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4777</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515230</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1111</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/19/2023 14:07:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>N/A</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1111</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4777</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 12:10:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4777</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 12:10:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4777</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 12:15:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4777</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 12:15:21</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>387067</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>BEEBE</LastName>
               <FirstName>WILLIAM</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ANTHONY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/29/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/05/2023 12:14:15</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W450</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>BEEBE</LastName>
               <FirstName>WILLIAM</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ANTHONY</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/29/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W450</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/05/2023 12:14:15</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>500</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4855</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4777</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 12:15:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4777</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 12:15:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4777</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 12:10:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4777</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 12:10:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <RoleCode>6</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4777</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/05/2023 12:20:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4777</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/05/2023 12:20:28</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>D</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>ONE (1) YELLOW "TRASHCAN" CONTAINING SUSPECTED CRACK COCAINE</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>560</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>253746</Property_ID>
         <DrugTypeCode>A</DrugTypeCode>
         <Quantity>0.6</Quantity>
         <QuantityUnit>GM</QuantityUnit>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>