<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-015291</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/30/2023 01:50:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/30/2023 01:50:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/30/2023 01:30:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/30/2023 01:30:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic Stop leading to a DUI Arrest</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 01:50:46</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2064</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/11/2023 07:30:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>N/B 295 @ 100</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>692391</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 01:50:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 03:57:51</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>692391</AddressId>
         <StreetName>N/B 295 @ 100</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.7336226666667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.1668571666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/30/2023 01:50:45</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/30/2023 01:50:45</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>65</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/08/2023 14:09:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 01:50:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:48</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-car camera operational. Trooper #7362 BWC was functioning and in use during this incident.  DUI # P-23-041   CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING:  -National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) certified to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs)  -Certified Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator  -NHTSA Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) certified   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)   On April 30, 2023, at approximately 0129hours, I, Trooper Litz #7362 was traveling in the area of Northbound Maryland 295 and Maryland Route 100. While traveling Northbound in lane 2, South of Maryland Route 100, I observed a silver Toyota Corolla bearing Maryland registration 1DR2493 traveling Northbound in lane 1, approximately 50 yards ahead of my vehicle. There were no other vehicles in between myself and the Toyota Corolla. I witnessed the Toyota cross the solid yellow line to its left, which was dividing lane 1 and the left shoulder area, with approximately 1/4 of the vehicles width. The Toyota then slowly returned its entire width back into lane 1. Then, for a second time, the Toyota drifted over the solid yellow line with approximately 1/4 of the vehicles width. I closed the distance between myself and the Toyota, and observed the vehicle from its passengers side from lane 2. While doing so, I was able to observe the driver both looking at, and talking at their phone while on a video chat with a female. Upon seeing this, I moved directly behind the Toyota in lane 1 and activated my emergency lights in an effort to effect a traffic stop on the vehicle. From the time I activated my emergency lights directly behind the Toyota to the time it came to a complete stop was approximately 36 seconds.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)   I approached the Toyota Corolla on the passengers side, and spoke to the driver through the passengers side window.I was able to identify the driver by his Maryland drivers license as Ashutosh Singh (O/M, DOB: 10/29/1993).I introduced myself to Singh and explained the reasons for the traffic stop.I immediately noticed Singhs eyes to be red and glassy and the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I asked Singh for his drivers license and the vehicles registration card. Singh was able to produce his drivers license, but had to be reminded that I also asked for the vehicles registration. Singh began to explain the friend he was video chatting with wanted to make sure that was getting to his home in Baltimore safely. I asked Singh where he was coming from, to which he informed me he was coming from Washington D.C. While speaking with Singh, I observed his words to be slowed and slurred. I asked Singh how much he had to drink while he was in Washington D.C., and he informed me he had 2 drinks. I thanked Singh for his honesty, and returned to my vehicle to conduct further routine searches of both Singh and the vehicle in the METERS/NCIC system. I also requested my shift partner, Trooper Garvey #7075 to my location.       Upon Trooper Garvey arriving on scene, I re-approached the Toyota and had Singh step to the back of the vehicle to talk with me further. While speaking with Singh outside the vehicle, I could still detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his breath and person. When asked again about what he had to drink while in Washington D.C., Singh first stated he had 2 beers. He then also stated he had 2 mixed drinks. At that time, I felt it appropriate to offer Singh the opportunity to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) in an effort to make sure he was safe to continue driving. Singh agreed to take the tests. While walking to the front of the Toyota, where the tests would be performed, I observed Singh stumbling over his own feet while walking.     PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed in front of Singhs vehicle, on the shoulder of Northbound Maryland 295 in the area of Maryland Route 100. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear. Lighting conditions were clear. Singh appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries.Singh was asked the following questions:   Glasses or contacts - Lacis Surgery -Singh stated this would not affect his abilities to perform SFSTs  Medical Conditions - Allergic to pollen - Singh stated this would not affect his abilities to perform SFSTs  Medications - Allegra -Singh stated this would not affect his abilities to perform SFSTs  Injuries - Wrist injuries -Singh stated this would not affect his abilities to perform SFSTs     HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 Clues Observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches away from Singhs eyes, slightly above his eye level. Singh was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his feet together, hands at his side and head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes only until told to stop. Singhs pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Singh was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. For the majority of the test, Singh was slightly leaning forward from the waist up and swaying back and forth.   1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes  2. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes  3. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes   Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was also observed in both eyes.      WALK AND TURN (4/8 Clues Observed)  Prior to Singh performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. While I explained and demonstrated the test, Singh was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch them heal-to-toe on an imaginary straight line. Singh was instructed, and I demonstrated, to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position while I gave him instructions. As I explained the motions of the test, Singh broke his position and returned to having his feet side-by-side. I instructed Singh to go back to the previously instructed position. Once I finished explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked Singh if he understood my directions, to which he advised he understood.    Instructional Stage:  1. Could not keep balance    First Nine Steps:  1. Stepped off-line on step 5    Turn Around:  1. Improper turn around   Second Nine Steps:  1. Stepped off-line on step 4  2. Missed heal-to-toe stepping on steps 2 and 3     ONE LEG STAND (2/4 Clues Observed)  Prior to Singh performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Singh was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while I gave the instructions. Singh was given the choice of which leg he would like to raise for the test. Singh elected to raise his left leg for the test. Once I finished explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked Singh if he understood my directions, to which he advised he understood.    0 to 10 Seconds:  1. Raised arms from seconds 1 to 3 before being reminded to keep hands at his side  2. Put foot down at 5 seconds   11 to 20 Seconds:  1. Put foot down at 14 seconds    21 to 30 Seconds:  1. Put foot down at 22 seconds     PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)      Singhwas offered the opportunity to take a PBT, to which he refused.     ARREST:  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Carson was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Singhfailing to maintain his lane of travel  *The odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Singhs person and breath  * Singhhaving red and glassy eyes  * Singhs speech being slow and slurred  * Singhinforming me he consumed alcoholic beverages before driving  * Singhs performance during SFSTs  At approximately 0150 hours, I placed Singh under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol, and sat him in the front passengers seat of my marked patrol vehicle, P-9, per agency policy. I then transported Singh to the Glen Burnie barrack of the Maryland State Police, and arrived to the barrack with Singh at approximately 0211 hours.    Singhwas read the DR-15 Advice of Rights form in English, as well as given a copy to read for himself. Upon the completion of the DR-15 Advice of Rights being read to Singh, I asked if he had any questions prior to his decision regarding the Intoximeter test. At approximately 0226 hours, Singh accepted the opportunity to take the Intoximeter test.     INTOXIMETER RESULT:      The test was administered at the Glen Burnie barrack of the Maryland State Police. The test was administered by Sergeant White #5951. Singh was given 3 attempts at providing a sample for the Intoximeter test. Singhs breath samples provided a final Blood Alcohol Content result of 0.14 at 0257 hours.   Singh was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to a licensed driver.  All events listed above occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.  Irequest this case be closed due to arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:50:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/08/2023 13:31:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Garvey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Killian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7075</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Swigert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4622</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Litz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Simon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7362</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504710</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/30/2023 01:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:00:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 04:00:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504710</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/30/2023 01:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:01:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 04:01:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504710</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/30/2023 01:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:02:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 04:02:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504710</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/30/2023 01:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:04:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 04:04:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504710</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/30/2023 01:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:05:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 04:05:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504710</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17523</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/30/2023 01:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17523</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:06:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 04:06:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:19:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:04</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375985</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>M</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Singh</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ashutosh</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/29/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/03/2023 04:17:05</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A232</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Singh</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ashutosh</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/29/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A232</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/03/2023 04:17:05</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:19:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:19:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:19:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:19:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:19:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:00:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 04:00:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152595</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7362</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 04:27:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7362</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 04:27:29</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2T1BURHE3EC174773</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>COA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1DR2493</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>