<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-043645</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/10/2023 14:35:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/10/2023 14:35:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/10/2023 14:29:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/10/2023 14:29:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/Accident</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 14:35:56</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0486</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/21/2023 11:10:31</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>715624</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 14:35:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/10/2023 21:05:33</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>715624</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>5022</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Old National</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PIKE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Braddock</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.493008</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.423215</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/10/2023 14:35:52</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/10/2023 14:35:52</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/21/2023 11:10:33</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 14:35:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/21/2023 11:10:33</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>VIDEO/AUDIO RECORDINGS: Car B-38 // Body Worn Camera Available // In Car Camera Available // Deputy Mayhew #602, Frederick County Sheriffs Office, Body Worn Camera Available     Defendant: Jeffrey Noe Lopez Grejalva  Date of Birth: 9/30/1996  Date of Arrest: 12/10/2023   margin-left:8px"&gt;Time of Arrest: 1515 Hours   CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING: *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Safety Administration.  VEHICLE IN MOTION: On 12/10/2023 at 1429 hours, I was dispatched to a motor vehicle collision in the area of Old National Pike (Route 40A) and Edgemont Road, Frederick, Maryland 21702. Deputy Mayhew #602, Frederick County Sheriffs Office, arrived on scene prior to my arrival.   PERSONAL CONTACT: Upon arrival, I made contact with Deputy Mayhew #602, Frederick County Sheriffs Office. The driver of vehicle one, a black 2015 Ford Explorer (MD Registration 2EZ7107), was identified as Jeffrey Noe Lopez Grejalva (H/M DOB: 9/30/1996), by name and date of birth. As I arrived on scene, I observed Grejalva swaying back and forth and side to side. Grejalva was unable to maintain his balance which caused him to stumble over his feet several times. As I made contact with Grejalva, I detected the heavy odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Grejalvas person. Grejalvas speech was slurred, and his eyes were bloodshot and glassy. Deputy Mayhew advised that Grejalva made several statements about not having a drivers license, and not wanted to go to jail. Deputy Mayhew also advised he detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Grejalvas person. Grejalva advised, The other vehicle was coming too fast, and I turned. Grejalva further advised, I dont have a license. I made contact with the driver of vehicle two, a 2024 Subaru Crosstrek (MD Registration 09522CL), as Andrew Christopher DeVriendt (W/M DOB: 6/25/1976). DeVriendt advised that he was traveling westbound on Old National Pike in the area of Edgemont Road in lane two. DeVriendt advised that Grejalva attempted a left turn onto Old National Pike from the driveway of Braddock Mountain Antiques, 5018 Old National Pike. DeVriendts vehicle struck Grejalvas vehicle in the drivers side front. DeVriendts daughter, Allison DeVriendt, was in the front passenger seat.  Beatriz Eugenia Zapata Parra (240-439-7808) witnessed the collision and remained on scene until my arrival. Parra advised me that the Ford Explorer pulled out in front of the Subaru. Parra advised that the the Subaru was not traveling at an excessive speed. Parra identified Grejalva as the driver of the Explorer. Parra was traveling behind the Subaru at the time of the collision.  I asked Grejalva, Cuantas Cervezas? (How many beers?). Grejalva responded with, Tres (Three). I asked Grejalva, Que Cerveza? (What beer?). Grejalva advised it was Modelo. Grejalva was then transported to the ambulance to be evaluated. While speaking with Grejalva, I continuously smelled the odor of an alcoholic beverage emit from his breath. While EMS was assisting Grejalva over to their stretcher, Grejalva stumbled over his feet, almost causing him to fall. EMS had to grab him to stabilize him.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING:  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN):  Not conducted due to Grejalvas condtion.   VERTICAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS(VGN): Not conducted due to Grejalvas condtion.   NINE STEP WALK AND TURN (WT):  Not conducted due to Grejalvas condtion.   ONE LEG STAND (OLS):  Not conducted due to Grejalvas condtion.    PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST: Preliminary Breath Test was not offered.   Grejalva was transported to Frederick Health Hospital. At FHH, a Video Remote Interpreter (VRI) was used to advise Grejalva the following (Reference Number SVL0814733):    I am going to read you a form that explains your advice of rights.  I am going to provide you a copy of the form to follow along with.  The form is going to ask you if you want to take test to measure the amount of alcohol in your blood.  At the end of the form, you will either agree to the test or refuse the test.  The form will explain the consequences for not taking the test or taking the test.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Grejlava was asked if he had any question, and he advised, No.   At approximately 1515 hours, Grejalva was advised of his Advice of Rights (DR-15) in Spanish. While the DR-15 was playing, Grejalva fell asleep several times. I had to wake Grejalva up each time. Grejalva was asked in Spanish, Do you want to submit to a blood test to measure your amount of alcohol? Grejalva agreed to submit to a blood kit. I asked Grejalva again, Just to confirm, you want to give your blood. He advised, Si, yes.  At 1627 hours, Chris Long, RN, drew blood from Grejalvas right arm for the first tube of blood. At 1633 hours, Long drew blood from Grejalvas left arm. The two tubes of blood were packaged per MSP Policy and the chain of custody was documented on the Blood Kit (B-371).   All events occurred in Frederick County, Maryland. CASE STATUS: Case remains open, pending laboratory analysis.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6996</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/14/2023 09:23:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6996</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/20/2023 05:50:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cain</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kenneth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0486</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Koontz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6996</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533120</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>08</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/10/2023 14:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6996</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 20:50:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6996</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 20:50:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6996</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 21:04:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 21:04:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>395116</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lopez Grejalva</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Noe</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/30/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/11/2023 20:55:40</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L122</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J160</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lopez Grejalva</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Noe</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/30/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L122</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J160</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/11/2023 20:55:40</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>413</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Harlan</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>301</SubNumber>
               <City>Frederick</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21702</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.458867</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.428845</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>707</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2871</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6996</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 21:04:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6996</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 21:04:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6996</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 21:04:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6996</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 21:04:53</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6996</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 20:50:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6996</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 20:50:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159784</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6996</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 21:07:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6996</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 21:07:28</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FM5K8B80FGA99366</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>XPL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2EZ7107</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>