<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-036813</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/20/2023 02:37:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/20/2023 02:37:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/20/2023 02:14:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/20/2023 02:14:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 02:37:17</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5082</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 00:48:27</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>689844</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7657</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/21/2023 01:44:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/21/2023 02:06:30</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>689844</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>N</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Crain Hwy @ Marlboro Pike</StreetName>
         <City>Upper Marlboro</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20772</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.7354964</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.8239286</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/20/2023 02:37:13</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/20/2023 02:37:13</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/14/2023 00:48:29</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/20/2023 02:37:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 00:48:29</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>THE FOLLOWING EVENTS WERE CAPTURED ON MY AGENCY ISSUED BWC.  Marked Car L-31: MVR available. Body Worn Camera: Body-worn camera available. Assisting Troopers/Officers: Tpr Murray - Body-worn camera available. Defendant:  Christopher Reyli Huitron-Encarnacion Date of Birth:  06/27/2005 Date of Arrest:  10/20/2023 Times of Arrest:  0237 hours DUI #: 23-MSP- 036813  (Forestville Barrack, 23-331)  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING  *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  VEHICLE IN MOTION   On 10/20/2023 at approximately 0214 hours, I Trooper was patrolling the area of Crain Highway and Pennsylvania Ave. in marked patrol vehicle L-31, when I observed a vehicle, later identified as a black 2009 Ford Focus bearing Maryland registration 8DT4880, driving Southbound in the Northbound turn lane. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle at the intersection of Crain highway, and Chevy Dr.  PERSONAL CONTACT   I approached the vehicle on the drivers side and attempted to make contact with the driver, later identified as Christopher Reyli Huitron-Encarnacion by his Maryland Learners Instructional Permit (H365115734502) however, he began slowly rolling forward. I ordered Huitron to stop the vehicle and he complied. I made contact with Huitron, and I immediately detected the strong odor of burnt marijuana emanating from the vehicle. I asked Huitron what he was doing. Huitron stated that he was going home. I informed Huitron that he was on the wrong side of the road and he replied my bad. I asked Huitron if he had had anything to drink and he stated no. I asked Huitron the last time he smoked marijuana and he stated he had smoked 1 (one) gram of marijuana three hours prior to driving. Huitron stated that he was heading home from the office and was utilizing GPS. Huitron was holding his cell phone with a map app open and Huitron stated that it told him to turn right. I asked Huitron if he knew he was on the wrong side of the road to which he replied no. Due to being stopped in the travel portion of the roadway, and with poor lighting conditions, I asked Huitron to move his vehicle off the main road to Chevy Dr. to which Huitron complied.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING   The evaluation was performed on Chevy Dr. which is a short, dead-end street (asphalt). The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear. Lighting conditions consisted of my patrol vehicle headlamps and my flashlight. Huitron appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. I detected the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage once Huitron stepped out of the vehicle.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12-15 inches from Huitrons eyes. Huitron was instructed to look at the tip of my pen and follow it with his eyes only and not to move his head. Huitrons pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes  2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes  3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes. VGN - Present.  WALK AND TURN (8/8 clues observed)  Prior to Huiton performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Huitron was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Huitron was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands at his sides. Huitron was advised to take nine (9) heel to toe steps in a straight-line. Huitron was to keep his hands at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Huitron was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot planted, and take a series of small steps with the other foot to turn around. Huitron was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps that were to be performed identical to the first series. Huitron was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. Instructional Stage: 1.) Did not maintain balance, stood with feet apart. Started too soon. Walking Stage (1st Nine): 1.) Missed heel to toe on every step. 2.) Stepped off line.  3.) Took 13 steps.  4.) Raised Arms more than six inches.  4.) Improper turn. Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  1.) Missed heel to toe on every step. 2.) Stepped off line and lost balance on step three.  3.) Took 15 steps.  4.) Raised Arms more than six inches.  ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)  Prior to Huitron performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Huitron was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Huitron chose to balance on his right foot initially and put his foot down after three (3) seconds. Instructional Stage: 1.) Did not stand still. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10:   Sways.  Put foot down.  Arm raised looking at watch.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Did not count aloud.  Seconds 11-20:    Sways.  Put foot down.  Arm raised looking at watch.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Did not count aloud.  Seconds 21-30:    Sways.  Put foot down.  Arm raised looking at watch.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Did not count aloud.  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Huitron was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and drugs: * I observed Huitron driving a vehicle on the wrong side of the road. * Strong odor of burnt marijuana emanating from the vehicle, and moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath. * Eyes bloodshot. * Admission to ingesting one gram of marijuana. * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests. I arrested Hutron for driving under the influence of alcohol and drugs at approximately 0237 hours and he was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. I searched the passenger compartment of Huitrons vehicle incident to arrest, and located a glass smoking device (bong), and an open bottle of New Amsterdam peach vodka (both in the front passenger floor board). It should be noted that the front passenger side floorboard was soaked in the alcoholic beverage. Huiton was transported to the Forestville Barrack for processing. While transporting Huitron, he stated that he was probably high as shit. Huitron stated that he was just following the map and had no idea he was on the wrong side of the road.  INTOXIMETER RESULT   Refused at approximately 0311 hours.  Huitron was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released from my custody at his residence located at 1323 Farrara Dr. in Odenton. All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland. Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7657</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/21/2023 19:15:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7657</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 14:37:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Murray</LastName>
            <FirstName>Niall</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7580</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Landis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dwayne</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5082</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Greenlee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Clint</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7657</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>526275</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/20/2023 02:14:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7657</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/21/2023 02:06:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7657</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/21/2023 02:06:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>18</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7657</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/21/2023 02:07:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/21/2023 02:07:25</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390881</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Huitron-Encarnacion</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christop r</FirstName>
               <DOB>06/27/2005 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/21/2023 01:53:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H365</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Huitron-Encarnacion</LastName>
               <FirstName>Christop r</FirstName>
               <DOB>06/27/2005 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H365</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/21/2023 01:53:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1323</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Farrara</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Odenton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21113</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2116</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.702302</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.06617</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7657</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/21/2023 02:07:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7657</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/21/2023 02:06:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7657</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/21/2023 02:06:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158250</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7657</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/21/2023 02:08:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7657</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/21/2023 02:08:34</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/21/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>13</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2009</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FOC</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8DT4880</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>