<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-039838</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/11/2023 00:34:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/11/2023 00:34:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/10/2023 23:57:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/10/2023 23:57:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop resulting in the driver being placed under arrest for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 00:34:34</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5364</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 11:51:45</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>10343 GEORGIA,SILVER SPRING</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>712744</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 00:34:35</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 12:12:21</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>712744</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>10343</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Georgia Silver</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>SPG</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.0458781166667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0247682666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/11/2023 00:34:31</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/11/2023 00:34:31</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/28/2023 18:47:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/11/2023 00:34:34</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSPQ031</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 11:32:08</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP unmarked vehicle N-7 is equipped with a mobile recording device  Defendant: Melanie A. Pino Date of Birth: 02/27/2002 Date of Arrest: 11/11/2023 Time of Arrest: 0030 hours DUI #: 23-245  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *Trained in administering advanced standardized field sobriety tests (ARIDE) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *Attended the DUI Conference held by the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On November 11, 2023, at approximately 2357 hours, I, Trooper Lear (#7154), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating unmarked MSP vehicle N-7 in Silver Spring, Montgomery County, Maryland. I observed a black Acura TLX pass me in lane one at a high rate of speed in the area of eastbound I-495 at Maryland Route 97. I observed the Acura exit onto the ramp to northbound Maryland Route 97 from eastbound I-495. I observed the Acura almost run off the left side of the exit ramp. I paced the Acura on northbound Maryland Route 97 for approximately three tenths of a mile at equal distance and equal speed. The Acura reached 62 miles per hour in a 55 mile per hour zone. I observed the Acura cross from lane one into lane two with more than a tires width on one occasion. I observed the Acura make a lane change from lane three to lane two in the intersection of Maryland Route 97 and Forest Glen Road. I activated my emergency equipment to conduct a traffic stop on the Acura. The Acura pulled over to the left hand turn lane on northbound Maryland Route 97 at Dayton Street. The Acura was bearing MD registration 8EM0661.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I made contact with the driver of the Acura and immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I immediately observed the drivers eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. The driver was identified by her MD drivers license as Melanie A. Pino (DOB: 02/27/2002, H/F). Pino admitted to her traveling at a high rate of speed. Pino advised she was coming from a friends house and was returning home. I asked Pino if she consumed any alcoholic beverages or smoked Cannabis that night. Pino denied participating in both. I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Pino. I advised the Rockville Barrack that I would be conducting standardized field sobriety tests and needed a backup unit. Trooper First Class Rowe #5975 and two Montgomery County Police Officers arrived on scene. During the standardized field sobriety tests, Pino advised she consumed one Margarita on the rocks. Pino advised she was not a big drinker.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the right sidewalk along southbound Maryland Route 97 at Dayton Street. The surface was dry, slight downgrade, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 50 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of light illuminating from light poles and my patrol vehicles headlights. Pino appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries that would prevent her from walking or standing.  I asked Pino the following questions:  - Injuries  No - Medication  Tylenol - Medical Conditions  No - Glasses/Contacts  None observed  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from Pinos eyes. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Pinos pupils were equal in size, showed equal tracking, and no resting Nystagmus was observed. She was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Pino if she understood the instructions and she stated, Yes.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 degrees  Present in both eyes  WALK AND TURN (3/8 clues observed) Prior to Pino performing the test, I properly examined and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Pino was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Pino was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in the position until told to begin. Pino was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Pino was to keep her hands flat at her side, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Pino was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Pino was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Pino was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her side, look at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Pino if she understood the test and she stated, Yes. Footwear: leather boots.  Instructional Stage: -Failed to maintain balance on one (1) occasion.          Walking Stage (1st Nine): -Took ten (10) steps.  Turn: -Completed satisfactorily.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): -Took ten (10) steps. -Stopped walking on all ten (10) steps.  Pino advised she took ten steps to be safe.  ONE LEG STAND (1/4 clues observed) Prior to Pino performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Pino was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-one thousand, two-one thousand), and continue the test until told to stop. I asked Pino if she understood the test and she stated, Yes. Pino chose to raise her right foot. Footwear: leather boots.  Instructional Stage:      -No clues observed.  Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: -No clues observed.  Seconds 11-20: -Swayed left to right for approximately two (2) seconds.  Seconds 21-30: -No clues observed.  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Pino was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  -Traveling 62 miles per hour in a 30 mile per hour zone. -Failed to maintain one lane direction on one occasion. -Changed lanes in an intersection. -Almost ran off the exit ramp. -Admitted to traveling at a high rate of speed. -The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. -Eyes were glassy and bloodshot. -Admitted to consuming one Margarita on the rocks. -Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus  6/6 clues observed. -Walk and Turn  3/8 clues observed. -One Leg Stand  1/4 clues observed.  I arrested Pino for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0030 hours and performed a search incident to arrest. Pino was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Rockville Barrack for processing. During transport, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Pinos breath and person. After arriving at the barrack, I gave Pino a copy of the DR-15 form in English to review while I played the entire form in English audio to her in the barrack. The English version audio can be found on mva.maryland.gov. Pino signed the DR-15 at approximately 0103 hours, agreeing to submit to the intoximeter test.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Pino beginning with her arrest. A preliminary search of Pino was conducted on the scene and it revealed that he had nothing in her mouth. I observed Pino from the time of the arrest until the time she submitted to the test and she did not put anything in her mouth. The test was conducted by Sgt. Tribue #5781 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Pinos breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of .12 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. Pino was released to the custody of her friend from the barrack.  All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland.  CASE CLOSED BY ARREST.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/25/2023 21:07:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/25/2023 21:08:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lear</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quinn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7154</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Moore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5995</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lear</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quinn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7154</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lear</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quinn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7154</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529306</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 00:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:11:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 12:15:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529306</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 00:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:11:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 12:14:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529306</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 00:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:11:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 12:15:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529306</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 00:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:11:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 12:16:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529306</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 00:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:11:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 12:13:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529306</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 00:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:11:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 12:14:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>529306</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/11/2023 00:30:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:11:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 12:13:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:11:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 12:16:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393319</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Pino</LastName>
               <FirstName>Melanie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>A</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/27/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/18/2023 12:02:50</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M450</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Pino</LastName>
               <FirstName>Melanie</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>A</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/27/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P500</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M450</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/18/2023 12:02:50</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1812</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Arcola</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Wheaton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20902</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.03836</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.04698</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:16:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:16:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:16:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:16:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:16:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:12:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 12:12:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159042</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 12:11:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 12:11:37</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>19UUB2F39HA004872</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>ACUR</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>0</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8EM0661</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>