<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-041619</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/24/2023 02:47:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/24/2023 02:47:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/24/2023 02:27:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/24/2023 02:27:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic Stop that led to a DUI arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/24/2023 02:47:42</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5660</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 17:57:47</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>ROBERT CRAIN HWY SW / LEELAND RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>714305</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/24/2023 02:47:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/27/2023 01:05:39</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>714305</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Crain Highway @ Leeland Road</StreetName>
         <City>Upper Marlboro</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20774</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.72506</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.85884</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/24/2023 02:47:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/24/2023 02:47:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/11/2023 17:57:47</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/24/2023 02:47:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:01</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>L-28 is equipped with an MVR this incident was also recorded with my body-worn camera.  Defendant: Lionel Harrell London Date of Birth: 06/05/1968 Date of Arrest: 11/24/2023 Time of Arrest: 0246 hours MD License #: L535522298422 DUI #: 23-391  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES   Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration on December 5th-8th, 2022.  Trained in administering Preliminary Breath Tests through the Maryland State Police Forensics Science Division on December 9, 2022.  Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement through the Baltimore County Police DepartmentsTraffic Training Team on May 15-16, 2023.  Vehicle in Motion (Phase 1):   On November 24, 2023, at approximately 0228 hours, I, Trooper Stacey #7390 of the Maryland State Police Forestville barrack was conducting traffic enforcement on Crain Highway in Prince Georges County, Maryland. I observed a gray Lexus RX bearing MD registration 1AR2869 traveling northbound on Crain Highway south of Leeland Road in lane #2, with an inoperable headlamp. I conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle, which pulled over onto the right shoulder.  Personal Contact (Phase 2):   Upon my drivers side approach of the vehicle I was met with the driver who I identified by his Maryland drivers license as Lionel Harrell London (B/M, DOB: 06/05/1968). The driver cracked his window approximately one inch, instead of rolling the window down all the way. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I asked London to roll the window down all the way to which he agreed. I asked London where he was coming from, and he advised he was coming from his moms house. He advised he had some alcoholic beverages while he was at his moms house. He also stated he was on his way home. Londons eyes were glassy and bloodshot. At this time I asked London to exit the vehicle to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, to which he agreed.  Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3): The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of the highway. The weather was clear and approximately 40 degrees. Lighting conditions were dark. The ground was level and free of any debris. My patrol vehicles overhead emergency lights in the front were deactivated prior to field sobriety tests as well as the vehicles spotlight. London was wearing flat heeled shoes. London appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible signs of injuries. I asked London the following questions: Medical Conditions: None Glasses or contacts: No  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from his eyes. London was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. London pupils were of equal size and showed equal tracking. London displayed the following clues:    Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eye  WALK AND TURN TEST (5/8 clues observed) Prior to London performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. London was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and to touch heel to toe on an imaginary line. London was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat as his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. London was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. London was instructed to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, London was explained and demonstrated to keep hislead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to the left to turn completely around. London was again explained and demonstrated the series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series, London was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. London advised he understood the test. Instructional Stage:    Starts too soon  Walking Stage (1st set of nine steps):     margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Misses heel to toe   margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Uses arms for balance   margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Stops the test after first 9 steps  Walking Stage (2nd set of nine steps):     margin-bottom:19px"&gt;Misses heel to toe   ONE LEG STAND (4/4 clues observed) Prior to London performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. He was instructed to stand with his feet together and hands down by his side while the instructions were given. During the test he was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start, once the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. London advised he understood the instructions given.  London displayed the following clues: Puts foot down:    0 to 10  11 to 20  21 to 30  Use arms for balance:    0 to 10  11 to 20  21 to 30  Sways:    0 to 10  11 to 20  21 to 30  Hops:    0 to 10   London was offered a Preliminary Breath Test to which he refused  ARREST: Based off of the following, I had reason to believe London was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:    Odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath  Eyes glassy and bloodshot  Clued observed during field sobriety  London was arrested at 0246 hours and transported to the Maryland State Police Forestville Barrack. At approximately 0255 hours, London was read the DR15 Advice of Rights played aloud via the MVA website English audio recording. London refused to take the intoximeter examination test at 0303 hours. London was given the appropriate citations and all pertinent paperwork and released to his wife at 0318hours.   All of the above events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/27/2023 01:16:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 14:07:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ortiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Angel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5858</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Murray</LastName>
            <FirstName>Niall</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7580</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rogers</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dominique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5660</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stacey</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7390</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531089</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/24/2023 02:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/27/2023 01:05:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/27/2023 01:05:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>55</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/27/2023 01:10:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/27/2023 01:10:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393947</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>London</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lionel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Harrell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/05/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/27/2023 01:09:06</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L535</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>London</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lionel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Harrell</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/05/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L535</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/27/2023 01:09:06</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12913</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Belle Meade</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>TRCE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Bowie</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20720</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4687</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.780199</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.952698</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/27/2023 01:10:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/27/2023 01:10:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/27/2023 01:10:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/27/2023 01:05:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/27/2023 01:05:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159304</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7390</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/27/2023 01:12:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7390</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/27/2023 01:12:38</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2T2BK1BA0AC018211</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2010</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>LEXS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>RX</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1AR2869</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>