<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-036024</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/14/2023 00:13:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/14/2023 00:13:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/13/2023 23:51:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/13/2023 23:51:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was stopped for a traffic violation. Upon contact with the driver, the odor of an alcoholic beverage was detected. SFST's was conducted and the driver was placed under arrest for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 00:13:54</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0104</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/24/2023 09:24:47</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>WESTERN,WALDORF</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>575793</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 00:13:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 05:41:51</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>575793</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Western</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>PKWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Waldorf</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20601</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-76.9186433</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.6292127333333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM MDT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/14/2023 00:13:53</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/14/2023 00:13:53</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/23/2023 12:49:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 00:13:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:52</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car camera and body worn camera operational. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Defendant: Birdine Jr., Alasandro Fitzgerald Kessall  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Date of Birth: 02/09/1995  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Time of arrest: 0010 hours font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Location: Western Parkway at Route 228, Waldorf, Charles County Maryland, 20601. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Maryland drivers license:MD-10272272985  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; DUI#: 23-180  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; 1stDUI font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-color:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-thickness:initial"&gt;CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; *Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement through Charles County Sheriffs Office. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-color:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-thickness:initial"&gt;NARRATIVE/ VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1): font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;   On 10/13/2023 at approximately 2351 hours, I, Tpr. Tripp with the Maryland State Police La Plata Barrack H was on patrol in lane two at Westbound Route 228 at Western Parkway, Waldorf, Charles County, Maryland 20601. I observed a blue Honda Civic in the left turn lane position two bearing Maryland registration 1FP3133, failed to travel through a steady green arrow signal. I then observed a gray passenger vehicle activate their horn to attempt to get the drivers attention but was unsuccessful. The gray passenger vehicle then moved to the left turn lane position one to pass the Honda. I then traveled onto Western Parkway and stopped behind the Honda. I then waited for the traffic light to turn to a steady green arrow signal and I observed the Honda Civic still stationary at the intersection for approximately five seconds before activating my emergency equipment.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2): font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; As I approached the vehicle, I observed the drivers eyes closed, his head tilted over to the drivers side window, and his left hand over his mouth. I also observed the drivers right foot on the brake. I attempted to wake the driver up by knocking on the window with my index finger. The driver then opened the door and took his right foot off the brake, unaware the vehicle was not in park. I advised the driver to place his foot on the brakes and to park the car. I made contact with the driver and requested his drivers license and registration card, which he only displayed his license. I was able to identify the driver through his Maryland drivers license as, Birdine Jr., Alasandro Fitzgerald Kessall (A.A, DOB: 02/09/1995). While speaking with Birdine, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle. I asked Birdine where he was coming from and he advised, My friends house. I then asked Birdine if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages and he advised, A coupled drinks. While speaking with Birdine, I observed his eyes were bloodshot and glassy, and his speech was slurred. While speaking with Birdine I observed his movements were at a slow pace. I advised Birdine that I needed him to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) to which Birdine agreed.As Birdine approached the front of his vehicle, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3): font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Tpr. Nain #7452 assisted with the traffic stop. While standing in front of Birdines vehicle, I asked Birdine if theres any medical conditions that I should be aware of and he advised, No. I then asked Birdine if he wears glasses or contacts and he advised, No. I asked Birdine if recently had any head injuries or concussions and he advised, No. I asked Birdine if he is a diabetic or had high blood pressure and he advised, No. I asked Birdine if there are any physical disabilities that I should be aware of and he advised, No. I then asked Birdine if he can perform the WAT (Walk and Turn) and the OLS (One Leg Stand) test and he advised, Yes. I then held up my pen approximately 12 inches from his face and asked if he can see my pen from that distance and Birdine advised, Yes.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS TEST: (6/6 clues observed). font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Birdines eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping hishead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hiseyes until told to stop. Hispupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. Hewas positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  Birdine displayed equal pupil size, equal tracking and no resting nystagmus in both eyes. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Birdine displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Birdine displayed nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Birdine displayed nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-color:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-thickness:initial"&gt;VERTICAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Birdine did not display vertical gaze nystagmus in both eyes. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; WALK AND TURN: (8/8 clues observed). font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Prior to Birdine performing the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Birdine was instructed to place hisright foot directly in front of hisleft foot and touch heel to toe. He was instructed and demonstrated to place hishands flat at hissides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Hewas advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. Hewas instructed to keep hishands flat at hissides, keep hiseyes focused on hisfeet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Birdine was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with hisrear foot to turn completely around. Birdine was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Hewas instructedonce he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep hishands down by hissides, look down at hisfeet, and count each step out loud. Birdine was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, Yes.  Birdine wore dark-colored sneakers for the test. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Birdine began the test too early. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Birdine could not keep his balance before beginning the test. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Birdine stepped off-line on his first, second, third, and seventh step, on his first set nine steps.  Birdine missed heel-to-toe on his second, third, fourth, fifth, sixth, seventh, eighth, and ninth step on his first set of nine steps.  Birdine raised his arms on his fourth step, on his first set of nine steps.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Birdine performed an improper turn by taking one step to turn around instead of a series of small steps as instructed.  Birdine took one step backwards.  Birdine stopped after the improper turn and was advised to continue the test. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Birdine stepped off-line on his first, second, fourth, sixth, eighth, and ninth, on his second set of nine steps.  Birdine missed heel-to-toe step on all nine steps, on his second set of nine steps.  Birdine took ten steps instead of nine.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; ONE LEG STAND: (4/4 clues observed) font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Prior to Birdine performing the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Hewas instructed to stand with hisheels together and hands down by hissides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of hischoice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While hisleg was raised, he was to keep hisleg straight, watch hisraised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Birdine was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, Yes. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Birdine raised his right foot for this test.  0-10 seconds  Birdine kept his foot down for approximately four seconds.   11-20 seconds  Birdine swayed at 12 and 18 seconds.  Birdine hopped at 13 and 18 seconds.  Birdine raised his arms at 12, 16, and 18 seconds.  Birdine placed his foot down at 20 seconds.  21-30 seconds  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Birdine swayed at 23 and 25 seconds.  Birdine hopped at 23 and 25 seconds.  Birdine raised his arms at 23 and 25 seconds.  Birdine was offered to take the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) and agreed to take to the test. His results were 0.13 BrAC.  Arrest: font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.  -Asleep behind the wheel  -Bloodshot and glassy eyes.  -Admission to consuming an alcoholic beverage.  -Slurred speech. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  -Clues displayed from the Standardized Field Sobriety Test.  -Positive preliminary breath test.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Birdine was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at 0010 hours.Birdinewas read his DR-15 Advice of Rights, and he agreed to take the Intoximeter test at 0028 hours. Birdine was then transported to the Maryland State Police La Plata Barrack for further processing. The Intoximeter test was administered by Cpl. Meurrens #6372 at 0058 hours. Birdines results were .13 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Birdine received the following citations:  TA-21-902(a1ii) Driving vehicle while under the influence of alcohol per se font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; TA-21-902(a1i) Driving vehicle while under the influence of alcohol  TA-21-902(b1i) Driving vehicle while impaired by alcohol  TA-21-901.1(b) Negligent driving  TA-21-901.1(a) Reckless driving  TA-21-201(a1) Driver failure to obey properly placed traffic control device instructions font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; TA-21-309(i) Driver failing make left turn from left turn lane  TA-13-411(c1l) Fail to maintain registration plate from frame/border  TA-13-409(b) Failure to display registration card on demand  Birdine was released to a valid, sober driver. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; All events occurred in Charles County, Maryland.  Case closed.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/15/2023 05:44:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/23/2023 12:39:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Nain</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7452</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alphrin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5237</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tripp</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sedrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7333</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525485</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 00:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525485</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 00:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525485</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 00:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525485</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 00:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525485</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 00:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525485</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 00:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525485</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15565</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 00:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15565</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525485</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21303</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 00:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21303</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525485</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16616</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 00:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16616</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>28</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:53:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 05:53:38</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390329</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Birdine</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alasandro</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Fitzgerald Kessall</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/09/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>10/14/2023 05:52:48</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B635</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A425</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Birdine</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alasandro</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Fitzgerald Kessall</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/09/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>B635</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A425</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/14/2023 05:52:48</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9324</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Rock Lynn</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Waldorf</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20603</Zip5>
               <Zip4>7024</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.99547</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.613223</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:53:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:53:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:53:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:53:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:53:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 05:46:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158036</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 05:59:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 05:59:20</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2HGFE2F5XNH510869</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CIV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1FP3133</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>8</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>