<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-040806</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/18/2023 01:04:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/18/2023 01:04:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/18/2023 00:43:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/18/2023 00:43:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>23-249 "N" DEL CID</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 01:06:59</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6354</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/07/2023 16:26:53</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>713498</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 01:43:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 01:43:28</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>713498</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I-495</StreetName>
         <City>Silver Spring</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.017996</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.015835</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/18/2023 01:06:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/18/2023 01:06:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/07/2023 16:26:54</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/18/2023 01:06:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:13</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E.) TEAM* The following incident was captured on in-car and body camera Defendant: Elmer Anival Del Cid  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: * I am trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (March 2013 SFST NHTSA Manual). * I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor as of February 2016. * I am a Certified Breath Test Operator by the Toxicologist of the State of Maryland as of March 2016. * I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of March 2016. * I am a distinguished graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute as of June 2015 * I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of May 2014. * I am a Preliminary Breath Test Instructor as of May 2019. * I am a RADAR and LIDAR Instructor as of October 2019. * I have apprehended more than 1,100 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On November 18, 2023 at approximately 0044 hours, I (Cpl. Wallace #6323) was on patrol in unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle DUI-1 on eastbound Rt. 193 in the area of Rt. 29, Montgomery County, Maryland. I observed a white Ford F-150 bearing Maryland registration 8BE4749 pass my patrol vehicle. The Ford was straddling the dotted white line for two eastbound lanes. The Ford went left over the dotted white line and solid white line prior to taking the ramp for the I/L I-495. The Ford took a wide turn on the ramp and went over the solid white line onto 495. The roadway was wet and the Ford accelerated away from my patrol vehicle and was unable to drive within a single lane.   Right on dotted white line, left  Right over dotted white line, left  Right on dotted white line, right over dotted white line, left  Accelerated away 84 MPH in a posted 55 MPH zone  Left on dotted white line, right  Left over dotted white line, right  There were other vehicles in the area  I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the Ford on the I/L I-495 just past MD 650.  The above referenced RADAR was calibrated before and after my shift and was functioning properly. I am a certified RADAR operator. Training certificates and calibration records will be made available upon request. This RADAR is specifically assigned to my vehicle.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Ford on the driver side and made contact with the male operator of the vehicle, who was the only occupant in the vehicle. He did not roll the window down all the way. I explained the reason for the stop and requested his drivers license and vehicle registration. He was identified by his Maryland Drivers license as Elmer Anival Del Cid. He stated that he was going to Upper Marlboro and was coming from his other house. While speaking with Del Cid, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from inside the vehicle. I deliberately observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. He continued to look forward when he was speaking to me. He was answering all of my questions with proper responses. I returned to my patrol vehicle to notify the barrack who I was out with. I returned to the Ford and requested Del Cid to exit his vehicle. He complied and exited his vehicle. While speaking with Del Cid outside of the vehicle, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. When asked about alcohol consumption he said maybe two or three beers (Modelo). I informed Del Cid that I wanted him to perform standardized field sobriety tests, to which he agreed to the tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. I asked Del Cid the following questions:  Glasses or contacts  No Head Injuries  No Medication  No Problems with knees or ankles or can he walk okay  No    He answered all of my questions in English.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus    Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes     Moved his head when instructed to keep it still  He stated that he had his beer around 12.  He stated that he owns a business and went to pay his workers and had beer with them.  WALK AND TURN (7/8 clues observed)  The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Instructional Stage:    He was unable to stand in the instructional stage and places his hand on the vehicle. He then stated that his English was not that good. I used the Google translation application to give him the instructions to the tests.     Del Cid stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed.  Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Stepped completely offline on steps 6 and 8.  Took 8 steps when instructed to take 9.  Stopped prior to the turn  Turn: Turned left using both feet Walking Stage (2nd Nine):    Stepped completely offline on steps 1 and 6.  Missed touching heel to toe by more than  inch on step 1.  Raised arms more than 6 inches from side for balance.   ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed.  Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10:    Swayed body to the left and right.  Right foot hit the ground 1 time.  Seconds 11-20:    Swayed body to the left and right.  Right foot hit the ground 1 time.  Seconds 21-30:    Swayed body to the left and right.     He stated that when he paid his worked he drank maybe 2 or 3 beers.  PBT refused    He would speak in Spanish and I would ask him what he was saying and he would say it in English.  He stated that he did not want to talk to anyone   ARREST Due to the number of observations, I concluded Del Cid was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0104 hours, I placed Del Cid under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. He was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and was transported to the Montgomery County Silver Spring station for processing. Upon arrival at the station, I provided Del Cid with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Del Cid listened to the DR-15 Advice of Rights from the MVA website (Spanish). At 0136 hours, Del Cid refused to take a breath test.  20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: Not applicable.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: ****Refusal****  Del Cid was polite and cooperative during the encounter. Del Cid was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released. All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland. Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 00:36:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 16:14:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>530276</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/18/2023 01:04:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 00:34:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 00:35:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 00:34:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 00:36:16</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393286</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Del Cid</LastName>
               <FirstName>Elmer</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anival</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/06/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/18/2023 01:34:44</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D423</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E456</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Del Cid</LastName>
               <FirstName>Elmer</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anival</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/06/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D423</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E456</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/18/2023 01:34:44</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1817</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Franwall</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Silver Spring</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20902</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2916</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.038928</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.04632</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 00:36:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 00:36:16</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:30</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 00:34:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 00:34:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>