<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-045524</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/25/2023 20:38:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/25/2023 20:38:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/25/2023 20:10:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/25/2023 20:10:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was stopped for a traffic violation and was later arrested for DUI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 20:38:54</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1788</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/30/2023 05:24:32</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>717038</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 20:38:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 22:33:38</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>717038</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2019</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Aris T Allen</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Edgewater</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21037</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.535658</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.971114</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/25/2023 20:38:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/25/2023 20:38:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 17:57:03</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 20:38:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The following incident was captured on in-car and body camera.  Defendant: Juan Pablo Escalante Mata Date of Birth: 06/25/1983 Date of Arrest: 12/25/2023 Time of Arrest: 2039 hours DC SDX: 4481273 DUI #: 23-226  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:  * Trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration  * I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of November 2017. * I am a graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute as of June 2023. * I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR though the Maryland State Police as of March 2017. * I have apprehended more than 150 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)    On Monday, December 25, 2023, at approximately 2012 hours, I, TFC. Lowe #6739 was in uniform of the day operating unmarked MSP vehicle, J-21. At that time, I was in the area of Whitehall Road and E/B Rt. 50, Annapolis, Anne Arundel County, Maryland when the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack received a call for a possible intoxicated driver on S/B Rt. 97 passing exit 10A. I then started traveling toward the area. The cell phone number for the witness was provided to me and I was able to call the complainant to get up to date locations. The caller continued to update me with the suspect vehicles driving pattern. They advised the vehicle was driving in between lanes and nearly striking other vehicles. I told the caller to advise me when they were reaching Rt. 50. The caller advised me the vehicle was taking to exit for Rt. 665 and Riva Rd. I went to that location and waited on the right shoulder until I observed the caller. The complainant turned the hazard lights on so I could see them. I then observed the suspect vehicle to be a black Toyota Corolla. I observed the Toyota in lane 1 and nearly strike the guardrail. I then got behind the Toyota to make observations. I observed the Toyota begin to weave within lane 1, traveling on the white dotted line back over to the solid yellow line. The Toyota began weaving again in lane 1 and travel over the solid yellow lane line again. At that time, I activated my emergency equipment and attempted to make a traffic stop on the black Toyota Corolla. The Toyota was bearing Maryland registration, 7FF9275. The vehicle hit its brakes and turned on the right blinker and traveled over the lanes of travel and appeared to be trying to pull over. The Toyota then struck the cement sidewalk that lined Rt. 665. The Toyota then came to a stop in the middle of lane 2.    PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)   I approached the Toyota via a drivers side approach and made contact with the male driver who was also the sole occupant of the vehicle. I introduced myself and advised him the reason for the stop was because he was swerving all over the road. The male handed me his license and he was identified by his DC drivers license as Juan Pablo Escalante Mata, H/M, DOB: 06/25/1983 (hereinafter referred to as Escalante.) I then asked Escalante for his vehicle registration which he provided to me. I requested for a Spanish-speaking officer to assist me on scene, but there was no one available. I asked Escalante where he was coming from and he replied, Annapolis. I asked Escalante where he was going and he shook his head and stated, Im sorry. As he spoke, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle. I also noticed his eyes were bloodshot and glassy. I asked Escalante how much alcohol he had consumed because I could smell it, and he replied, No, none. I advised him that I could smell it and he replied, Really? I asked Escalante why he was swerving in the road, and he just looked down and stated, Im sorry. At that time, I had Escalante move his vehicle up to a turn lane a few hundred feet, so we were not stopped in the roadway. Escalante understood me and moved where I requested. I then returned to my vehicle and requested another unit.   A routine check through METERS and MVA database revealed Escalante was driving on a valid DC driver license. On my second approach, I asked Escalante to exit his vehicle and turn the vehicle off and he complied. Since there was no translator available, I had to use a translator app for Escalante to understand me better. I advised Escalante that I could smell alcohol, and he replied, Yes. I asked how much he had to drink and he replied, Two beers. I again asked Escalante where he was coming from and he stated, Hagerstown. I used the translator app to ask Escalante if he would submit to standardized field sobriety tests, and he agreed.    PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   The evaluation was performed roadside. The weather was clear and approximately 45 degrees Fahrenheit. Lighting conditions consisted of patrol vehicle headlights, spotlight, and my flashlight. The road was level and free from any debris. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Escalante was wearing a red jacket, jeans and sneakers. Escalante appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any major visible injuries when walking from the vehicle. While speaking with Escalante outside his vehicle, I again detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage, this time emitting from his breath and person. I asked Escalante if he understood a bit of English and stated that he did.   Escalante was asked the following questions:    margin-left:31px"&gt;Do you have any medical conditions or injuries- None    margin-left:31px"&gt;Are you on any medications  None    margin-left:31px"&gt;Do you wear glasses or contacts?  Contacts       HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)    The first test that was given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus. The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA manual. Escalante stated he understood the instructions. Escalantedisplayed the following clues:  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes.  Escalante also showed Vertical Nystagmus.    WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)  The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA manual. Escalantedisplayed the following clues:  Instructional Stage:     Escalante did not maintain the instructional position.   Walking Stage (1st Nine)    Made a total of 8 steps  Missed heel to toe on steps 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, and 7.    Turn: Made a turn but not as instructed.   Walking Stage (2nd Nine):    Stepped off-line on step 1 and nearly fell off balance.   Missed heel to toe on all steps  Took only 8 steps   Other observations: On the second set of 9 steps, Escalante did not walk on the line that he was using for reference and had trouble keeping his balance.   ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA manual. Escalante displayed the following clues.   Balance and Counting Stage:    Put foot down count 1002, 1004, 1006, 1008, 1011, and 1023.  Escalante used his arms to balance the entire test. His arms were lifted parallel to the ground.    Other observations: Escalante did not count out loud as instructed and kept picking his foot up then putting it down. Eventually, Escalante began leaning on the front of his vehicle for support.   While on scene, Escalante was offered a preliminary breath test which he refused.   Based on my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper and the following, I had reason to believe Escalante was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:     margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from breath   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Eyes glassy and bloodshot.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Admission to consuming alcohol   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Driving behavior   margin-left:16px"&gt;Clues during field sobriety tests   Due to the number of observations, I concluded Escalante was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 2039 hours, I placed Escalante under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. Escalante was placed in handcuffs without incident. A preliminary search of Escalante was conducted on scene and there were no foreign objects in his mouth at the time. Escalante was then placed in the front seat of my patrol vehicle per Maryland State Police policy. While in my vehicle, I could still detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. Escalante was transported to the Maryland State Police Annapolis Barrack for processing. Escalantes vehicle sustained a flat tire and bumper damage from being driven into the sidewalk, so it was towed from the scene by Palmers towing. TFC. Jeans #6483 also got witness statements from the complainant that witnessed Escalante driving.  20 Minute Observation Period  At that Barrack, I called the language line for assistance with translation for the rest of the process. A secondary search was conducted upon arrival at the Barrack and revealed that Escalante had nothing in his mouth. I played Escalante the DR-15 Advice of Rights via the Motor Vehicle Administration audio recording in Spanish. Escalante was given a copy to follow along with as it played, and he read along to himself. At 0156 hours, Escalante agreed to submit to an Intoximeter test. Sgt. Jones #1788 of the Maryland State Police administered the test. The test revealed that Escalante had an alcohol concentration of .21 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.   Escalante was polite and cooperative the entire process.  Escalante was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and was released.   All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 10:53:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/30/2023 04:40:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jeans</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6483</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jones</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mujaihid</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1788</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lowe</LastName>
            <FirstName>Erin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6739</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535001</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/25/2023 20:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:35:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:35:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535001</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/25/2023 20:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:35:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:35:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535001</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/25/2023 20:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:36:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:36:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535001</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/25/2023 20:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:37:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:37:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535001</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/25/2023 20:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:37:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:37:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535001</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/25/2023 20:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:38:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:38:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535001</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/25/2023 20:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:40:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:40:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>535001</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/25/2023 20:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:40:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:40:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 22:34:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:41:38</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>396054</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Escalante Mata</LastName>
               <FirstName>Juan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Pablo</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/25/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/25/2023 22:12:23</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E245</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Escalante Mata</LastName>
               <FirstName>Juan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Pablo</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/25/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>E245</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/25/2023 22:12:23</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2820</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Pennsylvania</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>NW</StreetSuffixCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>104</SubNumber>
               <City>Washington</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20007</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3717</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.057722</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.90495</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>755</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3228</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:41:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:41:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:41:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:41:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:41:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:41:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:41:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:41:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:41:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:41:38</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/30/2023 05:17:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/30/2023 05:17:45</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>396407</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Young</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ivan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/24/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/30/2023 05:17:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>Y520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N242</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Young</LastName>
               <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ivan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/24/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>Y520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N242</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/30/2023 05:17:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5705</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Solomons Island</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>St Leonard</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20685</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2837</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.503776</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.458732</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>975</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8430</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/30/2023 05:17:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/30/2023 05:17:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>28</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/30/2023 05:18:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/30/2023 05:18:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>396408</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Young</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ashley</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Danielle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/28/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/30/2023 05:18:38</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>Y520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Young</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ashley</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Danielle</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/28/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>Y520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/30/2023 05:18:38</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5705</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Solomons Island</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>St Leonard</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20685</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2837</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.503776</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.458732</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>208</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>901</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4368</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/30/2023 05:18:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/30/2023 05:18:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/30/2023 05:18:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/30/2023 05:18:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/27/2023 09:35:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/27/2023 09:35:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>160177</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6739</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 22:36:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6739</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 22:36:49</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5YFEPMAE1MP178675</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2021</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>COA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7FF9275</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>