<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-044422</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/16/2023 03:03:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/16/2023 03:03:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/16/2023 02:43:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/16/2023 02:43:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI Traffic Arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/16/2023 03:03:57</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4437</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 09:49:07</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>29 MM I95 SB, BELTSVILLE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>716161</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/16/2023 03:03:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:10:31</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>716161</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>29</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I95 Sb Beltsville</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.9298418333333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0533163333333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/16/2023 03:03:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/16/2023 03:03:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 18:11:45</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/16/2023 03:03:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:15</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP unmarked vehicle Q-41 is equipped with a mobile recording device. Body worn camera worn, and operational.   Defendant: Daniel Nehemiah Harvell  Date of Birth: 04/10/1995  Date of Arrest: 12/16/2023  Time of Arrest: 0303 hours  DUI #: 23-314  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On Saturday, December 16, 2023, at approximately 0243 hours, I, Trooper Webb of the Maryland State PoliceCollege Park Barrack, was on routine patrol in my unmarked MSP vehicle Q-41 in lane 1 of southbound 95 at Maryland 212. At this time, I observed a green Ford Explorer in front of me in lane 1, bearing Maryland registration 3Z5834. I observed the Explorer veer from lane 1 to lane 2, and then to lane 3. The Explorer would then jerk back from lane 3 all the way back to lane 1. The vehicle would perform these actions three times without turn signals, crossing over the dotted-lane dividers. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. After turning on my lights, the vehicle pulled off the roadway to the right and onto the shoulder and came to a complete stop. After the vehicle came to a complete stop, I made contact with the driver.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I made contact with the operator via the passenger side window, and upon my approach I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I gave the driver my rank, name, ID number, agency and I informed the driver the reason for the stop. I also advised him that the stop was being audibly/visually recorded. I requested his license and registration card. The driver was identified by his Maryland drivers license as Daniel Nehemiah Harvell. I asked Harvell how much he had to drink, and he stated, Two shots. As I spoke to Harvell, I intentionally observed his eyes to be glassy and bloodshot with a gazed look and noticed his head and body movements were slow and lethargic. I returned to my patrol vehicle and conducted routine checks on Harvell.  I approached the vehicle again and requested that Harvell exit his vehicle and walk to the front of his vehicle, to which he complied. I continued to speak with Harvell outside of his vehicle, and as Harvell spoke, I smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I informed Harvell that I wanted him to perform field sobriety tests.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the shoulder of the highway. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 30 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of street lamps, patrol vehicle headlamps, spotlight, and my flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Harvell appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries.  I asked Harvell the following questions:  Injuries: No Medication: No Medical Conditions: No Glasses: No  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pointer finger was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Harvells eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Harvells pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking and no resting Nystagmus was observed. He was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Harvell if he understood the instructions, and he stated yes.   1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes  WALK AND TURN (2/8 clues observed) Prior to Harvell performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Harvell was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Harvell was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Harvell was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step. Harvell was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Harvell was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Harvell was again explained and demonstrated that the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Harvell was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Harvell if he understood the test, and he stated, Yes.  Instructional Stage: 1.) Nothing to report.  Walking Stage (1st Nine): 1.) Stepped off the line by more than a width of foot on steps 1, 3, and 7. 2.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 1, and 7.   Walking Stage (2nd Nine): 1.) Stepped off the line by more than a width of foot on steps 1, 2, and 5. 2.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 2, and 5.   Turn: 1.) Nothing to report.  ONE LEG STAND (4/4 clues observed) Prior to Harvell performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Harvell was instructed to stand with his heels together and his hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground, approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Harvell if he understood the test, and he stated yes.  Instructional Stage: 1.) Nothing to report.  Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10: 1.) Placed foot down on the ground.  Seconds 11-20: 1.) Swayed body to the left and right. 2.) Raised arms more than 6 inches. 3.) Placed foot down on the ground. 4.) Hopping on 1 foot.   Seconds 21-30: 1.) Placed foot down on the ground. 2.) Hopping on 1 foot.  Harvell submitted to a preliminary breath test with a .087 BrAC result.  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Harvell was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Swerving vehicle multiple times. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle. * Slow and lethargic head and body movements. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot with a gazed look. * Admitted to consuming 2 shots. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests. * PBT result of .087.  I arrested Harvell for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0303 hours, and he was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Maryland State Police  College Park Barrack for processing. Once at the barrack, I played the English audio DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Harvell in its entirety. At the conclusion of the form, Harvell verbally advised that he agreed to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the form indicating the same.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the observation period on Harvell in its entirety starting with his time of arrest. I escorted Harvell into the arrest processing room and remained in his custody until the time of test. Harvells mouth was checked and no foreign objects or piercings were observed.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: The intoximeter test was administered within the two-hour statutory time frame. This test was administered by a certified breath technician on equipment approved by the Chief Toxicologist in the Department of State Police Forensic Science Division.  .11 BrAC PER 210 LITERS OF BREATH  Harvell was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and later released to his wife. Harvell was polite and cooperative throughout the process.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:24:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 13:14:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Esuma</LastName>
            <FirstName>Smith</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7574</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dunlap</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6273</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Webb</LastName>
            <FirstName>Noah</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7303</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533899</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 02:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533899</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 02:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533899</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 02:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533899</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 02:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533899</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 02:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533899</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 02:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>533899</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 02:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>28</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:19:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:19:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>80922</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Harvell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nehemiah</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/10/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/21/2015 06:28:03</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H614</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Harvell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nehemiah</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/10/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H614</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/21/2015 06:28:03</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9010</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Canterbury Riding</StreetName>
               <City>Laurel</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20723</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.8459</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.123845</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>7204</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Westchester Dr</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Temple Hills</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20748</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.909666</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.790746</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>537</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5263</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/21/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>537</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5263</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/21/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:19:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:19:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:19:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:19:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:19:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:19:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:16:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159891</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/18/2023 09:20:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/18/2023 09:20:26</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2000</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>XPL</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>LL</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRN</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRN</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3Z5834</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>