<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000708</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/06/2023 18:38:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/06/2023 18:38:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/06/2023 18:07:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/06/2023 18:07:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/06/2023 18:38:09</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/14/2023 10:53:09</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>679612</AddressId>
      <City>MDC452</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:35:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 20:35:31</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>679612</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ramp from W/B 50 to I/L 495</StreetName>
         <City>Lanham</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20706</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.85564</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.94655</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/06/2023 18:38:07</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/06/2023 18:38:07</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/08/2023 21:11:37</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/06/2023 18:38:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 21:11:37</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Q-25 IS EQUIPPED WITH AN IN CAR CAMERA THE EVENT WAS AUDIBLY AND VISUALLY RECORDED Defendant: Howard, Alice Theresa Date of Birth: 11/15/1976 Time of Arrest: 1915 hours DUI#: 23-002 TRAINING/CERTIFICATES Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On January 6th, 2022, at approximately 1838 hours, I, Trooper Fleming #7439 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, was dispatched to the ramp from westbound US Route 50 to the inner loop of 495. The call for service was in response to a report a motor vehicle collision involving two vehicles. I arrived on scene. EMS/Fireboard was on scene and confirmed that those involved did not need or want to be transported to a hospital. Upon my arrival, I identified a white Dodge Charger bearing the Maryland registration 3DF8429 with heavy damage to the front of the vehicle. I exited my patrol vehicle to make contact with the drivers involved in the motor vehicle collision. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the driver of the white Dodge Charger who was standing outside of the vehicle and bent over inside the open passengers side. I confirmed that she had been the driver of the white Dodge Charger and was involved in the motor vehicle collision. I observed that her eyes were bloodshot and glassy. I then identified the driver as Howard, Alice Theresa (1/F, 11/15/1976) by her Maryland Drivers License. When I asked Howard for her vehicle registration, she stated I have all of that inside my box and pointed to the glove box of the vehicle. While waiting for Howard to grab her vehicle registration, Howard turned to me and asked if I could shine my flashlight on the glove box so she could see. Her speech was very slurred and mumbled at this time. I had difficulty communicating and understanding Howard due to her slurred and mumbled speech. I asked Howard where she was coming from, Howard stated that she was coming from Crofton. Howard could not find her vehicles registration despite her being the registered owner of the vehicle. Howard then explained to me how the collision happened. I then asked Howard what she was doing in Crofton. Howard stated With my husband, we were sitting, eating. I had two wines, thats all. I then asked for Howards phone number. After providing me her phone number, Howard stated I was eating dinner and I had two wines. Thats it. I asked Howard to perform standard field sobriety in order to determine if her consumption of alcohol prior to driving was a contributing factor to the collision. I asked Howard where she was coming from; Howard said she was coming from The Crab Shack in Crofton. I asked Howard if she had anything to drink there; Howard said Chardonnay, two glasses. I asked Howard how long ago she had consumed the alcohol; Howard answered A half an hour or two hours ago. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of the ramp from westbound US Route 50 to the inner loop of 495. The area level and dry. The area was clear of any debris. Howard appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. I asked Howard the following questions: Medical Condition  Howard informed me that she did not have any physical injuries that would affect her performance. Medication  Howard informed me that she regularly took prescribed medication for her blood pressure. Glasses or Contacts  Howard informed me that she wore glasses. Howard did not wear glasses for the HGN test. HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 Clues Observed) The test was explained. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus. The stimulus was held approximately 12-15 inches from Howards eye, slightly above eye level. Howard was instructed to look straight ahead, keep his head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. Howards pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Before beginning the test, I asked Howard if she understood my instructions, to which she confirmed. Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Additional Observations  Resting gaze nystagmus was not present. Vertical gaze nystagmus was present. WALK AND TURN TEST (7/8 Clues Observed) The test was explained and demonstrated. Howard was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Howard was then instructed to place her hands flat at her sides and remain in that position until told to begin. Howard was advised to take nine steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, she was instructed to keep her lead foot on the line, and take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Howard was instructed to complete the second series of nine steps in the same heel to toe fashion. Howard was instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, to count every step out loud, and once she began the test she was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Howard if she understood, and she confirmed that she did. Instructional Phase  Cannot Keep Balance  Howard could not remain balanced with her right foot directly in front of her left foot touching heel to toe while I was demonstrating and giving instructions for the walking stage of the test. Howard broke this form on two occasions. After breaking form for the second time, Howard stood with her feet side by side until told to begin the test. Starts Too Soon  Howard began the walking stage of the test before I could finish explaining the rest of the instructions and tell her to begin on one occasion. Walking Stage (First Nine Steps)  Misses Heel-Toe  On all nine of her first nine steps, Howard missed her heel to toe by more than one half inch. Steps Off Line  On all nine of her first nine steps, Howard stepped off line by more than one half inch. Actual Number of Steps  Howard stepped twelve times and counted ten out loud. Improper Turn - Howard turned clockwise when her right foot was behind her left foot which resulted in an unnatural turn and forced her to take a step backwards. Walking Stage (Second Nine Steps) Stops Walking  On her second step of her second nine, Howard loses her balance and stops walking. Misses Heel-Toe  On all nine of her second nine steps, Howard missed heel to toe by more than one half inch. Steps Off Line  On all nine of her second nine steps, Howard stepped off line by more than one half inch. Actual Number of Steps  Howard stepped ten times and counted ten out loud. ONE-LEG STAND TEST (2/4 Clues Observed) The test was explained and demonstrated. Howard was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, watch the raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two, etc.), and not put her foot down until the end of the test. I asked Howard if she understood the test, and she confirmed. Seconds 1-10 Raises Arms  Howard would keep her left arms raised greater than six inches from her body throughout the first ten seconds. Puts foot down  Howard lowered her foot to the ground, touching the ground with her entire foot three times during this period. Seconds 11-20 Raises Arms  Howard would keep her left arms raised greater than six inches from her body throughout the second ten seconds. Puts foot down  Howard lowered her foot to the ground, touching the ground with her entire foot three times during this period. Seconds 21-30 Raises Arms  Howard would keep her left arms raised greater than six inches from her body throughout the second ten seconds. Puts foot down  Howard lowered her foot to the ground, touching the ground with her entire foot two times during this period. Additional Observations  Howard started the test before I told her to begin on one occasion. Howard started counting at 1002. Howard started counting from 1001 again after reaching 1005 and putting her foot down. Howard stopped counting after reaching 1012. PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST While on scene, I informed Howard of her Preliminary Breath Rights. Howard was offered a PBT, to which she agreed (PBT Results: .17). ARREST Based on the totality of circumstances, I concluded Howard was driving a motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol. Howards involvement as a driver in a motor vehicle collision. Howards eyes were bloodshot and glassy. Howards swaying while standing upright and in place. Howards mumbled speech. The odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Howards breath and person. Admission to consuming an alcoholic beverage. Clues during Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (6/6), WAT (7/8), OLS (2/4) On January 6th, 2022, at approximately 1915 hours, I placed Howard under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack. A search incident to arrest of Howards person was conducted. The search of Howards person was negative. I transported Howard to the College Park Barrack. Howard was played the DR-15 Advice of Rights English recording provided by MVA. Howard was provided with a copy of the DR-15 to read along as well. At approximately 2007 hours, Howard agreed to take an alcohol concentration test. 20 MINUTE OBSERVATION I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Howard beginning with her arrest. A preliminary search of Howard was conducted on scene and it was revealed that she had nothing in her mouth. I observed Howard from the time of arrest until the time she submitted to the test and she did not put anything in her mouth. The test was conducted by Tpr. Peris #7511 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Howard had a result of .17 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 2021 hours. Intoximeter Result: .17 BrAC Howards vehicle was released on scene to Howard, Robert Francis (2/M, DOB: 09/24/1964). I processed Howard and released her to Howard, Robert Francis (2/M, DOB: 09/24/1964). Howard was issued the following citations. TA - 21-801(b) FAILURE TO CONTROL SPEED ON HIGHWAY TO AVOID COLLISION TA - 21-902(a1i) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL TA - 21-902(a1ii) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL PER SE TA - 21-902(b1i) DRIVING VEH. WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL TA - 21-901.1(a) RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OF PERSONS AND PROPERTY TA - 21-901.1(b) NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON TA - 21-310(a) FOLLOWING VEHICLE TOO CLOSELY The defendant was issued copies of the following documents: -Citations (listed above) -DR-15 Advice of Rights -DR-15a Order of Suspension -MSP 33 Notification to Defendant of Result of Test for Alcohol Concentration All documents were forwarded to the Prince Georges County, State Attorney Office. All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:26:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 20:45:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathanael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7454</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Aaron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fleming</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sierra</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7439</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490085</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/06/2023 18:07:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490085</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/06/2023 18:07:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490085</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/06/2023 18:07:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490085</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/06/2023 18:07:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490085</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/06/2023 18:07:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490085</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/06/2023 18:07:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490085</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15566</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/06/2023 18:07:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15566</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>46</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:04:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:13</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365431</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Howard</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alice</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Theresa</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/15/1976 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/06/2023 23:35:11</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A420</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Howard</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alice</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Theresa</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/15/1976 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A420</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/06/2023 23:35:11</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3414</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Brinkley</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>301</SubNumber>
               <City>Temple Hills</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20748</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.949969</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.803301</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>437</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4535</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:27:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:27:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:32</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 20:08:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148309</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7439</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 20:10:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7439</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2023 20:10:04</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2C3CDXHG1FH862051</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CHA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3DF8429</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>