<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012232</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/06/2023 00:48:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/06/2023 00:48:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/06/2023 00:26:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/06/2023 00:26:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI traffic stop.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 00:48:15</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/30/2023 20:54:24</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>689781</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:34:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 03:34:35</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>689781</AddressId>
         <StreetName>O/L 495 @ RT 1</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.89972</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.00843</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/06/2023 00:48:10</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/06/2023 00:48:10</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/15/2023 08:51:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 00:48:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>DUI/DWI Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP marked vehicle Q-18 is equipped with a mobile recording device. Body worn camera worn and operational.   Defendant: Keisha Lynn Sherman  Date of Birth: 9/5/1970  Date of Arrest: 4/6/2023  Time of Arrest: 0048 hours  DUI #: 23-083  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On Thursday, April 6, 2023, at approximately 0026 hours, I, Trooper Webb of the Maryland State Police  College Park Barrack was on routine patrol in my marked MSP vehicle Q-18. At this time, I was in the area of the outer loop of 495 near Route 1. While driving in lane 3, I observed a grey 2022 Chrysler Pacifica bearing District of Columbia registration GV2262 in front of me in lane 1. I observed the Chrysler to be traveling faster than the 55 miles per hour speed limit. It should be noted that I am trained to estimate vehicle speeds. I then followed the Chrysler maintaining a steady distance of four car lengths to gauge its speed for half a mile, I got a speed reading on the Chrysler as 91 miles per hour. It should be noted that as I followed this vehicle, it always swerved from lane one crossing the dotted line in to lane two on three different occasions. Each occurrence the Chrysler went over the dotted line by a tire width and would be in both lanes for a few seconds before correcting itself back in to lane one from lane two.I activated my emergency equipment and stopped the vehicle. The Chrysler pulled onto the right shoulder. Once the Chrysler came to a complete stop I approached it.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Chrysler from its passenger side and observed the driver (sole occupant) had glassy, bloodshot eyes. I advised the driver of my: rank, name, ID number, agency and that the stop was being audibly/visually recorded. I also gave the driver the reason for stop. I requested her drivers license and registration card. I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. Her movements were slow and lethargic. I identified her by her Maryland drivers license as Keisha Lynn Sherman. Sherman was unable to locate her registration card. I would ask Sherman where she was coming from, and she replied, From a dinner. When I inquired about her alcohol consumption. She replied Not much. I then asked how much is not much, and she said, One cocktail.  I walked back to my vehicle and conducted routine MVA checks on Sherman and her vehicle.  I approached the Pacifica again and asked Sherman to exit. Sherman was wearing heels. At first when I inquired if she would be ok walking and standing in these she said yes, but before doing the walk and turn test she asked if she could change in to flats, which I allowed her to change in to before the test. I continued to speak with Sherman outside her vehicle and as Sherman spoke, I continued to smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. I informed Sherman that I wanted her to perform field sobriety tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the shoulder of the Beltway. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 76 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of street lamps, patrol vehicle headlamps, spotlight, and my flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Sherman appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries.  I asked Sherman the following questions: Injuries  No Medication  No Medical Conditions  Arthritis Glasses  Yes  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pointer finger was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Shermans eyes. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Shermans pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking and no resting Nystagmus was observed. She was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Sherman if she understood the instructions and she stated yes.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes Vertical Nystagmus: Present in both eyes  WALK AND TURN (7/8 clues observed) Prior to Sherman performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Sherman was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Sherman was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Sherman was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Sherman was to keep her hands flat at her side, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Sherman was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Sherman was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Sherman was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her side, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Sherman if she understood the instructions and she stated yes.  Instructional Stage: 1.) Started too soon. Sherman began walking while I was giving instructions. 2.) Could not keep balance during instructions  Walking Stage (1st Nine): 1.) Took 10 steps instead of the instructed 9 steps. 2.) Missed heel to toe on steps 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, and 9. 3.) Stepped off line on steps 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, and 9.  4.) Used arms for balance. Her arms were more than 6 inches from her sides on all steps.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): 1.) Took 10 steps instead of the instructed 9 steps. 2.) Missed heel to toe on steps 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, and 9. 3.) Stepped off line on steps 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, and 9.  4.) Used arms for balance. Her arms were more than 6 inches from her sides on all steps.  Turn: 1.) Improper  Sherman turned in one fluid motion to the right while using her arms for balance.  ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed) Prior to Sherman performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Sherman was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Sherman if she understood the instructions, and she stated yes.  Instructional Stage:                                                             1.) Nothing to report  Balance and Count Stage:                                                        Seconds 0-10:                                                                  1.) Swayed body to the left and right.              2.) Used arms for balance. Shermans arms were more than 6 inches from her sides. 3.) Puts foot down on multiple occasions.  Seconds 11-20: 1.) Swayed body to the left and right. 2.) Used arms for balance. Shermans arms were more than 6 inches from her sides. 3.) Puts foot down on multiple occasions.  Seconds 21-30: 1.) Swayed body to the left and right. 2.) Used arms for balance. Shermans arms were more than 6 inches from her sides. 3.) Puts foot down on multiple occasions. Sherman submitted to a preliminary breath test with a .09 BrAC result.  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Sherman was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Evenly splitting dotted white lines with her vehicle. * Speeding * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle. * Slow and lethargic head and body movements. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot with a gazed look. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. * My observed signs of impairment as she performed field sobriety tests. * Sherman admitting to drinking one cocktail.  I arrested Serman for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0048 hours. She was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. Sherman was transported to the Maryland State Police  College Park Barrack for processing. Once inside the barrack, at 0118 hours I played the English audio DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Sherman in its entirety. She was given a paper copy to read along. At the conclusion of the form, Sherman verbally advised that she would not submit breath samples for the intoximeter test and signed the form indicating the same.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the observation period on Sherman in its entirety starting with her time of arrest. I escorted Sherman into the arrest processing room and remained in her custody until the time of test. Shermans mouth was checked and no foreign objects or piercings were observed. Sherman was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released to her friend at 0143 hours. Sherman was polite and cooperative throughout the process.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:48:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/13/2023 12:41:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathanael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7454</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dunlap</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6273</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Webb</LastName>
            <FirstName>Noah</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7303</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501635</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/06/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501635</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/06/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501635</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/06/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501635</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/06/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501635</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/06/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501635</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/06/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501635</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/06/2023 00:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>52</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:42:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:31</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373535</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sherman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Keisha</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/05/1970 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/06/2023 01:52:35</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sherman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Keisha</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynn</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/05/1970 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S655</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/06/2023 01:52:35</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetName>6938 33RD ST NW</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Washington</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20015</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>215</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4091</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:42:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:42:03</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 03:39:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151678</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7303</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/06/2023 03:42:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7303</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 03:42:59</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHRY</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>PACIFICA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>DC</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>GV2262</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>