<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008956</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/11/2023 03:59:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/11/2023 03:59:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/11/2023 03:36:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/11/2023 03:36:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>On Saturday, March 11th, 2023 at approximately 0336 hours, I, Trooper First Class Canizalez #7087, was on patrol operating marked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle MV-15. At that time, on Northbound I-270 in the area of Falls Road, Rockville, Montgomery County, Maryland, I observed a gray Mazda 6 bearing Delaware tags XQ378083 failing to maintain lane integrity. I observed the vehicle traveling in lane 4 when it abruptly crossed over the gore area of the transition lane from main lanes to local lanes. I continued my observations and observed the vehicle touch and cross over the white solid line with  of its vehicles left side. On two separate occasions while traveling in lane 1. Then vehicle was then scene crossing over a second gore area that transitioned towards the ramp from northbound I-270 onto westbound route 28 in the local lanes. I turned on my lights and sirens to conduct a traffic stop on that vehicle.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 03:59:07</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5364</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 11:31:35</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MD-28 WB EXIT 6 RAMP 7,ROCKVILLE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>686997</AddressId>
      <City>MDC224</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 03:59:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 00:08:01</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>686997</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Md-28 Wb Exit 6</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RAMP</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Rockville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20850</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.174782</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.087637</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/11/2023 03:59:04</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/11/2023 03:59:04</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/30/2023 16:48:22</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 03:59:07</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:05</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*****SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER***** MV-15 is not equipped with a mobile recording device Defendant: Ashley Marie Laflame  Date of Birth: 08/22/1983 Date of Arrest: 03/11/2023 Time of Arrest: 0357 hours DE SDX: 1358086  DUI #: 23-067 (Rockville)  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Certified by NHTSA to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) * Certified as a Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator  * Certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE)  * Attended the 2021 Maryland Impaired Driving Conference in Ocean City, Maryland * Participated in several DUI Special Assignments * DUI Award Recipient for 2021  2022. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On Saturday, March 11th, 2023 at approximately 0336 hours, I, Trooper First Class Canizalez #7087, was on patrol operating marked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle MV-15. At that time, on Northbound I-270 in the area of Falls Road, Rockville, Montgomery County, Maryland, I observed a gray Mazda 6 bearing Delaware tags XQ378083 failing to maintain lane integrity. I observed the vehicle traveling in lane 4 when it abruptly crossed over the gore area of the transition lane from main lanes to local lanes. I continued my observations and observed the vehicle touch and cross over the white solid line with  of its vehicles left side. On two separate occasions while traveling in lane 1. Then vehicle was then seen crossing over a second gore area that transitioned towards the ramp from northbound I-270 onto westbound route 28 in the local lanes. I turned on my lights and sirens to conduct a traffic stop on that vehicle and stopped on the ramp from westbound Route 28 towards southbound I-270.  CONTACT (PHASE 2) During my approach, I introduced myself and informed the driver the reason for the stop. I proceeded to question the driver on her travels and she stated she was coming from Bethesda and headed towards Baltimore. I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage from within the vehicle. I observed other signs of impairment from the driver such as slurred speech along with bloodshot and glassy eyes. The driver was identified by her Delaware Drivers License as: LAFLAME, Ashley Marie. (DE SDX: 1358086, W/F, DOB: 08/22/1983) While speaking with LAFLAME from the driver side, I questioned the driver on how many alcoholic beverages she consumed that night prior to driving. The driver stated not a lot. I then asked her to reiterate her answer with a quantity and she then proceeded to state nothing. I asked once more and her passenger stated she had a Twisted tea approximately 1 hour prior to driving. I asked LAFLAME to step out of the vehicle for further questioning in attempts to separate her from her vehicle. Once outside of the vehicle, I re-asked LAFLAME how much she had to consume and she stated one of those big boys of Twisted Tea. I proceeded to ask LAFLAME a series of separate questions which allowed me to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath. I asked the driver if she was willing to perform voluntary SFSTs and she advised that she would.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the left shoulder on the ramp from westbound Route 28 towards southbound I-270. (pavement). The surface was dry, level and free from any debris. The weather was clear and light condition consisted of my flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. LAFLAME appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. Prior to beginning the test, I asked LAFLAME the following questions: Glasses or Contacts: Yes. Medical Conditions: None. Injuries: None.  Medications: Medication for anxiety and depression. *TEST #1 HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN): 6/6 The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches, slightly above eye level. I instructed LAFLAME to look straight ahead, keeping her head stationary while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. I asked LAFLAME if she understood the test and she stated Yes. LAFLAME s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. LAFLAME was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Vertical Gaze Nystagmus: Present in both eyes.   *TEST #2 WALK AND TURN (WAT): 6/8 Prior to LAFLAME performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. LAFLAME was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe on the white solid line on the right shoulder. LAFLAME was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in that position until told to begin the test. LAFLAME was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. LAFLAME was instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, LAFLAME was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to the left to turn completely around. LAFLAME was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. LAFLAME was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her sides, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked LAFLAME if she understood the test and she stated, Yes.    LAFLAME was unable to maintain her balance during the instructional phase.  LAFLAME missed heel-to-toe on every step taken.   LAFLAME stepped off line on her 3rd step during her first set. LAFLAME also stepped off line on her 7th step during her second set.   LAFLAME took 8 steps during her first set.   LAFLAME raised her arms for balance at the 4th step during her first set  LAFLAME did not complete the turn correctly. She turned to the right and lifted her forward planted foot.   *TEST #3 ONE LEG STAND (OLS): 1/4 Prior to LAFLAME performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. LAFLAME was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count aloud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. LAFLAME was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, Yes. LAFLAME performed this test balanced on her right foot.    LAFLAME put her foot down at the 9th and 21st second mark.  LAFLAME used her arms for balance at the 11th second mark  I offered LAFLAME a preliminary breath test and she advised that she would take it.  PBT results: .22 ARREST: Based on the following, I had reason to believe LAFLAME was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of an alcoholic beverage: * LAFLAME failed to maintain lane integrity on two separate occasions and crossed over two separate gore areas during an abrupt lane change.  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from LAFLAMEs breath. * Bloodshot and glassy eyes. * Slurred speech * LAFLAME admitting to have consumed Not much alcohol prior to driving.  * LAFLAME admitted to have consumed 1 twisted tea approximately 1 hour prior to driving.  * LAFLAME stated after being offered the intoximeter test Already did it once, not going to do it again.  Due to the number of observations, I had reason to believe LAFLAME was driving under the influence of an alcoholic beverage and was unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0357 hours, I placed LAFLAME under arrest for Driving While Under the Influence of Alcohol. A preliminary search of LAFLAME was conducted on the scene and it revealed that she had nothing on her person. LAFLAME was seat belted into my marked MSP patrol vehicle MV-15 and was transported to the Rockville City Police Department per departmental policy. While conducting the secondary search on LAFLAME at the station, her oral cavity was checked and was clear and had nothing in her mouth. During the 20-minute observation period, LAFLAME remained in my custody and did not introduce any foreign object in her mouth. The DR-15 Advice of Rights was read to LAFLAME at 0425 hours. Upon completion of being read the DR-15, LAFLAME refused to submit to the intoximeter test. LAFLAME was later transported to the MSP Rockville Barrack per departmental policy to wait for her ride. INTOXIMETER RESULT  REFUSAL LAFLAME was given all pertinent paperwork and was later released to her family friend at 0630 hours.  Case status: closed by arrest. All events occurred in MontgomeryCounty, Maryland </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 07:08:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/29/2023 03:30:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shu</LastName>
            <FirstName>Wen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6755</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Saucerman</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4873</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498355</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 03:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 06:51:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 00:29:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498355</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 03:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 06:51:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 00:29:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498355</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 03:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 06:51:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 00:27:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498355</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 03:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 06:51:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 00:27:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498355</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 03:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 06:51:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 00:26:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498355</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 03:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 06:51:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 00:27:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 06:51:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:26</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371290</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Laflame</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ashley</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/22/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2023 06:34:43</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L145</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Laflame</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ashley</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/22/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L145</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2023 06:34:43</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5546</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Doral</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Wilmington</City>
               <StateCode>DE</StateCode>
               <Zip5>19808</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2629</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.699075</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.730616</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>302</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>589</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8811</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 00:30:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:44</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 00:30:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:44</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 00:30:46</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:44</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 00:25:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 00:25:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150765</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/14/2023 00:33:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 00:33:07</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/22/2023 22:45:11</DateOfInfo>
         <DateOfInfo>03/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JM1GL1V50H1134156</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MAZD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MAZDA6</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>DE</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>DE</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>23030</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicNumber>XQ378083</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicYear>2022</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>4</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicMonth>5</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehConditionCode>G</VehConditionCode>
         <VehDamageCode>0</VehDamageCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>