<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-038068</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/29/2023 02:43:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/29/2023 02:43:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/29/2023 02:30:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/29/2023 02:30:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>23-580 "R" MONGER</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 02:43:37</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6354</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 18:23:29</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>DULANEY VALLEY RD/ I695</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>612507</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 02:43:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/29/2023 03:07:37</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>612507</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Dulaney Valley</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Towson</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.60036</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.41289</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 DULANEY VALLEY RD / 0-0 I695</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>N/B DULANEY VALLEY RD TO I/L I-695</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/29/2023 02:43:34</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/29/2023 02:43:34</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/30/2023 18:23:30</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 02:43:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSPQ031</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 11:32:10</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E.) TEAM* The following incident was captured on in-car and body camera Defendant: Jamal Ajkeem Monger  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: * I am trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (March 2013 SFST NHTSA Manual). * I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor as of February 2016. * I am a Certified Breath Test Operator by the Toxicologist of the State of Maryland as of March 2016. * I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of March 2016. * I am a distinguished graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute as of June 2015 * I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of May 2014. * I am a Preliminary Breath Test Instructor as of May 2019. * I am a RADAR and LIDAR Instructor as of October 2019. * I have apprehended more than 1,100 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On October 29, 2023 at approximately 0228 hours, I (Cpl. Wallace #6323) was on patrol in unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle DUI-1 on northbound Dulaney Valley Road prior to I-695, Baltimore County, Maryland. I observed a silver Chrysler Pacifica traveling in front of my patrol vehicle, swerving left and right.    Right on dotted white line, left towards median, right on dotted white, left  Left on dotted white line, right.  Into right lane directly in front of another vehicle that had to brake  Left on dotted white line, right  Left over dotted white line, right  Left over dotted white line, right  Left over dotted white line, right  Braking and swerving  U-turn onto southbound Dulaney Valley Road  Left on dotted white line, over dotted white line, right  Left over dotted white line  Accelerated away at what appeared to be above the posted 40 MPH speed limit. I activated the front antenna of the Golden Eagle II Radar (S/N: EG-02387) in moving mode (same direction). A received a speed reading of 51 MPH in a posted 40 MPH zone. I activated my emergency equipment and attempted to conduct a traffic stop on the Chrysler. The Chrysler was bearing Maryland registration 6FH8719 and continued driving on southbound Dulaney Valley Road. The Chrysler was swerving left and right. The Chrysler passed an open shoulder on the right side and continued southbound. The Chrysler came to a stop in the travel lane on the overpass for I-695.  The above referenced RADAR was calibrated before and after my shift and was functioning properly. I am a certified RADAR operator. Training certificates and calibration records will be made available upon request. This RADAR is specifically assigned to my vehicle.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Chrysler on the drivers side and made contact with the male operator of the vehicle, who was the only occupant in the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop and requested his drivers license and vehicle registration. He stated that he was going home. He was identified by his Maryland drivers license as Jamal Ajkeem Monger. While speaking with Monger, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I deliberately observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I returned to my patrol vehicle to notify the barrack who I was out with.  I returned to the Chrysler and requested Monger to exit his vehicle and walk to the front. He complied and exited his vehicle. He dropped his wallet while exiting. While speaking with Monger outside the vehicle, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. When asked about alcohol consumption prior to driving, he stated that he had 2 shots of tequila at 1AM. I informed Monger that I wanted him to perform standardized field sobriety tests, to which he agreed to the tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests.  I asked Monger the following questions:  Glasses or contacts  Contacts Head Injuries - No Medication  No Problems with knees or ankles  No  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus    Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes  WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage:    Lost balance offline to the right and left.  Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Missed touching heel to toe by more than 6 inches on all 9 steps.  Turn: Turned left, moved foot that was supposed to be planted. Walking Stage (2nd Nine):    Missed touching heel to toe by more than 6 inches on all 10 steps.  Took 10 steps when instructed to take 9   ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. -Left foot raised. Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10:    Swayed body to the left and right.  Raised arms more than 6 inches from side for balance.  Seconds 11-20:    Raised arms more than 6 inches from side for balance.  Seconds 21-30:    Swayed body to the left and right.  Raised arms more than 6 inches from side for balance.  Left foot hit the ground 1 time.     Now stated 3 shots  PBT .16 BrAC.  ARREST Due to the number of observations, I concluded Monger was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0243 hours, I placed Monger under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. He was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and was transported to the Baltimore County Towson Precinct for processing.  Upon arrival at the precinct, I provided Monger with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Monger listened to the DR-15 Advice of Rights from the MVA website. At 0311hours, Monger refused to take a breath test.  20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: Not applicable  INTOXIMETER RESULT: ****Refusal****  Monger was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 00:26:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 12:18:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>527529</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/29/2023 02:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 03:21:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/29/2023 03:22:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 03:21:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/29/2023 03:23:39</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>391534</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Monger</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jamal</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Aikeem</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/12/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/29/2023 03:04:38</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M526</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Monger</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jamal</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Aikeem</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/12/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M526</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/29/2023 03:04:38</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>4804</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Althea</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21206</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5726</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.557606</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.332869</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 03:23:39</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 03:23:39</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 03:21:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/29/2023 03:21:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158474</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/29/2023 03:24:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/29/2023 03:24:14</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2023</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHRY</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>PACIFICA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6FH8719</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>