<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-044532</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/17/2023 00:15:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/17/2023 00:15:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/16/2023 23:33:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/16/2023 23:33:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 00:15:42</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4873</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/02/2024 16:49:21</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>716252</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 00:15:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 09:51:42</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>716252</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>9231</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>New Hampshire</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Silver Spring</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.980825</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.005061</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FOX ST AT 650</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/17/2023 00:15:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/17/2023 00:15:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 18:24:58</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/17/2023 00:15:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>N-12 is equipped with a mobile recording device. Defendant: Jose Serrano Ramirez  Date of Birth: 05/18/1994 Date of Arrest: 12/17/2023 Time of Arrest: 2353 hours MD SDX: MD-10274174383  DUI #: 23-269 (Rockville)  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Certified by NHTSA to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) * Certified as a Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator  * Certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE)  * Attended the 2021 Maryland Impaired Driving Conference in Ocean City, Maryland * Participated in several DUI Special Assignments * DUI Award Recipient for 2021  2022. * Gaithersburg Germantown Chamber of Commerce Award Recipient 2023 * Since 2020 have made over 120 DUI arrest VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On Saturday, December 16th, 2023 at approximately 2333 hours, I, Trooper First Class Canizalez #7087, was on patrol on northbound Route 650 in the area of Fox Street, Silver Spring, Montgomery County Maryland, when I observed a blue Toyota Camry bearing Maryland Registration 4FC6889 traveling at approximately 21 MPH in a 35 MPH zone. Furthering my observations, I observed the vehicle fail to maintain its lane integrity on two separate occasions with both left tires crossing the white broken lines at tire width. I initiated my lights and sirens to conduct a traffic stop on the vehicle. As I was pulling the vehicle over, the driver proceeded into Fox Street making a right turn from 650.  CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the vehicle and contacted the driver on his drivers side. I introduced myself and informed the driver the reason for the stop and asked for his license. Immediately, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from within the vehicle and observed an open can of Modelo beer in the front center cup holder. I observed other signs of impairment on the driver such as heavy slurred speech and bloodshot and glassy eyes. I questioned the driver of his travels and he stated he was coming from home and was headed to his wifes house. During my second approach I observed that the driver had discarded the Modelo can and threw it behind his driver seat spilling all over the rear driver side carpet. The driver was identified by his Maryland Drivers License as: SERRANO RAMIREZ, Jose. (MD SDX: MD-10274174383, H/M, DOB: 05/18/1994) I asked SERRANO RAMIREZ to step out of the vehicle for further questioning. While speaking with SERRANO RAMIREZ from outside of his vehicle, I questioned the him on how many alcoholic beverages he consumed that night prior to driving and he stated he had consumed 2 canned Modelo beers approximately 3 hours prior to driving. I continued to detect the odor of a strong alcoholic beverage from his breath even with traffic passing. I asked the driver if he was willing to perform voluntary SFSTs and he advised that he would. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the side walk on Fox Street in the area of Route 650. (pavement). The surface was dry, level and free from any debris. The weather was clear and light condition consisted of my flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. SERRANO RAMIREZ was not displaying any injuries. Prior to beginning the test, I asked SERRANO RAMIREZ the following questions: Glasses or Contacts: None. Medical Conditions: None. Injuries: None.  Medications: None.  *TEST #1 HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN): 6/6 The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from SERRANO RAMIREZ s eyes, and slightly above eye level. I instructed SERRANO RAMIREZ to look straight ahead, keeping his head stationary while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. I asked SERRANO RAMIREZ if he understood the test and he stated, Yes. SERRANO RAMIREZ s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. SERRANO RAMIREZ was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes. 4.) Vertical Gaze Nystagmus: Present in both eyes. *TEST #2 WALK AND TURN (WAT): 6/8 Prior to SERRANO RAMIREZ performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. SERRANO RAMIREZ was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on a straight imaginary line. SERRANO RAMIREZ was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin the test. SERRANO RAMIREZ was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. SERRANO RAMIREZ was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, SERRANO RAMIREZ was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to the left to turn completely around. SERRANO RAMIREZ was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. SERRANO RAMIREZ was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked SERRANO RAMIREZ if he understood the test and he stated, Yes.     margin-bottom:11px"&gt;SERRANO RAMIREZ was unable to maintain his balance during the instructional phase   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;SERRANO RAMIREZ stopped walking on his 5th step during his first set.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;SERRANO RAMIREZ stepped off line on his 2nd step during his first set and on his second set he stepped off line on his 4th step.    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;SERRANO RAMIREZ missed heel to toe on his 1st step during his first set. On his second set he missed heel to toe on every step taken.    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;SERRANO RAMIREZ took the incorrect number of instructed steps and took 10 step son his first set.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;SERRANO RAMIREZ did not properly turn as instructed.   *TEST #3 ONE LEG STAND (OLS): 2/4  Prior to SERRANO RAMIREZ performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. SERRANO RAMIREZ was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count aloud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. SERRANO RAMIREZ was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, Yes. SERRANO RAMIREZ performed this test balanced on his right foot.     margin-bottom:11px"&gt;SERRANO RAMIREZ put his foot down at the 5th and 21st second mark   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;SERRANO RAMIREZ used his arms for balance at the 12th and 20th second mark.  I offered SERRANO RAMIREZ a preliminary breath test and he advised that he would take it. While attempting, he would not blow and would just wrap his lips around the straw on several occasions. SERRANO RAMIREZ provided an insufficient breath sample and just barely blew into the straw but the Preliminary Breath Test was able to capture a sample.  PBT BrAC results: .15 ARREST: Based on the following, I had reason to believe SERRANO RAMIREZ was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of an alcoholic beverage: * SERRANO RAMIREZ failed to maintain his lane integrity on two separate occasions.  * SERRANO RAMIREZ traveling at a speed lower than the posted speed limit (approximately 21 mph in a 30-35mph zone).  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from SERRANO RAMIREZ breath. * Bloodshot and glassy eyes. * Slurred speech * Swaying in place while performing HGN * SERRANO RAMIREZ admitting to have consumed 2 canned Modelo beers bottle approximately 3 hours prior to driving.  * SERRANO RAMIREZ having consumed a canned Modelo beer while driving, open container and was poured out on the side of the road after he attempted to hide it behind his driver seat spilling on the rear driver side carpet.  Due to the number of observations, I had reason to believe SERRANO RAMIREZ was driving under the influence of an alcoholic beverage and was unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 2353 hours, I placed SERRANO RAMIREZ under arrest for Driving While Under the Influence of Alcohol. A preliminary search of SERRANO RAMIREZ was conducted on the scene and it revealed that he had nothing on his person and was later transported to the Montgomery County 3rd District. SERRANO RAMIREZ was read his DR15 Advise of Rights and refused to submit to the intoximeter test at 0030 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT  REFUSAL SERRANO RAMIREZ was given all pertinent paperwork and was later released to his relatives at 0050 hours.  Case status: closed by arrest. All events occurred in MontgomeryCounty, Maryland </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:11:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:12:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Saucerman</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4873</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534009</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 23:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:37:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:39:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534009</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 23:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:37:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:39:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534009</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15657</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 23:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15657</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:37:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:39:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534009</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 23:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:37:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:40:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534009</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 23:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:37:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:40:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534009</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 23:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:37:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:38:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534009</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 23:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:37:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:38:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534009</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15667</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/16/2023 23:53:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15667</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:37:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:41:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:37:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:42:02</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>396042</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Serrano ramirez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jose</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/18/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/25/2023 10:26:38</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S656</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Serrano ramirez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jose</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/18/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S656</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/25/2023 10:26:38</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1020</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>University</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>W</StreetSuffixCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>722</SubNumber>
               <City>Silver Spring</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20901</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.024553</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.034448</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:42:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:42:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:42:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:42:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:42:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:42:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:37:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:37:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>160172</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 10:43:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 10:43:09</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>4t1kz1ak3nu071032</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CAM</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>DBL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4fc6889</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>8</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>