<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-036946</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/21/2023 03:31:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/21/2023 03:31:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/21/2023 03:06:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/21/2023 03:06:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI, DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/21/2023 03:31:59</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5099</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/19/2023 03:14:30</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY / HAWKES HILL RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>710587</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/21/2023 03:32:00</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/01/2023 10:27:48</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>710587</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Easton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.060266</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.768788</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/21/2023 03:31:55</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/21/2023 03:31:55</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/19/2023 03:14:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/21/2023 03:31:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/20/2023 20:22:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police Easton Barrack I MSP marked vehicle I-35, does have MVR and incident was recorded via body camera/In car camera.  Defendant: Norvin Noe Roblero Herrera Date of Birth: 01/13/1991 Date of Arrest: 10/21/2023 Times of Arrest: 0329 hours DUI #: 23-58-225(Easton Barrack)  CERTIFICATION  TRAINING *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) *Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) *Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On 10/21/2023at approximately 0306hours, I, Trooper Repa #7124, Maryland State Police, Easton Barrack,was on stationary patrol in the area of Ocean Gateway at Hawkes Hill Road, Easton, Talbot County, Maryland. I observed a maroon Chevrolet sedan traveling at a high rate of speed. My incar front radar unit was already directed towards the vehicle and displayed the maroon Chevrolet traveling 78 mph in the 55 mph zone. I am certified to operate the in-car radar unit and made sure the unit was in proper working order. As I got behind the vehicle, I observed the vehicle was bearing Maryland registration 2FB7210 on a maroon Chevrolet sedan. I activated my vehicles emergency lights/siren and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the maroon Chevrolet sedan on the drivers side. I advised the driver the reason for the stop and requested his license and registration card. I asked the driver where he was coming from, and he advised from picking up his uncle in Cambridge, Maryland and headed to his house in Easton, Maryland. I observed the driver had glassy and bloodshot eyes. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on the drivers breath and I asked how much the driver had to drink tonight. At first the driver advised nothing. I asked again and told him I could smell alcohol on his breath. The driver advised me that he had two beers. I asked which kind and the driver advised Modelo. Alcoholic beverages were observed inside the vehicle. The driver was identified by his name and date of birth as Norvin Noe Roblero Herrera (DOB 01/13/1991 H/M). Roblero Herrera advised me multiple times that he was sorry as if he was in the wrong. I advised Roblero Herrera I was going to perform standardized field sobriety tests to which he complied. I positioned Roblero Herrera clear of traffic in front of my unmarked police cruiser.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed in front of my unmarked police cruiser. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and the temperature was in the 60s. Lighting conditions consisted of my patrol vehicles headlights, streetlamps, and my flashlight. All forward facing emergency vehicle lights were deactivated during the tests. Roblero Herrera appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. Prior to starting the test, Roblero Herrera randomly advised he was police in Guatemala.  I asked Roblero Herrera the following questions prior to performing field sobriety: Currently any injuries? No Currently taking any medications? High blood pressure medication Currently wears contacts or glasses? Yes, contacts  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. Iproperly explained the test. A pens tip was used as the stimulus for the test and held approximately 12 inches from Roblero Herreras eyes. Roblero Herrera was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Roblero Herrera s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Iasked Roblero Herrera if he understood the directions, and he stated, yes.Roblero Herrera moved his head when I first started the test. I demonstrated to Roblero Herrera how to properly conduct the test. Roblero Herrera stated he understood after demonstrating. Roblero Herrera was positioned away from passing traffic to ensure the results of the HGN test were not compromised.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes  *Vertical Gaze Nystagmus  Present in both eyes  WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)  Prior toRoblero Herrera performing the test, Iproperly explained the test and physically demonstrated how the test should be done. Before I could ask if Roblero Herrera if he understood the directions, he started the test.  Instructional Stage: 1.) Stepped offline. 2.) Started before Instructed.  Walking Stage (1stNine) 1.) Miss counted steps (22 steps)  Walking Stage (2nd Nine) 1.) Missed counted steps (17 steps).  Turn was done unsatisfactory. Roblero Herrera moved his pivot foot and turned in one fluent motion.  ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)  Prior to Roblero Herreraperforming the test, Iproperly explained the test andphysically demonstrated how the test should be done. Roblero Herrera was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, yes.  Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 11-20: 1.)Foot down. 2.) Swayed.  Seconds 21-30: 1.)Foot down. 2.) Swayed.  Preliminary Breath Test: I explained a Preliminary Breath Test (PBT). After explaining, Roblero Herrera submitted to the PBT test with the result of .12.  ARREST :  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Roblero Herrerawas driving a motor vehicle impaired: *smell of an alcoholic beverage on his breath. *admission to consuming an alcoholic beverage. *Glassy and bloodshot eyes. *Alcoholic beverages located in the vehicle *Observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests. *PBT results.  I arrested Roblero Herrerafor driving under the influence at 0329hours. He was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. Roblero Herrera was read the DR-15 form on the Motor Vehicle Administration website in Spanish on my in-car laptop. At the conclusion of the form, Roblero Herrera submitted to the intoximeter test and signed the DR-15 indicating the same (0350 hours). Roblero Herrera was transported to the Easton State Police Barrack for processing. At the barrack, Roblero Herrera failed to submit to a breath specimen test on two different attempts and the machine marked Roblero Herrera as a refusal.  Roblero Herrera was given all copies of pertinent paperwork at the Easton State Police Barrack. Roblero Herrerareceived a ride home from a friend.  All events occurred in TalbotCounty, Maryland.  I requested this case closed. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/16/2023 03:52:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7124</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/16/2023 23:14:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Goldman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stansbury</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Repa</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alexander</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>526408</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/21/2023 03:06:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/23/2023 23:00:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7124</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/23/2023 23:00:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/01/2023 10:58:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7124</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/01/2023 10:58:41</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>391795</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Roblero Herrera</LastName>
               <FirstName>Norvin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Noe</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/13/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/01/2023 10:57:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R146</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N615</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Roblero Herrera</LastName>
               <FirstName>Norvin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Noe</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/13/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R146</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N615</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/01/2023 10:57:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/01/2023 10:58:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/01/2023 10:58:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/23/2023 23:00:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7124</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/23/2023 23:00:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158563</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/01/2023 11:11:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7124</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/01/2023 11:11:58</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>MAR</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>MAR</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2FB7210</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>