<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-039014</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/05/2023 01:27:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/05/2023 01:27:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/05/2023 01:06:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/05/2023 01:06:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI TS - 23-589</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/05/2023 01:27:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/11/2023 02:51:59</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>15 MM I83 SB, LUTHERVILLE TIMONIUM</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>712139</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/05/2023 01:27:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 19:11:34</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>712139</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>15</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I83 Sb Lutherville Timonium</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.6333883333333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.4365228333333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/05/2023 01:27:40</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/05/2023 01:27:40</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/11/2023 02:52:00</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/05/2023 01:27:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSPQ031</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 11:32:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*This stop was captured on in-car and body worn camera* DUI #: 23-589 CASE #: 23-MSP-039014 SUSPECT: Greene, Marquita Lynne (B/F DOB: 11/27/1990) VICTIM: Society TRAINING, KNOWLEDGE, AND EXPERIENCE:   Certified to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests in January, 2018.  Graduated the Maryland State Police Training Academy in February, 2018.  Assigned to the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack in February, 2018.   Certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driver Enforcement (ARIDE) in March, 2018.  Certified as a RADAR/LIDAR operator in November, 2019.  Certified as Standardized Field Sobriety Test Instructor in January, 2020.  Graduated Basic Criminal Investigators Course in September, 2020.  Certified as Drug Recognition Expert (DRE) in June 2021.  Certified in National Traffic Incident Management (TIM) in August 2021.  Certified as Field Training Trooper (FTT) in March, 2022.   Certified as Drug Recognition Expert (DRE) Instructor in May, 2022.  Assigned to the State Police Impaired Driver Reduction Effort (SPIDRE) Team in April, 2023.  Graduated the University of Maryland DUI Institute Session XV in June, 2023.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Certified as Intoximeter EC/IR II Operator in July, 2023.  NARRATIVE:  On November 5, 2023 at approximately 0106 hours, I was on duty and in uniform operating unmarked MSP vehicle P-11. I was on routine patrol in the area of O/L I-695 at York Road, Baltimore County, Maryland, when I first observed the suspect vehicle. PHASE 1: VEHICLE IN MOTION  My attention was first drawn to the vehicle as it was traveling in lane 4 directly in front of me and began rocking back and forth in its lane. At one point, the suspect vehicle slowly drifted to the left crossing over the dotted lane lines for lane 3, taking an abnormally long time to change lanes. When the vehicle did change lanes fully into lane 3, it continued to drift left all the way across the lane causing both driver side tires to cross over the dotted lane line into lane 2 and then slowly drifting back to lane 3. After correcting back into lane 3, the suspect vehicle began to accelerate slightly while continuing to visibly rock back and forth in the lane.  After passing York Road, the suspect vehicle drifted right causing both driver side tires to touch the solid white shoulder line, then slowly back to the left towards the center of the lane, and then immediately back to the right causing both driver side tires to cross over the solid white shoulder and onto the shoulder. At the same time, we were on a slight curve in the roadway and the vehicle abruptly jerked back to the left, causing the vehicle to travel all the way across the lane and both driver side tires to cross the dotted lane lines into lane 2. At the same time, there was another passenger car in lane 2 between my vehicle and the suspect vehicle. When the vehicle corrected back to the right, it again caused both passenger side tires to cross over the solid white shoulder line. The vehicle continued to drive in this manner as if it could not recover from the original correction.  As we navigated another slight bend in the roadway prior to Charles Street, the suspect vehicle again drifted to the left causing approximately half the vehicle width to cross over the dotted lane lines, and then continue to straddle the lane line for the remaining length of the curve. As the road began to straighten out, the vehicle began to accelerate again while continuing to aggressively rock back and forth. As we began to pass Charles Street, the suspect vehicle drifted to the right causing both passenger side tires to cross over the dotted lane line for lane 4, and then all the way back to the left causing both driver side tires to cross over the dotted lane lines for lane 2. When the vehicle drifted to the left, there was the same passenger car from before directly beside the suspect vehicle. The suspect vehicle abruptly corrected back to the right while applying its brakes, but then almost immediately began to slowly drift back to the left, again crossing over the dotted lane line into lane 2 now behind the other vehicle.  As we then approached N/B I-83, the suspect vehicle made a last-minute lane change from lane 3 to lane 4 to then exit onto N/B I-83. On the ramp, the suspect vehicle was straddling the lane line for lanes 1 and 2 for the beginning portion of the ramp, and the continued to rock back and forth after correcting. After merging onto N/B I-83, the suspect vehicle changed lanes into lane 2 and immediately drifted to the left crossing over half the vehicle width into lane 1, before slowly correcting back to the right. When the vehicle corrected right, it completely crossed lane 2, went all the way across lane 3 in front of my vehicle, and then immediately drifted back to the left causing approximately half the vehicle width to straddle the lane line for lane 2.  As we then approached Timonium Road, the suspect vehicle again drifted to the left while straddling the dotted lane lines for lane 2 on two separate occasions within seconds of each other. After correcting back to the center of the lane, the vehicle began to slowly accelerate while continuing to rock back and forth. As the vehicle was accelerating, it completely changed lanes into lane 2 but crossed all the way over the lane causing half the vehicle width to cross into lane 1, abruptly jerked back to the right causing both passenger side tires to touch the dotted lane lines for lane 3, and then immediately back to the left towards lane 1.  At that time, I activated my emergency equipment to conduct a lawful traffic stop on the suspect vehicle in the area of Timonium Road. After activating my emergency equipment, the suspect vehicle did not react to my presence and continued driving at highway speed while in lane 2. As I continued to cycle my siren, the suspect vehicle appeared to be moving towards the right shoulder, crossing over the lane lines from lane 2 to lane 3, but then corrected back into lane 2 and continued to drive. I continued to follow behind the vehicle while cycling my siren and providing information to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack for another approximate one mile before the suspect vehicle finally pulled to the right side of the roadway. The vehicle stopped with half the vehicle on the shoulder and the other half in lane 4 at the top of the ramp from N/B I-83 to Padonia Road, Baltimore County, Maryland. The entire time I had my emergency equipment activated, there was a large shoulder available on the right shoulder, and a full shoulder was available at the location the vehicle stopped. The vehicle was a maroon Acura RDX bearing Maryland registration 7ET3506. PHASE 2: PERSONAL CONTACT  I made a passenger side approach to the vehicle and made contact with the driver and sole occupant of the vehicle. When I first approached the vehicle, I observed all the windows were still up and the driver was holding a phone in her hands that she was looking down at. After knocking on the window, the driver made a slow movement towards the driver side door to push the button for the window. After making my initial contact with the driver, she stated that she was OK and apologized. When I asked the driver why she was swerving, she claimed that she wasnt. The driver also did not realize that I had been trying to pull her over for so long. When I asked the driver for her license and registration, she immediately stated that the vehicle belonged to her sister. The driver already had a small packet of paperwork in her hand that she handed to me, even though I had only asked for the registration card. The driver also stated that she did not have her license on her, and that she was a nurse at the jail.  As the driver was speaking, I began to detect the heavy odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the passenger compartment of the vehicle. I also observed that the drivers speech was slow, thick, and slurred, her eyes were glossy, and she appeared drowsy with droopy eyelids. When I asked the driver where she was coming from that night, she stated, It was a birthday party. When I asked the driver where the party was, she struggled to remember the name of the location but eventually stated that she was at a restaurant called Top Hat. While the driver was thinking of the location she came from, she provided the name and date of birth of Marquita Lynne Greene (B/F DOB: 11/27/1990). Greenes identity was later confirmed using the MVA Browse function of METERS/NCIC.  When I asked Greene how many alcoholic beverages she had consumed that evening, she first stated, not a lot. When I asked Greene to clarify what that meant, she then stated she had two drinks. When I asked Greene what the drinks were, she stated she was drinking Angry Orchard, and her last drink was at approximately 2300 hours. As I was asking Greene to confirm her address, she stated, Im literally two seconds from my house.  Based on my initial observations, I ask Greene to exit her vehicle and speak with me further. Greene agreed to exit the vehicle. Greene was slow to exit her vehicle, and then took slow and deliberate steps toward the front of the vehicle. As I explained to Greene that I wanted to talk with her further to make sure she was safe to drive, she stated, Im safe to drive. You can even follow me. I like 5 minutes from here. Greene again stated that she had only consumed two beers and her last drink was at approximately 2300 hours, and that she began drinking at 2200 hours. Greene also went on to state that her mothers birthday was the day prior and she had passed away. Greene then again asked for me to follow her home, now stating that she lived 10 minutes away. As I spoke with Greene outside of her vehicle, I continued to detect the heavy odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. I further continued to observe that her speech was slow and slurred and she appeared drowsy. PHASE 3: PRE-ARREST SCREENING  Based on my observations and conversations with Greene, I asked her to perform standardized field sobriety tests to confirm she could safely operate a motor vehicle. Greene was initially hesitant because she was employed as a nurse at the Baltimore County Detention Center, but did eventually agree to submit to the tests. The tests were performed in front of Greenes vehicle where the ground was level and free from debris. The weather at the time was clear and approximately 42 degrees Fahrenheit. At the time, Greene was wearing a tank top shirt, button up shirt that was un-buttoned, jeans, and laced sneakers. Greene stated that she was wearing contacts at the time, but they did not change the color of her eyes or the shape of her pupils. Greene stated that she did not have any recent head injuries, and did not have any problems with her balance or ability to walk. Greene did state that she takes medication, but she stated it was normal over the counter medication for migraines such as Excedrin and Tylenol. STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS Instructions: The subject is told to stand with their feet together and their arms down at their side. A stimulus (ink pen) is held approximately twelve to fifteen inches from the subjects face, and they are asked to follow the stimulus with their eyes only and not to move their head. Prior to beginning the test, I ask the subject if they understand the instructions. I initially check for equal pupil size, resting nystagmus, and equal tracking. I next check for lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees. Finally, I check for vertical nystagmus. Both eyes are checked twice for each clue. Results: 6/6. Greene had brown eyes that were bloodshot and glossy. Greene had droopy eyelids and appeared drowsy. Both pupils appeared normal and equal in size. Both eyes were tracking equally and resting nystagmus was not present. Greene initially attempted to move her head with the stimulus, but stopped after being corrected. All clues were present and distinct, with an early onset of nystagmus. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was present. WALK AND TURN Instructions: The subject is told to stand with their right foot in front of their left foot in a heel to toe manner. They are told to stay in that position and keep their arms at their side until being told to begin the test. I ask to make sure they understand and then begin explaining and demonstrating the test. The subject is instructed to take nine heel-to-toe steps on a straight, imaginary line. On the ninth step, they are instructed to leave their lead foot planted and take a series of small steps to turn 180 degrees. They are then told to take an additional nine heel-to-toe steps back down the same imaginary line. They are told to watch their feet, count their steps out loud, keep their hands at their side, touch heel-to-toe on every step, and to not stop walking until the test is completed. I then ask if they understand the instructions before having them begin the test. Results:    Cannot Keep Balance: Greene struggled to enter into and maintain the starting position. Greene stumbled out of the starting position 10 times and was never able to hold the position for longer than 1-2 seconds at a time. As I began demonstrating the test, Greene stepped out of the starting position for the 11th time and was standing normally.  Starts Too Soon: Greene attempted to begin the test as I was placing her in the starting position and after I demonstrated the test, but as I was still giving instructions and before I told her to begin.   Steps Off Line: Greene stepped off line on steps one, two, and five of the first set of steps, and on steps two, five, six, seven, and eight of the second set of steps.   Misses Heel-to-Toe: Greene was walking with a larger-than-normal gate and missed heel-to-toe on all steps.  The Turn: Performed unsatisfactorily. Turned using both feet rather than keeping her lead foot planted and taking small steps around as instructed.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Other: Abnormally large gate. Was not looking down at her feet while walking. After finishing the test, I asked Greene if she remembered how I instructed her to walk and she stated that she did. When I asked if she was touching her heels to her toes as she walked, she nodded her head up and down.   Total Clues: 5/8 ONE LEG STAND Instructions: The subject is instructed to stand with their feet together with their hands at the side while I explain the instructions and demonstrate the test. They are told to raise either foot of their choice approximately six inches off the ground. They are told to begin to count, one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-threeetc. They are told to continue counting until I tell them to stop. They are told to watch their feet, to count out loud, to keep their arms at their side, and to not put their foot down. I then ask if the subject understands the instructions. Results:    Puts Foot Down: Greene put her foot down eight times during the entire test, and struggled to keep her foot raised for more than 1-2 seconds at a time.   Uses Arms to Balance: Greene occasionally and periodically raised her arms from her side as she lost her balance and put her foot down.   Other: Greene began the test by raising her right leg and standing on her left foot. Slow count and would restart counting after putting her foot down.    Total Clues: 2/4 After completing the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, I asked Greene, On a scale of one to ten, with one being completely sober and ten being blackout drunk, where do you think you are? Greene replied, Probably a three. ARREST  Based on my observations, as well as my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper and Drug Recognition Expert, I placed Greene under arrest for driving under the influence at approximately 0127 hours. Greene was polite and cooperative during my entire interaction with her. After being placed under arrest, Greene attempted to plea with me for leniency, asked me to take her home, and stated she needed to get home to her children. Greene went on to state that her children, ages 11 and 5, were home alone without a babysitter. I asked Greene if there was any family member or friend close by that she could call to check on her children, but she stated there wasnt. Greene was secured in my vehicle to be transported to the Baltimore County Towson Precinct for further processing. Greenes vehicle was secured on the right shoulder, and her phone and keys were removed from the vehicle to be transported with her.  Greene was mostly quiet on the way to the Precinct, but she would occasionally talk to herself and mumble under her breath. As Greene spoke, the heavy odor of an alcoholic beverage began to emanate throughout the passenger compartment of my vehicle. We arrived at the Towson Precinct at approximately 0142 hours. After arriving at the Precinct, Greene was allowed to call a friend at her request to pick her up from the Precinct.  Greene was provided a copy of her DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along as an audio recording of the form was played directly from the Motor Vehicle Administration website. When I began the recording, Greene stated that she could hear and understand the audio. While the recording was playing, Greene kept the form face up on the table to her left but she was looking around the room, not appearing to be following along. After the recording, Greene stated that she understood the form and did not have any questions. Greene initially refused to submit to the test. When I asked Greene to sign the form for her refusal, she then asked about the suspension as if she was not paying attention and seemed confused. After I explained the possible suspensions she was facing, she then changed her mind agreed to submit to an alcohol concentration test at approximately 0203 hours. Sgt. Pugh #0588, Baltimore County Police, a certified intoximeter operator, performed the test. The result of the test was .25 grams of alcohol per 210L of breath. DISPOSITION  Greenes friend arrived at the Precinct before we began the alcohol concentration test. Greene was released from the Precinct at approximately 0240 hours to a sober driver after being charged accordingly. All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/09/2023 11:33:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 11:33:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528480</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/05/2023 01:27:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 19:11:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 19:12:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>32</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 19:11:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 19:13:27</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392390</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Greene</LastName>
               <FirstName>Marquita</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/27/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 19:05:35</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G650</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M623</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Greene</LastName>
               <FirstName>Marquita</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lynne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/27/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G650</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M623</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/07/2023 19:05:35</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>10</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Stag Horn</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Cockeysville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21030</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.622931</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.470882</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 19:13:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 19:13:27</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/07/2023 19:11:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/07/2023 19:11:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>