<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-010126</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/21/2023 02:06:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/21/2023 02:06:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/19/2023 05:20:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/19/2023 05:20:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>SEXUAL ASSAULT REPORT</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 02:06:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5585</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 12:19:59</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>RAP</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>SAS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>10492</AddressId>
      <SubBeat>670</SubBeat>
      <City>MDC350</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 02:06:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 17:12:32</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>10492</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>55</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>WADE</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>CATONSVILLE</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <SubBeat>670</SubBeat>
         <Longitude>-76.72446900664902</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.267412211893316</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SPRING GROVE HOSPITAL</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>ROSEWOOD HOSPITAL</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SPRING GROVE HOPITAL ENTRANCE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SPRING GROVE HOPITAL</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SPRING GROVE HOSP</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SPRING GROVE HOSPITAL CENTER</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SPRING GROVE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/21/2023 02:06:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/21/2023 02:06:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/18/2023 12:20:03</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 02:06:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> Attachments: -Victim written statement  Neighborhood Check Due to the nature of the crime, being transported to GBMC, and the crime occurring two days prior, no neighborhood check was conducted.  Scene Processing Lamberts clothing was recovered and transported back to the Barrack for further processing. GBMC Nurse Laura then administered a SAFE exam.   Suspect Sean Young    Victim David Lambert 10-31-1071 410-402-6000 3283 Huntsman Drive, Huntingtown MD 20678   On March 21st, 2023 at approximately 0200 hours I, Trooper Sigman of the Maryland State Police, was dispatched to GBMC Hospital for a report of a rape that had occurred at Spring Grove Hospital located at 55 Wade Avenue (Building White D).  I then arrived at the GBMC emergency room and made contact with Spring Grove Police Officer Mannie #712. Officer Mannie advised me that his department had been made aware of a sexual assault that occurred on March 19th, 2023. Mannie stated that per department policy they transported the victim, David Lambert (10-31-1971) to GBMC Hospital.  I then made contact with Lambert, an patient at Spring Grove Hospital. Lambert advised that on the morning of March 19th at approximately 0520 hours Nurse Paulette unlocked the shower in building White D to allow him to take his bi-weekly shower. Lambert stated that he then checked the door behind him and ensured that it was locked and that he was the only person in the shower.Lambert stated that upon completing his shower he began to dry off. While drying off he felt someone grab him from behind and insert their penis into his anus.Lambert stated that he then swung his elbow at the individual sexually assaulting him.Lambert stated that the suspect then began to run away while completely naked. Lambert believed the penetration to have lasted no more than 10-15 seconds and did not believe that the suspect ejaculated. Lambert stated that he recognized the suspect as Sean Young who resided in the room next to his.Lambert stated that prior to this incident Young would routinely threaten him calling him a racist and threatened physical harm.Lambert stated that he immediately reported this incident to nursing staff but was unable to speak with a Spring Grove police officer until the evening of March 20th.  At this time it is unknown why there was a significant delay in reporting. Spring Grove Police stated that they were looking into this matter.  Lamberts clothing was recovered and transported back to the Barrack for further processing. GBMC Nurse Laura then administered a SAFE exam. Laura RN advised that the kit would take several hours to process. Per Sgt. Twardowski another Trooper would return to GBMC to collect the kit.  Lamberts clothing was then transported back the Golden Ring Barrack and processed in accordance with agency policy.  I respectfully request this incident be forwarded to CED for follow up.  All above events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 02:56:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/28/2023 17:10:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Twardowski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sigman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7376</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>54</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 02:51:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:27</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372107</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>YOUNG</LastName>
               <FirstName>SEAN</FirstName>
               <DOB>03/19/1969 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/21/2023 02:51:24</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>Y520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>YOUNG</LastName>
               <FirstName>SEAN</FirstName>
               <DOB>03/19/1969 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>Y520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/21/2023 02:51:24</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>55</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Wade</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Catonsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21228</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4663</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.7214317</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.2643724</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 02:51:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>51</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 02:54:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:27</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372108</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>LAMBERT</LastName>
               <FirstName>DAVID</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/31/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.77941545E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>03/21/2023 02:54:01</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L516</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>LAMBERT</LastName>
               <FirstName>DAVID</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/31/1971 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.77941545E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>L516</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D130</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/21/2023 02:54:01</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3283</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Huntsman</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Huntingtown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20639</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.5451</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.574912</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 02:54:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 02:54:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 02:54:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/21/2023 12:04:35</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/21/2023 12:04:35</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/18/2023 12:20:03</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6930</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 12:04:35</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 03/21/2023 at approximately 1114 hours, I, TFC Waugh #6930 was dispatched to GBMC hospital located 6701 N Charles St, Towson Md, 21204 to retrieve a Sexual Assault Evidence Collection Kit. I took the kit into my possession at 1121 hours and transported it to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack. Upon arrival to the Maryland State Police barrack, I completed a MSP-67 for the collection kit and the manilla envelope per MSP policy. Both were placed in the Golden Ring temporary storage locker #2 at 1225 hours. All of the above events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6930</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/21/2023 12:29:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6930</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/21/2023 12:36:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Miranda</LastName>
            <FirstName>Neil</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2271</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Waugh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6930</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>2</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/10/2023 10:48:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/10/2023 10:48:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40O</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/18/2023 12:20:03</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6650</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 10:48:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #2 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Focus of this Narrative: To document all investigative efforts conducted during a sexual assault investigation.  Exhibits Attached    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Maryland Department of Health Police/Spring Grove Police Case Report, by Officer Robert Manning   margin-left:16px"&gt;Sexual Assault Forensic Examination Assessment Documentation, Authorization and Release of Information   Detailed Narrative On March 21, 2023, at approximately 0200 hours, Trooper Sigman, assigned to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack, responded to the Greater Baltimore Medical Center (GBMC) in Baltimore, MD for a reported past rape that occurred at Spring Grove Hospital located at 55 Wade Avenue, Catonsville, Maryland 21228. Trooper Sigman made contact with Spring Grove Police Officer Robert Manning who advised his department was made aware of a sexual assault that occurred on March 19, 2023. Manning advised the victim, later identified as David Lambert (white/male, DOB: 10/31/1971)- a patient at Spring Grove Hospital, was transported to GBMC for a Sexual Assault Forensic Examination (SAFE). Trooper Sigman obtained a statement from Lambert where he describes the sexual assault. Please see the Narrative portion of this report for additional details. Lambert identified the suspect as Sean Young (later verified as Shawn Kevin Young -black/male, DOB: 03/19/1969) who was also a patient at the hospital. The Sexual Assault Forensic Examination was conducted and transported to the Golden Ring Barrack for storage.  On March 27, 2023, Trooper First Class (TFC) Waldys Batista #6650, assigned to the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division, assumed the investigation and coordinated with Sergeant David Jones of the Spring Grove Police Department to obtain their case report and schedule a recorded interview with Lambert and Young. On or about March 28, 2023, TFC Batista responded to Spring Grove Hospital Police Department and reviewed the investigative report provided by Sergeant Jones and conducted follow interviews with Lambert and Young.  Spring Grove Hospital Police Report Case Number: SGPD2023-000064 Reporting Officer: Robert Manning Incident Type: Sex Offenses: Forcible Sodomy Incident/Report Disposition: CASE CLOSED/UNFOUNDED Incident Occurred Date  Time: 03/19/2023 at 0500 hours Incident Discovered/Called in: 03/20/2023 at 2300 hours Location: Patient Care Building- White D Building Report Synopsis/Overview: Patient Lambert reports that on March 19, 2023, at approximately 0500-0600 hours, while he was in the shower, patient Shawn Young entered the shower, grabbed his waist from behind, and forcibly penetrated Lamberts rectum with his penis  NARRATIVE TEXT: On March 20, 2023, this officer was called in to take patient David Lambert from White D unit to GBMC for an alleged rape allegation. The alleged rape supposedly happened in the shower between the time of 500am-600am on the morning of March 19, 2023  Statement from patient/victim David Lambert on March 21, 2023, at 130am at GBMC Hospital. I was taking a shower on Sunday morning between 500/600am. After I was done in the shower stall I was drying off in front of the bench, with my back to the door. While I was drying off, I heard the bathroom door unlock and someone walks in. I didnt see who it was because I was medicated with a double dose of Benadryl the night before. As I heard someone waling closer to me, I continued to dry myself off and put lotion all over my body for dry skin. Thats when I saw Sean Young (patient/suspect) get closer to me. At which time Sean walked up behind me from the rear and pushed me against the wall grabbed me around my hips and forced his penis into my ass. I then attempted to elbow him in the face with my right elbow but did not connect with the blow. After about 10-20 seconds I was able to push Sean away from me thats when he ran out the door naked. I then got dressed exited the shower room and told the charge nurse. The patient/victim did not know the name of the charge nurse but described her as being a black female with an accent. The charge nurse told me she will notify the doctor. On Monday, March 20, 2023, I was meeting with my treatment team and advised them about the rape and was informed by them that they will look into it. All day long I kept asking the nursing staff to see my therapist or social worker but no one answered me. At about 830/900pm Dr. Eben arrived at the unit and thats when I told her I was raped by Sean. I then went to the hospital.  Statement from patient/suspect Sean Young on March 22, 2023, at 145pm on the unit. The patient/suspect was given his Miranda rights on the above date and time. This officer then asked the patient/suspect if he knew the patient/victim (David Lambert). He replied Yes. The patient/suspect was then asked where he was on March 19, 2023 between the hours of 500/600am in the morning. Mr. Young replied I was in bed sleeping. I did not see or touch David anytime in the shower.  Statement from Dr. Lelia Ford on March 23, 2023, at 845am. I was advised by Mr. Lambert on Monday, March 20, 2023, during the patients team meeting. Dr. Ford is a psychiatrist in the White D unit. Mr. Lambert advised me that he and Sean Young got into an altercation earlier in the day on Saturday March 18, 2023. And on Sunday, March 19, 2023, Sean came into the shower and raped me. But Mr. Lambert keeps repeating that he wants to be transferred to another unit because hes scared for his life.  Statement from Charge Nurse Juliet Ogbguli on March 23, 2023, at 1100am inside White D nursing station. I was on duty Sunday, March 19, 2023, in the morning. I was not notified by Mr. Lambert about the alleged incident after it happened or any time during the day. Nor did Mr. Lambert request to speak with any doctors or social workers.  Officer Mannings Investigative Findings per Police Report- Investigation revealed that on March 20, 2023, at approximately 1100pm this officer was called in for an alleged rape. The patient/victim involved was David Lambert from the White D unit. Upon arrival in the unit, I was informed by staff that Dr. Eben ordered the patient (David Lambert) to be taken to GBMC for a rape examination. Dr. Eben was not on site upon my arrival. At this point the patient (Lambert) approached this officer and stated are you here to take me to the hospital because I was raped yesterday morning in the shower. I replied Yes. At 1252am (March 21) this officer along with Lambert and staff exited the unit on the way to GBMC. At approximately 125am, we arrived at GBMC emergency room. The patient/victim David Lambert was then registered and placed in a trauma room waiting for the SAFE kit test to be performed. This officer then questioned Lambert, see: Statement from patient/victim David Lambert located above for details. TFC Batista observed the second time officer Manning described Lamberts statement; the officer used attempt to force his penis into the rectum of the patient/victim. The officer then questions Sean Young (see Youngs statement above). The officer obtains a copy of the Head Check/Observation Round sheet, and it was confirmed that Young was sleeping/in his bed at the time of the alleged incident. TFC Batista learned that the patients are not locked in their rooms, so it is possible for patients to exit their rooms after the head check. Charge Nurse Juliet Ogbbuli stated during an interview that Lambert did not advise her of the alleged rape incident at any time contradicting what he told officer Manning and TFC Batista a record interview on March 28, 2023. Officer Manning stated on his report (SEE EXHIBIT) that on March 23, 2023 he received a copy of the SAFE report from GBMC. Manning described (the) report from GBMC which states Mr. Lambert did not get raped or assaulted in any way he claims. Manning requested the case be closed due to doctor and staffing reporting Lambert fabricated his statements about the incident and documentation proved the incident did not occur.  Summary of David Lamberts Interview, conducted by TFC Batista and Cpl. Sexton On the morning of March 28, 2023, TFC Batista and Cpl. Sexton made contact with David Lambert at Spring Grove Hospital in Building White Ward B. Lambert advised his legal name was changed from David Peter Mokshefski to David Lambert through a circuit court judge in Maryland. Lambert began to describe the alleged incident in the following order:     margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert stated that Sean Young, later verified as Shawn Kevin Young, began to verbally attack him with racist remarks days prior to the alleged rape.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert and Young would continue the verbal altercations until it escalated to physical altercations.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert stated he was never the aggressor during the altercations.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert accused a staff member, he identified as Ochegbuam Alachebe, unlocking the shower for Shawn Young to attack him.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert also described that Alachebe physically assaulted him with Young and protected Young. (TFC Batista spoke to Alachebe who denied the allegations and advised he was not in the area of the showers and never opened any shower doors.)   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert stated the staff member let other patients in the shower earlier as well while Lambert was using the shower. The other members were not named.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert stated the incident occurred at approximately 0519 hours on March 19, 2023.    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert stated he was heavily medicated from the night before (2 full hoses of Benadryl)   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert oiled his skin while in the shower to treat dry skin and thats when Shawn grabbed him and pushed him against a wall.    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert stated Shawn penetrated his rectum, but he believes the penetration was only partial. The penetration was described by Lambert as quick.    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert stated he was half asleep and not entirely alert. He throws an elbow while getting assaulted by Young but misses. Young runs out of the shower and flees the area.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert stated that Young did not ejaculate inside him.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert advised the shower room had low light and the door did not lock from the inside.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert stated he did not want to pursue charges again Young because Young is fucked up in the head.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lambert also recalls that after the sexual assault, Young apologized for his actions while they spoke through a fence.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;The apology occurred after Lambert approached Young and told him he was diagnosed with HIV.   margin-left:16px"&gt;Lambert stated he is not currently on any prescribed medication.  Doctor Michelle Cater Interview Investigators made contact with Dr. Michelle Carter who was on duty on March 28, 2023. She advised Lambert was not given a high dosage of Benadryl the night before the alleged incident. She stated that on March 20, 2023, Lambert advised no sexual contact occurred. Then, Dr. Carter stated Lambert disclosed sexual contact in the shower on March 21, 2023. Dr. Carter did not have any additional information to disclose.  Attempts to Locate Shawn Young Investigators were not able to locate Shawn Young to interview him because he was released from Spring Grove on March 23, 2023. Investigators made several attempts to locate Young, but all were negative. Investigators made contact with Youngs family members on or about April 3, 2023. Family members advised Young is in and out of mental health facilities and described him as in an out of reality and not competent to hold a conversation. Young was hospitalized at Spring Grove Hospital for over a year prior to his release on March 23. Investigators spoke to local mental health facilities regarding Young location, but they did not disclose any information due to HIPAA. Investigators learned, from Youngs family, that he is possibly schizophrenic has spent the majority of his adult life in mental institutions.  SAFE Kit The SAFE kit will be sent to the Maryland State Police Forensic Science Division for testing and the Forensic Science supervisor, Jason Befus, was made aware that Shawn Youngs DNA sample was not collected.  Case open pending prosecutorial review.  Primary Investigator: TFC Waldys Batista #6650 Maryland State Police, Criminal Enforcement Division Office: 2433 W. Pulaski Hwy, North East, MD 21901 410-996-7813 </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6650</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 10:00:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6650</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/11/2023 10:08:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sexton</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2896</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Batista</LastName>
            <FirstName>Waldys</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6650</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499526</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1102 SS</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>09</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>2</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 05:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1102 SS</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6650</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 10:19:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6650</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/11/2023 10:19:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>3</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/17/2023 09:21:43</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/17/2023 09:21:43</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>40O</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/18/2023 12:20:03</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP6650</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 09:21:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #3 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On April 12, 2023, TFC Batista completed and submitted the case file for this sexual assault investigation to the Baltimore County States Attorneys Office for review. Shortly thereafter, TFC Batista was contacted by John Magee, Chief of the Sex Offense Division, who advised he reviewed the case in its entirety. Mr. Magee advised he will decline all criminal charges against Mr. Shawn Young due to lack of probable cause to believe that the alleged crime occurred.  Case closed- Prosecution Declined</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6650</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 09:22:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6650</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 09:25:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hall</LastName>
            <FirstName>Bradley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5585</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>40O</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP9800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Batista</LastName>
            <FirstName>Waldys</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6650</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499526</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>11</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1102 SS</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>09</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>3</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/17/2023 09:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1102 SS</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6650</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/17/2023 09:26:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6650</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/17/2023 09:26:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>