<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-001712</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/14/2023 21:42:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/14/2023 21:42:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/14/2023 21:42:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/14/2023 21:42:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI Kennedy Workman</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/14/2023 22:07:55</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 22:39:19</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>COASTAL HWY/ 49TH ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>539556</AddressId>
      <City>MDC208</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/14/2023 22:07:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2023 23:24:35</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>539556</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Coastal</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.06951</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.37443</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>5000-5098 COASTAL HWY / 1-99 49TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 COASTAL HWY / 1-20 49TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4901-4991 COASTAL HWY / 100-199 49TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4800-4898 COASTAL HWY / 1-99 49TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/14/2023 22:07:52</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/14/2023 22:07:52</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/30/2023 06:47:55</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/14/2023 22:07:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:23:03</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP marked vehicle V-11 is equipped with a mobile recording device  Defendant: Kennedy Christian Workman Driver license #: MD W-625-465-115-278 Date of Birth: 4/9/1999 Date of Arrest: 1/14/2023 Time of Arrest: 2156 DUI #: 23-96-009 PBT Results: .12 Intoximeter Results: refused Subsequent Offender: NO CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING -Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On January 14, 2023, at approximately 2142 hours, Trooper First Class C. Shubert #7062 with the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack, was on-duty operative V-11 in the area of Coastal Highway and 52nd St, Ocean City, Worcester County, Maryland 21842. At that time I was traveling northbound Coastal highway in lane three when I observed in the left turn lane attempting to make a U-turn was a white Mazda SUV bearing Maryland registration (6EX1045) that failed to use their turn signal while making a U-turn. I then activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle on 49th St. Ocean City, Worcester County, Maryland.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I exited my patrol vehicle and made contact with the driver and passengers and advised them why they were being stopped. While speaking with the driver I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the drivers breath and person and bloodshot and glassy eyes. I asked the driver for her license and registration. While the driver was retrieving her license I asked where they were heading to and she advised Seacrets. I then asked the driver where she was coming from to which she advised Shotties. The driver handed me her license and I identified the driver as Kennedy Christian Workman (W/F, 4/9/99) through her Maryland license. I then asked Workman how many alcoholic beverages she consumed prior to driving to which she advised One beer at the bar. I then returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine MVA checks, once completing MVA checks, I returned to Workmans vehicle and asked her to step out and walk to the front of her vehicle to conduct the standardized field sobriety test and to continue my investigation to which she consented. While at the front of her vehicle I continued to smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. I asked Workman how many alcoholic beverages she consumed throughout the day to which she advised Two mimosas in the morning, and a beer at the bar. She later advised she consumed an Nanticoke nectar alcoholic beverage.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on 49th St where Workmans vehicle made a complete stop. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 33 degrees. Workman appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. My front emergency lights were deactivated during all tests.  I asked Workman the following questions: Glasses- NO Medication-NO Physical disabilities-NO  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (_6_/_6_ clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. A black and gray pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12-15 inches from Workmans eyes. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Her pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. She was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked if she understood the instructions and she stated Yes. 1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes   WALK AND TURN (_3_/_8_ clues observed) Prior to Workman performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. She was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. She was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat to her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. She was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. She was to keep her hands flat to her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, I explained and demonstrated for Workman to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her lead foot to turn completely around. I again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps was to be performed identically to the first series. Workman was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was complete, keep her hands down by her sides, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Workman if she understood the test and she stated Yes. Instructional Stage: Conducted as instructed Walking stage (1st Nine): 1). Missed heel to toe more than half an inch on steps 2-9 Walking stage (2nd Nine): 1). Missed heel to toe contact more than half an inch on steps 1-7 2). Took eight steps instead of nine as demonstrated Turn: 1). Picked lead foot up after turning  ONE LEG STAND (_2_/_4 clues observed) Prior to Workman performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. She was instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, Workman was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand-two), and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Workman if she understood the test, and she stated Yes. Workman attempted the test for approximately three seconds, and stated YES Right foot Seconds: 1-10 Completed as demonstrated Seconds: 11-20 1). Hopping in an attempt to maintain balance 2). Put foot down on second 18 Seconds: 21-30 Completed as demonstrated Additional field test: (1).I then asked Workman if she graduated high school and if she knew the English alphabet to which she advised Yes, I graduated college. I then asked if she could start at the letter H and go to the Letter T without singing the alphabet to which she advised Yes. Workman stated H-G-I-J. I then asked Workman if she could count backwards from 57 to 36 to which she stated Yes. Workman counted from 57 to 1 and stopped.  Workman had the opportunity to take a preliminary breath test. Workman consented to a preliminary breath test with the result of .12 BrAC. ARREST: Based on the following, I had reason to believe Workman was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: * Driving behavior *Admitting to consuming alcohol *My observed signs of impairment  At approximately 2156 hours, I placed Workman under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I later checked her mouth for any foreign objects and did not locate any. Workman was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. While I made contact with the other occupants in the vehicle I observed a backseat passenger located in the trunk portion of the vehicle laying down and not having a seat or seatbelt. While on-scene I played the English audio version of the DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Workman via the MVA official website with a paper copy in front of her to read. At the conclusion of the DR-15 form, I verbally repeated the possible suspensions and sanctions that can be imposed by the MVA per the DR-15 form. Workman refused the Intoximeter test and signed the same at approximately 2213 hours. Alcohol Concentration Test Result: refused  Workman was later released to a sober adult. Workman received pertinent copies of paperwork. Workman was charged with the following: 21-902 (A1i) Driving motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol 21-902 (B1i) Driving vehicle while impaired by alcohol 21-604 (C) Driver turning vehicle without giving appropriate signal as required 22-412.3 (C3) Passenger age 16 or more in rear seat of motor vehicle without seatbelt restraint  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland. Case closed.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 00:04:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/19/2023 00:04:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Drew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7062</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491094</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/14/2023 21:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/18/2023 23:25:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/18/2023 23:25:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491094</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/14/2023 21:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/18/2023 23:25:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/18/2023 23:25:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491094</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15613</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/14/2023 21:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/18/2023 23:25:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/18/2023 23:25:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491094</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>18603</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/14/2023 21:42:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/18/2023 23:25:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/18/2023 23:25:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>23</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/18/2023 23:28:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:09</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366522</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Workman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kennedy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christian</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/09/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/18/2023 23:27:47</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K530</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Workman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kennedy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christian</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/09/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K530</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/18/2023 23:27:47</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2809</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sagewood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Glenwood</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21738</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 00:03:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:43</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/19/2023 00:03:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:43</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/18/2023 23:25:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/18/2023 23:25:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148804</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/18/2023 23:28:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/18/2023 23:28:29</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/18/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MAZD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6EX1045</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>