<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008561</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/08/2023 15:21:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/08/2023 15:21:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/08/2023 14:46:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/08/2023 14:46:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The operator was stopped for a traffic violation and observed to be operating unde the influence of a controlled dangerous substance.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 15:21:19</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0104</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/16/2023 10:02:23</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>6854 LEONARDTOWN,BRYANTOWN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>686714</AddressId>
      <City>MDC341</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 15:21:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 20:24:19</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>686714</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Bryantown</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Bryantown</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20617</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.84219</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.555378</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/08/2023 15:21:16</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/08/2023 15:21:16</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/12/2023 16:51:16</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/08/2023 15:21:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:20:57</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was captured on an in-car camera, H-6. This incident was captured on my body-worn camera.  NARRATIVE:   DUI #: 23-048   Defendant: James Delaney Garner Jr   Maryland License: G656367139837   Subsequent Offender: Yes (11/19/1999)   Intoximeter Results: .00  CERTIFICATIONS AND TRAINING: - Certified RADAR/LIDAR Operator - Certified in the administration of Standardized Field Sobriety Tests - Completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driver Enforcement Training - Completed over 75 previous arrests for Impaired Driving  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)   On March 8, 2023, at approximately 1451 hours, I was on duty, in uniform, operating unmarked patrol vehicle H-6, stationary at the intersection of Leonardtown Road and Huckleberry Drive, Bryantown, Charles County, MD conducting stationary LIDAR enforcement. I observed a blue GMC Savanna that appeared to be operating above the posted speed limit of 55 MPH approaching my location. I activated my Pro Laser IV (Serial number #0000557) and obtained a speed reading of 71 MPH in a posted 55 MPH zone. I pulled out behind the GMC, and the operator began changing lanes, between cars attempting to create distance between his vehicle and my patrol vehicle. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on Leonardtown Road north of Bryantown Road, Bryantown, Maryland.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)   I approached the GMC from the drivers side of the vehicle and made contact with the male driver. I identified the driver as James Delaney Garner Jr (W/M DOB:10/31/1967) by his Maryland Drivers License. I advised Garner of the reason for the traffic stop. While speaking with Garner, I observed his pupils were extremely pinpoint, he appeared extremely nervous, continuously licked his lips, and could not complete a sentence without losing track. Garner appeared extremely wired/hyper, his face continuously twitched, and his voice trembled as he talked. When Garner provided his registration card I observed his registration expired on 5/2022, Garner stated he was not sure about the registration as it was his girlfriends vehicle, Elizabeth Joan McPherson. I observed the registration plates displayed 5/2024, Garner stated he wasnt sure of that either. I would have to talk to his girlfriend. I asked Garner who the female in the car was with him, and he state Oh, thats my fianc. I asked Garner, You have a girlfriend and a fianc? Garner stated oh no well thats Elizabeth (the registered owner of the vehicle). I asked Garner how many alcoholic beverages he consumed and where he was coming from. Garner advised he did not drink, he had just gotten out of rehab. I asked Garner if he was under the influence of any drugs or medication that may be altering his normal functions. Garner stated he was not on any medications or drugs. I provided the Maryland State Police La Plata Barrack with the operators information. I asked Garner to step out of the vehicle, to which he complied. I requested Garner to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and he agreed.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   The evaluation was performed on the shoulder of Leonardtown Road north of Bryantown Road. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. I asked Garner if he had any injuries or medical conditions that would prevent him from completing any of the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Garner stated No then stated, well maybe my back, I do flooring for a living. Test #1 Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus: 4 out of 6 clues. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus present. Garners eyes showed equal pupil size (Pinpoint) and equal tracking with no signs of resting nystagmus. 1.) Garners displayed a lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes. 2.) Garners displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  Test #2 Walk and Turn: 5 out of 8 clues. Instructional phase: 1.)  Unable to keep balance while listening to instructions 2.)  Started test before being told to do so 3.)  Missed heel to toe on steps 7 and 8 in the first series of steps 4.)  Preformed the turn improperly 5.)  Stepped off-line on step 8 of the second series of steps Test #3 One Leg Stand: 2 out 4 clues Garner started with his right foot raised 1.)  Garner raised his arms greater than six inches from his body for more than half of the test. 2.)  Garner put his foot down for balance on count 6 and switched to his left foot, counted to 9 then switched back to his right foot.  ARREST   Based on the following totality of circumstances, I had reason to believe Garner was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of a CDS:      * The drivers behavior prior to the stop and personal contact during the stop.      * Pupils pinpoint.      * Driver continuously swaying from left to right for balance while standing.      * Failure to operate a vehicle in a safe manner continuously changing lanes and traveling above the posted speed limit.      * 4/6 clues on HGN, 5/8 clues on WNT, and 2/4 clues on OLS while conducting SFST  Due to my observations, I concluded Garner was driving under the influence of a controlled dangerous substance and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At 1516 hours, I placed Garner under arrest for driving while under the influence of CDS. Garner was handcuffed with his hands behind his back. A preliminary search of Garner was conducted on the scene. Garner was transported to the La Plata Barrack for processing.   Garner was played his DR-15 Advice of Rights in English via the Maryland MVA audio file. After hearing the form read in its entirety, I asked Garner if he wished to submit to the test. At 1635 hours, Garner elected to submit to take an intoximeter test to measure his breath alcohol concentration. The test was conducted at 1637 hours with a result of .00 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. Garner consented to speak with a Drug Recognition Expert. Maryland State Police Headquarters sent out two requests for a Drug Recognition but was unsuccessful at obtaining one. Garner was provided all pertinent paperwork and charged with driving under the influence of a controlled dangerous substance and released to a sober adult.  Case closed by arrest. All events occurred in Charles County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6842</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 20:20:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6842</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 16:35:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gardner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Hunter</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7503</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shank</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7587</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Howard</LastName>
            <FirstName>Travis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6842</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Esh</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zachary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5635</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Howard</LastName>
            <FirstName>Travis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6842</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Howard</LastName>
            <FirstName>Travis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6842</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497960</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 15:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6842</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 20:23:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6842</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 20:26:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497960</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/08/2023 15:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6842</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 20:23:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6842</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 20:25:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>55</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6842</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 20:23:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:37</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>76654</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Garner Jr</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Delaney</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/31/1967 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/12/2015 03:56:26</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G656</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Garner Jr</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Delaney</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/31/1967 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>G656</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/12/2015 03:56:26</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>40614</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Waterview</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Mechanicsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20659</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.67437</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.490832</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>416</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5269</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/12/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6842</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 20:28:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6842</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 20:28:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6842</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 20:28:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6842</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 20:23:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6842</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 20:23:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150673</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6842</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 20:23:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6842</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 20:23:03</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1GTGG25CX81235178</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2008</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SAV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLU</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1FA5309</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2022</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>5</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>