<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011304</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/29/2023 23:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/29/2023 23:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/29/2023 23:37:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/29/2023 23:37:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic Stop//Silver Nissan Altima//DUI//DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 23:56:51</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4027</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/31/2023 10:39:57</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>81.8 MM I95 SB, ABERDEEN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>689032</AddressId>
      <City>MDC100</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 23:56:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 03:01:42</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>689032</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>81</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>8 Mm I95 Sb Aberdeen</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.2309148666667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.4999202833333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/29/2023 23:56:47</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/29/2023 23:56:47</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>62</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/30/2023 04:45:32</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/29/2023 23:56:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:02</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP un-marked patrol vehicle M-50 is equipped with a mobile recording device. This incident was recorded.   Defendant: Terence Coleman Date of Birth: 03/31/1981 MD DL: MD-10272211214 Date of Arrest: 03/29/2023 Time of Arrest: 2356 (11:56 PM)  DUI #: 23-035 (JFK HighwayBarrack)   TRAINING/CERTIFICATIONS:    I am trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).  I am trained and certified to conduct preliminary breath tests by the Maryland State Police.    VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1):    On March 29, 2023 at approximately 2337 hours, I, TrooperJohnson(#7359) of the Maryland State Police JFK Highway Barrack, was working routine patrol on southbound I-95 in the median of mile marker 83.0, Aberdeen, Harford County, Maryland. At that time,I observed a silver Nissan Altima being operated with an inoperative headlight, which appeared to be traveling at a high rate of speed in lane 3. I exited the median and enter the traffic lanes of southbound I-95 and began to maneuver over to lane 3. As I maneuvered into lane 3 of southbound I-95, I approached the Nissan Altima in the area of mile marker 82.2. After I positioned my unmarked patrol vehicle, M-50, behind the silver Nissan Altima, I observed the vehicle to be crossing over the dotted white line that divides lane 2 and lane 3 on two separate occasions. The silver Nissan Altima was crossing the dotted white line that divides the two traffic lanes by the width of the vehicles tire. I then activated my emergency equipment, and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. The silver Nissan Altima pulled over onto the right shoulder of southbound I-95, in the area of mile marker 81.8, Aberdeen, Harford County, Maryland. The silver Nissan Altima was bearing DE registration XQ372615.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):     I exited my vehicle wearing my full Maryland State Police issued Class-C uniform complete with brass breast badge. I approached the vehicle on the passenger side, where I made contact with the driver. When the driver rolled the down the passenger side window, I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle. I introduced myself to the driver and advised him the reason for the stop. After I advised the driver the reason for the stop, I asked him where he was coming from and the driver advised me that he was out getting something to eat and drink with his cousin who recently got out of the hospital. He was heading home from a bar in Edgewood, MD. While speaking tothe driver of the Silver Nissan Altima, I observed him to have slurred speech and hiseyes to bebloodshotand glossy. The driver failed to display a license through any state. The driver was identified by hisname/date of birth as Terence Coleman (DOB: 03/31/1981 1/M). I then returned to my patrol vehicle to perform standard METERS/NCIC checks on Coleman and his vehicle. Coleman did have a valid Maryland permit, but did not have it in his possession. Upon the arrival of Trooper Stinchecum (#6925), I approached the silver Nissan Altima and proceeded to ask Coleman if I could speak with himoutsideof hisvehicle. Coleman complied and proceeded to meet me at the front of hisvehicle. Once Coleman met me at the front of his vehicle, I explained to him why I was having him exit his vehicle and continued to ask if he would be comfortable letting me conduct Standard field Sobriety Testing on him. I continued to smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Colemans breath and person as I was speaking with him outside of his vehicle. I advised Coleman that due to the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from hisbreath, and my observations prior to the traffic stop being conducted,that I would like to conduct Standard Field Sobriety Testing to make sure that he is okay to continue driving. Coleman complied.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):   The tests were performed on the right shoulderof southbound I- 95 at mile marker81.8,Aberdeen, Harford County, Maryland. The surface was dry, level, and clear from any debris. Lighting conditions consisted of the headlight from Colemans vehicleand my handheld flashlight. Coleman was positioned in a manner to ensure that headlights from passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. Coleman appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any physical injuries. I asked himthe following questions:  Do you have any Physical Injuries: None.  Do you have any Medical Conditions: None.  Are you taking any Medications: None.  Are you wearing any glasses and/or Contacts: None.   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed):   The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Coleman had equal pupil size and equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. During this test, Coleman had to be advised on multiple occasions to keep his head straight and to follow the tip og my pen with his eyes only. Coleman was also advised not to try and predict where the pen was going to move to. After this test was completed, Coleman stated I havent been at the bar at all. I just stopped to get the food, had one drink and left.    Lack of Smooth Pursuit: Present in both eyes.  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation: Present in both eyes.  Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 Degrees: Present in both eyes.   Additionally    Vertical Gaze Nystagmus: Not present    WALK AND TURN (5/8 clues observed): The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Coleman stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed.  Instructional Stage:    Lost hisbalance and stepped completely offline on four (4) separate occasions, had to get back into instructional position at the start of the test. Coleman had to use the cars hood for balance, due to him falling backwards when trying ot get back into instructional position.   Walking Stage (1stNine):    Stepped completely offline on step 3 and 5  Missed heel to toe by more than 1/2 an inch on steps 4, 6 and 7  Incorrect number of steps - Coleman took 10 steps instead of the instructed 9. Coleman ended the first set of steps with his right foot, instead of left.  Uses arms for balance   Turn: Turn was performed properly by Coleman.  Walking Stage (2ndNine):    Stepped completely offline on steps 2 and 4  Incorrect number of steps- Coleman took 8 steps instead of the instructed 9.    ONE LEG STAND (4/4 clues observed):    The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Coleman stated he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed.     Puts foot down on three (3) occasions  Uses arms for balance for entirety of test  Sways backwards towards his vehicle. Coleman had to place his hands on the hood of the vehicle.  Hops on foot on three(3) occasions    ARREST:    Due to the clues observed during Standard Field Sobriety Testing, the drivers admission to consuming one alcoholic beverage and Coleman to have bloodshot/glassy eyes, I concluded Coleman was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 2356 hours, I placed Coleman under arrest for driving while Under the Influence of Alcohol. He was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and was transported to the Maryland State Police JFK Highway Barrack for processing.   Upon arrival at the barrack, I provided Coleman a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights and read it to him in English. Hestated that he understood the form at 0035 hours. Coleman agreed to take the intoximeter. After the completion of the intoximeter test, Coleman was explained his results. Coleman stated there was no way he was a 0.14 off of only two Heineken beers.   INTOXIMETER RESULT:0.14  Coleman was polite and cooperative during the encounter. Hewas given all copies of pertinent paperwork and picked up by a sober driver.  All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland. Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 03:26:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 04:35:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stinchecum</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gage</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6925</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phillips</LastName>
            <FirstName>Billy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4332</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cory</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7359</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500707</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/29/2023 23:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 03:02:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 03:02:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500707</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/29/2023 23:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 03:04:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 03:04:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500707</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/29/2023 23:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 03:04:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 03:04:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500707</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/29/2023 23:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 03:05:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 03:05:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500707</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/29/2023 23:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 03:06:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 03:06:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500707</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/29/2023 23:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 03:07:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 03:07:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500707</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/29/2023 23:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 03:07:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 03:07:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>41</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 03:24:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:29</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372967</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Coleman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Terence</FirstName>
               <DOB>03/31/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/30/2023 03:15:14</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C455</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T652</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Coleman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Terence</FirstName>
               <DOB>03/31/1981 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C455</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T652</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/30/2023 03:15:14</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>230</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mayberry</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Aberdeen</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21001</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.202556</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.480111</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>220</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Powdersby</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Joppatowne</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21085</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5418</Zip4>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>319</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Stevens</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Aberdeen</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21001</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.193415</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.522241</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 03:24:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 03:24:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7359</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/30/2023 03:02:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7359</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/30/2023 03:02:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>