<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008059</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/04/2023 02:51:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/04/2023 02:51:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/04/2023 02:11:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/04/2023 02:11:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI / ACCIDENT</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/04/2023 02:51:55</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/04/2023 21:47:06</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>686311</AddressId>
      <City>MDC452</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 00:16:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 00:20:46</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>686311</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Capital Beltway</StreetName>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.8588582</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.9449302</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/04/2023 02:51:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/04/2023 02:51:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/07/2023 05:10:50</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/04/2023 02:51:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI Report  Marked Car # Q-35 equipped with an in-car camera and body camera.  MARYLAND STATE POLICE  SUMMARY Defendant: Dianne Ali Floyd  Date of Birth: 07/21/1972  Date of Arrest: 03/04/2023 Time of Arrest: 0232 Soundex: MD10272525293  DUI #: 23-050 MSP Case # 23-MSP-008059 Prisoner search: Nothing illegal on person Vehicle search: No alcoholic beverages in vehicle. One registered firearm in vehicle. Seized for safe keeping.  OFFICER TRAINING/EXPERIENCE * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. * Certified Intoximeter operator by the Maryland State Toxicologist. *Have had numerous DUI/DWI arrests and convictions over the past 20 years.  REPEAT OFFENDER No  DRIVERS LICENSE STATUS STATE: Maryland Valid Class: C  WEATHER/ROAD CONDITION 50 Degrees Wet roadway.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On Saturday, March 4, 2023, at approximately 0212 hours, I, Trooper B. Peris ID #7511 was dispatched and responded to a single vehicle collision. The location of the crash was the on ramp to E/B 50 from S/B 495, Prince Georges County, Maryland.  At the above listed date and time, responded to the area, finding a gray Lexus RX 350, crashed into the concrete jersey wall on the left side of the roadway. The vehicle was identified as a gray 2008 Lexus RX350 displaying Virginia registration TWX9284.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the vehicle on the drivers side and contacted the driver/sole occupant, later identified as, Dianne Ali Floyd, sitting in the drivers seat of the vehicle. I asked if the driver was okay, and she said yes. I then asked the driver to provide me with her license and registration for the vehicle. The driver had slurred speech and stated that she didnt know where her purse was. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle and driver. The drivers movements appeared to be slow, and she appeared to be confused. I asked the driver if had had consumed any alcoholic beverages, and they said, one glass of wine. Based on my observations, I had reason to believe the driver was possibly under the influence of an alcoholic beverage. I then began assisting the driver look through the vehicle for her purse. While assisting her, a fanny pack was located on the driver side rear floor board. Upon looking inside the purse, a firearm was located in a holster. The firearm was found to be a Wather PK380 Serial Number WB164865. The firearm had a loaded magazine inserted in the gun with 8 rounds of ammunition. Contact was later made with the Maryland Gun Center and the firearm was listed to her. She was further found to have an HQL. The Gun Center did not suggest any charges for the driver. The firearm was seized at that time. No purse was located in the vehicle.  I asked the driver to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests to which she agreed. The driver was asked to exit and asked to step to the front of their vehicle for testing. Note that my emergency lights were not in view of the driver to hamper any of the following testing. The driver was placed in a position not to be affected by passing motorists lights. The surface was flat, and the weather was cloudy with wet roads, approximately 50 degrees. The driver had a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on her breath during questioning.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   Testing was performed on the south side of her vehicle. The road was free from any debris. The driver was asked and provided answers to the following questions:  Medical Conditions- None Injuries- None Medication: None Glass/Contacts: Contacts currently wearing Number and type of alcoholic beverages consumed: One glass of wine Last time the beverages were consumed: 4 PM Last time they ate: 10 PM  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS  (6/6 clues observed)  The driver displayed the following clues:  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes 4) Vertical Nystagmus - No  *The driver was observed to have difficulty standing still during the test as they swayed during the entire test*  WALK AND TURN (6/8 clues observed)  Prior to being asked to perform this test, I demonstrated the test. The driver was asked if she understood the test prior to beginning, and she said, yes. The test was performed on a flat surface, free of debris, and in a safe location.  INSTRUCTIONAL PHASE The driver could not remain in the Instructional Phase during instruction as required. The driver swayed and was off balance.  WALKING PHASE (1st Nine): During the first nine steps the driver missed heel to toe on every step and stepped off-line. On steps 7,8, and 9 the driver staggered to the side raising her arms for balance and stopped walking to regain balance.  TURN During the turn, the driver did not leave her lead food planted and lost her balance falling to the side.  WALKING PHASE (2nd Nine): During the nine return steps the driver missed heel-to-toe on every step and stepped off-line, using her arms for balance.  ONE LEG STAND: (3/4 clues observed)  Prior to being asked to perform this test, I demonstrated the test. The driver was asked if they understood the test prior to beginning, and she said, yes. The test was performed on a flat level surface, free of debris, and in a safe location.  INSTRUCTIONAL STAGE: The driver was unable to stand heels together and arms down to their sides while instructions were given. The driver swayed during the instruction.  BALANCE AND COUNT STAGE: The driver began the test by raising their right foot off the ground and dropped her foot on count 2 and then started again dropping her foot on count 3. The driver the raised her left foot off the ground and dropped it on ground on count 3. The driver swayed as she performed the test and raised her arms for balance.  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT) **REFUSED** The driver was asked to submit to a preliminary breath test and did not elect to take the test.  ARREST As a result of my observations, I had reason to believe the driver was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of an alcoholic beverage in excess of 0.08 BrAC. I felt that the driver was also unable to operate a vehicle safely.  At approximately 0232 hours, I placed the driver under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. The driver was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy. The driver was advised of her DR-15 Advice of Rights via MVA audio version. The driver was also provided a copy in English/Spanish for them to follow/read along. The driver fell asleep while I was locating the DR-15 audio version. The driver also had difficulty staying awake during the reading. At the conclusion of the reading, the driver elected not to submit to the breath test. No alcoholic beverages were located in the vehicle. The firearm was placed in MSP property for safe keeping.  The driver was transported to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack for processing. The vehicle was towed from the scene by Gregs towing.  INTOXIMETER RESULT:  ***REFUSED BREATH TEST***  The driver was given copies of all pertinent paperwork and was released from the Barrack to a sober driver.  EXHIBITS: DR-15 DR-15A ACRS REPORT Citations Property Records P-341138 Photographed firearm.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  CASE STATUS: Closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 01:21:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7511</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/07/2023 05:05:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathanael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7454</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stallings</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffrey</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7589</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Aaron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>PERIS</LastName>
            <FirstName>BRYAN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7511</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497458</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/04/2023 02:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 00:22:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7511</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 00:22:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>50</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 00:28:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:55</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370763</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Floyd</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dianne</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ali</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/21/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 00:27:26</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Floyd</LastName>
               <FirstName>Dianne</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ali</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/21/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>F430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 00:27:26</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11208</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>WESTPORT</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Bowie</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20720</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.811358</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.951098</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>406</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3920</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 00:47:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 00:47:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 00:47:11</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 00:22:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7511</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 00:22:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 01:19:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7511</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 01:19:54</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/04/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>13</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>P</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>MAGIZINE AND 8 ROUNDS OF AMMUNITION</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>ACC</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>250</PropertyValue>
         <Value>250</Value>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>244826</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>BLK</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>BLK</SecondaryColor>
         <Make>WATHER</Make>
         <Model>PK380</Model>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>