<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-022125</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/20/2023 16:36:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/20/2023 16:36:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/20/2023 16:08:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/20/2023 16:08:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was arrested for DUI following a traffic stop.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 16:36:17</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0452</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/03/2023 18:28:17</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I270 S/B @ DEMOCRACY BLVD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>698369</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 16:36:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/20/2023 20:18:44</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>698369</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I270 S/B @ Democracy</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/20/2023 16:36:15</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/20/2023 16:36:15</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/03/2023 18:28:18</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 16:36:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:20</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP marked vehicle N-11 is not equipped with an MVR device. The below incident was captured with a body worn camera.   Defendant:            Thomas Michael Sullivan Date of Birth:        11/18/1984 Date of Arrest:  06/20/2023 Times of Arrest:  1634 hours DUI #:   23-146 (Rockville Barrack)   CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING  * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Trained and certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement. * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)   On 06/20/2023 at approximately 1600 hours I, Tpr. John #7358 was in the area of I-270 southbound at Tuckerman Lane. I was in lane one (furthest left lane) traveling at 80 MPH, when I observed a Black Jeep Grand Cherokee (the Jeep had a tinted license plate cover) in lane 6 (the furthest right lane), traveling at a high rate of speed. The Jeep was passing all of the traffic on I-270 southbound, I observed the Jeep pass my patrol vehicle and continue towards Democracy Blvd (Southbound I-270). I used the HOV lane that leads to Democracy Blvd in order to catch up to the vehicle. Once I reentered the main travel lanes of I-270 at Democracy Blvd, I observed the same Jeep with the tinted license plate cover pass multiple vehicles, changing lanes from lane four (the furthest right lane) to lane three and two. I was unable to catch up and properly pace the vehicle due to the traffic conditions and for the safety of the other motorists. I activated my emergency lights and sirens in order to safely pass the other vehicles and catchup to the Jeep. The traffic congestion picked up at the I-270 southbound spur to I-495 westbound. I observed the Jeep in lane three (the furthest right lane); I maneuvered behind the Jeep and initiated the traffic stop. I stopped the vehicle for speed greater than reasonable, due to the fact the driver was traveling at a high rate of speed and passed my patrol vehicle traveling at 80 MPH. The driver of the jeep traveled approximately 100 yards past the I-495 over pass. I could see the registration plate once I was behind the Jeep; it was bearing a Virginia registration (UMDO7). The Jeep pulled over to the right shoulder, I exited my vehicle and conducted the traffic stop.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)   I made contact with the driver via the drivers side window. I informed the driver the reason for the stop and requested his drivers license and registration card. While speaking with the driver, I immediately smelled the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle and observed the drivers eyes to be glassy with a gazed look. The driver looked through his paperwork, first handing me his insurance card, he grabbed his registration card with another stack of paper. He placed his registration card down and passed me another insurance card. I explained to the driver that I already had his insurance card, and that I needed his registration card, which he just sat down on the seat. The driver did not speak to me during the initial interaction; he would splay his body and head away from me and only take quick glances to acknowledge what I was saying. When I requested for his license one more time, I asked him where he was coming from today. He mumbled incoherently and looked away from me; I asked him what was that? He did not respond to me. I asked him two more times where he was coming from today he did not respond to me. The driver passed me his Virginia Drivers License and the driver looked forward. The driver was identified as Thomas Michael Sullivan (DOB: 11/18/1984- VA Soundex: A60066180). Sullivan portrayed a nervous body language; he looked forward moved around in his seat and tried to not make eye contact with me. I asked him to confirm his address; he looked at me and shook his head up and down as well as saying yes. I asked him again where he was coming from today. Sullivan looked forward took a deep breath and said something incoherently. I told him I could not hear him. Sullivan looked at me and said Little Bennett. I asked what he was doing there, he stated golfing. I then asked him if he was drinking today (meaning an alcoholic beverage. Sullivan stated he had a couple of beers. I returned to my vehicle to conduct an MVA check on Sullivans information and to request for another unit to assist with field sobriety tests.  TFC Emerick #6888 arrived on scene to assist with the field sobriety tests. I approached Sullivans vehicle on the drivers side and asked him to step out. Sullivan asked why do I have to do that, and then began to mess with the radio and AC controls on the vehicle. TFC Emerick opened the door and I escorted Sullivan to the front of the vehicle. On the walk there, I observed Sullivan to have very slow and lethargic body movements. Once Sullivan was outside of the vehicle I observed the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his persons. I asked Sullivan if he wanted to perform field sobriety tests, he paused and stated, Sure.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of I-270 at the I-495 overpass. The surface was dry, with a slight raised angle, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 74 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of natural light. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Sullivan appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries.  I asked Sullivan the following questions: Alcoholic Beverages: Sullivan stated just two beers. Injuries  Injury from baseball, in his right ankle. Medication  Adderall and a medication for his heart. Medical Conditions  Heart condition.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)   The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Sullivans eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Sullivans pupils were equal in size. He was positioned in a manner to ensure the passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Sullivan if he understood the instructions and he stated yup. *During the HGN test, I observed Sullivan to consistently sway back and forth attempting to keep balance. When performing the Vertical gaze nystagmus Sullivan looked up with his head, he looked at me and slurred the word sorry.  Results: 1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes. 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes *Vertical Gaze Nystagmus: Present in both eyes*  WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)   Prior to Sullivan performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted (I instructed Sullivan to stand closer to the concrete traffic barrier where it was more level). Sullivan was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Sullivan was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Sullivan was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Sullivan was to keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Sullivan was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Sullivan was argumentative about the slope I explained that the most level spot was close to the concrete traffic barrier. He angled himself towards the roadway.   Instructional Stage: 1.) Could not keep balance, feet broke apart multiple times. Sullivan used the concrete traffic barrier to regain his balance during the instruction phase.  Walking Stage (1st Nine): 1.) Missed heel to tow, between the first and second step, and eighth and ninth step.   Walking Stage (2nd Nine): 1.) Missed heel to toe between steps three and four.  2.) Improper amount of steps: ten steps taken.  Turn: 1.) Improper  used both feet to turn in one fluid manor.   ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)  Prior to Sullivan performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Sullivan was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Sullivan if he understood the test and he stated yes..   Instructional Stage: 1.) Nothing to report.  Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10: 1.). Nothing to report.  Seconds 11-20: 1.) Placed foot down.  2.). Raised arms more than approximately six inches for balance.  3.) Swayed left to right   Seconds 21-30: 1.) Placed foot down.  Sullivan originally did not want to submit to a Preliminary Breath Test. Once I informed him that he was under arrest, he said hold on I will take the Preliminary Breath test. Sullivan submitted to the Preliminary Breath Test result: .17 BrAC.   ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Sullivan was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:   * Traveling at a high rate of speed passing multiple motorists.  * Slow and lethargic head and body movements. * Odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle. * Eyes glassy with a gazed look. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. * Constantly loosing balance during the tests. *Slurred speech on the duration of the stop. * Attempting to not speak to me and splaying his body and head away from me on the initial approach. * My observed signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests. * PBT result of .17 BrAC.   I arrested Sullivan for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 1634 hours and he was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Second District Montgomery County Police department for processing. During the ride to the Police station Sullivan became emotional, stating that he was going to lose his family and crying. Sullivan stated he had two beers again. While at the station Sullivan asked me how he could explain that, he was arrested for his speeding to his wife. I explained that Maryland does not do that, Virginia is the only state that can. Sullivan was extremely emotional at the station, crying and asking me how he can explain this to his wife. I played the DR-15 English audio version; Sullivan stopped the audio version multiple times to ask questions about the DR-15. I had to explain to Sullivan that since he had a Virginia License I would not be able to confiscate it. I explained to Sullivan that it was his right to choose to take the Intoximeter test, and that there was no Correct decision. I explained that the MVA would contact the DMV and pass along the information. As well as, to the court system. Sullivan submitted to the Intoximeter test conducted by Montgomery County Police Officer Raymond #3068. Sullivans Intoximeter test result was insufficient. Another Intoximeter test was conducted as a test to show that the Intoximeter instrument did work properly.   INTOXIMETER RESULT:  ***Refusal due to an insufficient result***   Sullivan was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and was released from my custody at the Second District Montgomery County Police Station.  All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7358</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/21/2023 17:57:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7358</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/26/2023 01:05:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Emerick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6888</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>John</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7358</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Butler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andre</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0452</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>John</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7358</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>John</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7358</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511561</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15647</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/20/2023 16:34:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7358</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 20:17:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7358</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/20/2023 20:20:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511561</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/20/2023 16:34:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7358</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 20:17:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7358</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/20/2023 20:21:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511561</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/20/2023 16:34:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7358</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 20:17:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7358</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/20/2023 20:22:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511561</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/20/2023 16:34:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7358</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 20:17:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7358</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/20/2023 20:22:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511561</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/20/2023 16:34:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7358</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 20:17:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7358</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/20/2023 20:20:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511561</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/20/2023 16:34:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7358</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 20:17:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7358</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/20/2023 20:23:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7358</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 20:17:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:20</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>380375</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sullivan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/18/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/20/2023 20:03:39</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S415</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sullivan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Michael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/18/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S415</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/20/2023 20:03:39</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1335</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mason Mill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Herndon</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20170</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5700</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.382438</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.999427</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7358</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 20:24:39</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7358</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 20:24:39</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7358</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 20:17:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7358</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/20/2023 20:17:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154358</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7358</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/20/2023 20:25:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7358</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/20/2023 20:25:40</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C4RJFAG8FC142607</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2015</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>GCH</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>UMDO7</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>