<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-026957</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/30/2023 01:55:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/30/2023 01:55:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/30/2023 01:19:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/30/2023 01:19:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI: 23-403 "R" SUMMONS</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 01:55:40</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/10/2023 17:55:03</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>702402</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 01:55:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/30/2023 01:55:41</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>702402</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Tidewater</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Middle River</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.3797</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.34445</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>2-24</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/30/2023 01:55:38</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/30/2023 01:55:38</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/10/2023 17:55:04</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/30/2023 01:55:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:29:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E.) TEAM* The following incident was captured on in-car camera Title: DUI 23-403 R SUMMONS ID: 23-MSP-026957 Defendant: Taivon Raphael Summons TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:    I am trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).  I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor as of July 2021.  I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of September 2020.  I am a distinguished graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute as of August 2021.  I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of 2020.  I have apprehended more than 300 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On July 30, 2023 at approximately 0115 hours, I (TFC. Speak #7219) was on patrol in marked Maryland State Police vehicle DUI-7 on Eastern Avenue in the area of Carroll Island Road, Baltimore County, Maryland. I observed a white Volvo XC60 failing to drive within a single lane, traveling above the posted speed limit, and passing another vehicle where prohibited. The Volvo was bearing Maryland registration 5FH7569.    Right over dotted white lane line with the passenger side tires.  Stopped at a steady red traffic signal. Upon the traffic signal turning solid green, the Volvo accelerated rapidly.  Drove on double solid yellow lane line with the driver side tires.  Drove on double solid yellow lane line with the driver side tires.  Swerving side to side within the lane.  Observed speed at 58-MPH in a 40-MPH speed zone.  Following another car at less than one car length.  The Volvo then passed the other vehicle on a double solid yellow lane line. The two vehicles were traveling up a hill and no way to see if another car was traveling in the other lane.  While passing, the Volvo was observed at 71-MPH in a 40-MPH speed zone.  The Volvo accelerated away from my patrol vehicle at what appeared to be above the posted 40 MPH speed limit. I activated the front antenna of my Golden Eagle II Radar, which is a directional radar, in the moving mode (same). I heard a Doppler tone indicative of the estimated speed and obtained a speeding reading of 71 MPH in a posted 40 MPH zone (my radar unit was checked before and after my shift and was functioning properly). Upon observing these traffic violations, I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on Eastern Avenue at Tidewater Lane.  The above referenced RADAR was calibrated before and after my shift and was functioning properly. I am a certified RADAR operator. This RADAR is specifically assigned to my vehicle.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Volvo on the driver side and made contact with the male operator of the vehicle, who was the sole occupant. Before I was able to say anything, the driver stated, whats the quota of the month? I got two cousins that are police officers. I identified myself and explained the reason for the stop. While identifying myself, the driver stated, I went around them because they are purposely driving slow. I then requested his drivers license and vehicle registration. The driver stated he did not have his drivers license and that he left it in the house. He was identified by his name and date of birth as Taivon Raphael Summons. His identity was confirmed by completing a METERS/NCIC/MVA browse. While speaking with Summons, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from inside the vehicle. I observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I then returned to my patrol vehicle to notify the barrack who I was out with. While in my patrol vehicle, Summons was yelling from his vehicle and beeping the vehicles horn.  I returned to the Volvo and requested Summons to exit his vehicle. He complied and exited his vehicle. While speaking to Summons outside of his vehicle, in an ambient environment, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. Summons now laid down on the sidewalk and stated, My uncle is a county officer and he will get your ass, Im not playing with yall. I instructed Summons to get up from the ground and he stated, Im not getting up, do what you gotta do. Summons stood up and continued arguing. During this, I repeatedly asked Summons if he wanted to submit to the standardized field sobriety tests. Summons continued to argue and raise his voice. Summons now removed his t-shirt and continued to argue with myself and TFC. Riba Tankari (#7058). Unprompted, Summons attempted to say his alphabet in reverse. Summons then stepped off the sidewalk to the solid white fog line and attempted to complete the walk and turn test, without receiving any instructions. Summons displayed several clues in his attempt at the walk and turn test. Summons continued arguing and refusing to cooperate with instructions. He was asked on several occasions if he wanted to perform the standardized field sobriety tests. All standardized field sobriety tests were refused.   ARREST: Due to the number of observations and the refusal to cooperate with instructions Summons was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at 0131 hours. He was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy. While sitting in the front passenger seat, Summons made voluntary statements regarding his alcohol consumption without being asked. Summons stated, Im gonna be real with you, I wasnt drinking a lot. I was drinking like four hours ago. Summons continued by stating he was at a family reunion on his fathers side. He then stated, I probably drunk two Coronas (beer), thats it. Summons was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack for further processing.  Upon arrival at the barrack, I provided Summons with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Summons was advised of his DR-15 Advice of Rights. At 0216 hours, Summons agreed to take a breath test.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Summons beginning at 0131 hours. A search revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. Summons was observed from that time until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by TFC. White of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Summons had a result of .12 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 0228 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: *****.12 grams of alcohol*****  Summons was given all copies of the pertinent paperwork and transported to his residence.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/08/2023 19:21:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7219</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/08/2023 20:36:30</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Speak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7219</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Speak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7219</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Speak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7219</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>516402</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/30/2023 01:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/08/2023 19:19:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7219</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/08/2023 19:20:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/08/2023 19:19:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7219</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/08/2023 19:21:14</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>384610</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Summons</LastName>
               <FirstName>Taivon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Raphael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/12/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/08/2023 16:25:07</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S552</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Summons</LastName>
               <FirstName>Taivon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Raphael</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/12/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S552</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/08/2023 16:25:07</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>14</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Benoni</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CIR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Middle River</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21220</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/08/2023 19:21:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/08/2023 19:21:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/08/2023 19:21:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/08/2023 19:19:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7219</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/08/2023 19:19:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155930</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/08/2023 19:19:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7219</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/08/2023 19:19:32</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2023</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>VOLV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>XC60</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5FH7569</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>