<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-029270</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/19/2023 01:37:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/19/2023 01:37:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/19/2023 01:37:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/19/2023 01:37:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/fleeing</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 02:33:13</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1773</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/28/2023 09:15:19</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>WILMINGTON LN/ 2ND ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>704285</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 02:33:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/21/2023 08:12:09</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>704285</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Wilmington</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.085741</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.333737</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>200-220 WILMINGTON LN / 100-105 2ND ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/19/2023 02:33:10</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/19/2023 02:33:10</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/23/2023 12:23:38</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 02:33:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:06:36</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>                                                        Maryland State Police-Berlin Barrack V MSP marked vehicle V-11 is equipped with a mobile recording device.   Defendant: Alexander Frank Bucknavage Drivers license #: No license Date of Arrest: 8/19/2023 Time of Arrest: 0234 hours DUI #: 23-96-250 PBT Results: Refusal Intoximeter Results: Refusal   CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING   -Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. -Trained ARIDE test through the Maryland State Police. -Completed certified SFST instructor class.   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)   On 08/19/2023 at approximately 0137 hours, I, Trooper First Class C. Shubert #7062 with the Maryland State Police was on-duty operating unmarked patrol vehicle V-11 in the area of US Route 50 and Philadelphia Avenue, Ocean City, Worcester County, Maryland. At that time, I was traveling eastbound on US Route 50 in lane one when I observed behind me a maroon Toyota Camry bearing Pennsylvania registration (KLT2512) that came close to striking the rear of my patrol vehicle. Once the light went green, I proceeded through the intersection, the vehicle them made a quick left turn onto Philadelphia Avenue going the wrong way into on-coming traffic. I activated the emergency equipment to my patrol vehicle and attempted to initiate a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle then made a right turn onto a one-way roadway passing on-coming traffic on 1st St. I deactivated my emergency equipment and the vehicle made a right turn. I then pulled around and faced near where the vehicle made a right turn. While I was facing near where the vehicle turned I observed on sidewalk was a B/M, with a white shirt and light blue jeans, also a 5/M or a 2/M that came from the direction the vehicle was. I then circled back around and located the vehicle in the parking garage where the Madison Beach hotel is located. After attempting to locate the driver, a male returned to where the vehicle was parked and advised his friend told him to check on the vehicle. While speaking with the male I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the males breath and person, slurred speech and bloodshot and glassy eyes. The male advised his name was Buck Tyler Skylar with a date of birth 3/30/97. After realizing the male gave me a false name he was arrested. I later identified the male as Alexander Frank Bucknavage through his Pennsylvania identification card.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)   While I was facing near where the vehicle turned I observed on the left side of my patrol vehicle camera footage on the sidewalk was a B/M, with a white shirt and light blue jeans, also a 2/M wearing all black that came from the direction the vehicle was. I then circled back around and located the vehicle in the parking garage where the Madison Beach hotel is located. After attempting to locate the driver, a male returned to where the vehicle was parked and advised his friend told him to check on the vehicle. The male advised his name was Buck Tyler Skylar with a date of birth 3/30/97. After realizing the male gave me a false name he was arrested. I later identified the male as Alexander Frank Bucknavage through his Pennsylvania identification card. During the investigation Bucknavage eventually admitted to being the driver and asked If I was the officer that was following behind him and I advised; Yes.  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Bucknavage was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:   * Traveling the wrong-way into on-coming traffic two times. * Fleeing in an attempt to get away. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.   At approximately 0223 hours, I placed Bucknavage under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I placed Bucknavage in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. While still on-scene, I played the English audio version of the DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Bucknavage via the Motor Vehicle Administration (MVA) official website. At the conclusion of the audio version of the DR-15 form, I verbally repeated and reviewed the possible suspensions and sanctions that can be imposed by the MVA to Bucknavage driving privilege. Bucknavage contacted his attorney and his attorney advised him to refuse the Intoximeter test. Bucknavage refused to the Intoximeter test and signed the same at approximately 0259 hours.   TRANSPORT   Bucknavage was subsequently transported to Princess Royal. During transport, the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Bucknavage continued to be strong.    Bucknavage was released to an adult at approximately 0328 hours.    CHARGES   Bucknavage was charged with the following:  1. Driving vehicle while under the influence of alcohol (6370UR8) 2. Driving vehicle while impaired by alcohol (6360UR8) 3. Failure of individual driving on highway to display license to uniformed police on demand (62T0UR8) 4. Driving motor vehicle on highway without required license and authorization (62V0UR8) 5. Attempt by driver to elude uniformed police by means other than fail to stop and fleeing on foot (62L0UR8) 6. Negligent driving vehicle in careless and imprudent manner endangering property, life and person (62S0UR8) 7. Reckless driving vehicle in wanton and willful disregard for safety of person and property (62R0UR8) 8. Driver failure to stop at steady circular signal (62N0UR8) 9. Driving wrong-way one-way street (62M0UR8) 10. Failure to drive vehicle on right half of roadway when required (62P0UR8) 11. Person driving motor vehicle on highway or public use property on suspended out-of-state license (62W0UR8) 12. Driver changing lanes when unsafe (62Q0UR8)   Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/21/2023 11:09:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/21/2023 11:11:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Seth</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6944</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Messick</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7451</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jonischek</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4794</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shubert</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7062</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518718</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 01:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/21/2023 08:12:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/21/2023 08:12:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/21/2023 08:14:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 13:15:33</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>385680</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bucknavage</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alexander</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Frank</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/20/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/21/2023 08:14:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B251</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A425</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bucknavage</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alexander</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Frank</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/20/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B251</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A425</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/21/2023 08:14:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2344</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Prairie Rose</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>State College</City>
               <StateCode>PA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>16801</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2497</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-77.895474</Longitude>
               <Latitude>40.76659</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/22/2023 13:15:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/22/2023 13:15:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/21/2023 08:12:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/21/2023 08:12:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156329</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7062</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/21/2023 08:15:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7062</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/21/2023 08:15:47</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CAM</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>MAR</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>KLT2512</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>