<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-033867</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/26/2023 13:04:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/26/2023 13:04:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/26/2023 12:20:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/26/2023 12:20:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>FIRST DEGREE ASSAULT - RECKLESS ENDANGERMENT - FIREARM DISCHARGE</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/26/2023 13:04:35</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/05/2023 10:36:27</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>AST</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>FIREARM</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>RKE</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>EPRO</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>708108</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/26/2023 13:04:37</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 08:25:04</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>708108</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2527</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Old House Point</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Fishing Creek</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21634</Zip5>
         <Zip4>1513</Zip4>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.222375</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.320693</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/26/2023 13:04:32</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/26/2023 13:04:32</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/04/2023 21:31:00</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/26/2023 13:04:35</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:54</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>CASE NUMBER: 23-MSP-033867 INVESTIGATING TROOPER: Trooper First Class M. Mowbray #7119 NATURE OF CALL: First Degree Assault, Firearm Violation, Reckless Endangerment SCENE PROCESSING: Scene processing was conducted with the following results;   Four (4) photographs of scene/evidence  uploaded to RMS and VeriPic   One (1) photograph of the firearm used  taken by Deputy Mills (DSO)  One (1) copy of MSP Gun Center Report  One (1) copy of Criminal Summons on Charging Document  One (1) copy of the Extreme Risk Protective Order   margin-left:8px"&gt;One (1) copy of the Endorsement and Order for Emergency Evaluation  INCIDENT FOOTAGE: LABELED 23-MSP-033867 ON AXON EVIDENCE  INCIDENT CAPTURED BY BODY WORN CAMERA (BWC) TFC Mowbray #7119 Body Worn Camera (09/26/2023  Initial Report): partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=c73d31f714164c6baf3e9ff4af86c3f2partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 TFC Mowbray #7119 Body Worn Camera (09/28/2023  Criminal Summons/ERPO Service): partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=a88bc0b6ca4d4eaab800b0917a91796bpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  INCIDENT CAPTURED BY MOBILE VIDEO RECORDER (MVR) I-12 Mobile Video Recorder  Inward Facing (09/28/2023  Criminal Summons/ERPO Service_: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=40c8f426f66f4f0dbe4385aa3241b51epartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  NARRATIVE: On September 26, 2023, at approximately 1215 hours I, Trooper First Class M. Mowbray #7119 of the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack, was operating my unmarked Maryland State Police patrol vehicle I-12, parked stationary at the intersection of Creighton Road and Hoopers Island Road, Fishing Creek, Dorchester County, Maryland. While parked at the intersection I was approached by Larry Ritchie Powley (DOB: 03/11/1953) [hereinafter identified as Powley]. Powley began to inform me that his cousin; later identified as Edward Scott Poland (DOB: 07/17/1965) [hereinafter identified as Poland], was a drug user and that he was concerned about his welfare. Powley further explained that on September 25, 2023 he confronted Poland about his drug use and demanded that he urinate in a cup to collect a sample for a drug test. Powley stated that it was his intention to take Poland to a drug treatment facility to enroll him into rehabilitation. Powley explained that Poland refused to do so, at which point he slapped him. Powley also advised that at one point he used his firearm to fire rounds into the ground to get his point across that he was serious.   As Powley was speaking with me, I was dispatched to 2550 Old House Point Road, Fishing Creek, Maryland to assist the Dorchester County Sheriffs Office with a reported domestic disturbance. I asked Powley if he was familiar with that address and advised that what he was telling me was in relation to the call that I had been dispatched to. I then asked Powley to follow me to the address so that I could continue speaking to all parties there. After arriving at the aforementioned address, I continued to speak with Powley. Powley advised me that on September 25, 2023 he traveled to Polands residence; located at 2527 Old House Point Road, Fishing Creek, Maryland, and confronted him in regards to him owing taxes on the residence. Powley explained that he had been paying the taxes on the property due to the property being within his family for some time. Powley stated that he spoke with Poland and demanded that he urinate in a cup to which Poland denied. Powley stated that once Poland declined, he struck him in the face with an open hand. Powley estimated that he struck Poland three (3) times. Powley explained that at that time he waited for Poland to urinate in the cup for approximately thirty (30) minutes, however, he did not. Powley then stated that after Poland refused to urinate in the cup, he retrieved his .38 Special revolver and fired one (1) round near Polands feet. Powley further explained that he fired two (2) additional rounds from the firearm in the same area near Poland. Powley stated that shortly thereafter, Poland got into the truck with him and traveled to the University of Maryland Shore Medical Center at Easton Memorial where he attempted to have Poland evaluated due to his substance abuse history.   I then made contact with the complainant; identified as Marcus Layafette Flowers Jr. (DOB: 10/29/1956) [hereinafter identified as Flowers]. Flowers advised that he picked up Poland for work and observed bruising to the left side of his face. Flowers stated that Poland described an assault that took place with he and Powley and explained that he was driven to Easton to go to the hospital. Flowers advised that Powley arrived at his residence and began berating them. Flowers advised that at that time, he contacted law enforcement to make a response to remove Powley from his property.   I then made contact with Poland, who was inside of Flowers residence. Poland advised that on September 25, 2023, around 1500 hours, Powley arrived at his residence and began confronting him demanding that he urinate in a cup. Poland stated that he declined to do so at which time, Powley began to strike him in his face several times. Poland further explained that Powley again demanded that he urinate in the cup. Poland stated that he could not urinate in the cup and attempted to explain that to Powley. Poland advised that Powley became upset and pulled a silver six-shooter from his waistband in the small of his back and fired five (5) rounds towards his feet. I then transported Poland to 2527 Old House Point Road and surveyed the area in which the alleged shooting took place. Poland pointed out an area of grass near his porch where I observed three (3) furrows in the grass which appeared to be where bullets had entered the grass. Poland estimated that he was standing around six (6) to eight (8) feet away from Powley when he fired the rounds into the ground. Poland noted that prior to Powley firing another round, Powleys brother; identified as Thomas Lawrence Powley (DOB: 02/21/1950) [hereinafter identified as Thomas], arrived on scene and attempted to de-escalate Powley and witnessed him fire another round into the ground.  I observed Poland to have bruising to the left side of his face near his eye and temple area. Poland reported that the bruising was from the alleged assault.   Poland expressed that he did not wish to have Powley charged with any crimes related to the assault that were felonies, however, wished for Powley to not harass or contact him.  On September 27, 2023, at approximately 1407 hours I made contact with Thomas Powley via telephone. Thomas stated that on September 25, 2023, he arrived at 2527 Old House Point Road, Fishing Creek, Maryland and observed Poland and Powley in the front yard. Thomas stated that he observed Powley fire one (1) round into the ground near his own feet while Poland was standing several feet away from him. Thomas advised that he believed that Powley had only good intentions and wanted Poland to receive help with his substance abuse issues.  On September 27, 2023, the Maryland State Police Criminal Enforcement Division  Firearms Enforcement Gun Center conducted a check of Larry Ritchie Powley. During the check it was learned that Powley did not have any prohibiting factors which would disqualify him from possessing a firearm. Powley was also checked through MAFSS and was found to have no regulated firearms listed to him. That check did not include a check for non-regulated firearms (i.e. shotguns and rifles).  I provided Poland with the Maryland State Police case number as well as a Maryland Crime Victim and Witnesses pamphlet.  On September 27, 2023, Poland was granted a temporary protective order against Powley by the State of Maryland District Court Commissioners Office. (District Court Case #: D-021-FM-23-824339)  On September 28, 2023, Powley was charged with the following offenses related to this incident by a State of Maryland District Court Commissioner (District Court Case #: D-021-CR-23-000653); CR 3-202: ASSAULT-FIRST DEGREE CR 4-204 (B): FIREARM USE/FELONY/VIOLENT CRIME CR 3-203: ASSAULT-SECOND DEGREE CR 3-204(A)(1): RECKLESS ENDANGERMENT CR 4-203: WEAR, CARRY AND TRANSPORT HANDGUN UPON THEIR PERSON CR, 4-203(A)(1)(V): LOADED HANDGUN ON PERSON  On September 28, 2023, the Honorable Judge Melvin Jews granted a Temporary Extreme Risk Protective Order against Powley. The Honorable Judge Jews also issued an Endorsement and Order for Emergency Evaluation for Powley as well. (District Court Case #: D-021-FM-23-824405)   On September 28, 2023, at approximately 1330 hours, myself and Deputy D. Mills #0279 of the Dorchester County Sheriffs Office made contact with Powley at his residence; located at 2633 Hoopers Island Road, Fishing Creek, Maryland. While on scene Deputy Mills seized four (4) firearms from Powley, including a .38 revolver (Serial #: 74754) that was used in the aforementioned events. At 1335 hours I served Powley with the Criminal Summons on Charging Document for the case and placed him into my custody in regards to the court ordered emergency evaluation. I transported Powley to the University of Maryland Shore Medical Center at Cambridge and released him into their custody at 1456 hours. (MSP Incident #: 2023-00389849)  While transporting Powley to the hospital, he was remorseful for his actions. Powley provided another account of the event that occurred on September 25, 2023. Powley explained that he traveled to 2527 Old House Point Road to speak to Poland in regards to his substance abuse issues and an issue regarding owed taxes on that property. Powley explained that he asked Poland to urinate in a cup, so he could collect a sample for a test for illegal substances. Powley explained that Poland informed him that he didnt have to pee at which time Powley asked him to drink water. Powley further explained that he and Poland spoke for some time until he requested that he urinate in the cup. Powley stated that Poland became irate and began calling him a son of a bitch, which upset Powley due to the derogatory statements made by Poland. Powley stated that he told Poland to not speak of his mother in that way, which Poland responded to by again using the derogatory statement. Powley stated that he then smacked Poland in the face with an open hand and noted that Poland did strike him as well. Powley stated that Poland continued to use profanity and refused to urinate in the cup. Powley stated that he used his .38 revolver to fire rounds into the ground towards his own feet. Powley stated that Poland then got into the truck with him, and he transported him to the Easton Hospital. Powley noted that during the ride to Easton, Poland admitted to him that he was using crystal meth.  Powley was polite and cooperative during each encounter.   CONCLUSION: I respectfully request the case be closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Dorchester County.     </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 08:00:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 08:22:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Del Vecchio</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mowbray</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7119</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523323</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1420</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/26/2023 12:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1420</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 09:43:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 08:27:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523323</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1425</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/26/2023 12:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1425</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 09:43:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 08:27:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523323</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 5212</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/26/2023 12:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 5212</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 09:43:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 08:27:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523323</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1455</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/26/2023 12:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1455</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 09:43:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 08:27:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523323</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 5299</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/26/2023 12:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 5299</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 09:43:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 08:27:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523323</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1415 4E</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>20</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/26/2023 12:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1415 4e</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 08:27:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 08:27:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>58</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 07:35:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 08:28:54</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388860</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Poland</LastName>
               <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Scott</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/17/1965 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/27/2023 07:34:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P453</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E363</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Poland</LastName>
               <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Scott</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/17/1965 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P453</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E363</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/27/2023 07:34:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2527</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Old House Point</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Fishing Creek</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21634</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1513</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.222375</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.320693</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 08:28:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 08:28:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>70</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 07:43:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 08:28:29</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>224061</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Powley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Larry</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ritchie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/11/1953 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2019 13:39:08</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Powley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Larry</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ritchie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/11/1953 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/11/2019 13:39:08</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1219</StreetNumber>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Fishing Creek</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21634</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1519</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.224615</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.324668</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2633</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hoopers Island</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Fishing Creek</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21634</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.229512</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.330998</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2774</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Hoopers Island</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Church Creek</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21622</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.231902</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.339512</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>521</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3671</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 08:28:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 08:28:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 08:28:29</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>66</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 07:48:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 08:25:04</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388861</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Flowers</LastName>
               <FirstName>Marcus</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Layafette</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/29/1956 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>09/27/2023 07:48:39</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>F462</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M622</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Flowers</LastName>
               <FirstName>Marcus</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Layafette</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/29/1956 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>F462</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M622</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/27/2023 07:48:39</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2550</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Old House Point</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Fishing Creek</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21634</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1512</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.226099</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.321919</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>521</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5118</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>CP</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 07:48:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 07:48:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>73</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/27/2023 14:08:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 08:25:04</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388897</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Powley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lawrence</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/21/1950 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/27/2023 14:08:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Powley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Thomas</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lawrence</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/21/1950 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/27/2023 14:08:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3328</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Golden Hill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Church Creek</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21622</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1321</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.184578</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.383385</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>521</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5136</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/27/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>T</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 09:45:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 09:45:35</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 09:43:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/28/2023 09:43:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentProperty>
         <CreatorId>MSP7119</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/29/2023 07:29:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7119</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 07:29:56</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>6</StatusCode>
         <DocumentTypeCode>G</DocumentTypeCode>
         <Description>Firearm used in crime, seized by the Dorchester County Sheriff's Office.</Description>
         <PropertyTypeCode>MSPPR</PropertyTypeCode>
         <PropertyValue>0</PropertyValue>
         <Value>0</Value>
         <SerialNumber>74754</SerialNumber>
         <Evidence>N</Evidence>
         <EvidenceFlag>N</EvidenceFlag>
         <Property_ID>254695</Property_ID>
         <PrimaryColor>SIL</PrimaryColor>
         <SecondaryColor>BRO</SecondaryColor>
         <Quantity>1</Quantity>
      </IncidentProperty>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>