<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-018572</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>64</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/25/2023 02:04:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/25/2023 02:04:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/25/2023 01:43:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/25/2023 01:43:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 02:04:56</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3390</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 13:42:49</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>10304 DOWNSVILLE,HAGERSTOWN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>695172</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 02:04:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 03:31:22</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>695172</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>10304</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Downsville Hagerstown</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.7669502333333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.5973605333333</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/25/2023 02:04:54</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/25/2023 02:04:54</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>64</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/28/2023 23:44:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 02:04:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:54:46</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> Incident was captured on BWC O-34 is not equipped with MVR   Defendant: Vu, Long Hoang Nguyen Date of Birth: 11/07/1988 Date of Arrest: 05/25/2023 Time of Arrest: 0203 Hours MD License #: V-000-542-313-856 DUI #: 23-056  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES  Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.). I am trained and certified to conduct preliminary breathalyzer tests by the Maryland State Police Attended the National Highway Safety Administration DUI Convention in Ocean City, MD  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On 05/25/2023 at approximately at 0143 hours, I, Trooper First Class Capezuto #6694 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police Hagerstown Barrack, was operating marked Maryland State Police Vehicle O-34. I was traveling northbound Downsville Pike S/O Sterling Road. Downsville Pike has one lane traveling N/B and one lane traveling S/B which are divided by two solid yellow lines in this location. At this time, I observed a white Acura traveling southbound in the northbound lane headed in my direction. I then moved to my right to avoid a head on collision with the Acura. The Acura then crossed over the solid yellow lines and re-entered the correct side of the roadway. The Acura continued southbound. I safely made a U-turn and got behind the Acura TLX. The Acura was bearing MD registration 4EL6617.  At this time, I activated my emergency equipment to initiate a traffic stop. The Acura came to a stop on the right shoulder of Southbound Downsville Pike between Sterling Road and Progress Way.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the vehicle on the passenger side and made contact with the male operator and sole occupant of the vehicle. I informed the operator the reason for the stop. The driver then began to explain that he lived nearby and was trying to find his way home. The driver also showed me his GPS on his phone. I then requested his drivers license and registration. While the driver was looking for his license I asked him where he was coming from. The driver did not respond to me. The driver eventually provided his Maryland license. The operator was identified as Long Hoang Nguyen VU (A/M 11/07/1988). I again asked Vu where he was coming from, Vu responded but I could not understand his response. Vu then handed me his insurance card/bill instead of the registration card. I again asked Vu for the registration card. While speaking with Vu, I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from within the vehicle. I also observed Vu to have glassy bloodshot eyes, slurred speech and slow lethargic movements. I then asked Vu how much alcohol he has had, Vu responded 4-5 beers. I then asked Vu if thats the reason he was driving on the wrong side of the road. Vu responded Its dark.  A check through MVA revealed that Vus was valid.  I requested that Vu exit the vehicle. Vu initially exited the Acura with no shoes on. Vu then decided to put his sneakers on. While putting his sneakers on, Vu asked me if I was Taking him in. As I communicated with Vu outside of the vehicle, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and/or person. I asked Vu how long ago he consumed those beers, Vu hesitated and responded Pretty soon. I asked for clarification on how long ago, Vu then explained it was dark out. Vu then began to explain he was lost from his path. I then asked Vu what kind of beers he had, Vu stated Budweiser. I then asked if they were cans or bottles and Vu advised bottles. At that time, I asked Vu to perform standardized field sobriety tests, to determine if he was safe to drive and he agreed.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of southbound Downsville Pike between Sterling Road and Progress Way. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. Vu appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. Prior to beginning the test, I deactivated my vehicles forward facing emergency lights. I asked Vu the following questions.  Glasses/Contacts-None Injuries/Illnesses-None Medications-None I then asked Vu if there was anything else I should be aware of, Vu replied No sir.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus. It was held approximately 12-15 inches from Vus eyes, slightly above his eye level. Vu was instructed to look straight ahead, keep his head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes.   Vus pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was not observed  Vu had to be instructed numerous times to not move his head and to continue following the stimulus. Vu stated it was windy out multiple times throughout the test. The wind was minimal/light breeze.   WALK AND TURN (6/8 clues observed) The test was explained and demonstrated. Vu instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Vu was then instructed to place his hands at his sides and remain in that position until told to begin. Vu had to be told multiple times to touch heel to toe.  Vu was then advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step, count each step out loud and to keep his hands down by his side. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot planted, and to take a series of short choppy steps around his lead foot. After the turn, Vu was instructed to complete the second series of nine (9) steps in the same heel to toe fashion. Vu was also instructed to not stop until the test is complete. I then repeated the instructions to Vu.   Instructional Stage:    margin-left:8px"&gt;Cannot keep balance. (Feet became side by side while I was explaining the test)   Walking Stage (1st Nine)    Raised arms (Approximately shoulder height after initial step. Continued to raise throughout the test)  Missed heel to toe (Stepped on his foot on step 1 then lost his balance and stepped off to the left)  Stepped off line (Step 8)   margin-left:8px"&gt;Stopped while walking (After step 8, Vu stopped and looked at me for further direction. Vu stopped for approximately 5 seconds)  Turn: Completed incorrectly (Vu did not take short choppy steps. Vu took one large step to spin around his lead foot.)  Walking Stage (2nd Nine)    Stepped off line (Step 1, after initial part of step he stepped off to the right to catch his balance. Step 4,5,9)  Missed heel to toe (Step 5 after Vu stepped off line on first part of step 5.)   margin-left:8px"&gt;Raised arms (Around elbow height throughout the test)  Step 5 Vu lost his balance while stepping with his right foot. Vus right foot then landed off line and nearly parallel with his planted foot. Vu then completed the rest of the step and missed heel to toe.   ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed) The test was explained and demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch the raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two, etc). I asked Vu if he had any questions, Vu replied, No sir.  Instructional Stage:  Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10:    Put foot on ground    margin-left:8px"&gt;Used arms for balance (Arms around elbow height throughout)  Vu failed to straighten his lifted leg. Vu had a significant bend in his knee.  Seconds 11-20:    Put foot on ground    margin-left:8px"&gt;Used arms for balance (Arms around elbow height throughout)  Seconds 21-30:     margin-left:8px"&gt;Kept foot on ground from previous set.   At approximately the 12 second mark, Vu put his foot on the ground and kept it there. I instructed Vu to keep going. Vu did not pick his foot back up and stated he forgot what I said. Vu kept his foot on the ground for the remainder of the test.  While on scene, Vu was offered a preliminary breath test to which he did consent.  ARREST Based on the following totality of circumstances, I had reason to believe Vu was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:    Driving on the wrong side of the road.   Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle/breath/person.  Glassy bloodshot eyes.  Slow lethargic movements.  Slurred speech  Clues during Standardized Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (6/6), WAT (6/8), OLS (2/4).  Admitting to 4-5 beers  Getting lost while driving near his residence.   Forgetting instructions   Due to the number of observations, I concluded Vu was driving under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0203 hours, I placed Vu under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack, and searched his person for weapons and contraband, both with negative results. Vu was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and was transported the Hagerstown Barrack per department policy. Vu was read his DR-15 Advice of Rights in English via the Maryland Motor Vehicle Administration website. Vu was also given a paper copy to read along with. At approximately 0230 hours Vu agreed to take an alcohol concentration test.  20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Vu beginning on scene. Vu was observed from the time of arrest until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. A second check of Vuwas completed at the Hagerstown Barrack. Again, nothing was located in Vus mouth. The test was conducted bySgt. Ward #3285 of the Maryland State Policeon a certified instrument. Vu was given 6 attempts to provide a sufficient breath sample. Vu failed to do so.  INTOXIMETER RESULT Insufficient sample  While processing, Vu again advised he had 4-5 Budweisers. I processed Vu and drove him to his residence. Vu was released to a sober adult.   While driving I advised Vu that he had too much to drink, I then stated I believed he had more than 4-5 beers. Vu then advised me he had about 10 beers.  The defendant was issued copies of the following documents: -Citations -DR-15 Advice of Rights. -DR-15a Order of Suspension. All documents were forwarded to the Washington County, States Attorneys Office. All events occurred in Washington County, Maryland. Case closed by issuance of citations. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6694</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 05:29:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6694</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/27/2023 01:53:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>64</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ward</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3285</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>64</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Capezuto</LastName>
            <FirstName>Travis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6694</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508005</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/25/2023 01:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6694</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 03:53:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6694</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 03:54:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508005</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/25/2023 01:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6694</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 03:53:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6694</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 03:54:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508005</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/25/2023 01:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6694</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 03:53:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6694</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 03:54:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508005</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/25/2023 01:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6694</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 03:53:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6694</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 03:54:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508005</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/25/2023 01:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6694</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 03:53:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6694</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 03:54:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508005</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/25/2023 01:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6694</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 03:53:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6694</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 03:54:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6694</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 03:55:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:55</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377967</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>A</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>VU</LastName>
               <FirstName>LONG</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>HOANG NGUYEN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/07/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/25/2023 03:38:23</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>V000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>VU</LastName>
               <FirstName>LONG</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>HOANG NGUYEN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/07/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>V000</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/25/2023 03:38:23</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>18313</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Lyles</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Hagerstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21740</Zip5>
               <Zip4>9517</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.733874</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.58745</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6694</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 03:55:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6694</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 03:55:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6694</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 03:55:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:02</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6694</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 03:53:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6694</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 03:53:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153395</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6694</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 03:56:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6694</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/25/2023 03:56:59</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>19UUB6F5XMA003426</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2021</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>ACUR</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>0</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4EL6617</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>