<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-023711</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/02/2023 04:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/02/2023 04:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/02/2023 04:13:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/02/2023 04:13:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The driver was placed under arrest for DUI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 04:56:29</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2362</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/11/2023 13:37:17</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>680545</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 04:56:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/03/2023 02:24:44</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>680545</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>22711</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Three Notch</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Hollywood</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20636</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.49352</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.29133</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/02/2023 04:56:28</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/02/2023 04:56:28</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/03/2023 03:23:02</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 04:56:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:29:00</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was captured on body worn camera/in-car camera (T-32)  Defendant: Tyrae Maliq Dove  Maryland Soundex: D100809579534  Date of Arrest: 7/2/2023  Time of Arrest: 0453  DUI # 23-076  CERTIFICATE AND TRAINING: Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety through the Maryland State Police Academy and National Highway Safety Administration.  PHASE 1: VEHICLE IN MOTION:   On Sunday, July 2, 2023, at approximately 0413 hours, I, Tpr. Thomas from the Maryland State Police Leonardtown Barrack responded to the Sheetz located at 22711 Three Notch Rd, California, MD 20619 for the report of a subject passed out behind the steering wheel of a black Hummer. Upon arriving on scene, I observed the black Hummer in question bearing Virginia registration (TWB7742) in a parking spot near the front entrance of the Sheetz sitting stationary. While approaching the vehicle, I observed the vehicle to be running with the taillight and headlights activated. I also observe the key in the ignition. I approached the Hummer from the drivers side and observed a black male unconscious in the drivers seat. I knocked on the window twice before the driver woke up.  PERSONAL CONTACT:   I attempted to make contact with the driver of the Hummer twice by knocking on the window. After the second knock, the driver eventually woke up. Once the driver rolled his window down, I immediately smelled the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle. I advised the driver the reasoning for police contact. I asked the operator for his drivers license in which he could not provide me. The driver advised he did not have his license on him and provide me his Military ID. I was able to identify the operator as Tyrae Maliq Dove (B/M DOB: 7/5/1996). While talking to Dove, I continued to smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle and person. I asked Dove how many alcoholic beverages did he consumed prior to police contact. Dove advised he consumed A few Cutwaters and began to raise the alcoholic beverage up to me. I observed the alcoholic Cutwater beverage in the center cup holder of his vehicle. I asked Dove to perform Standardized Field Sobriety (SFST) in which he agreed to do. Once Dove was out of the vehicle, I noticed Doves eyes to be droopy and movement lethargic. I observed his speech to be slow. I continued to smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his person and breath.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING PHASE:   The evaluation was performed in the parking lot of the Sheetz. The surface was dry, level, and free of debris upon testing. I moved Dove to the clearest, level spot for testing. The testing was conducted during early morning hours and the area was lit by my handheld flashlight. The patrol vehicles forward-facing lights were deactivated prior to all three tests being conducted. Dove advised he had no prior head or lower body injuries. Dove advised, he does wear corrective lenses, and he was able to perform the tests.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6/6 Clues Observed.   The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. Dove was placed in a manner with his feet together, and his arms down to his sides. He was told to remain in that position for the duration of the test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12-15 inches from Doves eyes. Dove was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes and her eyes only until told to stop. Dove advised he understood the instructions that were given. The following observations were made:   1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit  present in both eyes  2. Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation-present in both eyes  3. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 degrees  present in both eyes  VGN- present  WALK AND TURN: 5/8 Clues Observed.   Prior to Dove performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Dove was instructed to take a regular step with his left foot, and place his right foot directly in front of his left foot, touching heel-to-toe. Dove was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides, and to remain in the position until told to begin. Dove was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel-to-toe on every step. Dove was to keep his hands flat by his side, keeping his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step out loud. On the ninth step, Dove was instructed and demonstrated to keep his lead foot planted, and to take a series of small steps in a 180-degree semicircle, around with his rear foot to face the direction he came from. Dove was, again, instructed and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps as to be performed identical to the first series. Dove was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, maintaining heel-to-toe contact, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. Dove advised he understood the directions.   Instructional Phase:  Started too soon   Walking Phase 1st Nine:  1. Stepped off-line 2,3, and 6  3. Improper turn. Dove raises lead foot when turning.   Walking Phase 2nd Nine:   Raise arms more than six inches on step 1.   Stops walking on step 1.  ONE LEG STAND 2/4 Clues Observed.   Prior to Dove performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Dove was instructed to stand with his feet together with his hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and the test was performed. Dove was explained when the test begins, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was instructed to keep his leg straight, look down at the raised foot, and count out loud, and continue the test until he was told to stop. Dove advised he understood the directions. Dove chose to lift his right foot, and balance on his right foot.   Seconds 21-30   Dove raises arms more than 6 inches  Dove puts foot down at second 23.   Dove was offered the Preliminary Breath Test, resulting in a .11 BrAC.   Based off the observations observed during my contact with Butler, I had reason to believe Dove was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:       Droopy, bloodshot eyes.      The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.      Admission to consuming alcohol.     Doves movement to be slow and deliberate.     Clues I observed during Standardized Field Sobriety Test.   At approximately 0453 hours, Dove was placed under arrest, and places in the front seat of my patrol vehicle. Dove was transported to the Maryland State Police Leonardtown Barrack- T for processing.   I made contact with Evens Moe Claude (B/M DOB:7/26/1995) who works at the Sheetz. Claude advised he found Dove in the parking lot with the vehicle running. Dove advised he attempted several times to knock on the window to make sure Dove was ok but was met with negative results. Claude advised he went back in the store and advised another worker identified as Catherine Anne Lockard (W/F DOB: 8/14/1983) to call 911.   At approximately 0532 hours, Dove was read his DR-15 Advice of Rights, and refused to take the intoximeter test.   Dove was cooperative during this incident. Dove was provided all the proper paperwork for the DUI portion and was release to a sober driver.   I request this case to be closed by arrest.  All the above events occurred in St. Marys County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7591</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 23:53:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7591</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/03/2023 02:58:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Marquis</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6369</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thomas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Payton</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7591</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>513150</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>18</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/02/2023 04:13:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7591</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 23:40:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7591</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 23:40:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7591</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 23:26:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>116288</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Dove</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyrae</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Maliq</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/05/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/22/2016 09:34:20</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T600</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Dove</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyrae</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Maliq</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/05/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D100</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T600</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/22/2016 09:34:20</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>21276</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Lexwood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>6A</SubNumber>
               <City>Lexington Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>654</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>BLK</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Carolina </StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>BLK</StreetSuffixCode>
               <SubTypeCode>BLDG</SubTypeCode>
               <City>Suffolk</City>
               <StateCode>VA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>23434</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.59182</Longitude>
               <Latitude>36.711861</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>46303</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sue</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Lexington Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.46866</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.25564</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7591</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 23:46:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7591</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 23:46:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7591</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 23:46:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7591</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/03/2023 01:30:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>381527</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Lockard</LastName>
               <FirstName>Catherine</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/14/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>I</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>07/03/2023 01:29:56</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L263</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C365</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Lockard</LastName>
               <FirstName>Catherine</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/14/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>I</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>L263</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C365</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/03/2023 01:29:56</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>21766</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>BLK</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>princeton</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <Zip5>20653</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7591</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/03/2023 01:30:17</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP7591</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/03/2023 01:31:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>328558</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Claude</LastName>
               <FirstName>Evens</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Moe</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/26/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/08/2021 06:28:40</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E152</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Claude</LastName>
               <FirstName>Evens</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Moe</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/26/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E152</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/08/2021 06:28:40</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>22508</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Iverson</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Great Mills</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20634</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.49594</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.286422</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>660</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8198</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/08/2021 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7591</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/03/2023 01:31:21</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:14</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7591</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/02/2023 23:40:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7591</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/02/2023 23:40:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154773</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7591</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/03/2023 02:37:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7591</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/03/2023 02:37:15</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2006</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HUMM</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>H3</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>VA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>TWB7742</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>