<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-014241</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/22/2023 03:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/22/2023 03:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/22/2023 03:38:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/22/2023 03:38:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>23-220 "R" THOMAS</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 04:05:26</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6354</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/08/2023 17:45:12</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>691582</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 04:32:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 04:38:15</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>691582</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I-695</StreetName>
         <City>Towson</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21286</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.574154</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.405823</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/22/2023 04:05:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/22/2023 04:05:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/08/2023 17:45:13</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 04:05:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E.) TEAM* The following incident was captured on in-car and body camera Defendant: Talaisha Nicole Thomas  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: * I am trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (March 2013 SFST NHTSA Manual). * I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor as of February 2016. * I am a Certified Breath Test Operator by the Toxicologist of the State of Maryland as of March 2016. * I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of March 2016. * I am a distinguished graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute as of June 2015 * I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of May 2014. * I am a Preliminary Breath Test Instructor as of May 2019. * I am a RADAR and LIDAR Instructor as of October 2019. * I have apprehended more than 1,000 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On April 22, 2023 at approximately 0335 hours, I (Cpl. Wallace #6323) was on patrol in unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle DUI-1 on the O/L I-695 in the area of Loch Raven Blvd, Baltimore County, Maryland. I observed a black SUVs left turn signal begin to blink, the SUV moved into the middle lane and came to a stop in the middle travel lane. There was another vehicle behind the SUV that had to stop and swerve around the SUV. I approached a black Cadillac SUV bearing Maryland temporary registration T1267980. I activated my rear lights to notify two tractor trailers that were approaching from the rear. Once the tractor trailers passed and there were no other vehicles coming, I activated my emergency lights and conducted a traffic stop on the Cadillac. The Cadillac moved onto the right shoulder and stopped with the rear of the vehicle over the fog line.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Cadillac on the passenger side and made contact with the female operator of the vehicle, who was the only occupant in the vehicle. She rolled down the wrong window. I explained the reason for the stop and requested her drivers license. She stated that she stopped because she forgot where she was going, later said she was going home. She was identified by her Maryland drivers license asTalaisha Nicole Thomas.While speaking with Thomas, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle. I deliberately observed her eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. She stated that she was coming from celebrating her friends birthday at Sizzle (a club on Pulaski Highway).I returned to my patrol vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with.  I returned to the Cadillac and requested Thomas to exit her vehicle and walk to the front. She complied and exited her vehicle. She stumbled backwards while I was speaking to her. As I communicated with Thomas outside of the vehicle, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. When asked about alcohol consumption she stated she had 2 glasses of red wine. She stated that she got there around 5 and left at 1:30. I informed Thomas that I wanted her to perform standardized field sobriety tests, to which she agreed to the tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed at the location of the stop. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. I observed her to be wearing a white top, jeans and red leather heels (put flats on).  I asked Thomas the following questions:  Glasses or Contact  No Recent head injuries  No Medication  No Problems with knees or ankles  No   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting Nystagmus    Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes   WALK AND TURN (6/8 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Thomas stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed.  Instructional Stage:    Lost balance offline to the right 2 times.  Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Missed touching heel to toe by more than  inch on all steps.  Stepped completely offline on multiple steps.   Raised arms more than 6 inches from side.  Took over 20 steps when instructed to take 9.     Began walking backwards when instructed to turn around and come back  Turn: Turned with both feet.   Walking Stage (2nd Nine):    Missed touching heel to toe by more than  inch on multiple steps.  Stepped completely offline on multiple steps.  Raised arms more than 6 inches from side.   ONE LEG STAND(3/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Thomas stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. -Left foot raised.  Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10:    Swayed body to the left and right.  Raised arms more than 6 inches from side.  Left foot hit the ground multiple times (unable to keep her foot off the ground)  PBT #209455 with a result of .14 BrAC.  ARREST Due to the number of observations, I concluded Thomas was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0354 hours, I placed Thomas under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. Thomas was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and was transported to the Baltimore County Towson Precinct for processing.  Upon arrival at the precinct, I provided Thomas with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Thomas listened to the DR-15 Advice of Rights from the MVA website. At 0428 hours, Thomas agreed to take a breath test.  20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD:  I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Thomas beginning at 0354 hours. (She had teeth Jules on her teeth) Thomas was observed from that time until the time she submitted to the test and she did not put anything in her mouth. The test was conducted by Officer Washburn of the Baltimore County Police on a certified instrument. Thomas had a result of 0.13 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 0431 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT:  ****0.13 grams of alcohol****  Thomas was polite and cooperative, she was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/08/2023 16:08:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/08/2023 16:48:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503655</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/22/2023 03:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 04:32:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 04:38:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>43</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 04:32:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:25</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374978</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Thomas</LastName>
               <FirstName>Talaisha</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/13/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/22/2023 04:21:38</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T420</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Thomas</LastName>
               <FirstName>Talaisha</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/13/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T420</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/22/2023 04:21:38</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>24</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Brook Village</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Reisterstown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21136</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.807372</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.460869</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 04:39:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 04:39:15</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 04:32:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 04:32:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152226</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 04:40:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 04:40:02</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CADI</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>T1267980</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>