<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-011578</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/01/2023 00:44:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/01/2023 00:44:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/01/2023 00:11:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/01/2023 00:11:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 00:44:42</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4437</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/11/2023 01:56:32</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I97 / CROWNSVILLE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>583527</AddressId>
      <City>MDC102</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 00:44:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 03:14:29</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>583527</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I97</StreetName>
         <City>Annapolis</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>401-1000 I97 / 1806-1829 CROWNSVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1001-2500 I97 / 1806-1829 CROWNSVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>401-1050 I97 / 1800-1825 CROWNSVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>401-1000 I97 / 1810-1845 CROWNSVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB 97 AT CROWNSVILLE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>401-1050 I97 / 1806-1829 CROWNSVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1051-2500 I97 / 1800-1825 CROWNSVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/01/2023 00:44:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/01/2023 00:44:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/07/2023 07:43:43</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 00:44:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI Report  Marked Car # Q-12 equipped with an in-car camera and body camera.  MARYLAND STATE POLICE  SUMMARY Defendant: Isaac Mendoza Jr Date of Birth: 02/15/1978 Date of Arrest: 04/01/2023 Time of Arrest: 0044 Hours  DUI #: J-23-052 MSP Case # 23-MSP-0011578  Prisoner search: Nothing illegal on person Vehicle search: No alcoholic beverages on scene  OFFICER TRAINING/EXPERIENCE * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. * Certified Intoximeter operator by the Maryland State Toxicologist. *Have had numerous DUI/DWI arrests and convictions over the past 20 years.  REPEAT OFFENDER Yes  LICENSE STATUS Lic # MD-10272432750 STATE:MD Valid Class:C J Alcohol restriction  WEATHER/ROAD CONDITION Clear dry 64 degrees  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)   On Saturday, April 1,2023, at approximately 0011 hours, I, Trooper B. Peris ID #7511 was on routine uniform patrol in the area of Annapolis, Anne Arundel County, Maryland. I received information from dispatch that a vehicle was following a possible drunk driver on 50 near South Haven Road, Anne Arundel County, Maryland.  At the above listed date and time, I began responding to the area of the driver. Prior to my arrival the witness was providing additional information as they continued monitoring vehicle and driver. The witness stated they were behind a white GMC truck, possibly a drunk driver. The witness reported that the vehicle drove off the roadway into a ditch, and then back onto E/B Rt 50 continuing Eastbound. The witness reported that the vehicle was traveling at speeds of approximately 40 mph in a posted 65 mph speed zones. The vehicle was reported to have stopped, and the driver was seen exiting the truck and possibly using the bathroom. The witness stated that the driver returned to the truck and continued E/B on 50. The witness then advised the vehicle had taken the exit to N/B I-97, and that they were following with their hazard lights on. The witness stated that the vehicle was still driving at slow speeds and in lane 1. The witness said the vehicle was swerving and moved to lane 2.  I was able to catch up with the vehicle and observed the white GMC truck in lane 2. I noticed that the truck was traveling at a slow speed impeding traffic. I then noticed that the vehicle was swerving across the solid white fog line several times. While attempting to find probable cause to stop the vehicle, the GMC suddenly just pulled to the right shoulder of the roadway and stopped. I pulled in behind the truck and exited my vehicle to make a consensual encounter. I did not activate any emergency equipment (lights).  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the drivers side door of the vehicle, and noticed that the drivers window was down almost half way. I asked the driver if everything was okay and that someone had been complaining about his driving. The driver stated that he was fine. I noticed that the driver was having trouble holding his eyes open, his speech was extremely slurred, and he was slumped in his seat. I was able to detect a moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle. When asked, the driver admitted to drinking two beers. Based off the previous callers information and my brief observations, I suspected the driver of being under the influence of an alcoholic beverage. The driver was asked to turn his vehicle off and exit to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, to which he agreed. The driver provided me a Maryland license at which time I positively identified him as, Isaac Mendoza Jr.The truck was identified as a white 2021GMC Sierra displaying MD tag2EM4003.  As the driver exited the truck, I noticed him to be very unsteady as he slid down the seat and used the truck for balance when reaching the ground. He then staggered as he walked to the rear of his truck for testing. The driver tried to use the truck for balance while standing at the rear; however, he was told several times he could not do so. The driver was told that everything was being recorded. While standing next to the driver at the rear of the vehicle, I was able to detect a stronger odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his breath.I continued to notice that the drivers movements and speech were slow and slurred. He also spoke with a mushed mouth. The driver continued to have difficulty keeping his eyes open, and he was swaying while standing still.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   Testing was performed on the side of the roadway. It was dry and approximately 64 degrees with cloudy skies. The road was level and free from any debris. The driver was asked, and provided answers to the following questions:  Medical Conditions-None Injuries-None Medication:None Glass/Contacts:None Number and type of alcoholic beverages consumed:2 Beers Last time the beverages were consumed:2 hours prior.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS  (6/6 clues observed) The drivers eyes were blood shot and glassy. His pupils were dilated and reacted to light normal. This test was explained, and the driver stated he understood. The driver was instructed to hold his head still, and move only his eyes. While observing his eyes, he was swaying.   The driver displayed the following clues:  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes 4) Vertical Nystagmus-Yes  *The driver was observed to have difficulty standing still during the test as they swayed during the entire test*  WALK AND TURN   (4/8 clues observed)  Prior to being asked to perform this test, I demonstrated the test. The driver was asked if they understood the test prior to beginning, and he said, Yes. The test was performed on a flat level surface, free of debris, and in a safe location.  INSTRUCTIONAL PHASE  The driver could not remain in the Instructional Phase during instruction as required. The driver tried to stand heel-to-toe and lost his balance on several attempts. The driver was also observed to start the test too soon.  WALKING PHASE (1st Nine):  During the first nine steps the driver took a total of 6 steps out before stopping, losing his balance, and stepping to the side. He then started from the beginning, lost his balance at step three, then continued walking to step 13.  TURN The subject never made the turn.  WALKING PHASE (2nd Nine): The driver never did the return nine steps.  ONE LEG STAND  (3/4 clues observed)  Prior to being asked to perform this test, I demonstrated the test. The driver was asked if they understood the test prior to beginning, and he said, Yes. The test was performed on a flat level surface, free of debris, and in a safe location.  INSTRUCTIONAL STAGE:   The driver swayed during the instruction.  BALANCE AND COUNT STAGE:  The driver began the test by raising his right foot off the ground. He put his foot down on count 2-3. He then tried to lift his left foot and began counting, although his foot never left the ground. When told he needed to lift his foot, he continued counting with his foot on the ground, skipping numbers.  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)  The driver was asked to submit to a preliminary breath test. The driver was informed that it was not admissible in court. The driver did not elect to take the test. He REFUSED to submit to a PBT.  ARREST  As a result of my observations, I had reason to believe the driver was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of an alcoholic beverage in excess of 0.08 BrAC. I felt that the driver was also unable to operate a vehicle safely.At approximately 0044 hours, I placed the driver under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. The driver was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy. I played the DR-15 Advice of Rights form to the driver via MVA audio version, online. The driver was also provided a copy in English/Spanish for him to follow/read along. At the conclusion of the reading, the driver REFUSED take the test of breath. Note that the breath test equipment and operator were available.  The vehicle was left on the side of the road secured out of the travel portion for the driver to make later disposition. The driver was then transported to the Maryland State Police Annapolis Barrack for processing.  INTOXIMETER RESULT:   ***REFUSED BREATH TEST***  The driver was given copies of all pertinent paperwork and was released from the Barrack to a sober driver. I also submitted an MVA Driver Re-Evaluation form due to him being a repeat DUI offender.  EXHIBITS:  DR-15 DR-15A Citations  Documents  All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland. CASE STATUS: Closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 03:47:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7511</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/06/2023 07:00:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Aaron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>PERIS</LastName>
            <FirstName>BRYAN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7511</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500981</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>05</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/01/2023 00:11:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <Remarks>DUI</Remarks>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 03:15:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7511</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 03:15:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 03:17:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:22</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>224667</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mendoza</LastName>
               <FirstName>Isaac</FirstName>
               <DOB>02/15/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>03/17/2019 03:24:15</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I220</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mendoza</LastName>
               <FirstName>Isaac</FirstName>
               <DOB>02/15/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>M532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I220</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/17/2019 03:24:15</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3111</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>New Coach</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Bowie</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20716</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1216</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.7443158</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.9331287</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>601</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9570</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/17/2019 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 03:59:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 03:59:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 03:59:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 03:15:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7511</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 03:15:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151523</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7511</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/01/2023 03:35:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7511</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/01/2023 03:35:41</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/01/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1GT49SEYXMF196713</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2021</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>GMC</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SIERRACLSC1500HD</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2EM4003</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
         <VehicleValue>0</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>