<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-006888</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/23/2023 00:18:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/23/2023 00:18:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/23/2023 00:00:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/23/2023 00:00:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The driver was stopped for a traffic violation and subsequently arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 00:18:08</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5857</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/03/2023 09:54:13</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>25698 MD-5,LEONARDTOWN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>685321</AddressId>
      <City>MDC184</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 00:18:09</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 05:19:19</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>685321</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>25850</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Point Lookout</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Leonardtown</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20650</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.649484</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.302559</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/23/2023 00:18:05</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/23/2023 00:18:05</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/03/2023 09:54:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/23/2023 00:18:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:16</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was captured on in-car camera (T-19) and body worn camera. Defendant: Andrew Mark Ponti Date of Birth: 1/29/1988 Date of Arrest: 2/23/2023 Time of Arrest: 0017 SDX: P-530-067-585-077 DUI#: 23-021 CERTIFICATE AND TRAINING  Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Safety Administration. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE ONE)  On 2/23/23 at approximately 0001 hours, I was travelling northbound on MD Rt. 5 in the area of Clarks Rest Rd when I observed a silver Ford Fusion bearing MD registration 5BH8780 cross over the solid double yellow center line twice. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE TWO)  I made contact with the driver of the vehicle, later identified as Andrew Mark Ponti (W/M DOB: 1/29/1988), by his Maryland ID card. I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. I asked Ponti how many alcoholic beverages he consumed today to which he stated he consumed 1 or 2 beers earlier today. Ponti was slurring his words. I asked Ponti if he would be willing to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests and he agreed. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE THREE)  The evaluation was performed on the shoulder of the roadway in front of Pontis vehicle. The surface was dry, level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight, the headlights of my vehicle and multiple street lights. I asked Ponti if he takes any prescription medication to which he stated he does for his blood pressure and his concussion he got a couple years ago. I asked Ponti if he wears corrective lenses or contacts to which stated he was wearing contacts. I observed Pontis eyes to be bloodshot and glassy at this time. HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN) (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and was held approximately 12 inches from Pontis eyes and slightly above eye level. Ponti was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following the tip of the stimulus with his eyes only. Pontis pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I asked Ponti if he understood the directions and he stated, Yes. 1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit: Present in both eyes. 2. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation: Present in both eyes. 3. Onset Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees: Present in both eyes. Vertical Nystagmus not detected.  WALK AND TURN (5/8 clues observed)  I explained to Ponti and demonstrated how the test should be completed. Ponti was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Ponti was then instructed to place his hands along his side and to remain in the starting position until told to begin the test. I advised Ponti to take nine heel to toe steps in a straight line. Ponti was told to keep his hands by his side, to look at his feet the entire time, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, I demonstrated and explained to Ponti to keep his lead foot on that line and turn around in a series of small steps to the left and turn completely around. I demonstrated three of the nine steps, both before and after the turn. Ponti was instructed once he began the test, he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet and count every step out loud. I then asked Ponti if he understood the instructions and he stated, Yes. Instructional Stage: 1) Ponti was unable to maintain the starting position breaking heel to toe, and had to reset one time. Walking Stage (1st Nine). 2) Ponti missed heel to toe contact by more than one half inch on a majority of the 43 steps. 3) Ponti stepped off line on a majority of 43 steps. 4) Ponti took 43 steps instead of the instructed 9 steps. 5) Ponti turned the opposite way as instructed. Walking Stage (2nd Nine) 2) Ponti missed heel to toe contact by more than one half inch multiple times. 3) Ponti stepped off line multiple times. 4) Ponti took 21 steps instead of the instructed 9 steps even after be reminded to only take 9 steps. One Leg Stand (4/4 clues observed)  Prior to Ponti performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Ponti was instructed to stand with his legs together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately six (6) inches. Ponti raised his left foot and balanced on his right foot. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, keep his hands at his sides, watch his raised foot, to count out loud by thousands, and continue the test until told to stop. I asked Ponti if he understood the test and he stated, Yes. Seconds 0-10: 1) Ponti swayed. 2) Ponti placed his foot down. 3) Ponti hopped. 4) Ponti used his arms for balance. Seconds 10-20: 1) Ponti swayed. 4) Ponti used his arms for balance. Seconds 20-30: 1) Ponti Swayed. 4) Ponti used his arms for balance. PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST: Ponti agreed to take a preliminary breath test, with a result of .16 BrAC. ARREST:  Based on the following, I had the reason to believe Ponti was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: Unable to maintain his lane and obey traffic control devices. Observed bloodshot and glassy eyes. Slurred and sluggish speech and body movements. Inability to follow directions. Detected an odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from breath and person. Admitted to consuming alcohol. Observations during Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Preliminary breath test of .16 BrAC.  Ponti was placed under arrest at approximately 0017 hours and transported to the Maryland State Police Leonardtown Barrack. Ponti was played an audio recording of the DR-15 Advice of Rights through MVAs website. Ponti was provided with a copy of the DR-15 to follow along with. Ponti signed the DR-15 Advice of Rights at 0047 hours and agreed to take the Intoximeter test. INTOXIMETER RESULTS: .17 BrAC Ponti signed and was given copies of all paperwork. Ponti was then released from the barrack to a sober driver. Case closed by arrest. All events occurred in St. Marys County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 06:18:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7152</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 06:18:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Engleman</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7197</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oles</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5857</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Baden</LastName>
            <FirstName>Craig</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7152</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496285</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 05:21:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7152</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 05:21:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496285</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 05:21:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7152</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 05:21:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>496285</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/23/2023 00:00:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 05:21:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7152</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 05:21:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 05:23:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:41</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>369988</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ponti</LastName>
               <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Mark</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/29/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 05:23:12</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A536</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ponti</LastName>
               <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Mark</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/29/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A536</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 05:23:12</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>23255</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Lindsay</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Leonardtown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20650</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.648784</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.307273</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 05:52:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 05:52:19</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:45</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 05:21:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7152</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 05:21:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150190</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/24/2023 05:26:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7152</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/24/2023 05:26:31</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3FA6P0H76DR389570</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FUS</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>5BH8780</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>