<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012531</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/08/2023 17:04:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/08/2023 17:04:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/08/2023 16:52:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/08/2023 16:52:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>dui</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 17:04:58</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/15/2023 08:03:24</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>166971</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 17:04:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 17:04:58</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>166971</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2902</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>WHITEFORD</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>WHITEFORD</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.39199444227827</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.71812916014113</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/08/2023 17:04:55</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/08/2023 17:04:55</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/15/2023 08:03:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 17:04:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:02:33</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI Case # 23-097 CASE # 23-MSP-012531 D-19 with in-car camera. Stop recorded on body camera.  TRAINING: STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY CERTIFIED A.R.I.D.E (Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement) CERTIFIED 2021 DUI CONFERENCE  DEFENDANT: Tiffany N. Conley 216 Constitution Rd.  Pylesville, MD  Phase #1 - Vehicle in Motion    On April 8th, 2023 at approximately 1704 hours, I, TPR Neal #7283 of the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack, was on duty, and was dispatched to the area of 2902 Whiteford Rd for a single vehicle collision into a utility pole. I arrived on scene and observed the vehicle, a black Hyundai Elantra bearing Maryland registration 1BP4511. The vehicles front end was partially wrapped around the pole in the corner of the intersection for Whiteford Rd and Graceton Rd.   Phase #2 - Personal Contact    Upon contact, I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle, which was unoccupied at the time. I then made contact with the driver and passenger. The driver was identified by her Maryland drivers license as, Tiffany Conley (White/Female, DOB: 03/04/2002). Conley displayed bloodshot and glassy eyes. The passenger had a head injury and was awaiting EMS for medical attention.  I asked Conley what had happened, in which she stated that she was emotional and came through (the intersection) and lost control. The strong smell of an alcoholic beverage, similar to the odor emitting from within the vehicle, emanated from her breath and person. I asked Conley how many alcoholic beverages she consumed, in which she advised one beer. Conley expressed to me that the collision was due to her being emotional and angry rather than the alcohol. Conley stated that she stopped at the stop sign prior to continuing through the intersection, and at some point became angry with her boyfriend.  Based on the above observations, I asked Conley if she would mind completing standardized field sobriety tests, in which she agreed.   Conley was wearing light blue jeans, a neon green hooded sweatshirt and gray tennis shoes.  Phase #3 - Pre-Arrest Screening  I asked Conley the following questions:  Medical Conditions  No Eyeglasses - No Injuries  Broken leg a year prior, had a rod and screws put in, stated walks with a limp, however, no limp was observed at all during all interactions Medications  Adderall  30 mg (stated had not taken that morning but typically does every morning and evening)   I am trained through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Transportation Safety Administration in administrating Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus - 6 of 6 clues    The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. My black ballpoint pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Conley eyes. Conley was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of my pen with her eyes until told to stop. Conley pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking.   - Lack of Smooth Pursuit  present  - Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  present - Onset of Nystagmus Prior to Reaching 45 Degrees - present  -Vertical Nystagmus  not present  Walk and Turn 4 of 8 clues   Prior to Conley performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Conley was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Conley was instructed to place her hands down at her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Conley was advised to take nine (9) steps straight out in front of her (imagining a straight line out extending out in front of hers), touching heel to toe on every step. She was to keep her hands down at her side, looking down at her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Conley was demonstrated and explained to keep her lead foot planted on that imaginary line and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around without stopping. Conley was again explained and demonstrated the second series of steps to be performed identical to the first series. Conley was advised once she started the test, she was not to stop until the test was completely finished. After explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked Conley if she completely understood the instructions, in which she stated she was not sure, so I explained it again. I asked Conley if she had any questions, in which she stated she did not.  *INSTRUCTIONAL POSITION * - no clues observed   *WALKING PHASE*     First 9 Steps - Stepped off-line on steps 9 - Raises arms greater than 6in (for balance) on steps 1 and 5 Stopped while walking (step 9 to ask is this 9? Incorrect turn  shuffle spin   One Leg Stand  3 of 4 clues    Prior to Conley performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Conley was instructed to stand with her feet together and hands down to her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. Conley was instructed not to begin the test until she was instructed to start. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately six (6) inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep both knees locked and both legs straight, keep her raised foot parallel with the ground, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand two, one thousand three...) and to continue the test until told to stop (30 seconds). Conley stated that she thought she understood the instructions, so I explained it again. She did not have any questions. Conley raised her left leg for the test.  *BALANCE AND COUNTING STAGE* - Sways - Puts foot down 2 times  -Uses arms for balance  I again asked Conley what alcoholic beverages she consumed prior to driving, in which she stated a slushie. I asked if that contained liquor and was a mixed drink. Conley admitted the drink was actually a mixed drink and demonstrated with her hands the size of the beverage. In doing so, she demonstrated a large beverage, approximately 23 oz or more. (see body camera video).  Based on my training at the Maryland State Police Academy, knowledge, and experience I placed Conley under arrest for DUI at 1717 hours.  Conley was transported to the Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack for processing.   At the barrack, Conley was provided a copy of the DR 15 Advice of Rights form to follow along with, while the DR-15 was read aloud. Conley stated she understood the form and submitted to the Intoximeter Test at 1752 hours. Sgt Sander #5429 was the breath technician and conducted the test with the result of .07 BrAC at 1800 hours. Conley admitted that the alcoholic beverage may have contributed to her decision making when it came to accelerating her vehicle into the utility pole.  Conley was released from the Barrack to her mother.    Case closed by arrest.   All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7283</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 08:22:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7283</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 20:06:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Neal</LastName>
            <FirstName>Emily</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7283</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Atkinson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5623</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Neal</LastName>
            <FirstName>Emily</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7283</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Neal</LastName>
            <FirstName>Emily</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7283</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501934</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 16:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7283</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 17:31:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7283</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/09/2023 17:32:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501934</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/08/2023 16:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7283</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 17:31:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7283</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/09/2023 17:33:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7283</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 17:31:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373852</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Conley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tiffany</FirstName>
               <DOB>03/04/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/09/2023 17:27:04</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C540</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Conley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tiffany</FirstName>
               <DOB>03/04/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C540</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/09/2023 17:27:04</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>216</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Constitution</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Pylesville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21034</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7283</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 17:35:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7283</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 17:35:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7283</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 17:35:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7283</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 17:35:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7283</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 17:31:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7283</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/09/2023 17:31:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151801</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7283</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/09/2023 17:31:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7283</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/09/2023 17:31:49</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/09/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HYUN</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ELN</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1BP4511</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/22/2023 15:21:55</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/22/2023 15:21:55</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/15/2023 08:03:25</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5198</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/22/2023 15:21:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:02:33</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Scanned and added DR15 with signature and time.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5198</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/22/2023 15:22:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5198</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 15:22:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5939</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eck</LastName>
            <FirstName>Theresa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5198</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>