<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-013316</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/15/2023 02:04:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/15/2023 02:04:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/15/2023 01:39:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/15/2023 01:39:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 02:04:25</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/28/2023 13:34:25</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>VIETNAM VETERANS MEMORIAL HWY/ W MACPHAIL RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>690755</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 02:04:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/15/2023 05:35:18</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>690755</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>MD-24</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Vietnam Veterans Memorial</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>bel air</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21014</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>W</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.3452995</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.5205018</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/15/2023 02:04:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/15/2023 02:04:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/27/2023 01:15:54</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 02:04:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:22</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police, Barrack D Marked MSP Vehicle D-7. In-Car Camera Operational.  Defendant: Nunez, Dominique Michael Date of Birth: 12/11/2000 Date of Arrest: 04/15/2023 Time of Arrest: 0202hours DUI #: 23-104(Bel Air) Blood test Result: .16 Br AC  BEHAVIOR/CONDUCT:Nunez was Polite, cooperative, respectful and remorseful.  CERTIFICATION  TRAINING NHSTA Trained/certified to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Test (SFST) Preliminary breath test operator certified Certified Radar/Laser Operator  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On 04/15/2023at approximately 0139 hours, I, Trooper Kumador #7052 of the Maryland State Police, Bel AirBarrack was patrolling southbound Baltimore Pike in the area of Atwood street in Bel Air, HarfordCounty, Maryland. I observed a White sedan traveling in the same direction with a malfunctioned left headlamp. I observed the vehicle come to a stop at a red traffic signal at the intersection of MD-24 and Baltimore Pike and later made a left turn on green traffic signal heading south on MD-24, traveling approximately 45 MPH. While following the vehicle in lane 1, I observed the vehicle traveling on the yellow left shoulder line for a while and then suddenly came to almost a complete stop for a green traffic signal and then picked up speed again. I initiated a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle came to a stop on the right shoulder. The vehicle displayed a Maryland registration 4EX9901.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I made a driver side approachof the vehicleand made contact with the operator, a Whitemale. I introduced myself and the reasonsfor the stop. The driver immediately stated that he knew why I stopped him, which was his malfunctioned headlamp and apologized for stopping in the middle of the roadway. I detected a strong odor of alcoholic beverage on his breath while speaking with him in his vehicle. I asked the driver to speak with me outside because they were two in the vehicle. The driver complied and while speaking with him outside, I continued to detect the odor of alcoholic beverage on his breath. I asked the driver how much alcoholic beverage he had consumed and he stated that he had two beers at Mcgurks Pub in Bel Air. The driver stated that his last drink was about half an hour before the stop. I identified the driver by his Maryland drivers license as Nunez, Dominique Michael DOB: 12/11/2000. His eyes were bloodshot and glassy.      PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   Due to the strong odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from Nunezs breath and the admission to consuming alcoholic beverages an hour before the stop and stopping in the middle of the roadway on a green traffic signal, I had reasons to believe that Nunez was operating his vehicle while under the influence of alcohol.  I told Nunez about my intention to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests to which he agreed. Upon the arrival of additional units, I requested Nunez to exit his vehicle for the second time for the tests, to which he agreed. The evaluation was performed in front of my patrol vehicle. The shoulder wasflat and free of any debris and the temperature was approximately 70 degrees.I asked Nunez the following questions: Contacts-No,Glasses-No, andAny Injuries-No.Any medication: No.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the Tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Nunezs eyes. Hewas instructed to look straight ahead, keeping hishead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hiseyes until told to stop. I asked himif he understood the directions, and he advised yes. His pupils were equal in size and did show equal tracking.   Lack of Smooth Pursuit-present  The distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation  present  The onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  present.  Vertical-present   WALK AND TURN (8/8) Before Nunez performed the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. He was instructed to place hisright foot directly in front of hisleft foot and touch heel-to-toe. He was instructed to place hishands flat at hisside and to remain in the position until told to begin. Hewas advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. He was to keep his hands flat at hisside, keep hiseyes focused on hisfeet, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, he was demonstrated and explained to keep hislead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around to hisleft with hisrear foot to turn completely around. He was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. He was then instructed that once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep hishands down by hisside, look down at hisfeet, and count each step out loud.  During the instructional stage:I explained and demonstrated the starting position to Nunez andplaced him in thestarting position. Hecould notstand straight in the starting position. He broke his feet one time and started the test before being told to start.  Walking stage (1st Nine).    Raised his arms more than 6 inches throughout the test.  Stopped walking on the 9thstep and started talking.  Missed heel-to-toe by more than an inch  Stepped offline during the teststeps.   Turn: The turn was unsatisfactory. Nunezturned swiftly in one fluid motion and nearly stumbled instead of taking a small series of steps toward his left as he was instructed.  Walking stage (2nd Nine).    Missed heel-to-toe by more than an inch  Raised his arms more than 6 inches throughout the test.  Stepped offline during the teststeps.  He took 10steps instead of 9   ONE LEG STAND (4/4) Prior to Nunezperforming the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. He was instructed to stand with hisheels together and hands down by hisside, while the instructions were given and during the test. He was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of hischoice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While hisleg was raised, he was to keep hisleg straight, watch hisraised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one thousand-two), and to continue the test until told to stop.     He raised his arms during the test.  He swayed side by side during the test and almost fell  He put his foot down multiple times during the test.  He hopped during the test and almost fell.   PRELIMINARY BREATH A preliminary breath test was not offered to Nunez, and he voluntarily agreed to take the with a result of .13 BrAC.  ARREST Based on the following, I havereasons to believe that Nunezwas operating his vehicle while under the influence of alcoholand unable to safely operate it    Extremely strong odor of alcoholic beverage on his breath  Admission to consuming alcoholic beverages an hourbefore the traffic stop,  Observed signs of impairment as he performedthe Standardized Field Sobriety Tests unsatisfactorily.  I arrested Nunezat 0202hours for driving his vehicle while under the influence of alcohol and transported him to the Maryland State Police, Bel Air barrack for processing. Nunezlistened to the Englishaudio version of DR-15 Advice of Rights in its entiretyin my patrol vehicle and at the conclusion, he voluntarily agreedtosubmit to the test. He signed the paper copy of the DR-15 at the barrack at 0224 hours.  20-MINUTES OBSERVATION PERIOD. Nunezs observation started as soon as his oral cavity check was completed at 0206 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT:  Breath test was explained and offered to Nunez by Sgt. Dudek # 5037with a result of.16 Br Ac  Nunez was charged with driving his vehicle under the influence of alcohol and other DUI related charges.  Nunezwasgiven copies of all pertinent paperwork andlater released to a sober licensed driver at the barrack.  Closed by arrest.  All events occurred in HarfordCounty, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 08:21:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/22/2023 08:31:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Whittenberg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6095</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Turner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6761</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kumador</LastName>
            <FirstName>Linford</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7052</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502723</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/15/2023 01:39:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 05:27:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/15/2023 05:27:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 05:27:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374323</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>NUNEZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>DOMINICK</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MICHAEL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/11/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16598737E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/15/2023 05:02:55</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D552</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>NUNEZ</LastName>
               <FirstName>DOMINICK</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MICHAEL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/11/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16598737E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>N520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D552</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/15/2023 05:02:55</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>304</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Cinnabar</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Abingdon</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21015</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.3324445</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.490348</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>613</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0425</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 05:28:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 05:28:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 05:28:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:55</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 05:27:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/15/2023 05:27:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151966</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7052</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/15/2023 05:30:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7052</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/15/2023 05:30:14</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>YV1TS91Z741343200</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2004</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>VOLV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>S80</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4EX9901</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>12</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>