<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008769</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/10/2023 02:30:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/10/2023 02:30:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/10/2023 02:15:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/10/2023 02:15:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 02:30:56</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/05/2023 18:43:53</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>686872</AddressId>
      <City>MDC452</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 02:30:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 14:35:47</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>686872</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>19</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm Capital Beltway Sb</StreetName>
         <City>Lanham</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.86034</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.94891</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>SB 495 SO 50</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/10/2023 02:30:53</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/10/2023 02:30:53</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/21/2023 11:26:17</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/10/2023 02:30:56</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:21:07</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>CASE NUMBER: 23-MSP-008769 DUI NUMBER: 23-055 INCIDENT RECORDED: The incident was visually and audibly recorded by body worn camera. DEFENDANT: Kirkland 2nd, Keith Anthony (1/M, 05/08/1985) TIME AND DATE OF ARREST: 03/10/2023 at 0242 hours VICTIM: State of Maryland WITNESS: N/A LOCATION: S/B 495 S/O RT 50 TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police.   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On March 10th, 2023, at approximately 0226 hours, I, Tpr. Norman #7454 responded to a call for a two vehicle collision on the I/L 495 in the area of RT 50, Prince Georges county, MD. I was in full uniform operating a marked patrol vehicle Q-35. The incident was audibly and visually recorded on my body worn camera.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) When I arrived on scene, I observed a blue Peterbilt tractor trailer on the right shoulder as well as a burgundy Kia Optima with heavy front-end damage parked in lane 6. The vehicle was driven by Keith Anthony Kirkland 2nd who was identified by his Maryland drivers license. Kirkland stated he was driving the vehicle and confirmed he was the sole occupant. I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Kirklands breath. Kirklands eyes were bloodshot and glassy. Kirkland was asked to perform some standardized field sobriety tests, to which he agreed to.    PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed in lane 6 of S/B 495 S/O RT 50. The surface was level, dry and free of any debris. Kirkland appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any serious injuries. I asked Kirkland the following questions: Alcoholic Beverages Consumed  Kirkland stated he had two drinks of Tequila at Nellies Sports Bar in DC around 12:00 AM. Medical Condition  Kirkland stated that he has no medical conditions and the only medication he takes is a topical ointment for Psoriasis Glasses or Contacts  Kirkland confirmed that he did not wear any glasses or contacts. Last Meal  Kirkland stated he last consumed food at 7:00 PM.   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 Clues Observed) The test was explained. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus. The stimulus was held approximately 12-15 inches from Kirklands eye, slightly above eye level. Kirkland was instructed to look straight ahead, keep his head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes. Kirklands pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Before beginning the test, I asked Kirkland if he understood my instructions, to which he confirmed.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Additional Observations  Resting gaze nystagmus was not present. Vertical gaze nystagmus was present.    WALK AND TURN TEST (6/8 Clues Observed)   The test was explained and demonstrated. Kirkland was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on an imaginary straight line. Kirkland was then instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and remain in that position until told to begin. Kirkland was advised to take nine steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot on the line and take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Kirkland was instructed to complete the second series of nine steps in the same heel to toe fashion. Kirkland was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keeping his eyes focused on his feet, to count every step out loud, and once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Kirkland if he understood, and he confirmed that he did.   Instructional Phase  Kirkland was unable to maintain his balance with his right foot in front of his left foot touching heel to toe.   Walking Stage (First Nine Steps)  Misses Heel-Toe  On all nine steps, Kirkland missed his heel to toe by more than one half inch. Steps Off Line  On all nine steps, Kirkland stepped with his feet side by side rather than heel-toe and steps off line by more than one half inch. Raises Arms  Kirkland Raised his arms to help balance himself on his ninth step. Improper Turn  Kirkland did not turn properly.   Walking Stage (Second Nine Steps) Misses Heel-Toe  On all nine steps, Kirkland missed his heel to toe by more than one half inch. Steps Off Line  On all nine steps, Kirkland stepped off line by more than one half inch. Stops Walking  Kirkland stopped walking and nearly stumbled over on his fifth step.  ONE-LEG STAND TEST  The test was explained and demonstrated. Kirkland was instructed to stand with his heels together and his hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch the raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two, etc.), and not put his foot down until the end of the test. Kirkland stated he understood the instructions to the test. Instructional Stage: Nothing observed Balances on right foot.  Seconds 1-10: Puts Foot Down  1 time Swaying  All ten seconds  Seconds 11-20: Swaying  All ten seconds Puts Foot Down  1 time  Seconds 21-30: Swaying  All ten seconds Puts Foot Down  3 times Uses arms to balance  Seconds 22 - 30 Hops  Seconds 28 -30   PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST While on scene I informed Kirkland of his Preliminary Breath Rights. Kirkland was offered a PBT, to which he agreed (PBT Results: .15).  ARREST Based on the totality of circumstances, I concluded that Kirkland was driving a motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol. Kirklands eyes were bloodshot and glassy. Kirklands movements were slow and lethargic. The odor of an alcoholic beverage was emanating from Kirklands breath and person. Clues during Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (6/6), WAT (6/8), OLS (4/4). Preliminary Breath Test results: .15 On March 10th, 2023, at approximately 0242 hours, I placed Kirkland under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack. A search incident to arrest of Kirklands person was conducted. The search of Kirklands person was negative. I transported Kirkland to the College Park Barrack. Kirkland was played the DR-15 Advice of Rights English recording provided by MVA as well as a cope to read along with. At approximately 0326 hours, Kirkland agreed to take an alcohol concentration test. Results of the test was 0.17 BrAC.  Kirklands vehicle was towed to Past and Present towings lot. I processed Kirkland, and he was released to a sober driver. Kirkland was issued the following citations. TA - 21-902(a1i) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL TA  21-902(a1ii) DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL PER SE TA - 21-902(b1i) DRIVING VEH. WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL TA - 21-901.1(a) RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OF PERSONS AND PROPERTY  TA  21-201(a1) DRIVER FAILURE TO OBEY PROPERLY PLACED TRAFFIC CONTROL DEVICE   The defendant was issued copies of the following documents: -Citations (listed above) -DR-15 Advice of Rights -DR-15a Order of Suspension  All documents were forwarded to the Prince Georges County, State Attorney Office. All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:44:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7454</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/20/2023 09:27:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dunlap</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6273</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dunlap</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6273</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathanael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7454</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498168</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/10/2023 02:15:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:37:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7454</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 14:37:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:41:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:46</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>371188</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Kirkland</LastName>
               <FirstName>Keith</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anthony</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/08/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/10/2023 06:28:54</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K624</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Kirkland</LastName>
               <FirstName>Keith</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anthony</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/08/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>K624</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/10/2023 06:28:54</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>410</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Shady Glen Dr</StreetName>
               <City>Capitol Heights</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20743</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>368</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9478</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:41:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:41:26</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:00</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:37:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7454</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 14:37:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150721</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AC</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7454</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/18/2023 14:42:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7454</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/18/2023 14:42:56</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5XXGT4L39GG107284</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2016</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>KIA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>OPT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>MAR</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3DZ2430</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>