<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-005443</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/12/2023 02:47:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/12/2023 02:47:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/12/2023 02:25:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/12/2023 02:25:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 02:47:28</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3033</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 12:02:16</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>683979</AddressId>
      <City>MDC151</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 02:47:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/12/2023 05:05:06</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>683979</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>28</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I270 Nb</StreetName>
         <City>Frederick</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.38241</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.33908</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/12/2023 02:47:26</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/12/2023 02:47:26</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/12/2023 23:48:37</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 02:47:28</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:52:53</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*Maryland State Police Frederick Barrack* Vehicle: Red Unmarked Ford Explorer B-18 Body Camera Equipped and Functioning: Yes In-car Camera Equipped and Functioning: Yes  OFFICERS ON SCENE: TFC Berger, TFC Carter  Defendant: Edras Eliseo Santos Ramirez Date of Birth: 05/22/2000 Date of Arrest: 02/12/2023 Time of Arrest: 0246  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On February 12, 2023 at approximately 0225 hours I, Tpr Berger #7011, was on routine patrol in the area of N/B I-270 around the 26 mile marker when I observed a grey Toyota Camry bearing MD registration 2ES7179. The Toyota was traveling in lane one but having difficulty staying in its lane. It was continuously swerving within its lane and I observed it swerve partially into lane two three times within a mile. The Toyota was also passing multiple vehicles at a high rate of speed. I initiated a pace on the Toyota and obtained a speed of 95 MPH in a posted 65 MPH zone. Towards the end of the pace, I observed the Toyota swerve into lane two by half a car length before swerving back into lane one. This was at a speed of 95 MPH. At this time, I deemed it unsafe to continue making observations and conducted a traffic stop on the Toyota on the right shoulder of N/B I-270 at MM 29.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  Upon initial contact with the driver, I was able to identify him by his MD Drivers License as Edras Eliseo Santos Ramirez (H/M DOB: 05/22/2000). I was able to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. I observed his eyes were glassy and bloodshot. While collecting the necessary documents from Santos Ramirez, I asked where he was coming from. He advised that he was at a family dinner in Gaithersburg. When he spoke I observed his speech to be slurred. I asked how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed and he advised he had consumed two Modelo beers with his last one being consumed around 0030 hours. I asked Santos Ramirez to perform field sobriety and he complied.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  Field Sobriety was performed on the right shoulder of N/B I-270 at MM 29. I was again able to smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The light condition consisted of my flashlight; my spotlight, headlights, and forward face emergency equipment lights were turned off. His vehicle headlights were turned off. Santos Ramirez was faced away from N/B traffic. The weather was clear and approximately 35 degrees with a mild wind when vehicles passed. Santos Ramirez appeared to be in good physical condition. He was wearing a jacket, jeans and sneakers.  I asked Santos Ramirez the following questions:  -Glasses or contacts - None -Medical Conditions - None -Known Injuries - None -Medications - None  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  I properly explain and demonstrated the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus. I asked Santos Ramirez if he understood the tests instructions and he stated, Yes.   1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes 4.)  Vertical Gaze Nystagmus  Not Present  WALK AND TURN (5/8 clues observed)  I properly explain and demonstrated the Walk and Turn. I asked Santos Ramirez if he understood the test and he stated, Yes.  Instructional Stage: 1.) During the instructional stage, nothing was observed.  Walking stage (1st Nine): 1.) During the first 9 steps, nothing was observed.  Turn: 1.) Santos Ramirez did not perform the turn to satisfaction. He turned on his back foot rather than the lead foot as instructed.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): 1.) During the second 9 steps, Santos Ramirez stepped off line and missed heel to toe contact on his second step. He then stopped the test and had to be instructed to continue. He took 11 total steps.  ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)  I properly explain and demonstrated the One Leg Stand. I asked Santos Ramirez if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, Yes.  Instructional Stage: 1.) Nothing was observed.  Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10: 1.) On seconds 0-10, he put his foot down and swayed.  Seconds 11-20: 1.)  On seconds 11-20, nothing was observed.  Seconds 21-30: 1.) On second 21-30, he put his foot down.  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST  Santos Ramirez was offered a preliminary breath test; in which he accepted with results of .098 BrAC.  ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe that Santos Ramirez was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  *Excessive speed *Inconsistent speed *Failure to maintain lane integrity *Odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the driver breath *Glassy and bloodshot eyes *Slurred speech *Slow and lethargic movements *Admission to drinking an alcoholic beverage prior to driving *My observed sign of impairment during Field Sobriety *PBT results of .098 BrAC  I arrested Santos Ramirez for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0246 hours. He was placed in the front seat of my patrol vehicle. He was transported to the MSP Hagerstown Barrack due to an intoximeter operator not being available in Frederick County.  While en route to the Hagerstown Barrack, I played the DR-15 Advice of Rights in Spanish to Santos Ramirez in its entirety. At approximately 0304 hours, he signed the DR-15 form and submitted to the intoximeter test.  INTOXIMETER TEST  Santos Ramirez submitted to an intoximeter test with a result of .069 BrAC (011723) at approximately 0354 hours. The test was conducted by Sgt. Matthai.  During the processing portion of this incident, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on Santos Ramirez breath and person. He continued to slur his words. He was almost unable to provide a breath sample for the intoximeter test, nearly resulting in a refusal by default. It should also be noted that I asked Santos Ramirez, prior to starting SFSTs, if he needed an interpreter, which he declined. He confirmed after every set of instructions that he understood.  Santos Ramirez was given all copies of pertinent paperwork, he was released at his residence at 0439 hours.  I am trained to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  All events other than the intoximeter testing occurred in Frederick County, Maryland. The testing occurred in Washington County, MD.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7011</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 06:44:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7011</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/12/2023 06:44:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Berger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gabriel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7011</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rishell</LastName>
            <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5730</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Berger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gabriel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7011</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Berger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gabriel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7011</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494829</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/12/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7011</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 05:04:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7011</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/12/2023 05:06:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494829</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/12/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7011</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 05:04:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7011</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/12/2023 05:06:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494829</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/12/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7011</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 05:04:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7011</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/12/2023 05:07:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494829</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/12/2023 02:46:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7011</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 05:04:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7011</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/12/2023 05:07:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7011</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 05:04:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368847</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Santos ramirez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Edras</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ELISEO</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/22/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/12/2023 04:56:02</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E362</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Santos ramirez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Edras</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ELISEO</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/22/2000 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S532</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E362</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/12/2023 04:56:02</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1814</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Beaver Creek</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Frederick</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21702</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.410555</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.4510737</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7011</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 05:09:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7011</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 05:09:00</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:50</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7011</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/12/2023 05:05:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7011</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/12/2023 05:05:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>