<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-020737</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/09/2023 23:48:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/09/2023 23:48:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/09/2023 23:21:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/09/2023 23:21:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI / DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 23:48:10</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 16:43:14</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>BOWLEYS QUARTERS RD/ EDWARDS LN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>697176</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 23:48:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:01:31</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>697176</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Bowleys Quarters</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Middle River</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.39594</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.33398</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>400-400 BOWLEYS QUARTERS RD / 3601-3652 EDWARDS LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/09/2023 23:48:08</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/09/2023 23:48:08</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/23/2023 19:41:35</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/09/2023 23:48:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:06</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>R-24 equipped with in-car camera and body-worn camera. Contact Sgt. Twardowski (joseph.twardowski@maryland.gov) for camera footage.  Case# 23-MSP-020737 Defendant: Brian Shannon Siatkowski Date of Birth: 05/05/1972  Date of Arrest: 06/09/2023 Time of Arrest: 2335 hours DUI #: 23-318 Citation #: 4NG0XD0     Certificates and Training *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration  *Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) Certified  *Certified Emergency Medical Technician by the Maryland Institute of Emergency Medical Services Systems  *Certified RADAR/LIDAR operator by the Maryland State Police  *Certified License Plate Reader (LPR) operator by the Maryland State Police  *Apprehended over 125 impaired drivers while working as a Maryland State Trooper  *2023 Distinguished graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute  Vehicle In Motion (Phase 1)  On June 9th, 2023 at approximately 2321 hours I, Trooper Sigman #7376, currently assigned to the Golden Ring Barrack, was on routine patrol of Bowleys Quarters Road and Edwards Lane when I observed a Black Jeep traveling at a high rate of speed exiting the Walmart parking lot. The black Jeep then failed to yield, turned onto Bowleys Quarters Road, and crossed the double yellow center lines and almost collided head on with my patrol vehicle. I then took evasive action to avoid a serious collision. I then turned around and began to follow the black Jeep bearing Pennsylvania registration KHJ8180. While behind the vehicle I observed it continue to fail to maintain right of center as well as cross the solid white fog line and cross onto the right shoulder with both passenger side tires. I then activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the black Jeep bearing Pennsylvania registration KHJ8180. The Jeep then made a sudden right turn into the Royal Farms Store on Bowleys Quarters Road. The Jeep then came to stop in a parking space.  Personal Contact (Phase 2)  Upon stopping in the parking space the driver of the black Jeep bearing Pennsylvania registration KHJ8180 began to exit the vehicle and did not appear to notice my vehicle with emergency lights activated behind him. I then advised the driver to remain in the vehicle. I then made a drivers side approach of the Jeep. Upon arriving at the drivers window I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I then identified myself, the reason for the stop, and requested the drivers license. I observed that the driver displayed bloodshot glassy eyes, slurred speech upon conversation, and struggled to grasp his license. The driver then handed me his Pennsylvania drivers license which identified him as Brian Shannon Siatkowski (05/05/1972). Siatkowski advised that he was driving to the bar from his boat. I then asked Siatkowski how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed prior to driving. Siatkowski replied two Coors Light. Siatkowski was unable to sit up straight in his vehicle and began to lean against the center console for balance.  I then requested to exit his vehicle and walk to an empty parking space. Upon exiting his vehicle Siatkowski displayed gait ataxia and raised his arms to maintain balance. While outside the vehicle I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. Siatkowski then advised me that in addition to consuming alcohol he also took a muscle relaxer at 4pm. I then asked Siatkowski if he would submit to standardized field sobriety testing. Siatkowski agreed.  Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3)  The evaluation was performed in an empty parking space of the Royal Farms. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 60 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlights, and overhead lights, and my vehicles takedown lights. My vehicles front facing emergency lights were deactivated for the duration of the field sobriety tests. Siatkowski appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries and or defects.  I asked Siatkowski the following questions:  Injuries- prior shoulder injury Medical conditions- none Medications- muscle relaxer Glasses or contacts- wearing contact lenses Alcoholic beverages- two Coors beers Controlled dangerous substance- denies    Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The test was explained. I then began the test. I did not observe any resting nystagmus. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit - present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - present in both eyes *Vertical Gaze Nystagmus - present in both eyes  During the test Siatkowski had difficulty following directions. Siatkowski had to be told multiple times to follow the stimulus and keep his head still. Siatkowski also swayed from side to side.     Walk and Turn (5/8 clues observed)  Prior to Siatkowski performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. I asked Siatkowski if he had any questions. Siatkowski stated that he understood the test.    Instructional Stage: Steps out of starting position   Walking Stage (1st Nine):  Steps off line Misses heel to toe Takes three steps Raises arms for balance    Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  Steps off line Misses heel to toe Takes three steps Raises arms for balance      Turn: Nothing to report  One Leg Stand (3/4)  Prior to Siatkowski performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Siatkowski advised that he understood the test.  Instructional Stage: Sways from side to side     Balance and Count Stage  Seconds 0-10: Raises arms for balance Sways from side to side Puts foot down      Seconds 11-20: Sways from side to side Puts foot down      Seconds 21-30: Sways from side to side Puts foot down Raises arms for balance  During the test Siatkowski put his right foot down and attempted the test with his left foot.   I then offered my PBT to Siatkowski. Siatkowski Refused.  Arrest  Based on the following, I had probable cause to believe Siatkowski was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and prescription medication:  *Unable to maintain a single lane of travel *Failure to yield when exiting a parking lot onto a highway *Almost striking my vehicle head on forcing me to take evasive action to avoid a serious collision *Failure to maintain right of center *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on Siatkowski breath and person *Admission to consuming multiple alcoholic beverages *Glassy eyes *slurred speech *Gait ataxia *Poor SFST     At this time Siatkowski was placed under arrest for DUI. Siatkowski was then handcuffed, searched, and placed in the front seat of R-24 and seat belted inside. Siatkowski was then mirandized. A search incident to arrest was then conducted. I located a cold beer behind the drivers seat that had approximately 25% remaining. I also observed a used condom laying next to the Gray Goose. I then contacted Siatkowski who was asleep at her home in York Pennsylvania with her child. She advised that she would drive to the Golden Ring Barrack to pick up her husband.  Siatkowski was then transported to the Golden Ring Barrack. While enroute to the Barrack Siatkowski stated are you giving me a pass? I fucked up. I again advised Siatkowski that he was under arrest for DUI. Siatkowski continued to repeat I fucked up while driving to the barrack. Siatkowski then advised me that he was going to tell me a secret that he had never told anyone. Siatkowski then removed a retainer from his mouth which revealed that he had a fake tooth. Siatkowski stated not even my wife knows about this. Siatkowski continued to slur his speech and ramble while speaking with me.   Once at the Golden Ring Barrack Siatkowski was walked inside and placed in the Troopers room. A physical copy of the DR15 was placed in front of Siatkowski and the audio version was played aloud. At the conclusion of the audio Siatkowski stated that he wished to take the intoximeter test. I then advised Siatkowski that he had to remove his fake tooth so that the 20-minute observation time could begin to take the test. Siatkowski refused and stated that no one knew about it and thus he would not take it out. I then requested Sgt. Fike to come and explain to Siatkowski that he had to remove his fake tooth prior to the test. Siatkowski then became rude with myself and Sgt. Fike. Siatkowski then repeatedly stated is that the law? Siatkowski eventually removed his false tooth and the observation period began.    20-Minute Observation Period:  During the observation period Siatkowski picked up his false tooth and put it back in his mouth. Myself and Sgt. Fike again explained to Siatkowski that he could not have anything in his mouth and could not touch his face. Siatkowski then stated ill admit I had some drinks. but did not want to remove his tooth. It was then explained that the test would be counted as a refusal if he did not remove it. Siatkowski then removed it and the observation period began. During the observation period Siatkowski began to touch his face and mouth. Sgt Fike repeatedly advised Siatkowski that he could not touch his face or mouth and that the observation time would have to be reset. Siatkowski continued to touch his mouth during the observation period. Sgt Fike then advised Siatkowski that the test would be counted as a refusal as he continued to not follow instructions.     Intoximeter Result:  N/A  Siatkowski was then issued the appropriate citations as well as a DR15A. Siatkowski was then released to his wife in the front parking lot of the Golden Ring Barrack.  All above events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:13:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/17/2023 10:39:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Twardowski</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sigman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7376</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510172</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/09/2023 23:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510172</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/09/2023 23:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510172</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/09/2023 23:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510172</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/09/2023 23:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510172</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/09/2023 23:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510172</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/09/2023 23:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510172</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15912</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/09/2023 23:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510172</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15916</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/09/2023 23:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510172</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/09/2023 23:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510172</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/09/2023 23:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510172</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/09/2023 23:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510172</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>12</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>20970</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>12</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/09/2023 23:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>51</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:08:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:54</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>379401</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>SIATKOWSKI</LastName>
               <FirstName>BRIAN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>SHANNON</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/05/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/10/2023 00:07:51</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S322</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>SIATKOWSKI</LastName>
               <FirstName>BRIAN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>SHANNON</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/05/1972 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S322</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/10/2023 00:07:51</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2240</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Trotter Ridge</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>York</City>
               <StateCode>PA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>17408</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4210</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.798251</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.966812</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:08:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:08:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:08:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:08:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:07</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:03:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153955</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/10/2023 00:11:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/10/2023 00:11:34</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C4BJWEG2DL529551</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>PA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>khj8180</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>