<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-019541</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/31/2023 20:15:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/31/2023 20:15:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/31/2023 18:54:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/31/2023 18:54:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>TRAFFIC STOP/DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 20:15:30</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3033</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/15/2023 10:21:19</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>SILVER CREST DR/ WATER STREET RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>696042</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 20:15:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 22:29:05</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>696042</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Silver Crest</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Walkersville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-77.328378</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.491082</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>312-323 SILVER CREST DR / 9350-9399 WATER STREET RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/31/2023 20:15:26</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/31/2023 20:15:26</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>51</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/14/2023 11:10:33</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 20:15:30</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:53:20</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>**CAR B-66/IN-CAR CAMERA AVAILABLE/BODY-WORN CAMERA AVAILABLE**  ASSISTING:   OFC #C. Faith #1717, Maryland Natural Resources Police, IN-CAR CAMERA NOT AVAILABLE/BODY-WORN CAMERA NOT AVAILABLE  S/TPR HOPKINS #6060, IN-CAR CAMERA NOT AVAILABLE/BODY-WORN CAMERA AVAILABLE   Defendant: Daniel Christopher Donnally Date of Birth: 12/30/1980 Date of Arrest: 05/31/2023 Times of Arrest: 1926 hours  DUI #: 23-MSP-019541 (Frederick Barrack, Walkersville Resident Trooper Program)  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING  * Successfully attended and completed the S.P.I.D.R.E. Teams Enhanced DUI Enforcement: The Complete Course. * Successfully attended and completed the Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) Training Course. * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police. * Trained and certified to operate Preliminary Breath Testing (PBT) through the Maryland State Police and the Office of the Chief Medical Examiner. *Certified through the Maryland State Police as a Collision Reconstructionist (RECON).  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On 05/31/2023, at approximately 1847 hours, I (TFC Blumenauer #6357) of the Maryland State Police was on duty on routine patrol in marked MSP patrol vehicle B-66, in the area of Silver Crest Drive and Water Street Road in Walkersville, Frederick County, Maryland. During this period time, I was completing a patrol check of the Deerfield neighborhood. While approaching the intersection for Silver Crest Drive and Water Street Road, I observed a vehicle parked in the sideways (crooked) in middle of the intersection. The vehicle immediately grabbed my attention when I observed the front and rear windshield wipers of the vehicle were moving very quickly. It should be noted, at this time, the weather was approximately 75 degrees, with clear skies and no rain. I observed the vehicle as a green Subaru Forester bearing Maryland registration 3DZ6027. I observed the vehicles month and rear registration tabs were also missing from the rear license plate as required. While pulling up behind the vehicle, I used my patrol vehicles in car loudspeaker to call out to the driver (00:35 time stamp in body-worn camera video). I then asked the driver if he was okay, and I then observed the vehicle operator exit the front drivers seat of the vehicle and began walking toward my marked police vehicle. I immediately exited my patrol vehicle, and approached the driver. It should be noted, I observed the vehicles engine was running, and all of the vehicles windows were partially rolled down.   It should be noted, when I initially pulled on scene, I did not immediately activate my patrol vehicles front facing emergency equipment (rear lights were activated) to activate the vehicles front facing interior camera. It should be noted, prior to approaching the vehicles operator, I activated my body-worn camera. Prior to activating the body-worn camera, the previous one minute (sixty (60) seconds) on video prior to the camera being activated is available for view with video only (no audio).   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I immediately made contact with the operator, who I observed immediately exit the front drivers seat of the vehicle. I exited my patrol vehicle and approached the operator. I then inquired with the operator if he was okay. The operator immediately stated Thank you so much dude. The operator then advised Im okay. Im just in a bad spot. I then advised the operator he was parked in the middle of the roadway. I then advised the operator that his windshield wipers were on, and asked if he knew the wiper blades were still activated. The operator advised he was aware the wipers were still activated, and I asked if he could turn them off. The operator advised that he was broken, and advised he wanted to go home. The operator then advised he resided in Walkersville on Burlington Avenue. The operator then advised Dude, I am so hurt right now. I then identified the driver by his Maryland drivers license as Daniel Christopher Donnally (DOB 12/30/1980). Donnally then began to explain he was going to rehabilitation on June 1st. Donnally then stated I am drowning myself in alcoholism. (**03:12 time stamp on body-worn camera video**). I then requested Donnally to turn off the wiper blades to the vehicle, and to walk to the right shoulder of the roadway so we could speak further. Donnally then reached inside of the vehicle, turned the vehicle ignition off, and then walked to the right shoulder away from the roadway. Donnally then advised he was committed to checking himself into rehab. I asked Donnally if the rehab was for his drinking, and he advised Yes. After speaking with Donnally for a period of time, I then requested his drivers license, registration, and vehicle insurance. While speaking with Donnally, I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. While speaking with Donnally, I observed his eyes were bloodshot and glassy. I also observed Donnallys speech was slow (delayed), and Donnally was slurring his words. While Donnally was gathering his documents, I observed an open miller lite beer can in the center console in plain view.   At approximately 1905 hours, OFC C. Faith #1717, of the Maryland Natural Resources Police (NRP) arrived on scene to assist. After advising Donnally I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath, I then inquired with Donnally how many alcoholic beverages he had prior to driving. Donnally then advised Ive had a few beers, and Ive had a couple shots of liquor. I then asked Donnally if the beer was the open Miller Lite can that was sitting in the center console, and he stated Pretty much. I then asked Donnally how many Miller Lite cans he had consumed, and he stated Three. I asked Donnally at what time was his last alcoholic beverage, and he stated he didnt know what time his last drink was. Donnally then advised If you want to give me the blow and go, Im cool with that. I then asked Donnally if he felt that he was at a safe point to be operating a motor vehicle, and he advised I really dont think so. Donnally then stated, Id really just prefer if you gave me a fucking pass.  I then asked Donnally if he took any medications and he advised No. I then asked Donnally if he had a current injuries, and he advised I got a bunch of fucking brain magma. I then asked Donnally to elaborate, and he advised he had a previous brain injury in October of 2019 where he was assaulted and he needed 74 staples in his scalp. I asked Donnally if he uses any other drugs, and he advised he smokes marijuana daily. I asked Donnally if he smoked marijuana during the day prior to me interacting with him, and he advised he did not.  At approximately 1915 hours, S/Tpr Hopkins #6060 arrived on scene to assist.    PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) I asked Donnally the following questions: Glasses/Contacts  No. Injuries/Illnesses  No. Medication  No. Medical Conditions  No.  The evaluation was performed directly in front of my patrol vehicle in the asphalt roadway on Silver Crest Drive. The surface was dry, and free from any obvious debris. The surface was flat in elevation. The weather was clear skies, and approximately 80 degrees in temperature. All patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Donnally appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. Donnally was wearing a green t-shirt, gray cargo-style shorts, and no shoes. It should be noted Donnally was offered to wear his shoes prior to SFSTs.   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pointer finger was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Donnallys eyes. Donnally was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Donnallys pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. It should be noted Donnallys pupils were constricted. I then asked Donnally why his pupils were constricted, and he advised I have head trauma. Donnally was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic, and the sun glare would not interfere with the test results. I asked Donnally if he understood the instructions, and he made verbal acknowledgement and he stated Yes.      margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes.  2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes. 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes.  When initially starting the test, Donnally did not follow the stimulus as instructed. It should be noted, vertical nystagmus was not present. I observed Donnally continue to sway in place while the test was conducted.   WALK AND TURN (7/8 clues observed) Prior to Donnally performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Donnally was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot, and touch heel to toe. Donnally was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his side, and to remain in the instructional stage position until told to begin. I then asked Donnally if he understood, and he stated Yes. Donnally was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line, touching heel to toe on every step. Donnally was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Donnally was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Donnally was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Donnally was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Donnally if he understood the instructions of both stages of the test and he stated, Yes.  Instructional Stage:     margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Broke instructional stage. Donnally stood with his feet shoulder with apart, and had his hands locked behind his back.    Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Raised arms more than six (6) inches from his sides.  Stepped off line on step 2, 3, 8  Missed heel to toe on steps 2, 3, 7, 9  Stopped walking after 10 steps.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Took 10 total steps.   It should be noted Donnally started walking with his right foot instead of his left foot.  Turn:Completed unsatisfactorily. Donnally spun around and stopped. Donnally had his feet shoulder-width apart, starting walking with his left foot in front of his right foot.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine):         Stepped off line on steps 1, 3, 5, and 8 (almost fell over).    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Missed heel to toe on step 6.        ONE LEG STAND (4/4 clues observed) Prior to Donnally performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Donnally was instructed to stand with his heels together, and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count aloud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. I asked Donnally if he understood the test and Donnally stated Yes.   Instructional Stage: It should be noted, Donnally swayed in place while the test was being demonstrated. Donnally also broke the instructional stage position, and placed his feet approximately shoulder width apart with his hands behind his back. Donnally was instructed to go back into the instructional stage position. Donnally then broke the instructional stage position a second time, by placing his feel approximately shoulder width apart. Donnally was then placed into the instructional stage position a third time.   Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: 1.) Swayed while balancing. 2.) Raised arms more than six (6) inches from his sides throughout test. 3.) Put foot down at 7 second mark. 4.) Began to hop after 6 seconds.    Seconds 11-20: 1.) Swayed while balancing. 2.) Raised arms more than six (6) inches from his sides throughout test. 3.) Hopped at the 19 second mark.   Seconds 21-30:  1.) Swayed while balancing.    Raised arms more than six (6) inches from his sides throughout test.   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Put foot down at the 21 second mark, and then kept foot down on ground the remainder of the timed period.    After completing the SFSTs, I then informed Donnally that I was requesting him to submit to a preliminary breath test. (*At 36:46 mark on body-worn camera video*). At one point while speaking with Donnally, he asked, Im going down. Donnally then advised he really didnt want to take the PBT, and I advised Donnally the test was optional. Donnally then stated If I take it, Im going to jail. Donnally at one point then mumbled to himself, Im so fucking fucked. Donnally then stated Here, give it to me. I then asked Donnally if he wanted to take the test, and he stated No, no. (*At 38:43 mark on body-worn camera video*) I then proceeded to place the PBT back in the assigned plastic case. Donnally then stated, Alright fuck it, Ill take the test. (*At 39:00 mark on body-worn camera video*) Donnally then advised he was consenting to submit to the PBT. I reminded Donnally a second time the test was optional, and he did not have to take the test. (*At 39:06 mark on body-worn camera video*) The PBT test was a result of a .24 BAC. (*At 40:12 mark on body-worn camera video*)  I arrested Donnally for driving under the influence of alcohol at 1926 hours. (*At 40:46 mark on body-worn camera video.*) While placing Donnally under arrest, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I also checked Donnallys mouth which revealed he had nothing in his mouth (*At 41:41 mark on body-worn camera video.*)   ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Donnally was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: *Slurred speech and slow, delayed movements and responses * Eyes glassy and bloodshot with a gazed look. * Extremely strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. * Admission to drinking several alcoholic beers prior to driving. * My observed signs of impairment as Donnally performed field sobriety tests. * PBT .24 BAC.  At approximately 1940 hours, I transported Donnally to the Frederick Barrack for processing. Donnally was seated in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. I arrived at the Frederick Barrack at approximately 2005 hours. While at the Frederick Barrack, Donnally was read the DR-15 Advice of Rights in the English language via the Maryland Motor Vehicle Administration (MVA) website certified audio version, and was also was provided an English copy to read (*At marker on body-worn camera video.*). At 2018 hours, consented to the Intoximeter test (*At 1:31:55 marker on body-worn camera video.*)  Once at the Frederick Barrack, Donnally signed the DR-15 Advise of Rights indicating he was agreeing to take the Intoximeter test. (*At 01:34:00 marker on body-worn camera video.*)   20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Donnally beginning with his arrest. A preliminary search of Donnally was conducted on scene, and it revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. I observed Donnally from the time of arrest, until the time he consented to the Intoximeter test, and he did not put anything in his mouth.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: ***.22 BrAC***   The specimen was collected at 2040 hours. The test was administered bySgt. Cain #0486, who is a certified Intoximeter operator in the State of Maryland.   Donnally was issued nine (9) traffic citations related to the traffic stop and DUI. At approximately 2131 hours, Donnally was picked up by his wife from the MSP Frederick Barrack. It should be noted during the interaction and processing of Donnally during the course of the investigation, he was polite and cooperative throughout the process.   All events occurred in Frederick County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 13:09:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/06/2023 13:09:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hopkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Douglas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6060</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Conklin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Gary</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5549</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>51</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Blumenauer</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6357</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 18:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 22:57:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 22:59:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 18:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 22:58:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 22:59:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 18:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 22:59:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 22:59:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16352</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 18:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16352</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 23:00:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 23:00:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15667</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 18:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15667</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 23:00:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 23:00:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 18:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 23:01:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 23:01:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 18:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 23:02:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 23:02:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16619</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 18:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16619</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 23:04:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 23:04:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508975</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16862</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 18:54:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16862</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 23:05:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 23:05:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>42</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 22:33:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>352450</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Donnally</LastName>
               <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Chirstopher</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/30/1980 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/14/2022 03:04:39</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D540</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Donnally</LastName>
               <FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Chirstopher</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/30/1980 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D540</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/14/2022 03:04:39</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>207</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Burlington</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Walkersville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21793</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.337088</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.493898</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>508</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>728</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3508</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 13:14:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 13:14:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 13:14:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 13:14:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/06/2023 13:14:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 22:58:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 22:58:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153649</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6357</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 22:32:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6357</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 22:32:09</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JF1SG63675H728095</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2005</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>SUBA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FOR</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRN</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRN</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3DZ6027</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>