<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-005334</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/11/2023 02:33:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/11/2023 02:33:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/11/2023 02:18:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/11/2023 02:18:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was stopped for a traffic violation and later arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 02:33:48</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4913</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 10:58:29</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>416 ROWE,ANNAPOLIS</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>558963</AddressId>
      <City>MDC102</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 02:33:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 03:48:58</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>558963</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Rowe Blvd @ Melvin Ave.</StreetName>
         <City>Annapolis</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21401</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-76.50559</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.98881</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 ROWE BLVD / 0-0 MELVIN AVE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/11/2023 02:33:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/11/2023 02:33:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/12/2023 04:54:43</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 02:33:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>J-16 is MVR and BWC equipped, this stop was recorded.  Defendant: Scott Kim Schill Date of Birth: 10/15/1989 Date of Arrest: 2/11/2023 Time of Arrest: 0230 hours MD SDX: MD-10272913823 DUI #: J-23-025  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:  * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police. * Apprehended more than 210 impaired drivers during my career with the Maryland State Police to date. * Attended the 2016 DUI Conference * Completed the 2017 DUI Institute at the University of Maryland. * Received the Smooth Operator Award * Received the Aggressive Drivers are Public Threats (ADAPT) Award. * Completed the Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Course (ARIDE).   VEHICLE IN MOTION  On February 11, 2023, at approximately 0218 hours, I (TFC Jeans #6483) was conducting stationary RADAR enforcement southbound Rowe Blvd and Herbert Sachs Dr., Annapolis, Anne Arundel County, Maryland. I was in the uniform of the day and operating unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle J-16. At that time, I was stopped in the left turn lane of southbound Rowe Blvd and was utilizing my agency issued Golden Eagle II Radar unit in the stationary mode using my front antenna. I observed a vehicle traveling northbound on Rowe Blvd coming toward my location and it appeared to have been exceeding the posted speed limit of 40 MPH. I activated the front antenna of the Radar unit and obtained a speed of 51 MPH in a posted 40 MPH zone. Once the vehicle passed mine, I pulled out behind the vehicle, which was bearing Maryland registration 1BE2848 on a gray Honda Civic, and activated my emergency to conduct a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle came to a stop on Rowe Blvd at Melvin Ave.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  After coming to a stop, I approached the Honda and made contact with the operator, and sole occupant, of the vehicle by a driver side approach. I stated to the male driver the stop was being audibly and visibly recorded and that he was stopped for his speed, 51 MPH in a posted 40 MPH zone. When asked if there was any reason for the speed, the driver stated he had just left from a gig downtown where he was playing music. When asked where he had been playing, he stated he was at Stan Joes, which is a bar downtown Annapolis. I requested his drivers license and registration card, which the driver was able to display to me. When asked if he lived at the current address on his license, the driver stated that he did. The driver was identified as Scott Kim Schill, W/M, DOB: 10/15/1989. While speaking with SCHILL, I smelled a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the interior of the vehicle and intentionally observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I asked SCHILL how much alcohol he had and he stated he only had one beer a few hours ago. I advised SCHILL to stay in the vehicle and he complied.  A routine check through the MVA database revealed that SCHILL was driving on a valid commercial drivers license and was not wanted. On my second approach, I asked SCHILL if he would exit his vehicle to complete Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, which he agreed to. While communicating with SCHILL by the front of his vehicle, I again smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of northbound Rowe Blvd prior to Melvin Ave. The weather was clear and approximately 48 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of my patrol vehicle headlights, spotlight, flashlight and street lamps. The shoulder was level and free from any debris. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. SCHILL appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any major visible injuries when walking from the vehicle.  I asked SCHILL the following questions:  Medical Conditions  None Injuries  None Medication  None  SCHILL was not wearing glasses during the time of the stop. SCHILL also had not fallen recently and had not spun around in circles recently.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from SCHILLS eyes. SCHILL was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. SCHILLS pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. SCHILL was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. SCHILL was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, Yes.   1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes.  SCHILL did not show signs of vertical nystagmus.  WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)  The walk and turn test was properly explained and demonstrated per the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. At the conclusion of the demonstration and explanation, SCHILL was asked if he understood the test, to which he stated yes.  Instructional Stage:  1.) Lost balance and did not place his right foot back in front of his left foot.  Walking Stage (1st Nine):  1.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 2, 5, 7 and 9. 2.) Stepped off line on step 9. Turn: Did not follow instructions and turned with both feet and did not leave his lead foot planted.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  1.) Stepped off line on steps 1 through 4 and 9. 2.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 1, 2 and 3.   ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues, Right foot and left foot raised)  The one leg stand test was properly explained and demonstrated per the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. At the conclusion of the demonstration and explanation, SCHILL was asked if he understood the test, to which he stated yes.   Instructional Stage:  1.) Nothing to report.  Balance and Count Stage:  1.) Hopped on count 4 to try and maintain his balance. 2.) Placed his foot down on counts 1004 and 1005. 3.) Swayed to maintain his balance on counts 1003 and 1004.  SCHILL had his right foot raised initially and when he began to hop, sway and place his foot down after count 1005, he switched to his left foot and started his count over again. Once SCHILL placed his foot down on the ground, he would stop counting and stand there. In a span of 30 seconds, SCHILL only counted to 1015 in a 30 second period.  While on scene, SCHILL was offered a preliminary breath test, which showed a result of .09 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe SCHILL was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from vehicle/breath. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot. * Admitting to consuming alcoholic beverages. * Clues during standardized field sobriety testing. * Positive preliminary testing  Due to the number of observations, I concluded SCHILL was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0230 hours, I placed SCHILL under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. SCHILL had gum in his mouth and he spit the gum out. A preliminary search of SCHILL was conducted on scene and there were no other foreign objects were in his mouth. SCHILL was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy. Once belted in the vehicle, I shut my passenger side door and walked around to the drivers side and got into my vehicle. When I did, I noticed the extremely strong odor of an alcoholic beverage had engulfed my patrol vehicle. That odor was not there prior to SCHILL getting into my vehicle. The vehicle was parked in the Grauls parking lot.  20 Minute Observation Period  A secondary search was conducted upon arrival at the Barrack and revealed that SCHILL had nothing in his mouth prior to the time he was asked to submit to the test. The DR-15 Advice of Rights was read to SCHILL on 2/11/2023 at 0250 hours. SCHILL was also provided a copy to read over at which time he elected to submit to an intoximeter test. The test was administered by Sgt. Jones of the Maryland State Police Annapolis Barrack and revealed SCHILL had a .09 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath in his system.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: .09 BrAC  SCHILL was given copies of all pertinent paperwork and was released to a sober rider. SCHILL was cooperative throughout the process and released.  All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 04:47:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/12/2023 00:58:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jeans</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6483</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494720</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 02:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 04:44:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 04:44:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 04:45:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:59</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368762</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Schill</LastName>
               <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kim</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/15/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.04769165E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 03:40:20</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Schill</LastName>
               <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kim</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/15/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.04769165E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S400</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 03:40:20</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2027</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Bank</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21231</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2714</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.588034</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.286673</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>472</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0246</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 04:45:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 04:45:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 04:45:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:54</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 04:44:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 04:44:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149708</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 04:47:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 04:47:13</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2HGFG3B51DH515480</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CIV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1BE2848</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>8</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>