<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002358</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/20/2023 00:18:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/20/2023 00:18:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/20/2023 00:03:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/20/2023 00:03:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 00:18:38</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4913</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 13:51:50</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>US-50 WB TO JENNIFER EB / WEST ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>681162</AddressId>
      <City>MDC102</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 00:18:39</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/20/2023 05:48:57</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>681162</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>Exit 22</StreetNumber>
         <StreetDirCode>W</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Rt. 50</StreetName>
         <City>Annapolis</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21401</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.539799</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.983807</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/20/2023 00:18:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/20/2023 00:18:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/23/2023 02:50:10</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 00:18:38</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:23:05</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Incident recorded on J-6s in-car-camera and Body-worn camera. DUI NARRATIVE Nathaniel Hitch 7051  DUI INFORMATION Defendant:MANLEY, TIFFANY NICOLE Date of Birth: 01/19/1994 License Number: MD - M540793630052 Date of Arrest: 01/20/2023 CC#: 22-MSP-002358 (Annapolis Barrack) Time of arrest: 0018 hours.  Training and Awards Recipient of the Maryland Highway Safety Offices DUI award for 2021. Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Trained in administering the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Trained in A.R.I.D.E. (Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Attended the MSP Enhanced DUI class provided through the Maryland State Police SPIDRE Team. Attendee of the 2022 Ocean City DUI conference.  Vehicle in Motion (Phase 1)  On 01/20/2023 at approximately 0002 hours, I TFC. Hitch #7051 was on duty in the Annapolis area on Route 50 westbound in the area of the 24 mile marker. At that time, I observed a white hatchback vehicle traveling ahead of my location that appeared to be exceeding the posted speed limite of 55 miles per hour. I activated the front antenna of my Golden Eagle II RADAR in the front-facing mode and obtained a speed reading of 80 miles per hour in lane 3. The Hatchback was the only vehicle within my RADARs field of influence. A Function test was conducted on my RADAR equipment before and after use and was found to be in working order.  The vehicle was a Subaru Crosstrek bearing a Maryland registration plate of 8CE8948. The Crosstrek activated its turn signal and moved into lane 2. However, the vehicle left its turn signal on after completing its turn. I conducted a traffic stop on the Crosstrek, it came to a stop on the right shoulder of Rt. 50 at exit 22.  Personal Contact (Phase 2)  I made contact with the driver and front seat passenger of the Crosstrek. The driver was later identified by her Maryland Drivers license as MANLEY, TIFFANY NICOLE (MD - M540793630052; DOB - 01/19/1994; White Female). The passenger was later identified by his Maryland license as MANLEY Jr., WILLIAM JOSEPH (MD - M540887441770; DOB  10/06/1999; White Male).  Immediately upon approaching the vehicle, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of Tiffanys vehicle. I advised Tiffany of the reason for the traffic stop and requested her drivers license and vehicle registration, Tiffany had her drivers license ready for me, but had difficulty locating her vehicle registration. I asked Tiffany where she was coming from and she stated she was coming from her birthday dinner. I asked Tiffany how much she had to drink that night, Tiffany replied hesitantly oh no, no, I was not drinking. I asked her if she had drank at all, she stated no, and looked away. As I spoke with Tiffany, I observed her eyes were watery and slightly bloodshot. When I asked a third time, advising the occupants I could smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from the vehicle, William Manley stated that he had been drinking that night.  I returned to my patrol vehicle to complete routine MVA/METERS checks. I also requested a secondary unit respond to my scene. Tpr. Fuller #7354 responded to my scene to assist.  I walked back to the Crosstrek and requested Tiffany step out of her vehicle, which she complied. As Tiffany got out of her vehicle she used her car door to help herself out of her vehicle. I then had Tiffany walk to the front of her vehicle. As Tiffany walked to the front of her vehicle, the odor of an alcoholic beverage became stronger and emanated off her breath and person. Once in front of the vehicle, I advised Tiffany that I had her step out of her car due to the odor of an alcoholic beverage. I asked tiffany again if she had drank that night. Tiffany stated she had not drank, but told me some of the details of her day, including a dinner earlier in the evening. I then asked Tiffany if she had drank with her family at the dinner, Tiffany stated uh, so we had dinner at 6, and I had a drink, yeah.  Due to the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating off of Tiffanys person, her admission to drinking, her using her car door to step out, her trouble finding her vehicle registration, and her driving with her turn signal on, I suspected Tiffany may be under the influence of an intoxicating substance. I requested Tiffany perform to the Standardized Field Sobriety Testing. Tiffany submitted to the SFST. Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3) The evaluation was performed in front of Tiffanys (from here referred to as Manley) vehicle. The roadway was lit by my flashlight and my vehicles front facing lights. The evaluation was performed on a dry and debris-free surface. My front-facing emergency lights were deactivated for the duration of the field sobriety testing. I asked Manley the basic medical questions as they relate to the Standardized Field Sobriety Test. Her answers are located in the below text: Are you wearing contacts  No. Do you have any head, neck, back, or leg injuries  I have scoliosis. I have a double curve (Manley advised it did not impair her). Do you take any medications  No. Do you have any medical issues I need to be aware of  No.  The weather conditions were cold and wet. Manley appeared to be in good physical condition.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (Not completed) The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Manleys pupils were equal in size and no resting Nystagmus was observed. I observed equal tracking in both eyes. Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes. Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus  not observed.  Walk and Turn (3/8 clues observed)  The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Manley affirmed that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Manley took off her heels for the duration of the test. Instructional Phase:  Unable to maintain balance. Manley split her feet apart repeatedly, even after I advised her to stay in the instructional position. First 9 Steps:  Nothing to report. Turn:  Incorrect turn: Swiveled around by planting both feet and rotating on the balls of both feet. Second 9 Steps  Incorrect number of steps. 8. (Manley started counting her steps before actually taking a first step.  One Leg Stand (0/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Manley affirmed that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Manley raised her left leg. Manleys results are as follows: First 10 seconds  Nothing to report Second 10 seconds  Nothing to report Third 10 seconds Nothing to report  PBT Test  Refused  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Manley was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol. *Odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. *Watery and bloodshot eyes. *Admission to drinking. *Observed signs of impairment based off SFST results.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: 0019 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULTS: Refused.  CHARGES Charges are attached to report.   Manleywas placed under arrest at approximately 0018 hours and she was transported to the Annapolis Barrack. While at the barrack, Manleywas read a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights at 0044hours using the online DR-15 recording. Manley advised she understood her rights and refused the intoximeter test. Manley was charged with driving Under the Influence of Alcohol under citation number 2490VP2. Manley was released to a sober driver (MANLEY, WILLIAM JOSEPH; MD - M540887441136) at 0104 hours.  All events occurred in Anne Arundel County Maryland.  Case Closed by Arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 05:49:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/22/2023 23:53:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fuller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hitch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathaniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7051</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gerber</LastName>
            <FirstName>Elix</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5226</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hitch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathaniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7051</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hitch</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nathaniel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7051</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>491741</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/20/2023 00:18:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 04:35:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/20/2023 04:43:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 04:35:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:07</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>366662</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Manley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tiffany</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/19/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/20/2023 04:10:34</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M540</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Manley</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tiffany</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nicole</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/19/1994 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M540</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/20/2023 04:10:34</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1006</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Liberty Nest</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Davidsonville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21035</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.611214</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.976002</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>995</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5842</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 04:44:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:39</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 04:44:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:39</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 04:44:01</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:39</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 04:42:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/20/2023 04:42:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148850</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7051</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/20/2023 04:46:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7051</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/20/2023 04:46:01</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/20/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JF2GPADC4G8270687</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2016</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>SUBA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CROSSTREK</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4H</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>WHI</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8CE8948</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>5</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>