<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-005316</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/11/2023 00:47:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/11/2023 00:47:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/11/2023 00:34:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/11/2023 00:34:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driver was stopped for a traffic violation and later arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 00:47:50</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4913</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/13/2023 11:00:40</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>322 ROWE,ANNAPOLIS</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>683875</AddressId>
      <City>MDC102</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 00:47:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 05:09:56</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>683875</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Forbes St. @ Melvin Ave.</StreetName>
         <City>Annapolis</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21401</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/11/2023 00:47:48</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/11/2023 00:47:48</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>59</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/12/2023 04:53:38</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 00:47:50</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>J-16 equipped with a mobile recording device and BWC, this stop was recorded.  Defendant: Tyjay Simone-Ibrion Sparrow Date of Birth: 3/20/2002 Date of Arrest: 2/11/2023 Time of Arrest: 0046 hours MD SDX: S-160-809-766-227 DUI #: J-23-024  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:  * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police. * Apprehended more than 210 impaired drivers during my career with the Maryland State Police to date. * Attended the 2016 DUI Conference * Completed the 2017 DUI Institute at the University of Maryland. * Received the Smooth Operator Award * Received the Aggressive Drivers are Public Threats (ADAPT) Award. * Completed the Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Course (ARIDE).  *UNDER 21 YEARS OF AGE*  Narrative:  Vehicle in Motion (Phase 1)  On February 11, 2023 at approximately 0034 hours, I (Tpr. Jeans #6483) was conducting stationary speed enforcement on Rowe Blvd at Herbert Sachs Dr., Annapolis, Anne Arundel County, Maryland in unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle J-16. At that time, I was in the uniform of the day and utilizing my agency issued Golden Eagle II RADAR unit in the stationary mode. At that time, I observed a vehicle coming toward my location and it appeared to have been exceeding the posted speed limit of 40 MPH. I activated the front antenna of my Golden Eagle II RADAR unit and obtained a speed of 50 MPH in a posted 40 MPH zone. I am certified by the Maryland State Police to operate RADAR and the unit was tested before and after my shift and found to be functioning properly. I pulled out behind the vehicle, which was observed to be a black Audi bearing Maryland Registration T1202188. I activated my emergency equipment and the vehicle made a right onto Melvin Ave. before turning right onto Forbes St. and coming to a stop.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I made contact with the operator of the vehicle by making a driver side approach. I stated to the female driver the stop was being audibly and visibly recorded. I stated to the female driver the reason for the stop was for her speed and requested her Drivers License and Registration card. I asked the driver if there was any reason for her speed and she shook her head no. I then asked where she was coming from and she stated downtown. The driver was identified as Tyjay Simone-Ibrion Sparrow, B/F, DOM: 3/20/2002. While speaking with the driver, I detected the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the drivers breath and person and intentionally observed the drivers eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I then asked SPARROW how much alcohol she had prior to driving and she originally stated she had nothing. I then asked SPARROW if she took a breath test if she would blow zeros and SPARROW just looked straight forward and did not answer. I then advised SPARROW I asked because I could smell the alcohol and asked again how much alcohol she had and SPARROW stated a jello shot. I returned to my patrol car and requested another unit for Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. A routine check through the MVA database revealed SPARROW had a valid license and was not wanted.  When another unit arrived on-scene, I made my second approach and asked SPARROW if she would perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, to which she agreed. SPARROW exited her vehicle and walked to the front of her vehicle like she was instructed to do. While communicating with SPARROW by the front of my vehicle, I again detected the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person and observed her eyes to be bloodshot and glassy.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed on Forbes St. at Melvin Ave. The weather was clear and approximately 50 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of patrol vehicle headlights, spotlight, street lamps and my flashlight. The roadway was level and free from any debris. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. SPARROW appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any major visible injuries when walking from the vehicle.  I asked SPARROW the following questions:  Medical Conditions  None Injuries  None. Medication  None Had not fallen or hit their head.  SPARROW was not wearing glasses at the time of the stop. SPARROW also had not spun around in circles or hit her head recently.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (4/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from SPARROWS eyes. SPARROW was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. SPARROWS pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. SPARROW was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. SPARROW was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, Yes.   1.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes 2.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes.  SPARROW did not show signs of vertical nystagmus.  WALK AND TURN (3/8 clues observed)  The walk and turn test was properly explained and demonstrated per the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. At the conclusion of the demonstration and explanation, SPARROW was asked if she understood the test, to which she stated yes.  Instructional Stage:  1.) Lost balance  Walking Stage (1st Nine):  1.) Missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 6 through 9. 2.) Stopped walking on step 9 and ask if she had to turn around.  Turn: Completed satisfactorily.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  1.) SPARROW missed heel to toe by more than an inch on steps 1 through 7.  ONE LEG STAND (2 out of 4 clues observed, right foot raised)  The one leg stand test was properly explained and demonstrated per the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. At the conclusion of the demonstration and explanation, SPARROW was asked if she understood the test, to which she stated yes.  Instructional Stage:  Nothing to report  Balance and Count Stage: SPARROW would count up but when she placed her foot down on the ground, she would start her count over at 1001.  1.) Placed her foot down on counts 1003, 1005 and 1005. 2.) Hopped to try and maintain her balance on counts 1004, 1005, and 1005.  Due to SPARROW placing her foot down on the ground, hopping and saying it was cold, SPARROW only counted up to 1005 three times for a total of 15 seconds in a 30 second period.  A preliminary breath test was offered to SPARROW and revealed SPARROW had an alcohol concentration of .05 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. When I asked SPARROW how much alcohol should be in her system, she stated zero.  ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe SPARROW was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:   * Odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from vehicle/breath. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot. * Admitting to consuming alcoholic beverages. * Clues during standardized field sobriety testing. * Positive preliminary testing. * Under 21 years of age.  Due to the number of observations, and the fact SPARROW was under the age of 21, I concluded SPARROW was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. When I told SPARROW to put the tongue piercing in her pocket, she asked if her friends could just drive her home. At approximately 0046 hours, I placed SPARROW under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. Prior to the preliminary breath test, SPARROW had a tongue piercing in her mouth, which she removed. A preliminary search of SPARROW was conducted on scene and revealed no other foreign materials were in her mouth. SPARROW was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy. Once SPARROW was placed into my patrol vehicle, I shut the door. When I walked around to get into my vehicle, the moderate odor of an alcoholic beverage had filled my vehicle. That smell was not there prior to me arresting SPARROW. SPARROW was transported to the Maryland State Police Annapolis Barrack for processing. A passenger in the vehicle who was 21 and not under the influence took possession of the vehicle.  20 Minute Observation Period  A secondary search was conducted upon arrival at the Barrack and revealed that SPARROW did not have anything in her mouth prior to being asked to submit to a breath test. The DR-15 Advice of Rights was read to SPARROW on 2/11/2023 at 0124 hours. SPARROW was also provided a copy to read over. Ultimately, SPARROW refused to submit to an intoximeter test.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: Refusal  SPARROW was given copies of all pertinent paperwork and was released to a sober driver. SPARROW was polite and cooperative throughout the process.  All events occurred in Anne Arundel County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 05:13:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/12/2023 00:20:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jones</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mujaihid</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1788</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jeans</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kyle</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6483</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494702</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 00:34:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 05:10:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 05:10:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>494702</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16352</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/11/2023 00:34:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16352</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 05:11:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 05:11:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>20</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 05:12:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:34</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>368767</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Sparrow</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyjay</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Simone-Ibrion</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/20/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16636063E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 05:00:03</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S160</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Sparrow</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tyjay</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Simone-Ibrion</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/20/2002 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16636063E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S160</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 05:00:03</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3386</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Riva</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Davidsonville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21035</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1703</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.600675</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.944743</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>667</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>289</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8522</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 05:12:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:44</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 05:12:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:44</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 05:12:18</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:44</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 05:10:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 05:10:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>149710</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6483</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/11/2023 05:13:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6483</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/11/2023 05:13:01</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>02/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WAUAUGFF5H1048576</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>AUDI</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>A3</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>T1202188</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>