<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-021272</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/13/2023 21:47:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/13/2023 21:47:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/13/2023 21:33:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/13/2023 21:33:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 21:47:17</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/21/2023 16:54:03</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY/ FRIENDSHIP RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>530809</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 21:47:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 23:29:21</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>530809</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.190035</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.343374</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 / FRIENDSHIP</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>PULLING INTO THE EXXON OFF OF 50 / FRIENDSHIP</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10699-10715 OCEAN GTWY / 9982-9985 FRIENDSHIP RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10623-10697 OCEAN GTWY / 9982-9985 FRIENDSHIP RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>10701-10729 OCEAN GTWY / 0-0 FRIENDSHIP RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/13/2023 21:47:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/13/2023 21:47:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/21/2023 00:10:01</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 21:47:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/21/2023 00:10:01</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> text-align:center"&gt;SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER - 4TH DUI  MVR STATEMENT  This incident was audibly and visually recorded on MVR and BWC assigned to V-23.  DEFENDANT  John Joseph Vogel III DOB: 07/06/1973 DE SDX: 1778056 ARREST: 06/13/2023 at 2144 hours  DUI # 23 96 164  NARRATIVE VEHICLE IN MOTION: PHASE 1  On 06/13/2023 at approximately 2133 hours, I was on patrol in the area of Eastbound Route 50 and Seahawk Road looking for a BOLO vehicle described as a white Town and Country minivan displaying Delaware registration PC26453. The Town and Country was described by callers as reckless operation, driving all over the roadway, and driving in the grass median dividing Eastbound and Westbound lanes on Route 50. I caught up to the vehicle at a red light Eastbound Route 50 and Samuel Bowen Boulevard. I identified the vehicle correctly to match the lookout due to the color, make, model, and license plate. Once the light turned green, I observed the Town and Country have difficulty maintaining their lane. The vehicle drifted towards the dotted white line and almost into lane 1, then jerked to correct and stay in lane 2. The vehicle then drifted to the right shoulder and crossed the white fog line. At this time I activated my emergency equipment to initiate a traffic stop due to the multiple calls on the vehicle being operated in an unsafe manner, the observed difficulty maintaining a lane, and the presence of other vehicles around making it a high risk for a crash to occur.  At 2315 hours, I contacted the caller listed on the card, Joanna (410-726-5804) and left a voicemail requesting a callback at the Berlin Barrack. Joanna returned my call and agreed to complete a witness statement. Joanna emailed her written statement. Joanna advised in her statement that she called 911 because of the danger the driver posed to her family as well as other vehicles on the roadway. Joanna also wrote that she witnessed the driver stop at the traffic light located at Route 50 and Friendship Road, open the driver side door and vomit and urinate on himself. The email is attached in this report.  PERSONAL CONTACT: PHASE 2  I approached the vehicle on the driver side, the driver window was already down and immediately upon walking up to the open window I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage. The driver was smiling and had blood shot and glassy eyes. I introduced myself, stated my ID number, advised the driver and sole occupant of the vehicle he was being audibly and visually recorded, and stated my reasons for the stop. The driver nodded in agreement when I advised the reasons for the stop, including him driving all over the roadway. I also noted that the driver had no pants on, only boxers. I asked the driver if he had his license and registration and he advised he did, and looked to his passenger seat/center console area, then back at me. I asked if he could retrieve his license and registration, and the driver reached into his front passenger seat and grabbed his pants. While he was attempting to locate his ID in his pants, I asked the driver where he was coming from, to which he replied Im a teacher.I asked the driver what happened with his pants, and he stated I took them off. I asked why he had taken his pants off and he advised he was done talking. The driver then advised he was a teacher, it was the last day of school, and he and some co-workers had gone to a party. The driver then located his wallet and attempted to hand me the entire wallet, stating There you go sir. The driver had difficulty locating his ID inside his pallet, pulled out a credit card and flipped through different parts of the wallet before locating his ID. The driver was identified by his Delaware License as John Joseph Vogel III (W/M, DOB 07/06/1973, DE SDX 1778056). I asked Vogel how many alcoholic drinks he had had that night and where he as coming from. Vogel advised he was not going to keep talking, and that he was going to refuse all tests.  I asked Vogel to step out of the vehicle and put his pants on. Vogel had to hold onto the vehicle to maintain his balance stepping out of the vehicle. I asked Vogel to put his pants on. Vogel had difficulty putting his pants on, as he lost his balance, had fumbling movements to get his pants right side out, and was unable to multitask by talking and putting pants on at the same time. Vogel stated upon stepping out of his vehicle Im busted, I got it. I wanted to point out, I wont take any tests or anything. I asked to confirm that he was advising he did not want to submit to any SFSTs, and Vogel stated Yes sir, is that fine. Vogel then attempted to put his pants on and after almost falling over, grabbed onto TFC Philips for help. Vogel stated again Im drunk, okay, you got me.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING: PHASE 3  Vogel refused all tests. After Vogel had gotten his pants back on, I asked an additional time if he would like to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests and Vogel again declined to submit to any tests.  ARREST AND TRANSPORT  Vogel was placed under arrest for DUI at 2141 hours. A search incident to arrest was completed yielding no weapons or contraband, however Vogel had wet pants from urinating on them. Once placed in handcuffs, Vogel entered a hyper and excited state. Vogel began talking faster and appeared very anxious. Vogel stated Dude Im a school teacher, I fucked up. I dont have no drugs, I have nothing. I went to fucking EVO, it was the end of the year... Vogel then tried to walk away and back towards his car. I advised Vogel he was not leaving at this time and that he was okay. Vogel then yelled Put me in jail! Put me in jail! Just put me where you gotta put me dude! My wifes gonna fucking kill me, no offense, one, two, three. four, of whatever you guys are, my wife is gonna fuck me up more than anything you can do! I tried to calm Vogel down by explaining none of us were going to hurt him, and that I just needed him to get into my patrol vehicle so that I could transport him to the Barrack. Ultimately, Vogel did get into the vehicle. Vogel advised he was prescribed Vyvanse, but did not wish to advise if he had taken any that day or with drinking. Vogel also advised he had taken shots at the bar. Vogel continued yelling and using profanity.  Vogel was transported to the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack without incident. During transport Vogel stated Seriously, I drank too much after school. Vogel then advised he was going to stop talking because everything was being recorded. Vogel then asked my name again, and after I advised Trooper Furness he asked what I did for work. Vogel became emotional talking about his five-year-old daughter who had passed away due to terminal cancer in 2011. When we pulled into the Berlin Barrack parking lot, Vogel began to get nervous again. I had to remind Vogel the location we were going to was the Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack. Vogel asked Youre a Statie? Thats awesome! Fuckin book the shit outta me dude!  Walking into the Barrack, Vogel advised I smoke a shitload of weed but advised he had not smoked any marijuana yet that day, as he was waiting until he got home before bed. Vogel was also concerned walking into the barrack because he thought Sgt. Harper looked angry with him, despite Sgt. Harper simply standing holding the door open for us to enter.  PAPERWORK AND RELEASE  At the Barrack, Vogel was read his DR-15 Advice of Rights, and also supplied a copy of his own to follow along with. Vogel talked over me the entire time I was reading his DR-15. Vogel yelled profanity, and expressed his dissatisfaction with the fact he was being arrested, stating that there were worse crimes being committed. Vogel interrupted me to ask what the quickest way to get released was, and I advised him that was to stop interrupting and let me finish reading the form. Vogel continued to be disruptive, complain, use profanity, state I did it, I did it all. Ill sign it. You got me, Im a faking school teacher who drives to Salisbury for a bunch of black kids who wont come teach them. And here I am, coming from Bethany Beach, to teach the black kids. Vogel then uttered something indistinguishable before continuing Fuck. Guess what. At the end of the year, I fucking celebrate? And you know its fucking wrong. Just stop okay, I did it, I did it all. Vogel continued on this rant as I was reading his DR-15, and attempted to take the DR-15 sheet I was reading from out of my hands. Vogel would switch emotionally between angry and almost crying during his DR-15. Vogel whined Shut up dude, then apologized for being rude, then advised he was again tired of listening to the form and stood up to face away from me and instead stare at the wall. After I completed reading the form, I advised Vogel he was going to sign the form listing if he was submitting ot or refusing the Intoximeter test, as well as acknowledgement that I had read him the DR-15 and he had been given a copy to read along with. Vogel stated I aint signing shit dude. Vogel muttered more incoherent statements before stating And Im sorry, I apologize, you are awesome, this guys awesome (Sgt. Harper), youre awesome. Put me in prison.  Vogel was given and explained all pertinent copies of his paperwork including the following citations:  TA 21 902 a1i - DUI TA 21 902 b1i - DWI TA 21 902 c1i - DWI Drugs + Alcohol Cannot Drive Safely TA 21 901.1 b - Negligent Driving TA 21 901.1 a - Reckless Driving TA 21 201 a1 - Fail to Obey Properly Placed Traffic Control Device Instructions TA 21 301 a - Fail to Drive Vehicle on Right Half of Roadway TA 13 409 b - Fail to Display Registration Card  Vogel remained loud and disruptive during processing. Vogel refused to give a name or phone number for his wife or any contacts who could come pick him up from the Barrack. We were able to get in contact with his wife without his help. While completing his paper work, Vogel made many statements admitting he was driving under the influence, as well as about his work, and his child, and the arrest, including the following statements:  So please, can someone tell my principal I cannot be at work tomorrow, and maybe you can go teach the black kids. I aint one of those fucking hood rats from Salisbury like the kids Im teaching. Way to go officer, you got me! Way to go on focusing all your time tonight on a guy who drank too much at EVO! WOOOOOO! While Jamal Purnell forms a gang! Stabs people. Give me some charges alright, give me all of them! You know what I fucking do? Smoke a lot of weed and drink a little. Vogel asked Sgt. Harper what he does for work, and Sgt. Harper advised again that we were State Troopers currently at work. I will give you Justin Purnell. Hey! You know what Justin Purnell does? Sell coke! And heroin. (Vogel loudly gasped and clapped) But hey you got me! I am 100% being a dick and an asshole, and you dont deserve it, but its the alcohol that does it! Vogel asked What did I come in at? in reference to what his Intoximeter reading was. I informed Vogel that he had refused to take the Intoximeter test.  Vogel was walked out to the lobby to wait for his wife to arrive to dive him home. A few minutes later, Vogel was escorted into a holding cell until his wifes arrival as he refused to wait inside the lobby and attempted to leave the barrack by himself on foot. Once his wife arrive, Vogel was released to her custody without incident.  Due to the facts above, I request this case be closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7275</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 23:37:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7275</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/21/2023 00:01:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pinto iii</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7212</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phillips</LastName>
            <FirstName>Riley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7211</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Drew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1464</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Furness</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7275</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>510707</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/13/2023 21:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7275</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 23:35:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7275</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 23:35:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>49</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7275</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 23:36:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>379776</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Vogel</LastName>
               <FirstName>John</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Joseph</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/06/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>06/13/2023 23:22:04</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>V240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Vogel</LastName>
               <FirstName>John</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Joseph</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/06/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>III</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>V240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/13/2023 23:22:04</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>8</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>jordyn</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>ocean view</City>
               <StateCode>DE</StateCode>
               <Zip5>19970</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>484</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>885</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8264</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7275</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 23:36:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7275</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 23:36:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7275</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 23:35:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7275</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 23:35:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154102</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/13/2023 21:47:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/13/2023 21:47:19</UpdatorDate>
         <StatusCode>8</StatusCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>