<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-032633</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/17/2023 03:40:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/17/2023 03:40:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/17/2023 03:20:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/17/2023 03:20:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI 23- 154 - TaA21 902 2 : (Driving, Attempting To Drive) Vehicle While Under the Influence Of Alcohol Per Se/ Wyatt, Kurtis</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/17/2023 03:40:57</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/19/2023 11:32:15</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>1771</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/17/2023 03:40:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/11/2023 01:19:08</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>1771</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1400</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Baltimore</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westminster</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21157</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.945158</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.548752</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>CARROLL COUNTY LANDFILL</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>AREA OF CARROLL COUNTY LANDFILL</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/17/2023 03:40:54</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/17/2023 03:40:54</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/11/2023 02:35:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/17/2023 03:40:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:51</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>23-MSP-032633   G-16 is equipped with a mobile recording device/ This incident was captured by TFC. Loudins Body Worn Camera. (This report is a summary of this incident. See the dash and body worn camera footage for the complete incident)  Incident:  DUI 23-154/ TA 21-902 b2i: Driving while impaired by alcohol while transporting minors.  Incident Date/time:   September 17, 2023, at approximately 0321 hours.  Incident location:   1023 Baltimore Blvd, Westminster Carroll County Maryland Road. (Sheetz)  Attachments:  Intoximeter worksheet DR 15 Advise of rights DR. 15A MSP for 33- Result for test for alcohol concentration Citations Notice to Appear Copy of Drivers license MVA printouts   Qualifications:  Maryland State Police Academy (June 2014) I am trained to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through NHTSA and the Maryland State Police. A.R.I.D.E.: Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (November 2017)  Accused:   Wyatt,Kurtis Mark  DOB: 07/25/1985  Address: 270 n Cranberry Road, Westminster Maryland 21157   Vehicle in Motion (Phase I)   On September 17, 2023, at approximately 0321 hours, M/Tpr Fair advised that he observed a vehicle that appeared disabled in the roadway on MD Route 140 at the landfill in Westminster Carroll County Maryland. I responded immediately from the Westminster Barrack to assist. While traveling eastbound on MD Route 140, I observed a blue Jeep with its flashers on, that appeared to be stopped in lane two of MD Route 140 westbound.  I used the cross-over just east of the landfill to turn around and when I came over the hill I observed the vehicle traveling westbound on MD Route 140. I observed the vehicle weaving in lane one and then changed lanes from lane one to the left turn lane without signaling. When the vehicle turned to go eastbound on MD Route 140, I observed a cell phone in the right hand of the driver, and it appeared as though he was talking to someone on speaker. The vehicle failed to use its turn signal when it turned right into the Sheetz parking lot located at 1023 Baltimore Blvd, in Westminster Carroll County Maryland. The vehicle then pulled into a parking spot and I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle.  Contact (Phase II)   I made contact with the driver at the driver side window and identified myself. I explained the reason for the traffic stop to the driver and advised that driver the traffic stop was being recorded. I also observed that the driver parked in a parking spot that states, no trucks or SUVs and was for passenger cars only. The driver advised that he was looking for his husband. I asked if his husband was in danger, and he advised that he was not. The drivers speech was slurred, and his eyes were bloodshot and glassy.   I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from the vehicle and when I asked the driver if he had anything to drink, he advised  I did, I did earlier at a friends house. I requested the driver exit the vehicle and when he did he lost his balance and nearly fell backwards, catching himself before falling. I continued to detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his person and requested he perform Standardized Field Sobriety, to which he agreed.   Pre Arrest Screening:  Mr. Wyatt was asked the following questions:  About how long ago was your last drink? He advised about an hour or two ago. What do you typically drink? Mixed drinks.  Glasses or contacts? Yes. He advised he was wearing them. Gum, fake teeth or dentures? No Medications? Yes, a few. He did not specify Injuries? None  He swayed to his front and back while speaking with me.   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN)-6/6clues observed  I instructed Mr. Wyatt to look at the tip of my pen. I then requested Mr. Wyatt stand with his feet together and to place his hands down at his side. I advised Mr. Wyatt that I was going to shine my flash light on the side of his face, to see his eyes. I advised him that I was going to check his eyes and I asked Mr. Wyatt if he could see my pen, and he advised that he could. I advised him to follow the tip of my pen with his eyes and not to move his head. I observed Mr. Wyatt swayed to his front and back.    Resting Nystagmus- not present   Equal Pupil size-both pupils were the same size   Equal tracking-both eyes displayed equal tracking   Lack of Smooth Pursuit-Present  Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation-Present   Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees-Present   Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was observed.   Walk and Turn (WAT)- 6/8clues observed  I asked Mr. Wyatt to use the parking spot white line to help him with this test. The area was well lit and free from debris. I asked Mr. Wyatt to place his left foot on that line and to place his right foot in front of it, heel touching toe and to remain in that position, until I told him to begin. He got into position and began walking while I was trying to explain the test. I asked him to get back into position. He had difficulty maintaining the instructional position and then stood with two feet together while I finished explaining the test.   Mr. Wyatt was advised that he would be taking nine heel touching toe steps on the line, turn while keeping his lead foot planted and to take nine more heel touching toe steps. He was told to keep his hands down at his side, look at his feet and to count his steps out loud. He was then advised that if he stepped off-line at any point, he was to get back into position and to continue the test until completed. He advised that he understood the test.  Instructional phase:   1.)Starts too soon  2.)Cannot keep balance  Walking phase:  3.). Missed heel to toe contact - Mr. Wyatt Missed heel to toe contact on steps three, four, five, six, eight and nine of the first nine steps. Mr. Wyatt missed heel touching toe contact on all steps of the second nine (he took ten) steps. The second nine steps were large steps (nearly a foot). 4). Improper turn  Turned around with feet together, not as demonstrated. 5.) Stops walking-Turned and stared at me after the turn 6.) Improper number of steps - Mr. Wyatt took ten total steps.  One Leg Stand (OLS)- 2/4clues observed   Mr. Wyatt was requested to place his feet together and to keep his hands down at his side. I advised Mr. Wyatt that when he was told to begin, he would raise, whichever foot he chooses, approximately six inches off the ground, keep his legs straight, point his toe and would be counting in one thousand. He was advised that if he put his foot down, he was to pick it back up and continue where he left off, until I advised him to stop. Mr. Wyatt acknowledged that he understood. He raised his right foot and balance on his left (He was wearing sneakers). He then said that he had a question but had difficulty forming a sentence, and again I noticed his speech was slurred.   1). Swayed - Mr. Wyatt to his left and right - Within the first 10 seconds. Approximately on second five. 2). Put foot down  Mr. Wyatt put his foot down within approximately five seconds, raised his foot again and put it down again, crossing his right foot in front of his left.  It should be noted that Mr. Wyatt had difficulty counting properly. Three thousand, four One thousand four, five one thousand, four one thousand. Losing track of where he was while counting.   Mr. Wyatt was offered the preliminary breath test, and he refused   Mr. Wyatt was placed under arrest at approximately 0340 hours for driving under the influence of alcohol. I observed two drinking containers in the middle console. When I picked up the open one, it had liquid inside and I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from it. Mr. Wyatt advised that it was not his, and it was Tennessee Honey, which is an alcoholic cocktail.   Mr.Wyatt was transported to the Maryland State Police Westminster barrack. Mr. Wyatt was read his Dr-15 Advice of Rights at approximately 0444 hours, and he elected to take the breath test. Cpl. Eyler #0670, provided Mr. Wyatt with instructions and conducted the test. Mr. Wyatt provided a breath sample of .17 Breath alcohol content per 210 Milliliters of breath.   Mr. Wyatt was charged with the following charges:  TA 21 1124.2 d2- Driver using hands to use handheld telephone device while motor vehicle is in motion.  TA 21-1003 aa- parking where prohibited by official sign.  TA 21 901.1 (b) Negligent driving vehicle in careless and imprudent manner endangering property, life and person.  TA 21 901 (a) Reckless driving vehicle in a wanton and willful disregard for safety of persons and property  TA 903 c Driver consuming alcoholic beverage in passenger area of motor vehicle on highway.  TA 21 902(b1i) Driving while impaired by alcohol.  TA 21 902 b1i- Driving under the influence of alcohol.  TA 21 902 a1ii- Driving under the influence of alcohol per se.   Mr. Wyatt signed and was provided a copy of the District Court Notice to Appear Form, Notice to Counsel, Dr- 15 Advice of Rights, DR 15 a, MSP form 33 and the citations listed above. He was picked up by his husband from the Westminster Barracks.  Mr. Wyatt was polite and cooperative.  All events occurred in Carroll County Maryland.  Case closed on arrest </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6490</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 22:30:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6490</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/11/2023 01:17:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gibson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cameron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5039</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Loudin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6490</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522086</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/17/2023 03:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6490</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 21:09:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6490</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 21:09:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6490</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 21:22:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/11/2023 01:19:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389579</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Wyatt</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kurtis</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kurtis</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/25/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/04/2023 21:21:13</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K632</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Wyatt</LastName>
               <FirstName>Kurtis</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Kurtis</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/25/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>W300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K632</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/04/2023 21:21:13</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>270</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>N</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Cranberry</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Westminster</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21157</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.976254</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.583201</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6490</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 21:22:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6490</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 21:22:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6490</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 21:09:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6490</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 21:09:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157741</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6490</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/04/2023 21:32:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6490</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 21:32:02</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/04/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2023</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2ET6637</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>