<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-018678</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/25/2023 21:00:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/25/2023 21:00:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/25/2023 20:22:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/25/2023 20:22:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Motor vehicle collision resulting in DUI Arrest</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 21:00:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 17:15:57</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OL @ NPRTHPOINT</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>695271</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 21:00:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/12/2023 07:51:59</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>695271</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Perring Pkwy</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/25/2023 21:00:40</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/25/2023 21:00:40</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 10:49:51</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/25/2023 21:00:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 19:56:06</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The incident was visually and audio recorded.  DEFENDANT: Susan Irene Heuer Date of Birth: 06/22/1984 Date of Arrest: 05/25/2023 DUI #: 23-325 (Golden Ring Barrack, Baltimore County) Time of Arrest: 2103 Hours Minor in the vehicle: No Colorado Drivers License: 171827602   Certificate and Training: I am a certified police officer in the State of Maryland with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with live participants at the Maryland State Police Academy. Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On Thursday, May 25th, at approximately 2023 hours, I, Tpr. Muhammad #7282 of the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack operating marked patrol vehicle R-7, was in full uniform and in full capacity, was dispatched to the Outer loop in the area of Northpoint Blvd for reports of a vehicle driving erratically, swerving in and out of different lanes, and almost striking other vehicles. Corey Alexander Carroll Hall (1/M/ 02/15/1985), called into the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack and stated that he was following behind the vehicle. Hall stated that in the area of Belair Rd, the vehicle drifted from lane 1 to the left shoulder almost striking the concrete barrier and then drifted back into lane 1. Hall advised that the vehicle was driven by a #2 female and that there was a small child in the back seat. Hall continued to follow the vehicle as the vehicle took exit 30 A (Perring Parkway). Hall followed the vehicle to the intersection of Perring Parkway  Putty Hill Ave. Hall stated that the driver was passed out behind the wheel in the left turn lane at the intersection of Perring Pkwy  Putty Hill Ave. When I arrived on scene at 2036 hours, I, observed a white Ford Fiesta bearing Colorado registration BXZF05 in the left turn lane at the Intersection of Perring Pkwy  Putty Hill Ave. There was a #2 female in the driver seat unconscious with the keys still in the ignition and the vehicle still running. I also observed a #2 male child in a car seat behind the passenger seat.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I attempted to make contact with the unconscious driver of the Fiesta via the driver side door. I used my baton to tap on the driver side window of the vehicle to get the attention of the driver. As I started to tap on the window the driver woke up, let her foot off the break and slowly started to drift forward. I yelled several times stop, put the vehicle in park but the driver looked at me with a blank stare and continued to drift forward. As the vehicle drifted forward, the vehicle struck the rear of a Subaru Crosstrek in the left turn lane. The driver of the Fiesta was now conscious, and I instructed her to turn the vehicle off. The driver of the Fiesta was later identified by her CO drivers license as Susan Irene Heuer (2/F/ 06/22/1984). I asked Heuer to step out of the vehicle and immediately placed her in handcuffs. Tpr. Jake Lowery of the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack #7448 secured the child that was in the backseat of the Fiesta in his patrol vehicle. The child who was identified as Josiah Heuer (1/M 04/25/2022, 1-Year-old) is the son the driver Susan Heuer. When I made contact with Heuer I could instantly smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage imitating from her breath and person. I asked Heuer how many drinks did she have, and she stated that she had 5 little ones. I asked Heuer 5 little ones of what. Heuer stated that she had 5 little ones of Vodka. Baltimore County EMS was on scene and advised that Heuer refused medical treatment. I asked Heuer if she would submit to Field Sobriety Test, and she replied Im not doing that. Eye Condition: bloodshot/red, watery. Walk: Normal Speech: Normal PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)   HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS  Test Refused  WALK AND TURN  Test Refused  ONE LEG STAND  Test Refused  sBased on the following, I had reason to believe Heuer was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Heuer breath. * Slow and lethargic head and body movements. * Eyes glassy and moderately red with a gazed look. * Admitted to consuming 5 little ones of vodka prior to driving. *At fault for motor vehicle collision.  I arrested Heuer for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 2117 hours and he was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. I played the English audio DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Heuer in its entirety. At the conclusion of the form, Heuer verbally advised that she refused to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the form indicating the same. Heuer was transported to Baltimore County Fire Department Station 10  Parkville. Heuer was released to her husband Michael Heuer from the fire station. Josiah Heuer was also released to Michael.  DISPOSITION OF DEFENDANT AND TRAFFIC CHARGES- Heuer was charged with: Ta 21 902 B2 : (Driving, Attempting To Drive) Veh. While Impaired By Alcohol While Transporting A Minor TA 21 902 B1 I: (DRIVING, ATTEMPTING TO DRIVE) VEH. WHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL TA 21 902 A1 I: (DRIVING, ATTEMPTING TO DRIVE) VEH. UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL TA 21-901. NEGLIGENT DRIVING and other traffic citations. All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland Case Status  Closed by arrest.    </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7282</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/12/2023 08:49:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7282</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/12/2023 10:41:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kennedy</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jonathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6844</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Holloway</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alva</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4912</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lowery</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jake</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7448</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zinn</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5682</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Muhammad</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jihad</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7282</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508111</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14584</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/25/2023 20:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14584</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7282</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/12/2023 07:50:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7282</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/12/2023 07:50:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7282</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/12/2023 08:06:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7282</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/12/2023 12:15:25</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>379587</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Heuer</LastName>
               <FirstName>Susan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Irene</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/22/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13210828E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>06/12/2023 08:06:07</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Heuer</LastName>
               <FirstName>Susan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Irene</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/22/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.13210828E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>H600</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/12/2023 08:06:07</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7282</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/12/2023 10:01:39</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7282</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/12/2023 10:01:39</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7282</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/12/2023 07:50:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7282</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/12/2023 07:50:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154039</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7282</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/12/2023 08:09:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7282</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/12/2023 08:09:32</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/12/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3FADP4EJ6GM179275</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2016</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FIE</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>BXZF05</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>10</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>