<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025602</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/17/2023 22:27:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/17/2023 22:27:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/17/2023 22:14:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/17/2023 22:14:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>23-96-210 Milligan DUI refusal</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 22:27:46</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/25/2023 00:26:04</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>PHILADELPHIA AVE/ 12TH ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>586493</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 22:27:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 19:35:05</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>586493</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Philadelphia</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.081697</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.342534</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1100-1112 PHILADELPHIA AVE / 0-0 12TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>NB PHILADELPHIA/ 12TH</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1201-1221 PHILADELPHIA AVE / 200-204 12TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1101-1121 PHILADELPHIA AVE / 200-204 12TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1100-1112 PHILADELPHIA AVE / 105-112 12TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 PHILADELPHIA AVE / 105-112 12TH ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/17/2023 22:27:44</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/17/2023 22:27:44</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/23/2023 22:37:34</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/17/2023 22:27:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP6805</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/10/2024 13:18:20</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MD Soundex: M-425-098-760-599  DUI #: 23-96-210 Subsequent offender: No MSP unmarked unit V-24 isequipped with a camera system. This incident was recorded on my agency issued body worn camera. Ocean City Police Department was also on scene.  Narrative:  On 07/17/2023 at approximately 2214 hours, I was operating MSP unmarked patrol vehicle, V-24, in the area of southbound Philadelphia near 12th Street Ocean City, MD 21842.  Phase One - Vehicle in Motion:  On the date of this incident, the weather was clearand cool, and traffic was moderate. While on patrol, I observed a black SUV traveling southbound in lane three with no headlights or taillights activated. I got behind the vehicle bearing MD registration T1412107 and conducted a traffic stop in the area of southbound Philadelphia ave and 12th Street.  Phase Two - Personal Contact:    I made contact with the operator at the drivers side window and I could immediately detect a moderate to strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle. I advised the operator for the reason of the stop and asked to see his license and registration. I asked the operator if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages, which he denied. The operator stated that he had passengers in the vehicle that he dropped off, and they had been drinking earlier. While speaking with the operator, I could see that he had watery, glassy, and bloodshot eyes. I advised the operator to wait in the vehicle and I would be right back. I was able to identify the operator as Bryan Scott Milligan.  Phase Three - Pre-Arrest Screening:   Upon the arrival of a second unit, I made my second approach to the drivers side of the vehicle. I askedMilligan to exit the vehicle, so I could make sure that he was safe to drive. I escortedMilligan away from the street and on to the sidewalk. While escortingMilligan, he stated that he had consumed three mixed drinks called the hoopdie on the Tiki cruise earlier. While speaking withMilligan outside his vehicle, I could still detect the moderate to strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.   I asked Milligan if he wore glasses or contacts, which he was already wearing glasses. I asked him if he had any injuries that prevented him from walking, turning, or standing, and he stated yes. Milligan stated he had swollen feet and many other medical issues. I then askedMilliganif he took any medications or illegal substances, and he said that he takes prescribed medications but no other drugs.The roadway was flat and free of debris.    After askingMilligan these questions I asked him to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Testing, which he refused. I explained toMilligan all the observations that I have made and that by him refusing, I would have to make my determination to arrest him based on those observations.Milligan stated do what you got to do.Milligan then explained how he was in the fire service for thirty years, and he was a dispatcher, so he knew what my job was. After speaking withMilligan for another minute,Milligan stated he had a few drinks at Mamas Cantina earlier. The correct name of the restaurantMilligan was at is called Mothers Cantina.Milligan finished by saying Its Ocean City. I asked him what that meant and he replied I dont know, whatever  The first test administered was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test:    Test refused  Test refused.  The second test administered was the Walk and Turn Test:    Test refused  Test refused.  The third test administered was the One Leg Stand Test:    Test refused  Test refused.  Upon completion of the tests, I offered Milligan to submit to a Preliminary Breath Test, which he refused.  Based on my training at the Maryland State Police Academy, training, knowledge, experience and prior DUI arrests, I placed Milligan under arrest for Driving under the Influence of Alcohol at approximately 2225 hours. While on scene, I askedMilligan who he had in his car with him, and he stated he was a friend. I askedMilligan if he had more or less than him to drink, and he replied probably less.  While on scene, I played an MVA audio recording to Milligan of his DR-15 Advice of Rights at approximately 2230 hours. Milliganrefused to submit to the Intoximeter Test.   I transported Milligan to the MSP Berlin Barrack for further processing.  Milliganwas released with the following citations:  1. 21-902 (a) (1): Driving Vehicle under the Influence of Alcohol  2. 21-902 (b) (1): Driving While Impaired by Alcohol  3. 21-901.1(a): Reckless driving vehicle in wanton and willful disregard for safety of persons and property  4. 21-901.1 (b): Negligent Driving in Careless and Imprudent Manner Endangering   Property, Life, and Person  5. 22-226(a): Failure to display two lighted front lamps when required  6. 22-209(b): Failure to display  reflect red color light on rear lamps and reflectors as required  7. 16-112(c): Failure of individual driving on highway to display license to uniformed police on demand  I request this case beclosed by arrest.  All events occurred in Worcester County, MD </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 03:40:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/23/2023 04:16:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sweitzer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7100</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515045</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>A</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/17/2023 22:14:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>A</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 19:35:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 19:35:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>49</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 19:40:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:50</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>382862</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Milligan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Bryan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Scott</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/31/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 19:40:03</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Milligan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Bryan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Scott</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/31/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M425</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/18/2023 19:40:03</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>29568</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Brant</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>302</SubNumber>
               <City>Easton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
               <Zip4>7142</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.049081</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.77357</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 19:40:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 19:40:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:13</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7100</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/18/2023 19:35:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7100</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/18/2023 19:35:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>