<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-016877</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/12/2023 01:44:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/12/2023 01:44:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/12/2023 01:20:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/12/2023 01:20:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 01:44:33</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/26/2023 11:05:16</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>VALE RD/ CROFTON DR</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>693728</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 01:44:34</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/13/2023 23:47:34</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>693728</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Vale</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Bel Air</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>DR</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.3701</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.54365</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>400-412 VALE RD / 1304-1307 CROFTON DR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/12/2023 01:44:31</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/12/2023 01:44:31</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 10:47:46</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 01:44:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 19:56:01</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The incident was audibly and visually recorded from my BWC. MSP unmarked unit D-24 is equipped with MVR equipment. DEFENDANT: TWEEDIE, THOMAS JOSEPH Date of Birth: 01/15/2001 (22 years old) Date of Arrest: 05/12/2023 Time of Arrest: 0143 hours DUI #: 23-125 (Bel Air Barrack, Harford County) Subsequent Offender: No Minor in the vehicle: No MD-DL. # MD-10272279323 CDL: No Certificate and Training: *I am a certified police officer in the state of Maryland with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with participants at the Maryland State Police Academy and prior DUI/DWI arrests and convictions. *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *RADAR / LIDAR Certified 2019. *Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator Certified. *Advance Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement Certified (ARIDE): Attended ARIDE with the Maryland State Police in January 2021 *UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND DUI INSTITUTE: I attended the University of Maryland DUI Institute, and I completed the course with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with live participants (From June 5 to June 10, 2022) *Certified as SFST witness expert by Honorable Judge Martin H. Schreiber II in Baltimore City Circuit Court on September 27, 2022. *Certified SFST witness expert by Honorable Judge David E. Carey in Harford County District Court on October 11, 2022. *I have apprehended more than 170 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On May 12, 2023, at approximately 0121 hours, I, Trooper First Class Reckeweg # 7214 of the Maryland State Police currently assigned to the Bel Air Barrack (unmarked MSP patrol vehicle D-24), was dispatched to assist Corporal Atkinson #5623 of the Maryland State Police with a traffic stop on the area of Vale Road and Crofton Drive, Bel Air, Harford County. Upon arrival, I observed a red Jeep bearing Maryland registration 7FB2365 in lane one (1) on northbound Vale Road north of Crofton Drive. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I contacted Corporal Atkinson, who advised that the Red Jeep was swerving on the roadway while on northbound Maryland Route 924 and Vale Road, and he had detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage in the drivers breath and person. Corporal Atkinson advised that the driver was identified as TWEEDIE, THOMAS JOSEPH (W/M, DOB 01/15/2001, Maryland Soundex MD-10272279323) and handed TWEEDIEs drivers license. Corporal Atkinson approached the Jeep via the drivers side window and asked TWEEDIE to exit the Jeep and walk to the front of his patrol vehicle. At the front of the patrol vehicle, I could detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from TWEEDIEs breath and person. I asked TWEEDIE where he was coming from and where he was going. TWEEDIE advised that he was coming from Sean Bolans Irish pub and going to his house. While talking to TWEEDIE, I instantly noticed his eyes were glassy and bloodshot. TWEEDIEs speech was slurred. I asked TWEEDIE how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed that evening, and he said he had consumed two drinks (tequila and pineapple) ten (10) minutes prior to the traffic stop. I observed TWEEDIE having difficulty keeping his balance as he swayed from left to right. I advised TWEEDIE that I would perform standardize field sobriety tests on him, which he agreed to submit. The summary of the first contact is as follows: Attitude: Cooperative Eye Condition: Glassy/bloodshot Mental State: Normal. Walk: Normal Speech: Slurred. I asked TWEEDIE the following questions: Medication- No Medical Conditions- No Glasses: Yes (wearing contacts) Any pain in the body- No PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The below standardized field sobriety tests were performed in lane one (1) on the roadway. That area of the road was level and free of debris. Before beginning the standardized field sobriety tests below, I turned off my front emergency lights. The weather conditions were clear. Lighting conditions consisted of my patrol vehicle headlights and my flashlight. TWEEDIE appeared in good physical condition and displayed no visible signs of injury. I explained and demonstrated the standardized field sobriety tests below to TWEEDIE. TWEEDIE stated he understood my instructions and had no questions about the standardized field sobriety test. -HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN) / (6/6 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: YES) The first test given was the horizontal gaze nystagmus test. The tip of my index finger from my right hand was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from TWEEDIEs eyes, slightly above his eyebrows. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. TWEEDIEs pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I observed his eyes to be red. TWEEDIE was positioned to ensure passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked TWEEDIE if he understood the instructions, and he stated, Yes. The following clues and observations were made during the test: Lack of Smooth Pursuit- Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation- Present in both eyes The onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 Degrees- Present in both eyes Additional test Vertical Gaze Nystagmus- Present in both eyes -WALK AND TURN (WAT) / (5/8 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: Yes) Before TWEEDIE performed the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. TWEEDIE was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. TWEEDIE was instructed and demonstrated to put his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until instructed to begin. TWEEDIE was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on each step. TWEEDIE was asked to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count each step out loud. On the ninth step, TWEEDIE was explained, and I demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and planted and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around to his left. TWEEDIE was again explained, and I demonstrated that the second series of nine (9) steps were to be completed identically to the first. He was instructed to keep his hands by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. I asked TWEEDIE if he understood the test. TWEEDIE stated, Yes. TWEEDIE was instructed to begin the test. Instructional Stage: Cannot Keep balance Started before instructed Walking Stage (1st Nine) TWEEDIE stepped offline on steps 2 and 7. TWEEDIE missed heel to toe by approximately 2 inches on steps 4 and 6. Walking Stage (2nd nine): TWEEDIE stepped offline on steps 3 and 7. TWEEDIE missed heel to toe by approximately 2 inches on steps 4 and 8. Turn: Completed Unsatisfactory. TWEEDIE did not leave his front foot planted and used both feet to walk in a circle. -ONE LEG STAND (OLS) (LEFT LEG) (3/4 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: Yes) Before TWEEDIE performed the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. TWEEDIE was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given during the test. TWEEDIE was instructed to begin the test when he was asked to start and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to watch his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (thousand-one, thousand-two), and continue the test until told to stop. I asked TWEEDIE if he had any questions about the test (OLS) which he replied, No. TWEEDIE raised his right foot. Instructional Stage: Nothing to report. Balance and Count Stage: 1. Puts foot down: TWEEDIE puts his foot down on the 14 and 16-second mark 2. Raise arms: TWEEDIE raised his arms more than 6 inches at the 06, 07, and 29-second mark. -PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT) (AGREED)- The final test offered to TWEEDIE was the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT). TWEEDIE was advised that he could refuse this test. TWEEDIE agreed to submit to the PBT with results of .19BrAC ARREST Based on my knowledge, training, and experience as an MSP Trooper, previous DUI arrests, and clues gathered thus far, I had reason to believe TWEEDIE was driving a motor vehicle while impaired (under the influence of Alcohol). *Swerving on the roadway. * Physical control of a motor vehicle. *admission of consumption of alcoholic beverages. *Odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. *Bloodshot eyes. *Slurred speech. *Watery eyes. * My observed signs of impairment as he performed the standardized field sobriety. ARREST / ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) / CERTIFIED BREATH TEST (AGREED)/ SERGEANT SANDER #5429 (Maryland State Police). I arrested TWEEDIE for driving under the influence of Alcohol at approximately 0143 hours. TWEEDIE was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to Maryland State Police Bel Air-Barrack for processing, where a mouth check was performed 20 minutes before his submission to the breath test. TWEEDIE was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along with as the DR-15 advice of rights was played to him from the official MVA website. At the conclusion of the DR-15, TWEEDIE agreed to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the DR-15, indicating the same at approximately 0224 hours. TWEEDIE provided two breath examples with positive results of .17 BRAC. TWEEDIE was given all copies of pertinent paperwork, and TWEEDIE was released to a sober adult that came to Bel Air Barrack. INTOXIMETER RESULT: Results of .17BRAC (0246 hours) TWEEDIE was cooperative during the processing. Case Status  Closed by arrest. All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 23:12:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/24/2023 21:27:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Atkinson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5623</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Atkinson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5623</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506302</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/12/2023 01:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/13/2023 23:42:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/14/2023 00:00:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/13/2023 23:42:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:07</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>376811</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>TWEEDIE</LastName>
               <FirstName>THOMAS</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>JOSEPH</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/11/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.26898669E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>05/12/2023 02:40:07</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>TWEEDIE</LastName>
               <FirstName>THOMAS</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>JOSEPH</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/11/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.26898669E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>T300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/12/2023 02:40:07</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 00:01:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 00:01:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/14/2023 00:01:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/13/2023 23:48:01</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/13/2023 23:48:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>