<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-026286</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/23/2023 21:31:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/23/2023 21:31:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/23/2023 20:58:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/23/2023 20:58:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Single vehicle accident no injuries, vehicle was towed off scene. driver was arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 21:31:28</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0104</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/05/2023 13:00:36</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>BERRY RD/ BENSVILLE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>530589</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 21:31:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 20:42:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>530589</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Berry</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Waldorf</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20602</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Distance>0</Distance>
         <Longitude>-77.01549</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.6361</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>9101-9199 BERRY RD / 0-0 BENSVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>9100-9358 BERRY RD / 0-0 BENSVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>228 @ SCOTLAND HEIGHTS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>9001-9099 BERRY RD / 0-0 BENSVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>228 @ 229</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>228/ 229</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>8301-8999 BERRY RD / 0-0 BENSVILLE RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/23/2023 21:31:26</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/23/2023 21:31:26</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/03/2023 15:42:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/23/2023 21:31:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DWI Case Number: 23-127 / 23-MSP-026286  Maryland Drivers License: M200108599582  Subsequent Offender: No   Preliminary Breath Test: Refused   This incident was recorded on in-car and body worn camera.  Vehicle in Motion:  On July 23, 2023,at approximately 2058 hours, I, Tpr. Fuller#7440responded to the area of eastbound Berry Road, in the area of Bensville Road for a single vehiclecollision. I arrived on scene and located a white Mercedes CLA 250, in lane one, with heavy front end damage. The white Mercedes was bearing Maryland Registration 4EE2366. Initial investigation revealed that the white Mercedes was traveling east on Berry road. The driver of the white Mercedes failed to control their speed and, ran off the road to the right and struck a guardrail with the front of their vehicle. At the time of the collision, it was not raining and the roadway was dry.  Personal Contact:  I made contact with the driver of the Mercedes, who identified herself by her Maryland Drivers License as Mugg, Casmine Melissa (A.A/F 07/23/1974). When I was able to speak to Mugg, she verified that she was the driver of the Mercedes involved in the accident.I observed Mugg stumble multiple times as she walked and dissociative behavior. I observed her eyes to be glassy and bloodshot. Mugg had a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath. I asked Mugg if she had any alcoholic beverages to drink. Mugg initial statement was, No. Mugg changed her statement stating I had some wine, I had a shot of tequila. Mugg later admitted to having wine while she was in DC in the area of Adams Morgan. I requested Mugg to complete Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and sheagreed.  Pre-Arrest Screening:  Mugg refused medical treatmentby EMS.I asked Mugg if she had any injuries or medical conditions, and she advised she had low iron and high blood pressure. Mugg decided to take her shoes off before starting the test.  I am trained in the administration of Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. That training was received at the Maryland State Police Academy. I have also completed Advance Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement training. I have utilized my training in numerous prior DUI arrests involving impairment by alcohol.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Mugg eyes. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Her pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting Nystagmus. Shewas positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. Mugg was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, Yes.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes  Vertical Nystagmus  None   WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)  Prior to Mugg performing the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Mugg was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. She was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Shewas advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Shewas instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Mugg was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around. Mugg was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Shewas instructedonce she began the test she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her sides, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. Mugg was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, Yes. Mugg decided to put her shoes back on for the remainder of the tests.  Instructional Stage:  Nothing Observed.  Walking Stage (1st Nine):  Missed Heel to toe. Mugg missed heel-to-toe steps on all steps by greater than half an inch for the first nine steps.  Incorrect number of steps. Mugg took 14 steps for the first set of nine steps.   Turn:   Improper turn. Mugg did not leave her lead foot plant and shuffled her feet while making the turn.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine):   Stopped during the test. Mugg stopped after making an improper turn for approximately 4 seconds after saying she understood the test.  Missed Heel to toe. Mugg missed heel-to-toe steps on all step by greater than half an inch for the second nine steps.  Incorrect Number of Steps. Mugg took 15 steps for the second set of nine.  ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)  Prior to Mugg performing the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Shewas instructed to stand with her heels together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised he was to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Mugg was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, Yes.  Instructional Stage:  Nothing observed.  Balance and Count Stage:  Used arms for balance. Mugg raised her right arm greater than 6 inches at 16 seconds  Puts foot down. Mugg put her put down at 1, 5, 8, 14, 16, 21, 22, 28, 29 seconds  Sways, Mugg sways to her left at 16 seconds   While on scene, Mugg refused to submit to a preliminary breath test.       ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Mugg was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:   -Strong odor of alcoholic beverage on breath.  -Dissociative behavior.  -Glassy and bloodshot eyes.  -Mumbled speech.  -Clues during Field Sobriety Testing.  - Admission to alcoholic beverage consumption.   Due to the number of observations, I concluded Mugg was driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 2142 hours, I placed Mugg under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. Mugg was placed in the front passenger seat of my MSP assigned vehicle, H-30 per department policy. Mugg was transported to the Maryland State Police La PlataBarrack for processing. While processing Mugg I continued to detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath, and Mugg continued to show glassy and bloodshot eyes.  The DR-15 Advice of Rights was read to Mugg at which time she refused to submitto the Intoximeter Test.  Mugg was given copies of all pertinent paperwork and was released into the custody of a sober driver.  All events occurred in CharlesCounty, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/29/2023 00:42:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7440</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/02/2023 21:12:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alphrin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5237</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Maszarose</LastName>
            <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6174</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Fuller</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7440</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515731</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/23/2023 20:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7440</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515731</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/23/2023 20:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7440</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515731</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/23/2023 20:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7440</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515731</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/23/2023 20:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7440</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515731</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/23/2023 20:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7440</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515731</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/23/2023 20:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7440</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/29/2023 00:10:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:19</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383308</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mugg</LastName>
               <FirstName>Casemine</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Melissa</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/24/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/23/2023 23:34:37</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C255</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mugg</LastName>
               <FirstName>Casemine</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Melissa</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/24/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C255</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/23/2023 23:34:37</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1003</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Dorset</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Waldorf</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20602</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.909958</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.601938</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>210</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7360</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/29/2023 00:10:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/29/2023 00:10:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/29/2023 00:10:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/29/2023 00:10:42</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:15</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7440</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/28/2023 23:55:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155406</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7440</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/29/2023 00:12:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7440</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/29/2023 00:12:03</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WDDSJ4GB4HN419493</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MERZ</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CLCLASS</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4EE2366</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>11</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>