<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-015696</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/03/2023 02:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/03/2023 02:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/03/2023 01:48:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/03/2023 01:48:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Ebike crash DUI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 02:08:57</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 08:37:27</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN GTWY/ INLET ISLE LN</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>105817</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 02:08:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 07:10:18</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>105817</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Ocean City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21842</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.10129</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.33521</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>50 EB PRIOR TO THE HARRY KELLEY BRDGE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>50 EB /INLET ISLE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 50 / INLET ISLE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12825-12912 OCEAN GTWY / 12900-12903 INLET ISLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 50/ INLET ISLE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12914-13000 OCEAN GTWY / 12900-12903 INLET ISLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12825-12912 OCEAN GTWY / 12904-12931 INLET ISLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12851-12913 OCEAN GTWY / 12900-12903 INLET ISLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12915-13001 OCEAN GTWY / 12900-12903 INLET ISLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12911-12925 OCEAN GTWY / 12900-12951 INLET ISLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12911-12925 OCEAN GTWY / 0-0 INLET ISLE LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/03/2023 02:08:53</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/03/2023 02:08:53</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/16/2023 18:07:00</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 02:08:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:54:30</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police Berlin Barrack V (9096) TFC R. Phillips #7211 May 3rd, 2023  Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle  V-35 is a marked Ford Explorer that is equipped with an MVR system. This incident was also audibly and visually recorded on Axon Body Camera. All videos associated with the incident labeled (23MSP015696).         Driver/Defendant: Vaughn Christopher Johnson        Date of Birth: 09/24/2001    MD Soundex: MD-102-732-741-69    Subsequent offender: Yes     Date and time of arrest: 5/3/2023 at 0149 hours    Intoximeter Results: Refusal     margin-bottom:11px"&gt;DUI Folder # 23-96-106             Training/certifications:         Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Safety Administration (NHTSA).    margin-bottom:11px"&gt;NHTSA certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E).       Narrative:   On May 3rd, 2023 at 2246 hours, I (TFC Phillips), was on marked patrol in the area of eastbound U.S. Route 50 at the Harry W. Kelly Bridge. At this time, I observed a blue and Black Super73 E-Bike traveling in the opposite direction in lane 2 on westbound U.S. Route 50. The operator was a white male with a camo jacket, grey pants, a dark colored backpack and no helmet.   Phase 1: Vehicle in Motion   I activated V-35s in-car Kustom Golden Eagle II radar unit. I retrieved a digital reading of 26-mph in a 35-mph zone. I continued to watch the e-bike as it passed me in my rear mirrors. I observed the e-bike strike a cement curb in the area of westbound U.S. Route 50 and Inlet Isle Lane. The collision caused the operator and the e-bike to flip and slide into the turn lane. Due to the collision, I activated my emergency lights and responded to the scene.   Phase II: Personal Contact   On approach the operator was lifting the e-bike onto the sidewalk from the turn lane. He sat back on the e-bike. He was bleeding from his nose from the collision, I requested EMS to respond to the scene. The operator repeatedly mumbled he was fine. I asked him to step off the e-bike and have a seat on the curb. The operator had dropped his cell phone and an ear phone in the collision but did not seem to notice. When I advised him his nose was bleeding, he responded: That always happens. He advised he rode this way regularly and was headed back to Ocean Pines. I continued to ask him if he was okay, he continued to deny having any injuries from the collision. When I requested his drivers license or identification card, he advised he was suspended and couldnt drive. He explained that this was due to a prior DUI.   He was then identified as Vaughn Johnson through his Maryland drivers license. His license was confirmed to be suspended through the Berlin Barrack. EMS arrived on scene at 0152 hours. Johnson was checked by EMS, he refused claiming he was fine (Run#23-01343).   Johnson explained he was coming from work at Papis Tacos on 15th Street where he is a bartender. While I spoke to Johnson, I detected the strong odor of alcoholic beverages emanating of his breath and person.  As Johnson Spoke, I made the following observations:    I observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy.  He displayed a glazed expression.   margin-left:8px"&gt;His speech was slow and at times slurred,   Due to these observations and the nature of collision, Johnson was asked to step onto the sidewalk. I asked how much he had to drink, and he responded: I had one drink at work, and then I went to pickles for a little bit and we had like three or four. I then asked when he got off work, and he responded: Like 11 oclock. He advised he went to Pickles bar after work. When asked how long he was at Pickles, he responded Probably an hour and a half. I then asked what kind of alcoholic beverages he consumed. He responded: I was drinking Captain diets.   Phase III: Pre-Arrest Screening  Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs)   The evaluation was performed on the sidewalk. The surface was level and free from any debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight, vehicle headlamps, and the street lights. The weather was clear. He was asked if he had any physical or mental disabilities, he responded: My face is a little fucked up. Johnson appeared to be in good physical condition besides his nose bleeding from the collision. He advised he did not wear glasses and that he did not take any medication. I observed Johnson to have blue eyes. He was wearing a gray camo jacket, grey pants, and gray vans.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN): 6 of 6 clues    Displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  Displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.   Walk and Turn (WAT): 3 of 8 clues  Walking Stage:     Missed heel-to-toe on steps 4 and 6 during first series of steps.   Stepped offline on steps 4, 5, and 6 during first series of steps.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Raised arms throughout first series of steps.  Note: Johnson did not count out loud.   One Leg Stand (OLS): 3 of 4 clues    Put foot down during first 10 seconds and last 10 seconds.  Raised arms throughout the test.  Swayed throughout the test.  Note: Put foot backwards instead of to the front as instructed.   Preliminary Breath Test (PBT): Refused.  Arrest:  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Johnson was under the influence of alcohol:    Nature of the collision.  Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.  Bloodshot and glassy eyes.  Glazed expression on face.  Admission to having consumed several alcoholic beverages in a 3-hour time period (2300 hours to 0150 hours).  Slurred/slow speech.  My observed signs of impairment.    Johnson was placed under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at 0207 hours. At this time, I inspected inside his mouth for any foreign objects and none were found. The e-bike was towed by City Towing.   Transport:   Johnson was transported to the Berlin Barrack without incident. I continued to smell the strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person.  Advise of Rights (DR-15):   Johnson was given his advice of rights via audio version of the DR-15 form through a Barrack computer. A paper copy was also placed in-front of him. At the conclusion of the audio, Johnson refused to submit to a breath test at 0236 hours.   Intoximeter Result: Refused  Release:   Johnson was released to a sober person at 0307 hours.Johnson was polite and cooperative throughout the investigation and arrest.  Charges:  1. Driving Vehicle While Under the Influence of Alcohol 2. Driving While Impaired by Alcohol 3. Failure to Control Speed to Avoid Collision. 4. Negligent Driving  Case closed by arrest. All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7211</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/08/2023 07:55:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7211</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/16/2023 14:14:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phillips</LastName>
            <FirstName>Riley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7211</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505115</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/03/2023 01:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7211</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 07:12:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7211</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 07:12:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505115</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/03/2023 01:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7211</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 07:12:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7211</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 07:12:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505115</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/03/2023 01:48:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7211</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 07:15:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7211</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/08/2023 06:20:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7211</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 07:22:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375996</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Vaughn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christopher</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/24/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/03/2023 07:21:47</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>V250</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Johnson</LastName>
               <FirstName>Vaughn</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Christopher</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/24/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J525</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>V250</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/03/2023 07:21:47</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7211</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/08/2023 06:21:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7211</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/08/2023 06:21:28</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7211</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 07:12:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7211</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 07:12:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152601</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AC</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7211</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 07:30:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7211</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 07:30:02</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/03/2023 07:30:02</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleTypeCode>XX</VehicleTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>