<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-028324</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4800</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/11/2023 02:23:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/11/2023 02:23:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/11/2023 01:59:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/11/2023 01:59:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI arrest of Heather Ann Highfield.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/11/2023 02:23:45</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3675</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 16:58:10</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN EXPY/ RACETRACK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/11/2023 02:23:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 03:20:48</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>583779</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>EXPY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Berlin</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.170578</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.38053</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 E/O 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB/ 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 PRIOR 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>MERGING OFF OF 90 INTO OCEAN PINES</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB BETWEEN BRIDGE AND OCEAN PINES EXIT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 WB / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>90 EB PAST 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>EB 90 / 589</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11083-11086 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1296-1352 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1240-1295 OCEAN EXPY / 11079-11082 RACETRACK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/11/2023 02:23:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/11/2023 02:23:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>96</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/19/2023 10:33:09</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/11/2023 02:23:45</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:06:30</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Heather Ann Highfield Delaware SOUNDEX: 1385239 Breath Test Result: Refusal DWI Citation #: 4RP0J79 DWI MVR/Body Cam #: Video tagged as 23-MSP-028324 (Axon View XL Software).   TROOPER CERTIFICATES / TRAINING / SPECIAL ASSIGNMENTS  1. Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. 2. Certified SFST Instructor. 3. Chemical Breath Test Operator. 4. Graduate of the University of Marylands DUI Institute. 5. Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. 6. Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.). 7. Trained in Cannabis Impairment Detection (Maryland State Police). 8. Assigned to the Berlin Barrack V Special Enforcement Team (focusing exclusively on DUI enforcement) from October 2017 - June 2022.   NARRATIVE   -PHASE I: VEHICLE IN MOTION  On 08-11-2023 at approximately 0159 hours, I (Corporal J. Ruiz #6312), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating marked MSP vehicle V-15 in the area of Maryland Route 90 near Mile Marker 8 at the base of the Isle of Wight Bay Bridge (Ocean Pines). I was stationary on the right shoulder area, monitoring all westbound traffic. At that time, I observed a sport utility vehicle traveling westbound pass my location. I made the following observations on the same vehicle:  NEAR MILE MARKER 8  1. The vehicles right tires crossed (1 tire width) the solid white line into the shoulder area on two (2) occasions. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane each time.  I safely entered the roadway and closed in on the same vehicle near Mile Marker 7.  BETWEEN MILE MARKER 7 AND THE MARYLAND ROUTE 589 EXIT  2. The vehicles right tires were directly on top of the solid white shoulder line on two (2) occasions. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane each time.  3. The vehicles right tires crossed the solid white shoulder line on three (3) occasions. The vehicle drifted back into the westbound lane each time.  ADDITIONAL OBSERVATIONS   4. The vehicle failed to maintain proper lane position due to pronounced and excessive weaving (alternately moving toward one side of the lane and then the other) during the entire duration of my observations.  5. Total distance traveled was approximately 1.88 miles.   DWI INDICATORS / REASON FOR STOP  The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHSTA) published a The Visual Detection of DWI Motorists booklet in March 2010. The research revealed that DWI cues related to problems in maintaining proper lane position include:  1. Weaving across lane lines 2. Drifting 3. Weaving  All of the above DWI indicators were exhibited by the SUV prior to my initiating a traffic stop on the same vehicle.   TRAFFIC STOP / STOPPING SEQUENCE OF VEHICLE  I activated the emergency lights to my patrol vehicle prior to the MD Route 589 exit. The SUV continued to travel another approximately 1,900 feet, coming to a complete stop on the MD Route 589 overpass. The vehicle was a black 2020 Chevrolet Traverse bearing Delaware registration XQ423563.   -PHASE II: PERSONAL CONTACT  I made contact with the driver via the driver side door, and I immediately smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop and requested the drivers license and the registration card to the vehicle. The driver was identified as Heather Ann Highfield by her Delaware drivers license. I asked Highfield where she was traveling from, and she responded: I was with my stepdaughter at the Cowboy Coast. I asked Highfield where she was traveling to, and she replied: Home.    As Highfield spoke, I made the following observations:  1. I intentionally observed her eyes to be glassy and bloodshot.  2. Highfield displayed a glazed look/expression on her face as she interacted with me.  3. Highfield was wearing a blue band on her right wrist (consistent with wristbands provided to bar patrons to indicate that the patron is at least 21 years old).  4. When asked how much she had to drink earlier in the evening, Highfield advised: I did have a little bit and I, uh, paced myself. I knew I had to drive.   I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Highfield.   I later returned to the Chevrolet and requested Highfield exit the vehicle and walk to the front of it, to which she complied. Highfield was smoking a cigarette. I requested that she put out the cigarette, and Highfield complied. While at the front of the vehicle, I continued to speak with Highfield. I asked Highfield again where she was traveling from, and she stated: Cowboy Coast. During my second interaction with Highfield, she advised the following:  1. Highfield had consumed: 2 drinks while at Cowboy Coast. When asked what kind of drinks she had consumed, Highfield stated: Honestly, I dont know. The bartender said it was his special. I, honestly, I dont know. It was a fruit drink.  2. When asked how much time had passed since she consumed her last drink prior to driving, Highfield advised: Uh, bout 45 minutes ago.  3. As Highfield spoke, I smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. I informed Highfield that I wanted her to perform field sobriety tests which she agreed to submit to.    -PHASE III: PRE-ARREST SCREENING  STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS (SFSTs)  The evaluation was performed on the small right shoulder area on the overpass. The surface was level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight and vehicle headlamps. Weather was clear and approximately 74 degrees. I asked Highfield if she had any significant medical issues with her eyes, arms, or legs which would prevent her from performing the field sobriety tests or if she had taken any medication prior to driving. Highfield responded: No. Highfield appeared to be in general good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries, limps, or any limb ailments.  Highfield was wearing a pink tank top, blue jeans, and white Keds-style shoes.  **HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: 6 of 6 clues**   1. Highfield displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.   2. Highfield displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  3. Highfield displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.   **WALK AND TURN: 6 of 8 clues**  1. Highfield could not maintain her balance during the Instruction Phase. Highfields feet broke from the start position on four (4) occasions, and she stumbled to her right each time.  2. Highfield missed heel-to-toe on steps 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 13, and 15 during the first series. Highfield missed heel-to-toe on steps 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, and 10 during the second series. All misses were of more than half an inch.   3. Highfield took 15 steps during the first series and 10 steps during the second series. Both were contrary to my instructions.  4. Highfield did not complete the turn in a satisfactory manner, lifting her lead foot and turning to the right which was contrary to my instructions.  5. Highfield stopped walking after the turn. I had to prompt Highfield to continue the test as instructed.  6. Highfield was unable to maintain a straight line and stepped off the line on steps 2, 3, 4, 6, 7, 9, 13, and 15 during the first series and steps 2, 3, 5, 6, and 10 during the second series.    **ONE LEG STAND: 3 of 4 clues**  1. Highfields body swayed to the left and right on seconds 2, 3, 5, 6, 8, 12, 15, 17, and 18.  2. Highfield raised her arms (higher than 6 to her sides) for balance on second #5.  3. Highfield put her right foot down on seconds 5, 6, 8, 13, 15, and 18.   ADDITIONAL ANNOTATIONS REFERENCE FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS // ADDITIONAL TESTING  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN):  A. Highfield removed her eyeglasses for this test only. B. Highfields body swayed to the left and right during this test. C. Highfield displayed vertical nystagmus. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus is an involuntary jerking of the eyes (up and down) which occurs when the eyes gaze upward at maximum elevation. The presence of this type of nystagmus is associated with high doses of alcohol for that individual and certain other drugs.  Walk And Turn (WAT):  A. The solid white shoulder line was used for this test. B. At no point during the test did Highfield count her steps out loud as instructed.  One Leg Stand (OLS):  A. At no point during the test did Highfield count out loud by thousands as instructed. B. Highfield placed and maintained her hands on her lap during the test, which was contrary to my instructions.   **ALPHABET TEST**:  Highfield advised that she was a high school graduate and that she was capable of reciting the English alphabet and numbers. I instructed Highfield to recite from the letter F to the letter S.   -Highfield recited in the following manner: F-G-H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P-Q-U-R-S.   **COUNT TEST**:  I instructed Highfield to count backwards from 36-19.  -Completed satisfactorily.    PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT)  After the conclusion of all Field Sobriety Tests, I offered Highfield the opportunity to submit to a preliminary breath test (PBT). Highfield submitted to a PBT with a reading of 0.189 BrAC.    ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Highfield was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  * Driving vehicle in a negligent manner which caused it to commit 7 lane violations in addition to excessive weaving  DRIVING SKILLS IMPAIRED. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot. * Glazed look/expression on face. * Admission to consuming at least one (1) alcoholic beverage prior to operating a motor vehicle.  * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person. * My observed signs of impairment as she performed field sobriety tests.  * PBT reading of 0.189 BrAC.  I determined that Highfield was impaired by the presence of an alcoholic beverage in her system that adversely affected her ability to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. The inability to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests properly can also adversely affect the persons ability to operate a motor vehicle safely. I placed Highfield under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0216 hours on 08-11-2023. At this time, I visually inspected the inside of Highfields mouth for any foreign objects and none were found.    ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15)  Highfield was placed and secured in the right front seat of my patrol vehicle. Highfield was given her Advice of Rights via the audio version of the DR-15 Form (played through the patrol vehicles laptop speakers). A copy of the DR-15 Form was placed directly in front of Highfield, attached to the sun visor. At the conclusion of the audio version, I verbally re-explained the drivers license sanctions and penalties (section printed in red) to Highfield. Highfield stated that she understood her Advice of Rights and refused to submit to a breath test at approximately 0235 hours on 08-11-2023.   TRANSPORT / PLACEMENT INTO CELL #2  Highfield was subsequently transported to the Berlin Barrack for processing. During transport, the odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Highfield continued to be strong. Highfield was placed in Barrack Cell #2 during processing.   RELEASE  Highfield exited Cell #2 at the time of her release. After exiting Cell #2, I entered the cell in order to perform a visual search of the cell. There was a distinct and strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of Cell #2. The odor was not present at the time Highfield entered the cell.  Highfield was provided all forms and citations prior to her release. Highfield was released to a sober driver at approximately 0325 hours on 08-11-2023.   CHARGES  Highfield was charged with the following citations:  1. Driving Vehicle While Under The Influence Of Alcohol (4RP0J79) 2. Driving Vehicle While Impaired By Alcohol (4RQ0J79) 3. Failure To Obey Traffic Control Device (4RR0J79) 4. Negligent Driving (4RS0J79)   Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Worcester County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 03:44:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 04:46:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Benjamin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7043</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Phillips</LastName>
            <FirstName>Riley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7211</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jonischek</LastName>
            <FirstName>Todd</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4794</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>96</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4800</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ruiz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Francisco</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6312</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517768</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/14/2023 03:22:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 03:20:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 03:22:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517768</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/14/2023 03:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 03:20:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 03:21:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517768</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/14/2023 03:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 03:20:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 03:21:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>517768</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/14/2023 03:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 03:20:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 03:21:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 03:20:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 03:23:07</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>384950</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Highfield</LastName>
               <FirstName>Heather</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/12/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/12/2023 03:47:23</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H214</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H360</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Highfield</LastName>
               <FirstName>Heather</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ann</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/12/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H214</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H360</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/12/2023 03:47:23</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>25748</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Gum Tree</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Dagsboro</City>
               <StateCode>DE</StateCode>
               <Zip5>19939</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4497</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.2988746</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.5434985</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>302</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>448</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0705</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/12/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 03:23:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 03:23:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 03:20:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 03:20:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156056</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6312</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/14/2023 03:30:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6312</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/14/2023 03:30:20</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/12/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1GNERJKW4LJ268459</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2020</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>TRV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>DE</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>XQ423563</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>8</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>