<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-016090</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/06/2023 02:17:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/06/2023 02:17:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/06/2023 02:03:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/06/2023 02:03:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop leading to the arrest of the operator for DUI/DWi</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/06/2023 02:17:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4993</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 15:05:11</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>E CHURCH ST/ N SALISBURY BLVD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>530532</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/06/2023 02:17:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/08/2023 01:22:50</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>530532</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Church</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Salisbury</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>N</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>BLVD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.595512</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.367335</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>400-413 E CHURCH ST / 200-299 N SALISBURY BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>400-424 E CHURCH ST / 200-299 N SALISBURY BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/06/2023 02:17:39</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/06/2023 02:17:39</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/02/2023 03:14:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/06/2023 02:17:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:52:52</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Patrol Vehicle E26 is equipped with in an in car camera Dash Cam footage: partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=568b84cdb2714477af911f19ee31c3a6partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 Body Cam Footage: https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=355cf437951b4038a2d900056bfe8762partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 In-Car Camera: https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=643a3591ccab488393fb594b70dda012partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 Crime: Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol Weather: Clear Defendant: Eric Jean-Charles Date of Birth: 11/21/995 Date of Arrest: 05/06/2023 Time of Arrest: 0213 hours License: J-526-234-009-891 DUI #: 23-54-090 DUI Citation #: 4Y70UR7 Subsequent Offender: No Accident Involved: No SCENE PROCESSING: * DR15 Advice of Rights * DR15A CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING:  * I am trained to administer standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * I have successfully completed the Advanced Roadside Impairment Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) course through the Maryland State Police. * I have successfully completed standardized field sobriety instructor school through the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * I have attended the Maryland DUI Conference which is held and sponsored by the Maryland Highway Safety Office. * I have apprehended more than 130 impaired drivers during my tenure as a Law Enforcement Officer in 4 years.    Phase #1 - Vehicle In Motion:  On May 6th, 2023 at approximately 0203 hours, I, TFC Ramsay was on patrol in the area of southbound Route 13 and Calvert Street Salisbury, Wicomico County, Maryland.  At the above date and time, I observed a black Nissan passenger car bearing Maryland registration A363375 make a left hand turn off of Market Street. I know there to be a sign on Market Street that advises you are not allowed to make a left hand turn from that road position. As the vehicle passed my location I observed the windows of the vehicle to be extremely dark. The windows were so dark I was unable to see anything inside the vehicle. I executed a U-turn and activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the vehicle.  Phase #2 - Personal Contact:  I immediately exited my patrol vehicle and made contact with the operator, Eric Jean-Charles(B/M 11/21/1995), I identified myself, told him the reason for the stop, and advised him that he was being audibly and visually recorded. While speaking with Jean-Charles, I detected the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the passenger compartment of the vehicle. I also detected the odor an an air freshener that had just been sprayed as if to mask an odor. I observed Jean-Charles eyes to be bloodshot, watery, and glassy. Phase #3 - Pre Arrest Screening: I asked Jean-Charles if he wanted to perform standardized field sobriety tests. Jean-Charles stated he did. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from Jean-Charless breath and person while speaking with him outside of the vehicle. Jean-Charles had placed a piece of gum in his mouth between my initial contact with him and me asking him to exit the vehicle to conduct field sobriety tests. I asked Jean-Charles how many alcoholic beverages he consumed and he advised not a lota little casa migos. I know casa migos to be tequila. I then began Standardized Field Sobriety Tests and I started with the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test. Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus:   I explained the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test to Jean-Charles. After explaining the test I asked him if he understood the test and if he had any questions. Jean-Charles stated he understood the test and began.  Resting Nystagmus: No Equal Tracking: Yes Equal Pupil Size: Yes *Lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes *Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes *Onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees *Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was present Total Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Clues:6 of 6  Walk and Turn: Weather: Clear Surface: Level concrete sidewalk free of any debris   I instructed Jean-Charles into the instructional phase. I then explained and demonstrated the Walk and Turn test to Jean-Charles. Instructional Phase: Broke balance   1st 9 steps: N/a  Turn: Incorrect  2nd 9 steps: Stopped walking Stepped off line  Total Walk and Turn Clues:4 of 8  One Leg Stand: I next explained and demonstrated the One Leg Stand test to Jean-Charles. I asked Jean-Charles if he understood the test and he stated he did. Clues: Swayed Put foot down Used arms for balance Hopped Total One Leg Stand Clues:4 of 4  Preliminary Breath Test: I explained to Jean-Charles the reasons for using a preliminary breath test, and asked if he wanted to submit a breath sample. Jean-Charles did not wish to give a breath sample. While explaining the test to him Jean-Charles stated, I dont wanna take that test and I dont wanna get back into the vehicle.  Arrest and Transport:   Based on the following, I had reason to believe Jean-Charles was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol  * Eyes bloodshot, watery, and glassy * The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person * Admittance to consuming alcoholic beverages * Observations during SFSTs  Jean-Charles was placed under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol at 0213 hours. On the way to the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack, the odor of an alcoholic beverage was present in my patrol car that was not there prior to the traffic stop.  20 Minute Observation Period:   Jean-Charles was read/listened the DR-15 Advice of Rights when we arrived at the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack. Jean-Charles refused to submit to the intoximeter test at 0310 hours and signed the DR-15. Jean-Charles was given all the appropriate paperwork and released to a sober driver. While waiting to decide if he would like to take the breath test, Jean-Charles threw up and fell asleep multiple times in the chair he was sitting in.   I request this case closed.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7057</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/19/2023 12:36:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7057</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/19/2023 13:10:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hopkins</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dra'karr</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7202</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mareck</LastName>
            <FirstName>Keven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3258</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ramsay</LastName>
            <FirstName>Lee</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7057</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>505509</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/06/2023 02:03:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7057</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/08/2023 01:23:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7057</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/08/2023 01:23:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7057</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/08/2023 01:24:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:03</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>51967</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Jean-Charles</LastName>
               <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
               <DOB>11/21/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/07/2015 17:47:12</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J526</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Jean-Charles</LastName>
               <FirstName>Eric</FirstName>
               <DOB>11/21/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J526</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/07/2015 17:47:12</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>27758</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Crittenden</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21801</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.65096</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.365271</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>783</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3243</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/07/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7057</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/08/2023 01:24:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7057</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/08/2023 01:24:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7057</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/08/2023 01:24:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:04</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7057</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/08/2023 01:23:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7057</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/08/2023 01:23:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>