<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-019698</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/01/2023 23:50:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/01/2023 23:50:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/01/2023 23:24:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/01/2023 23:24:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The driver was arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 23:50:47</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3143</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 08:12:46</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>POINT LOOKOUT RD/ CEDAR LANE CT</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>696222</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 23:50:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 00:16:09</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>696222</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Point Lookout Rd/ Cedar Lane Ct</StreetName>
         <City>Leonardtown</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20650</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.62494</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.28943</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>24798-24800 POINT LOOKOUT RD / 22600-22700 CEDAR LANE CT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/01/2023 23:50:44</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/01/2023 23:50:44</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>82</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/04/2023 23:51:34</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/01/2023 23:50:47</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:04</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was captured on in-car camera (T-19) and body worn camera. Defendant: Robert Arthur G Rand Date of Birth: 7/21/1991 Date of Arrest: 6/1/2023 Time of Arrest: 2345 SDX: R530745071574 DUI#: 23-059 CERTIFICATE AND TRAINING  Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Safety Administration. Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE). VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE ONE)  On 6/1/2023 at approximately 2324hours, I was on MD RT 4 S/B prior to Wheatleys Content Farm Ln, when I observed a maroon Plymouth Acclaim bearing MD registration 4Z9924 with its left turn signal on. The vehicle continued with its turn signal on for long period of time and once I got closer to the vehicle they turned off the turn signal. I continued following behind the vehicle and observed it sway from shoulder line to center line multiple times. The right-side tires crossed over the white shoulder line completely on three separate occasions. The vehicle also braked erratically for an unknown reason. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE TWO)  I made contact with the operator on the drivers side of the vehicle, later identified as Robert Arthur Rand (W/M DOB: 7/21/1991) by his Maryland drivers license. I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the vehicle and his person. I asked Rand how many alcoholic beverages he consumed today to which he stated none. Rands speech was sluggish and his body movements were lethargic. I asked Rand if he would be willing to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests and he agreed. The passenger was identified as Lillian Mae Miller (W/F DOB: 5/11/1996). PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE THREE)  The evaluation was performed on the right-hand shoulder of the roadway. The surface was dry, level and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of my flashlight, the headlights of my vehicle. I asked Rand if he takes any prescription medication to which he stated no and smoked cannabis earlier in the day. I asked Rand if he wears corrective lenses or contacts to which stated he no. I continued to observe Rands eyes to be bloodshot and glassy at this time. Rand stated he has no physical ailments that would prevent him from completing the tests. HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN) (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and was held approximately 12 inches from Rands eyes and slightly above eye level. Rand was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following the tip of the stimulus with his eyes only. Rand s pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I asked Rand if he understood the directions and he stated, Yes. 1. Lack of Smooth Pursuit: Present in both eyes. 2. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation: Present in both eyes. 3. Onset Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees: Present in both eyes. Vertical Nystagmus detected. WALK AND TURN (6/8 clues observed)  I explained to Rand and demonstrated how the test should be completed. Rand was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Rand was then instructed to place his hands along his side and to remain in the starting position until told to begin the test. I advised Rand to take nine heel to toe steps in a straight line. Rand was told to keep his hands by his side, to look at his feet the entire time, and to count every step out loud. On the ninth step, I demonstrated and explained to Rand to keep his lead foot on that line and turn around in a series of small steps to the left and turn completely around. I demonstrated three of the nine steps, both before and after the turn. Rand was instructed once he began the test, he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet and count every step out loud. I then asked Rand if he understood the instructions and he stated, Yes. Instructional Stage: Could not maintain starting position and had to reset 5 times. Rand stated he is left foot ambidextrous. Started too soon. Walking Stage (1st Nine). Rand raised arms more than 6 inches on steps 3 and 4. Rand Stopped walking after step 4 and walked backwards 4 steps, then started 9 new steps. Walking Stage (2nd Nine) Rand lost balance and stepped off line by more than 1 in after the turn and turned the wrong way. Rand stopped walking and asked for clarification on the instructions after the turn. Rand stopped walking multiple times due to the light blinding him because he was not looking as his foot as instructed. Rand stepped of line on steps 7 and 8 and did not finish the test. One Leg Stand (3/4 clues observed)  Prior to Rand performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Rand was instructed to stand with his legs together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately six (6) inches. Rand raised his left foot and balanced on his right foot. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, keep his hands at his sides, watch his raised foot, to count out loud by thousands, and continue the test until told to stop. I asked Rand if he understood the test and he stated, Yes. Seconds 0-10: Rand raised his arms more than 6 inches for balance. Rand put his foot down. Rand swayed. Seconds 10-20: Did not finish. Seconds 20-30: Did not finish. Rand advised he consumed a pint of alcohol around 4pm today. PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST: Rand agreed to take a preliminary breath test. Result: .17 BrAC ARREST:  Based on the following, I had the reason to believe Rand was operating a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: Unaware of turn signal being used for long period of time. Failure to maintain lane, swaying and crossing shoulder line. Observed bloodshot and glassy eyes. Inability to follow directions. Detected an odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from breath and person. Admitted to consuming alcohol. Observations during Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. Preliminary breath test result of .17 BrAC.  Rand was placed under arrest at approximately 2345 hours. A search incident to arrest located a half empty bottle of Fireball Whiskey 33% ABV sitting under the drivers arms rest. Rand was transported to the Maryland State Police Leonardtown Barrack. Rand was played an audio recording of the DR-15 Advice of Rights through MVAs website. Rand was provided with a copy of the DR-15 to follow along with. Rand signed the DR-15 Advice of Rights at 0021 hours and AGREED to take the Intoximeter test. INTOXIMETER RESULTS: .14 BrAC Rand signed and was given copies of all paperwork. Rand was then released from the barrack to a sober driver. Case closed by arrest. All events occurred in St. Marys County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 05:36:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7152</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 05:36:56</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Thomas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Payton</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7591</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Oles</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5857</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>82</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Baden</LastName>
            <FirstName>Craig</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7152</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509132</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/01/2023 23:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 04:07:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7152</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 04:07:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509132</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/01/2023 23:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 04:08:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7152</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 04:08:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>509132</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/01/2023 23:24:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 04:08:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7152</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 04:08:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 04:09:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:15</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378720</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Rand</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Arthur G</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/21/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/02/2023 00:26:38</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Rand</LastName>
               <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Arthur G</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/21/1991 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R530</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R163</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/02/2023 00:26:38</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>8011</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Keech</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Charlotte Hall</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20622</Zip5>
               <Zip4>3351</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.828286</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.495831</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 04:12:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:16</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 04:12:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:16</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 04:17:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:52</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378728</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Miller</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lillian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Mae</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/11/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/02/2023 04:17:43</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L450</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Miller</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lillian</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Mae</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/11/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M460</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L450</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/02/2023 04:17:43</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PA</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 04:17:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:16</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 04:07:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7152</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 04:07:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153689</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7152</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/02/2023 04:15:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7152</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/02/2023 04:15:30</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1P3XA4638PF675655</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>1993</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>PLYM</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ACC</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>MAR</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>MAR</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4Z9924</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>