<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-030475</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/29/2023 21:08:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/29/2023 21:08:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/29/2023 20:12:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/29/2023 20:12:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>HEAD-ON MOTOR VEHICLE COLLISION. AT-FAULT OPERATOR DWI/DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 21:09:01</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2637</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>09/29/2023 11:09:05</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>CONOWINGO RD/ LITTLE NEW YORK RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>624291</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 21:09:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/30/2023 16:50:10</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>624291</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Conowingo</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Rising Sun</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.042026</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.714961</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3800-4199 CONOWINGO RD / 127-130 LITTLE NEW YORK RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/29/2023 21:08:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/29/2023 21:08:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/29/2023 03:23:59</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/29/2023 21:09:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:47</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>2</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>SCENE PROCESSING:  Photographs and copies of paperwork can be found in Attachments.    The appropriate paperwork was placed into outgoing barrack mail for mailing to the MVA.    I, Trooper First Class Scott (#7217) of the Maryland State Police, am equipped with a body-worn camera, which was actively recording during this incident. However, at the hospital, my body-worn camera was only recording with the permission of the suspect, with respect to healthcare privacy. It was deactivated/re-activated per his request/consent at the hospital, and was deactivated when not in contact with him to uphold patient privacy. My body-worn camera was not deliberately activated/used to record any other patients presence/medical care.  I would note here, I uploaded a corrected copy of the MVAs DR-15A to this report. The original copy was mailed to the MVA describing the suspects movements as lethargic, which was based on my personal recollection. However, upon review of the body-worn camera footage, I feel a better description would actually be off-balance or dazed as opposed to lethargic. The corrected copy has the word lethargic crossed out and initialed for any future use or reference, and includes the corrected description of the suspects off-balance/dazed appearance.  TRAINING AND CERTIFICATION:  - Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests (SFSTs) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.   - Enhanced DUI Enforcement course through Maryland Police and Correctional Training Commissions.   - Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.) Training.  SUSPECT:  NAME: LUKE MASON GOODRICH (W/M)   DATE OF BIRTH: APRIL 15, 1979   ADDRESS: 11007 CHELSEA WAY, LAUREL, MARYLAND 20723   DATE/TIME OF COLLISION: AUGUST 29, 2023 @ APPROX. 2012 HOURS   DATE/TIME OF TEST REFUSAL: AUGUST 29, 2023 @ APPROX. 2242 HOURS   DWI #: 23-122    VEHICLE REGISTRATION: MARYLAND 4FE5785   VIN: WBAJA7C57KWW08130   YEAR/MAKE/MODEL: 2019 BMW SEDAN  VICTIM:  NAME: KENNETH RICHARD DOLLENGER (W/M) DATE OF BIRTH: JANUARY 14, 2001 ADDRESS:17 HAINES AVENUE, RISING SUN, MARYLAND 21911  VEHICLE REGISTRATION: MARYLAND 74234CG VIN: 5NPEC4AC9DH585733   YEAR/MAKE: 2013 HYUNDAI REGISTERED OWNER: DAVID KENNETH DOLLENGER  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE ONE):  On August 29, 2023, at approximately 2012 hours, I, Trooper First Class Scott (#7217) of the Maryland State Police, was dispatched to the area of Route 1 and Little New York Road, Rising Sun, Maryland 21911 in response to a head-on motor vehicle collision involving an impaired operator. I arrived on scene at approximately 2022 hours.    Upon arrival, I observed two disabled vehicles. One vehicle, a Hyundai passenger car (see VICTIM), was in the roadway of Route 1, whereas the other vehicle, a black BMW, (see SUSPECT) was resting with its rear bumper atop the guardrail of southbound Route 1. I learned over the course of investigation that both operators were conscious and outside their vehicles. Emergency medical services was on scene coordinating medical aid for those involved.    Between speaking with the involved operators and via telephone with two witnesses, I gathered the black BMW was traveling northbound on Route 1 as the victims Hyundai was traveling southbound. The black BMW attempted to overtake the vehicle(s) ahead of it, crossing the center-line from the northbound lane into the southbound lane. Once in the southbound lane, the BMW collided head-on with the Hyundai.    At the time of my arrival, I gathered the operator of the Hyundai, Kenneth Richard Dollenger (see VICTIM) was being treated in an ambulance. The operator of vehicle one, Luke Mason Goodrich (see SUSPECT) was standing along the southbound guardrail near his vehicle with his dog.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE TWO):  Upon contact with Goodrich, I observed he was injured. He had blood about his hand(s) and around his nose/mouth. When I first started to attempt to talk to him, Luke seemed off-balance and dazed. He was seated against the guardrail, but seemed to shift about in a manner as if he was having trouble balancing himself. He then shook his head and took some time to start responding to me attempting to talk to him. As Goodrich spoke, I noticed his speech was slurred.  Goodrich was claiming that he was a passenger of the BMW, and that the operator was a friend of his named Todd. He claimed to not know where Todd went, and despite my questioning he was insistent that he was not the operator. Goodrich told me he was traveling to Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. He told me I had stopped a while back because I didnt want to drive . . . I had been drinking. He then offered a different response, saying I didnt drive because I was drinking. However, the extensive damage to the BMW and the deployment of several airbags made it appear unlikely Goodrich could have been in the front passenger seat and be capable of walking around still. When confronted on this, Goodrich said he was actually seated in a back passenger seat. I found his explanation convoluted and I had some difficulty following it (which caused me to suspect he was lying), but Goodrich claimed to have let his friend Todd drive because Goodrich himself had been drinking.    When examining Goodrichs vehicle, I observed a small shot bottle of Absolut Vodka in plain view on the rear passenger floorboard (towards the passenger side). However, I did not climb completely aboard the vehicle to attempt to examine it closer. I was able to read a portion of its label (I could essentially see the lettering -LUT over top of the lettering -KA) and recognized the font and lettering as the Absolut Vodka brand. Absolut is a commonly known brand of vodka with bold blue lettering.    Another thing I observed was that there did not appear to be any blood anywhere else in the vehicle except for the area of the drivers seat. I did not see any blood along the back passenger seats, and the front passenger seat had a blanket folded atop of it. The drivers seat had blood smeared on it, and the drivers airbag also had blood spattered on it. As I observed previously, Goodrich had a noticeable amount of his blood about his hand(s) and face. Injuries to his hands and, especially, his face would logically leave blood on the front drivers airbag (i.e. that extending from the steering wheel). I also saw droplets of blood leading from the area of the drivers seat, along the pavement to the guardrail where Goodrich was located. There was blood smeared on the guardrail as well.    Eventually, I was also able to make telephone contact with two witnesses: Amber Jones (DOB: 10/26/1991), and her husband, James Jones (DOB: 10/07/1992). Amber and James told me they personally witnessed the vehicle collision in this case and they remained on scene for under five minutes. They described the operator of the BMW as a tall, white male (James said possibly latino, but Amber corrected this to white), with short brown hair. They said he was skinny, wearing a black or brown short sleeve polo or t-shirt. They also said he had a dog with him and he was in (approximately) his late thirties. They said they personally saw this individual climb out of the drivers seat of the BMW before he said He cant get out!. They also said that, after the dog got out of the BMW, the described male stopped showing concern about any other potential occupants. The male didnt mention anyone else in the car. Amber and James said they did not see anyone else in the car, nor did they see anyone else disembark from it.    Overall, the description of the male provided by Amber and James matched Goodrich. Their lack of visual on anyone else escaping from or being in the BMW, coupled with their description of Goodrichs apparent lack of concern once his dog was free from the vehicle, indicates there was not another human occupant.    Ultimately, both Goodrich and Dollenger were transported via ambulance to ChristianaCare Christiana Hospital in Delaware for treatment. I remained on scene for a time to continue investigation. I walked up and down both sides of Route 1 near the area of the collision. I shined my flashlight into the treeline along both sides of Route 1 and verbally called out several times to determine if anyone was lying in the woods near the scene of the accident. I did not hear or see anyone in the treeline during my check.  Once I checked the treeline and both vehicles were towed, I cleared the scene, en route to the North East Barrack to collect a blood-kit, DR-15, and DR-15A to bring to Christiana Hospital to present to Goodrich. The following facts caused me to believe Goodrich operated the BMW while impaired/under the influence of alcohol:  - Goodrich was involved in a motor vehicle collision. He was injured, with a fair amount of blood about his hand(s) and face. - Witnesses reported observing a male matching Goodrichs description getting out of the drivers seat of the BMW (the at-fault vehicle as I gathered). - Goodrich claimed he was a passenger of the BMW, and he let a friend drive because Goodrich himself had been drinking (the item of note here being the admission of drinking). - I observed a small bottle of Absolut Vodka on the rear passenger floorboard of the BMW. - Goodrich was slurring his words.     - Goodrich seemed off-balance and dazed when I first attempted to talk to him. - I did not observe blood along any of the seats in the BMW, except for the drivers seat and the drivers airbag. Considering the blood on his person, Goodrich should have left blood where he claimed to sit if he was being truthful. - Droplets of blood led from the drivers seat to the guardrail where Goodrich stood. - A check of the treeline failed to reveal another individual hidden nearby.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE THREE):   Considering the circumstances, Goodrich was obviously incapable of participating in standardized field sobriety tests. I transported a blood-kit and the appropriate paperwork to Christiana Hospital in Delaware. I made contact with Goodrich there. He was laying in a hospital bed as I spoke to him. He consented to certain parts of our interaction being recorded and not others. Off-camera (per his request that I deactivate the camera), he told me he drank five or six pale ales a couple of hours before the crash. Despite confronting him with the witness information indicating his operation of the BMW, he still claimed his friend Todd drove the vehicle.    I read Goodrich his DR-15 Advice of Rights verbatim and in its entirety in English. Goodrich asked me to re-activate my body-worn camera when he was deciding whether to take the test. He ultimately said he did not feel he was capable of making an informed decision and refused to consent to a blood test for alcohol content.    Goodrich later consented to allowing me to access the pocket of his jeans while I was attempting to collect his drivers license. Upon accessing one of the pockets of his jeans, I observed what appeared to be a car ignition key. I asked him if I could re-activate my body-worn camera. He consented to my camera being re-activated, and then verbally acknowledged his consent while the camera was on. With his verbal consent recorded, I reached into the pocket of his jeans and retrieved the ignition key for the BMW.    I also noticed as I spoke to him in the better lighting of the hospital that Goodrichs eyes were bloodshot. I also detected the odor of alcohol emanating from his breath as he spoke.    I also learned upon checking the BMWs registration that it is actually registered to Goodrich.    Based on the following facts, there is probable cause to believe Goodrich operated his BMW while under the influence of/while impaired by alcohol:  - Goodrich was involved in a motor vehicle collision. He was injured and bleeding a fair amount. - Witnesses reported observing a male matching Goodrichs description getting out of the drivers seat of the BMW (the at-fault vehicle as I gathered). - Goodrich claimed he was a passenger of the BMW, and he let a friend drive because Goodrich himself had been drinking (the item of note here is the admission of drinking). - I observed a small bottle of Absolut Vodka on the rear passenger floorboard of the BMW. - I did not observe blood along any of the seats in the BMW, except for the drivers seat and the drivers airbag. Goodrich was bleeding a fair amount on scene. - Droplets of blood led from the drivers seat to the guardrail where Goodrich stood. - A check of the treeline of the crash scene failed to reveal another individual hidden nearby.     - Goodrichs eyes were bloodshot, and his speech was slurred. On contact, he seemed dazed and off-balance.I know through training, knowledge, and experience that these are indicators of alcohol impairment.     - Goodrich had an odor of alcohol emanating from his breath as he spoke.     - Goodrich admitted to drinking five or six pale ales a couple of hours prior to the crash. This was off-camera due to his request. He admitted to drinking on camera while at the crash scene.     - Goodrich is the registered owner of the BMW, the at-fault vehicle.     - Goodrich consented to me accessing the contents of his jeans pocket. He also allowed me to record this and his consent. I located the BMWs ignition key in his jeans pocket.     - The witnesses observations, the presence of the ignition key in his pocket, the vehicle being registered to him, and the location of blood in the vehicle as compared to him collectively indicate Goodrich was actually the operator, not a passenger.     - Goodrich refused to consent to a blood-test to measure his blood alcohol content.    Based on the totality of the above circumstances, and my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper, there is probable cause to believe Goodrich is the at-fault operator of the BMW, and thereby operated said vehicle while impaired by/under the influence of alcohol, endangering other motorists and the life of Dollenger, whose vehicle Goodrich struck head-on. Dollenger was also transported for medical care as a result of the collision.  CLOSING REMARKS:  Due to mutual sanitary concerns between myself and Goodrich (his hands were caked with blood), Goodrich opted not to sign his copies of the DR-15 and the DR-15A. They were accordingly marked Unable to Sign. Goodrich was provided with copies of the appropriate paperwork and notified of the tow company that collected his vehicle (Banks Auto Recyclers and Towing, which was written on a citizens brochure). Goodrichs dog was collected by Cecil County Animal Control from the crash scene. The decision for animal control to collect his dog was made because of Goodrichs impaired state, and his communicated desire to call someone from an extended distance to collect his dog. He was duly notified of Cecil County Animal Control possessing his dog pending his release from the hospital.    Goodrich was notified that he is required to appear in court when requested. After issuing him the appropriate copies of his paperwork, I cleared from ChristianaCare Christiana Hospital, en route back to the Maryland State Police North East Barrack to return the unused blood-kit and place Goodrichs paperwork and drivers license in outgoing mail to the MVA.    Goodrich was charged with Driving Under the Influence of Alcohol, Driving While Impaired by Alcohol, Driving While Impaired by a Controlled Dangerous Substance, Driving While Impaired by Drugs/Drugs and Alcohol Cannot Drive Safely, Reckless Driving, Negligent Driving, Driver Changing Lanes When Unsafe, and Failure to Drive Vehicle on Right Half of Roadway When Required.    Case cleared.    All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/30/2023 19:18:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/16/2023 13:48:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Jones</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7445</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Spayd</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5369</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Scott</LastName>
            <FirstName>Conor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7217</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>519924</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/29/2023 20:12:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/30/2023 19:10:09</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/30/2023 19:10:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>44</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/30/2023 17:10:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7230</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/03/2023 04:11:01</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386534</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>GOODRICH</LastName>
               <FirstName>LUKE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MASON</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/15/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.71680794E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>08/30/2023 16:56:54</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G362</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>GOODRICH</LastName>
               <FirstName>LUKE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>MASON</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/15/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.71680794E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>G362</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/30/2023 16:56:54</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>11007</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Chelsea</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Laurel</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20723</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1096</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.899636</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.142673</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>570</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>772</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>1974</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>08/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 22:54:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 22:54:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 22:54:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>22</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 22:57:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/02/2023 22:57:33</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386848</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>DOLLENGER</LastName>
               <FirstName>KENNETH</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>RICHARD</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/14/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/02/2023 22:57:19</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K530</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>DOLLENGER</LastName>
               <FirstName>KENNETH</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>RICHARD</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/14/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D452</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>K530</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/02/2023 22:57:19</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>17</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Haines</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Rising Sun</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21911</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1792</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.063451</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.700203</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>V</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 22:57:33</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:20</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/16/2023 13:11:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/16/2023 13:11:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>387968</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>U</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>JONES</LastName>
               <FirstName>JAMES</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/16/2023 13:11:37</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>JONES</LastName>
               <FirstName>JAMES</FirstName>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/16/2023 13:11:37</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1366</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Chrome Hill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Jarrettsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21084</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1622</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.433102</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.619421</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>484</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>667</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0002</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/16/2023 13:11:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:27</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/16/2023 13:12:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/16/2023 13:12:59</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>387969</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>U</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>JONES</LastName>
               <FirstName>AMBER</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/16/2023 13:12:50</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A516</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>JONES</LastName>
               <FirstName>AMBER</FirstName>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A516</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/16/2023 13:12:50</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1366</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Chrome Hill</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Jarrettsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21084</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1622</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.433102</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.619421</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>484</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>667</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0002</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/16/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/16/2023 13:12:59</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/30/2023 19:10:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/30/2023 19:10:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156614</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 22:55:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/02/2023 22:55:13</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WBAJA7C57KWW08130</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>BMW</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>4S</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4FE5785</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156721</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>VI</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7217</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 22:58:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7217</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/02/2023 22:58:59</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>4</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5NPEC4AC9DH585733</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HYUN</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>74234CG</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>