<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-030853</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/01/2023 21:12:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/01/2023 21:12:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/01/2023 20:33:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/01/2023 20:33:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>09/01/2023 23:36:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/01/2023 21:12:15</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4816</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/16/2023 10:38:34</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>W/B I-68 at 70 mile marker</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>705696</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/01/2023 21:12:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/02/2023 14:26:41</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>705696</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>70</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I68 Wb</StreetName>
         <City>Little Orleans</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-78.34769</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.70442</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/01/2023 21:12:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/01/2023 21:12:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>52</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/25/2023 14:31:54</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/01/2023 21:12:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:40</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI Case Number 23-090  Attachments: MVA printout of Vehicle Registration MVA printout of Erin Lee Leishears Drivers Licence including photograph Copy of Citations issued Copy of DR-15 Copy of DR-15A Copy of Notification of results of test for Alcohol Consentration Copy of Statement of Probable Cause  Suspect Name: Erin Lee Leishear Sex: Female Race: White DOB: 09/09/1970  On August 1, 2023, I, Cpl. Kyle was dispatched by the Maryland State Police Cumberland Barrack to respond to westbound Interstate 68 at the 70-mile marker, located in Allegany County, Maryland for a motorist who was contacted by CHART courtesy patrol and was acting strangely. EMS was also alerted to respond to the call. Upon my arrival, EMS was already on scene as well as The CHART courtesy patrol worker Michael Lee Shaffer. Both Mr. Shaffer and the EMS on scene related the operator/sole occupant of the vehicle appeared to be under the influence of alcohol and was having trouble answering simple questions. I observed a silver Honda Accord bearing Maryland registration IFE5689 parked on the right shoulder of the interstate. The drivers side door was open, and an EMT was at the door attempting to speak to the driver/sole occupant of the vehicle. Upon my contact of the driver, I immediately detected a strong odor of alcoholic beverage coming from the drivers person and from inside the vehicle. I asked the driver what happened this night, and she mumbled, being stupid. I asked her how she was being stupid, and she mumbled drinking. I did observe the drivers eyes to be watery and blood shot, and she was unable to concentrate on what she was saying or doing. I then asked the driver (later identified by her MVA photo to be Erin Lee Leishear) if she had a drivers license, she stated she did. I asked Ms. Leishear for her drivers license and she began to look in a backpack and then retrieved what appeared to be a scrapbook and looked through it. Ms. Leishear did not seem to be able to keep focused on what she was doing, and I had to repeat several times I needed her drivers license which she was never able to produce. I then asked Ms. Leishear for her name, and date of birth. Ms. Leishear stated her name was Erin Lee Leishear and her date of birth was 9/9/1970. It is noted Ms. Leishear was very slow to respond to questions and when she did respond was lethargic and slurring her words. Ms. Leishear also seemed as though she was confused by simple questions. I asked EMS personnel if they had any indication of any medical issues which they would need to treat, they responded they did not. I asked Ms. Leishear to exit the vehicle. Ms. Leishear was not able to exit the vehicle without assistance and did need to use the vehicle for balance once in a standing position. I did notice Ms. Leishear was wearing white Croc style shoes which were worn on the wrong feet. I asked Ms. Leishear where she was from, and she stated Howard County, I asked where she was heading, she stated she was going to Fulton which is also in Howard County Maryland. I then asked if she knew where she was, and she stated she did not. I asked Ms. Leishear where she had been drinking whether it be at a bar or her home or in the vehicle, she stated she did not know. I then asked her to step out and come to the rear of my vehicle. Ms.Leishear had could not exit the vehicle without assistance and once out of the vehicle, Ms. Leishear had to use the vehicle to balance herself. Once at the rear of the vehicle, Ms. Leishear tried to lean her back against the vehicle when she slid off of the vehicle and fell to the ground. Ms. Leishear was assisted to a standing position and leaned up against the rear of the vehicle. Ms. Leishear was asked if she was ok, and she stated she was. Ms. Leishear was asked if she was the registered owner of the vehicle which she stated she was. This was later confirmed to be false, the registered owner is Barbara Lee Hildreth. I then asked Ms. Leishear to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Ms. Leishear was not able to concentrate on the stimulis for this test. I did notice her eyes to be watery and bloodshot. I did notice Nystagmus in both eyes, however, Ms. Lieshear did not hold focus on the stimuls long enough to perform a proper test.  Ms. Leishear stated she did not want to take the walk and turn or one leg stand tests. It was obvious Ms. Leishears lack of balance would make these test unsafe for her.  Based on my observations and Ms. Leishear admission to drinking, Iplaced Ms. Leishear under arrest at approximately 2111 hours for driving under the influence of alcohol. Ms. Leishear was placed in my marked patrol unit and was transported to the MSP Cumberland Barrack. While en route to the barrack, Ms. Lieshear was whimpering and did pass out. Ms. Leishears cell phone was taken with her to the barrack. Buckely Towing was contacted and did remove the vehicle to be stored at their tow lot.  I attempted to look for a drivers license inside the vehicle and was able to observe a partially empty fifth bottle of Smirnoff Vodka and an empty mini bottle of watermelon vodka. There were also two empty mini bottles of watermelon vodka in the grass beside the vehicle. While attempting to find Ms. Lieshears drivers license or other form of identification, I did observe a prescription bottle of Meloxicam which is a non controlled arthritis medication bearing the name Erin Leishear. I was unable to locate any type of wallet or identification for Ms. Leishear besides the prescription bottle with her name on it.   I was later provided with an MVA printout of Ms. Leiishears license information and found that Ms. Leishear has a driving restriction for corrective lenses and is court ordered to participate in an ignition interlock program related to a prior DUI conviction on 11/09/2022. It is noted there was no ignition interlock mechanism in the vehicle.  Upon arrival at the Cumberland Barrack, Ms. Leishear was read the DR-15 Advice of rights and consented to take a breath test at 2230 hours.The test of breath was conducted by Sgt. Divelbiss who is a trained and certified operator of the EC/IR Breathalyzer. The breath specimen collected from Ms. Leishear was found to contain an alcohol concentration of .28 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. Ms. Leishear was issued appropriate paperwork. Ms. Leishear was unable to provide a name or phone number of a person to pick her up from the barrack. Ms. Leishear was therefore transported to the Allegany County Detention Center to await a hearing in front of a District Court Commissioner pursuant to MSP policy  All events did occur in Allegany County, Maryland.    </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP0414</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 15:46:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP0414</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/24/2023 19:31:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cosgrove</LastName>
            <FirstName>Laurence</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6630</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Divelbiss</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4425</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Brant</LastName>
            <FirstName>Pennie</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0414</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>520302</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/01/2023 20:33:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP0414</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 14:42:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP0414</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/02/2023 14:42:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>52</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP0414</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 14:38:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP0414</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/02/2023 18:10:14</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386813</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Leishear</LastName>
               <FirstName>Erin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/09/1970 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/02/2023 14:36:27</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Leishear</LastName>
               <FirstName>Erin</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/09/1970 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L260</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/02/2023 14:36:27</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>70</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Mm I68 Wb</StreetName>
               <City>Little Orleans</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-78.34768999999999</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.704420038813126</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>310</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2888</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP0414</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 18:10:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP0414</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 18:10:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP0414</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 18:10:14</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:21</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>77</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP0414</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 15:43:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/02/2023 15:43:05</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>386817</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hildreth</LastName>
               <FirstName>Barbara</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/06/1946 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/02/2023 15:36:03</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H436</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B616</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hildreth</LastName>
               <FirstName>Barbara</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/06/1946 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H436</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B616</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/02/2023 15:36:03</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP0414</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 15:43:05</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:17</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>56</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP0414</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 15:44:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/02/2023 15:44:10</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>266929</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Shaffer</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/22/1967 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2020 12:56:54</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S160</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Shaffer</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <DOB>04/22/1967 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S160</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2020 12:56:54</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1223</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>McKenzie Hollow</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Meyersdale</City>
               <StateCode>PA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>15552</Zip5>
               <Zip4>8539</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-78.9256198</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.7383518</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>814</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>521</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>4672</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2020 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP0414</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 15:44:10</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:17</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP0414</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 14:42:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP0414</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/02/2023 14:42:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156710</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP0414</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/02/2023 14:47:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP0414</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/02/2023 14:47:59</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1HGCV1F46JA113074</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2018</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>4T</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1FE5689</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>10</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>