<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-025113</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/14/2023 02:30:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/14/2023 02:30:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/14/2023 02:10:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/14/2023 02:10:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI, DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 02:30:41</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/15/2023 10:40:22</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>700972</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 02:30:42</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/15/2023 04:54:01</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>700972</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Trappe</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21673</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.058648</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.6267655</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/14/2023 02:30:36</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/14/2023 02:30:36</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/30/2023 18:27:14</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/14/2023 02:30:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 14:28:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police Easton Barrack I MSP marked vehicle I-51, does have MVR and incident was recorded via body camera/In car camera.  Defendant: Jahdeja Olivia Baines Date of Birth: 07/18/2001 Date of Arrest: 04/14/2023 Times of Arrest: 0210hours DUI #: 23-58-150(Easton Barrack)  CERTIFICATION  TRAINING *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) *Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) *Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On 07/14/2023at approximately 0210hours, I, Trooper Repa #7124, Maryland State Police, Easton Barrack,was on mobile traffic in the area of Ocean Gateway and Wise Lane, Trappe, Talbot County, Maryland. While on routine patrol, I observed a gray Toyota sedan unable to maintain their lane. The gray Toyotas right-side tires went over the white solid white line twice both approximately a foot after correcting itself in lane 2 each time. The gray Toyota Camry was bearing Maryland registration 3FA7903. TFC Johnston was using pro laser 3 in the area and pointed his laser at the gray Toyota. TFC Johnston advised the vehicle was traveling 62 mph in a 55 mph zone. TFC Johnston is certified to operate the pro laser. After getting a speed, I observed half the gray Toyota travel over the solid white line before it corrected itself in lane 2. I activated my vehicles emergency lights/siren and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the gray Toyota on the drivers side. I advised the driver the reason for the stop and requested her drivers license and registration card. The driver was identified by her drivers license as Jahdeja Olivia Baines (DOB 07/18/2001 W/F). I asked Baines where she was coming from and where she was headed. Baines advised from her house in Easton, Maryland and to her boyfriends house in Cambridge, Maryland. I observed her eyes to be glassy and bloodshot. I asked how much she had to drink and Baines advised nothing. I smelled a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on her breath. I advised Baines I could smell the alcohol on her breath and Baines advised earlier in the day she drank Taylor Port wine. I advised Baines I was going to perform standardized field sobriety tests to which she complied. I positioned Baines clear of traffic in front of her vehicle.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed in front of the gray Toyota. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and the temperature was in the 70s. Lighting conditions consisted of flashlights and vehicle headlights. All forward facing emergency vehicle lights were deactivated during the tests. Baines appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. Prior to HGN I observed Bainess pants were all wet in the crouch area. I asked Baines why it was wet, and she advised she went to the bathroom on herself.  Prior to performing Field Sobriety Tests, I asked Baines the following questions: Any injuries- advised no Any medications- birth control Wear contacts or glasses- advised no  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. Iproperly explained the test. A pens tip was used as the stimulus for the test and held approximately 12 inches from Bainess eyes. Baines was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes until told to stop. Bainess pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Iasked Baines if she understood the directions, and she stated, yes.Baines was positioned away from passing traffic to ensure the results of the HGN test were not compromised.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes  *Vertical Gaze Nystagmus  Present in both eyes  WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)  Prior toBaines performing the test, Iproperly explained the test and physically demonstrated how the test should be done. I asked Baines if she understood the instructions to the test to which she stated yes.  Walking Stage (1stNine) 1.) Missed heel to toe more than a half an inch on step 2.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine) 1.) Missed heel to toe more than a half an inch on step 3 and 9. 2.) Stepped offline more than an inch on step 3.  Turn was done unsatisfactory. Baines failed to do turn as instructed and did one fluent motion.  ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed)  Prior to Baines performing the test, Iproperly explained the test andphysically demonstrated how the test should be done.Baineswas asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, yes.  Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 1-10: 1.) Foot down.  Seconds 11-20: 1.Foot down. 2.Swayed.  Seconds 21-30: 1.Foot down. 2.Swayed.  Preliminary Breath Test: I explained a Preliminary Breath Test (PBT). After explaining, Baines agreed with the result of .11. During the test, Baines advised she drank prior to leaving her house.  ARREST :  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Baines was driving a motor vehicle impaired: *smell of an alcoholic beverage on breath. *unable to maintain single lane. *admission to consuming an alcoholic beverage. *Glassy and bloodshot eyes. *using the bathroom on herself. *Observed signs of impairment as field sobriety tests were performed. *PBT results.  I arrested Bainesfor driving under the influence at 0230hours. She was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. Baines was read the DR-15 form on the Motor Vehicle Administration website in English on my in-car laptop. While the Dr-15 was being played, I drove Baines to the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack. At the conclusion of the form and when we arrived at the barrack, Baines agreed to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the DR-15 indicating the same (0248).  INTOXIMETER TEST: Baines blew a .12 on the intoximeter test.  Baines was given all copies of pertinent paperwork at the Easton State Police Barrack. Baines received a ride home from her mother.  All events occurred in TalbotCounty, Maryland. Request this case be closed. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/24/2023 08:22:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7124</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/24/2023 09:23:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Johnston</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7204</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Goldman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stansbury</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5099</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Repa</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alexander</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7124</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>514555</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/14/2023 02:10:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 05:03:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7124</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/15/2023 05:03:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>21</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 05:14:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:55</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>208575</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Baines</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jahdeja</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Olivia</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/18/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16616527E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>10/09/2018 11:57:07</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J320</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Baines</LastName>
               <FirstName>Jahdeja</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Olivia</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/18/2001 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16616527E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>B520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J320</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/09/2018 11:57:07</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1070</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>N</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Washington</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>506</SubNumber>
               <City>Easton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.0644705</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.793796</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>443</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7761</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 05:14:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 05:14:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 05:03:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7124</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/15/2023 05:03:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155142</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7124</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/15/2023 05:20:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7124</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/15/2023 05:20:37</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>07/15/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>4T1BE46K07U718253</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2007</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CAM</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3FA7903</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>