<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-019419</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/31/2023 01:21:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/31/2023 01:21:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/31/2023 00:47:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/31/2023 00:47:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>On May 31st, 2023 at 0108 hours, I Trooper Lowery #7448 arrested Niccol Mayfield for DWI, DUI, and DUI by controlled dangerous substance.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 01:21:59</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/07/2023 16:45:39</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>695903</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 01:22:00</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 02:43:13</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>695903</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Charles</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Towson</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.62836</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.39211</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/31/2023 01:21:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/31/2023 01:21:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 10:48:43</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 01:21:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 19:56:06</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DWI # 23-302  R-43 is equipped with a mobile video recording device and I had my Axon body camera throughout theincident. This incident was both audibly and visually recorded.  All video requests can be emailed to Sgt. Twardowski atJoseph.Twardowski@Maryland.Gov.  Defendant: Niccol Dannet Mayfield  Date of Birth: 11/08/1989  Date of Arrest:05/31/2023  Time of Arrest: 0108 hours  MD DL: MD-10272478218  Training Certifications:  -Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police.  -NHSTA certified to conduct field sobriety test (SFST).  - Certified Preliminary Breath Test Operator.  -Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement through Baltimore County Police Department.  Narrative:  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On May 31st, 2023 at approximately 0040 hours, I Trooper Lowery #7448, was on routine patrol in marked Maryland State Police vehicle R-43. I was running rear radar Kustom Golden Eagle II (SN DE45549) which was tested before and after shift. I saw a vehicle in my rearview mirror approaching in lane 1 at a high rate of speed. My radar read 78 MPH in a 55 MPH posted zone. The vehicle then got into lane 4, and I got behind the vehicle. I saw there was no rear registration plate on the vehicle. I then initiated a traffic stop on the gray Nissan Murano.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2):  I approached the gray Nissan Murano and saw there was a paper registration NY: ZJU7029 inside the vehicles rear window. I approached the passenger side door and spoke with the driver, Niccol Mayfield (DOB 11/08/1989), later identified by her Maryland drivers license. I immediately detected a strong odor of marijuana and an alcoholic beverage emanating from inside the vehicle. I advised Mayfield the reason for the stop, and asked for her drivers license and registration. After Mayfield handed me her registration I asked how much alcohol has she had to drink tonight. Mayfield stated Two drinks. I then asked Mayfield how much marijuana she used prior to driving. The NY registration: ZJU7029, would not return through MVA/METERS. I then ran the VIN: JN8AZ1FY1EW302628 through Maryland. The vehicle came back to a 2013 Nissan Murano, and no registered owner.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3):  The surface was flatand free from debris. Weather conditions were clear and the temperatures were in the high 60s  Due to speeding 78 MPH in a 55 MPH zone, the smell of marijuana and alcohol emanating from inside the vehicle, and admission to drinking alcohol prior to driving I asked Mayfield to perform Standardized Field Sobriety tests.  I asked Mayfield to step outside the vehicle and Mayfield stated Are you locking me up?  I asked the following questions before asking Mayfield to perform Standardized Field Sobriety tests.  How much alcohol have you had to drink today? Two drinks of margaritas, twenty minutes prior to driving.  Medication? None.  Narcotics? Mayfield advised she smoked marijuana twenty minutes prior to driving.   Diabetic? No.  Injuries? None.  Highest level of education? Some college.  Where are you coming from? Tomes bar in Baltimore City, Maryland.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (4/6 clues observed)  The first test given was Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Mayfields eyes. Mayfieldwas instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes, not moving her head, until told to stop. Mayfields pupils were equal in size, had no resting nystagmus and showed equal tracking.  1) Lack of Smooth Pursuit- Present in both eyes.  2) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation- Present in both eyes.  3) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees- Not present.  Vertical Nystagmus- Not present.   WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)  Prior to Mayfieldperforming the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should beconducted. Mayfield was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot with heel to toe touching. Mayfield was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her sides and to remain in that position until told to begin the test. Mayfield was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. Mayfieldwas instructed to keep her hands flat at her sides, keeping her eyes focused on her feet and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, I explained and demonstrated to Mayfield to keep her lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to the left to turn completely around. I again explained and demonstrated to Mayfield the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Mayfield was instructed that once she began the test that she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keeping her hands down by her sides, looking down at her feet, and counting aloud each step. I asked Mayfield if she understood the test, and she stated Yes.For demonstration purposes, I only demonstrated three (3) steps in each direction, with a satisfactory example of the turn.  Mayfield was bare foot for the Walk and Turn test. Mayfield advised she had heels in her vehicle. I asked Mayfield if she wanted to wear heels, and she stated no.  WALKING STAGE (1st Nine):  1) Mayfield missed every heel to toe step in excess of  an inch to step 9.  2) Mayfield created an improper turn. Mayfield stopped at step 9, then asked This way or that way? Mayfield then spun to her left keeping her right foot planted. Then turned again to her left facing the guard rail.  WALKING STAGE (2nd Nine):  1)Mayfield missed every heel to toe step in excess of  and inch to step 6.  3) Mayfield took 6 steps instead of the instructed 9.  4) Mayfield then stopped the test when she reached the metal guard rail at step 6.  ONE LEG STAND (3/4) clues observed:  Prior to Mayfield performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Mayfield was instructed to stand with her feet together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While her leg was raised she was instructed to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Mayfield was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, Yes. Mayfield utilized her left leg for the One Leg Stand test.  1) Puts foot down  One time between 0-10 second mark. Two times between 10-20 second mark.  2) Sways-One time between 0-10 second mark.  3) Hops-One time during 0-10 second mark.  ARREST:  Based on my training, knowledge, and experience, and the following observations: the strong odor of analcoholic beverage and marijuana emanating from Mayfields person, speeding 78 MPH in a 55 MPH zone, admission to drinking alcohol and smoking marijuana twenty minutes prior to driving, and her demeanor beingconsistent with someone under the influence of alcohol and CDS, Mayfield would in fact be a driver under the influence of alcohol, and CDS. Mayfield was then placed under arrested on May 31st, 2023 at 0108 hours. Mayfields oral cavity was checked after the arrest.  I placed Mayfield in my front passenger seat in vehicle R-43 to be transported to Golden Ring R barrack. Upon arrival, I took photographs of Mayfield.  On May 31st, 2023 at approximately 0130 hours, the DR-15 Advice of Rights was read to Mayfield in English.  On May 31st, 2023 at 0152 hours, Mayfield provided a breath specimen that contained an alcohol concentration of .05 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  Mayfield was provided a copy of the citations for DUI/DWI, traffic infractions, DR-15 Advice of Rights, and the Intox EC/IR-II test.  Mayfield was released to a sober driving after receiving the documents for DUI/DWI.  I request this case the closed by arrest.  All the above events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 03:59:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7448</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 04:08:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zinn</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5682</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lowery</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jake</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7448</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508853</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7448</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508853</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7448</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508853</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14587</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14587</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7448</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508853</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7448</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508853</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16627</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16627</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7448</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508853</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>18599</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>18599</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7448</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508853</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21304</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21304</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7448</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>508853</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16709</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/31/2023 00:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16709</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7448</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:48:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>378517</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Mayfield</LastName>
               <FirstName>Niccol</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dannet</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/08/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 02:35:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M143</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Mayfield</LastName>
               <FirstName>Niccol</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dannet</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/08/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M143</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>N240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 02:35:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:49:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:49:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:49:31</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:08</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7448</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 02:47:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153611</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/31/2023 02:51:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7448</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/31/2023 02:51:30</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JN8AZ1FY1EW302628</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>MUR</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/05/2023 22:56:10</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/05/2023 22:56:10</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/17/2023 10:48:43</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 22:56:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 19:56:06</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On June 5th, 2023 at 2300 hours, I Trooper Lowery #7448, submitted an MVA referral for Mayfield.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7448</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/05/2023 22:57:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7448</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/05/2023 23:03:48</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Zinn</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5682</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lowery</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jake</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7448</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>