<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-026051</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>07/21/2023 16:44:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>07/21/2023 16:44:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>07/21/2023 16:17:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>07/21/2023 16:17:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Vehicle collision resulting in DUI arrest.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>07/21/2023 16:44:13</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5948</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 09:54:40</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>HARFORD RD/ FALLSTON RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>701629</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/21/2023 16:44:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 02:51:53</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>701629</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Harford</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>07/21/2023 16:44:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>07/21/2023 16:44:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/26/2023 02:57:18</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>07/21/2023 16:44:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/26/2023 02:57:18</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText> DUI Case #23-181  Incident was recorded by my state issued body camera. Title on Evidence.com 23-MSP-026051.    TRAINING/CERTIFICATES  * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, 2022.  Phase #1 - Vehicle in Motion  On July 21, 2023, at approximately 1617 hours, I, TFC De La Cruz was dispatched to make contact with drivers at Advanced Auto Parts located at 212 Mountain Road, Fallston Md 21047 involved in a motor vehicle collision which occurred at Rt 152 and RT 147. I arrived on scene and observed a black Chevy Silverado pickup truck displaying Maryland registration 1BT1336 that had rear-ended the other vehicle while it was stopped at a traffic light.  Phase #2 - Personal Contact  I contacted the driver of the Silverado who was out of the vehicle. The driver was later identified through his Maryland drivers license as John William Ritter (DOB:10/22/1961). I immediately could smell a strong odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from Ritters person. Ritter was lethargic with his movements and stumbled as he walked around his vehicle. I asked Ritter where he was coming from and he stated from work. I asked Ritter if he had anything to drink and Ritter stated A beer. Ritter had bloodshot and very glassy eyes. Ritters speech was slow and slurred. Based on the above observations, I asked Ritter to perform standardized field sobriety tests, to which he agreed. While standing directly in front of Ritter, prior to performing field sobriety, I could detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. I asked Ritter again if he had consumed any alcoholic beverages prior to driving. Ritter now stated, I had a couple of beers. Two beers, three beers, Budweiser.  Phase #3 - Pre-Arrest Screening  The evaluation was performed in the parking lot of Advanced Auto Parts. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. My vehicles front emergency lights were deactivated during all Field Sobriety Testing.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6 clues)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12-15 inches from Ritters eyes, slightly above his eye level. Ritter was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. I held the stimulus in front of Ritters eyes to check for resting nystagmus, which was not present.  Lack of smooth pursuit  Both eyes  Distinct Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Both eyes  Onset Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees  Both eyes  Walk and Turn  4 of 8 Clues  Prior to Hall performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. I asked Hall if he understood the test and he advised he did.  Instructional Stage:    Balance  Ritter stepped out of the instructional stance.  Ritter began told to do so.   Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Missed Heel to Toe  numerous times  Stepped off-line  Steps 4,5,7,8  Number of Steps - 10   Turn:    Completed turn unsuccessful  Ritter did not perform the turn as instructed. Due to Ritters extreme lack of balance. Ritter fell and I had to catch him to prevent him from injuring himself.   Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  *** Due to Ritters lack of balance and falling during the turn I concluded the rest of the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests to prevent him from hurting himself ***    One Leg Stand  N/A  Not performed.    ARREST  Due to the number of observations, I concluded Ritter was driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 1641 hours, I placed Ritter under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. I transported Ritter to the Bel Air Barrack for processing. While en route to the barrack, my vehicle was filled with the odor of an alcoholic beverage. I read the DR-15 form to Ritter at the barrack. I asked Ritter if he had any questions and if he agreed to submit to the intoximeter test. Ritter refused to take the test.  Ritter was issued all pertinent paperwork, including DUI citations, and he was released to the custody of his wife.  Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7273</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/02/2023 03:52:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7273</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/02/2023 04:31:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Parker</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5175</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>DeLaCruz</LastName>
            <FirstName>Christopher</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7273</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>515496</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>07/21/2023 16:17:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7273</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 02:52:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7273</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 02:52:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>61</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7273</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/02/2023 03:42:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/02/2023 03:42:52</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>383885</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Ritter</LastName>
               <FirstName>John</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/22/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>07/31/2023 02:54:28</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>R360</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Ritter</LastName>
               <FirstName>John</FirstName>
               <DOB>10/22/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>R360</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/31/2023 02:54:28</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7273</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/02/2023 03:42:53</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7273</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>07/31/2023 02:52:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7273</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/31/2023 02:52:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>155659</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7273</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/02/2023 03:46:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7273</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/02/2023 03:46:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3GCPKSE79CG113925</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2012</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SLV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>PK</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLK</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1BT1336</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2021</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>5</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>