<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-015304</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/30/2023 03:31:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/30/2023 03:31:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/30/2023 03:18:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/30/2023 03:18:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>23-235 "R" BUSHROD</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 03:32:01</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6354</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/03/2023 11:53:51</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>WHITE MARSH BLVD/ PERRY HALL BLVD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>692408</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 03:32:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/30/2023 04:18:28</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>692408</AddressId>
         <StreetName>White Marsh</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Nottingham</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>BLVD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.47193</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.37987</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 WHITE MARSH BLVD / 0-0 PERRY HALL BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/30/2023 03:31:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/30/2023 03:31:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/03/2023 11:53:51</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 03:32:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 09:52:35</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>           *STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E.) TEAM* The following incident was captured on in-car and body camera  Defendant: Gregory Bushrod Jr.  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: * I am trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (March 2013 SFST NHTSA Manual). * I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor as of February 2016. * I am a Certified Breath Test Operator by the Toxicologist of the State of Maryland as of March 2016. * I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of March 2016. * I am a distinguished graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute as of June 2015 * I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of May 2014. * I am a Preliminary Breath Test Instructor as of May 2019. * I am a RADAR and LIDAR Instructor as of October 2019. * I have apprehended more than 1,000 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On April 30, 2023 at approximately 0316 hours, I (Cpl. Wallace #6323) was on patrol in unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle DUI-1 on westbound Pulaski Hwy approaching White Marsh Blvd Baltimore County, Maryland. I observed a gray Chevrolet Suburban bearing Maryland registration 6DB8762 traveling in front of my patrol vehicle. The Chevrolet was delayed in taking the ramp for westbound White Marsh Blvd and drove through the gore area. When on White Marsh Blvd the Chevrolet was swerving left and right and unable to drive within a single lane.    Right on dotted white line, left  Left on fog line, right on dotted white line  Driving on dotted white line, left  Right on dotted white line, jerk left  Left towards fog line, jerk right  Right towards dotted white line, left  Right and left in lane  Left on fog line, right  Left over fog line, right  Left over fog line, right  I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the Chevrolet. The Chevrolet moved to the right lane and came to a stop in the travel lane when there was a grass shoulder on the left side.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Chevrolet on the driver side and made contact with the male operator of the vehicle, who was the only occupant in the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop and requested his drivers license and vehicle registration. He was identified by his Maryland drivers license as Gregory Bushrod Jr. While speaking with Bushrod, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I deliberately observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. He stated that he was heading home. I returned to my patrol vehicle to notify the barrack who I was out with.   I returned to the Chevrolet and requested Bushrod to exit his vehicle and walk to the front. He complied and exited his vehicle. He dropped his lighter when exiting his vehicle. He told the person on the phone that he was on the beltway, but was on White Marsh Blvd. While speaking with Bushrod outside the vehicle, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. When asked about alcohol consumption prior to driving, he stated that he had 3 beers (dogfish IPA). He stated that he just left Sizzle. I informed Bushrod that I wanted him to perform standardized field sobriety tests, to which he agreed to the tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests.   I asked Bushrod the following questions:  Glasses or contacts  Glasses Head Injuries  No Medication  No Problems with knees or ankles  No  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus     font-size:11pt"&gt;Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes   font-size:11pt"&gt;Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes   font-size:11pt"&gt;Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes  WALK AND TURN (3/8 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Bushrod stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage:    Attempted to begin prior to being instructed.  Continued to place the wrong foot in front of the other.   Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Stepped completely offline on step 3  Stopped after step 10.  Turn: Turned left using both feet, stumbled left. Walking Stage (2nd Nine):    Stumbled backwards after the test when turning around.  ONE LEG STAND (2/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Left foot raised Balance and Count Stage:  Seconds 0-10:    Swayed body to the left and right.  Left foot hit the ground 1 time.  Seconds 11-20:    Swayed body to the left and right.  Left foot hit the ground 1 time.  Seconds 21-30:    Swayed body to the left and right.  Left foot hit the ground 1 time.     Stated he does not drink ofter.   PBT #209455 with a result of .12 BrAC.  ARREST Due to the number of observations, I concluded Bushrod was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0331 hours, I placed Bushrod under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. He was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack for processing.  Upon arrival at the barrack, I provided Bushrod with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Bushrod listened to the DR-15 Advice of Rights from the MVA website. At 0411hours, Bushrod agreed to take a breath test.  20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Bushrod beginning at 0330 hours. A search revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. Bushrod was observed from that time until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by Sgt. Horton of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Bushrod had a result of .12 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 0420 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: ****.12 grams of alcohol****  Bushrod was polite and cooperative during the encounter. Bushrod was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 04:21:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/03/2023 11:15:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>65</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504723</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/30/2023 03:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 04:19:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/30/2023 04:19:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 04:19:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:17</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375695</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Bushrod</LastName>
               <FirstName>Gregory</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/26/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>04/30/2023 04:08:31</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B263</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G626</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Bushrod</LastName>
               <FirstName>Gregory</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/26/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>B263</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G626</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/30/2023 04:08:31</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6616</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Eberle</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21215</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.709195</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.354462</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 04:20:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 04:20:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 04:19:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/30/2023 04:19:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152496</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/30/2023 04:20:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/30/2023 04:20:55</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/30/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2012</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SUB</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6DB8762</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>