<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-018081</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/21/2023 02:06:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/21/2023 02:06:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/21/2023 01:40:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/21/2023 01:40:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Accident investigation leading to DWI arrest</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 02:06:31</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5750</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>06/29/2023 18:52:24</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>100575</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7347</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 00:00:02</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/24/2023 00:01:37</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>100575</AddressId>
         <City>UPPER MARLBORO</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.7625700000002</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.811440038065285</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>S/B RT 4 AT ANNE ARUNDEL COUNTY LINE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/21/2023 02:06:28</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/21/2023 02:06:28</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>06/29/2023 18:52:26</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/21/2023 02:06:31</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/29/2023 18:52:26</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP unmarked vehicle MD registration 9EM6883 is equipped with inoperable in-car camera, help-desk ticket # 235158. This stop was recorded on L-41 Body Worn Camera #7347.   Defendant:Subrena Laton Coleman  Date of Birth: 09/20/1961  Date of Arrest:05/21/2023  Time of Arrest:0240 hours  DUI #:23-156  MD Drivers License #:C455778488729  Forestville Barrack  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *Completed the Advanced Roadside Impairment Driving Enforcement Program. *Trained and certified to operate the Preliminary Breath Test through the Maryland State Police.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On Sunday, May 21th, 2023, at approximately 0140 hours, I, Trooper Clark # 7347 of the Maryland State Police  Forestville Barrack was dispatched to a single vehicle collision on Northbound Route 4 prior to Anne Arundel County Line, Prince Georges County MD. I arrived at the scene and observed a black Toyota Rav 4 displaying Maryland registration A348875 with heavy front end damage into the ditch.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I made contact with the driver who was later identified as Subrena Laton Coleman DOB: 09/20/1961, African American female from her Maryland drivers license. While speaking with Coleman, I smelled a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath. I asked Coleman how much alcoholic beverage she had consumed before driving. He replied stating, 4 bottles of tequila. I advised Coleman that I was going to put her through the Standardized Field Sobriety Test to make sure she was safe to drive. She replied stating, yes.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluationwas performed on a flat surface on the shoulder of the beltway. The surface was dry, level and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 60 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of patrol vehicles headlights, overhead lights and my flashlight.My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during the test.Before administering the Standardized Field Test, I asked Coleman if she had anyinjuries that couldprevent her from completing the test correctly. She stated no. I asked the following questions: * Do you have glasses on: No * Do you have any Medical conditions that couldprevent you from taking this test: Diabetes and high blood pressure * Do you currently have any Injuries: No  WALK AND TURN (7/8 clues observed) Prior to Coleman performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Coleman was instructed to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot and touch heel to toe. Coleman was instructed and demonstrated to place her hands flat at her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Coleman was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. Coleman was instructed to keep her hands flat at her side, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Coleman was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the ground, and to take a series of small steps around with her lead foot to turn completely around. Coleman was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Coleman was instructed that once she began the test, she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by her side, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Coleman if she understood the test, and she stated, yes.  INSTRUCTIONAL STAGE: 1. Coleman did not keep balance (Lost her balance and broke her feet apart) 2. She began walking too soon before being told to do so.  WALKING STAGE(FirstNine) 3. She missed heel to toe on all steps 4. She stepped off-line while walking 5. She swayed during the test  WALKING STAGE(SecondNine):  6. She took ten steps instead of nine as she was instructed  TURN  7.Coleman did not keep her lead foot still on the ground during the turn and only took one step during the turn instead of several small steps as she was instructed to.  ONE LEG STAND (refusal) I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Coleman was instructed to stand with her feet together and hands down by her sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was asked to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately 6 inches and parallel to the ground.While her leg was raised, she was instructed to keep her leg straight, watch her raised foot and to count out loudby thousands (one thousand one, one thousand-two), and continue the test until told to stop. Ricks was asked if she understood the test and the instructions to which she stated, yes.  No clues observed due to refusal  ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Coleman was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: *Strong odor of alcoholic beverage coming from her breath * Observed signs of impairment while she performed the test. * Eyes glassy and bloodshot with a glazed look. * Slurred speech and very talkative. * Difficulties walking. * Her admittance to have consumed alcohol prior to driving  I arrested Coleman for driving under the influence of alcoholat approximately 0240 hours, and she was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Maryland State Police  Forestville Barrack for processing.  20 MINUTES OBSERVATION PERIOD Once at the barrack, a secondary search and mouth check was conducted on Coleman. Coleman was under my custody until her release time.I playedthe English audio DR-15 Advice of Rights form to Coleman in English in its entirety. At the conclusion of the form, Coleman verbally advised that she agreed to submit to the chemical breathalyzer test and signed the form indicating the same. Sgt. Hooten # 5750 administered the chemical breathalyzer test on Coleman which resulted in insufficient breaths. Coleman was charged with driving under the influence of alcoholand was givena copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, DR-15A Officers Certification Order of Suspension, and all appropriate citations. She was released to a sober driverat approximately 0413 hours.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7347</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 01:07:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7347</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/24/2023 02:09:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Murray</LastName>
            <FirstName>Norman</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5466</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hooten</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5750</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Clark</LastName>
            <FirstName>Eleanor</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7347</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507513</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/21/2023 01:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7347</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 00:43:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7347</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/24/2023 00:43:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>507513</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/21/2023 01:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7347</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 00:44:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7347</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/24/2023 00:44:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>61</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7347</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 00:39:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:59</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>377878</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Coleman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Subrena</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Laton</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/20/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 00:19:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C455</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S165</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Coleman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Subrena</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Laton</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/20/1961 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C455</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S165</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 00:19:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>412</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5438</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7347</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 00:39:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7347</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 00:39:50</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:03</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7347</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 00:43:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7347</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/24/2023 00:43:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>153354</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7347</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/24/2023 00:51:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7347</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/24/2023 00:51:11</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>2T3RFREV9JW816538</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2018</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>RAV</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>A348875</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>