<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-034288</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/30/2023 05:04:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/30/2023 05:04:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/30/2023 04:41:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/30/2023 04:41:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 05:04:55</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5364</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 11:27:08</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>E 495 TO N 650 RAMP / NEW HAMPSHIRE AVE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>366599</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 05:04:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/31/2023 08:28:31</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>366599</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>I-495 W/O MD 650</StreetName>
         <City>Silver Spring</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20903</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.987639</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.019159</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/30/2023 05:04:49</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/30/2023 05:04:49</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/02/2023 13:47:11</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/30/2023 05:04:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 16:26:58</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>***** SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER***** N-12 forward mobile recording device not functioning. Defendant: Alberto Martinez Villatoro Date of Birth: 05/04/1990 Date of Arrest: 09/30/2023 Time of Arrest: 0513 hours No Soundex DUI #: 23-205 (Rockville) * Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Certified by NHTSA to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) * Certified as a Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator  * Certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE)  * Attended the 2021 Maryland Impaired Driving Conference in Ocean City, Maryland * Participated in several DUI Special Assignments * DUI Award Recipient for 2021  2022. * Gaithersburg Germantown Chamber of Commerce Award Recipient 2023 * Since 2020 have made over 120 DUI arrest VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On Saturday, September 30, 2023 at approximately 0441 hours, I, Trooper First Class Canizalez #7087 was dispatched to the left shoulder on the Innerloop of I-495 just West of Route 650, Hillandale, Montgomery County, to respond for a single vehicle collision. Upon arrival I observed a white Honda Pilot bearing Maryland registration 2FH1353 with heavy damage to its front left fender. My investigation revealed that the white Honda Pilot (vehicle 1) was traveling in lane 1 on the Innerloop of I-495 just West of Route 650 when the driver fell asleep and drifted to the left and struck the concrete barrier with its front left fender.  CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the vehicle to contact the driver who was already outside of his vehicle. Upon my approach I introduced myself, asked the driver and asked the driver what had occurred. The driver stated that he was waiting on his friend who was driving and had left in a taxi to get a tow truck for the vehicle. I asked what had occurred and the driver stated that the damages on the vehicle had come from a flat tire. I asked the driver if he had any identification and he said no I was not the driver. I then asked him for his name and he stated Alex. Later finding out that that was not his name and Alex is the middle name of the registered owner of the vehicle Alexander. While speaking to the driver, I immediately detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the drivers breath even with traffic passing. The driver was later identified as: MARTINEZ VILLATORO, Alberto. (NO SDX, H/M, DOB 05/04/1990). I proceeded with my investigation and asked MARTINEZ VILLATORO to call the registered owner to see how far he was with the tow. The driver called and passed the phone to me and I spoke to the registered owner of the vehicle and he advised to me that he was not driving and was headed into work going into Chambersburg PA. After advising the registered owner of the damages to the vehicle and what had occurred, he requested that I gave the phone back to MARTINEZ VILLATORO to speak to him.  During this conversation, I overheard MARTINEZ VILLATORO say to the registered owner in Spanish I fell asleep and hit the wall I was coming from the club. I questioned the driver on his travels and he stated he was coming from the club and was headed home. MARTINEZ VILLATORO was also displaying other signs of impairment such as bloodshot and glassy eyes. When asked about consuming any alcoholic beverages he stated he had consumed 8-9 Heineken beer bottles approximately 15 minutes prior to driving. I asked MARTINEZ VILLATORO if he was willing to perform voluntary SFSTs and he advised that he would.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the left shoulder of I-495 in the area West of Route 650. (pavement). The surface was dry and clear from any debris. The weather was clear and light conditions consisted of my flashlight. MARTINEZ VILLATORO was not displaying any visible injuries. Prior to beginning the test, I asked MARTINEZ VILLATORO the following questions: Glasses or Contacts: None. Medical Conditions: None. Injuries: None. Medications: None.  *TEST #1 HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN): 6/6 The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches, slightly above eye level. I instructed his to look straight ahead, keeping his head stationary while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. I asked MARTINEZ VILLATORO if he understood the test and he stated Yes. MARTINEZ VILLATORO pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Vertical Gaze Nystagmus: Present in both eyes.   *TEST #2 WALK AND TURN (WAT): 5/8 Prior to MARTINEZ VILLATORO performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. MARTINEZ VILLATORO was instructed to place his left foot on a straight imaginary line then place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. MARTINEZ VILLATORO was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin the test. MARTINEZ VILLATORO was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. MARTINEZ VILLATORO was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, MARTINEZ VILLATORO was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to the left to turn completely around. MARTINEZ VILLATORO was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. MARTINEZ VILLATORO was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked MARTINEZ VILLATORO if he understood the test and he stated, Yes.     margin-left:8px"&gt;MARTINEZ VILLATORO was unable to maintain his balance during the instructional phase.   margin-left:8px"&gt;MARTINEZ VILLATORO stepped off line on his 2nd step during his second set.   margin-left:8px"&gt;MARTINEZ VILLATORO stopped walking on his 5th step during his second set.    margin-left:8px"&gt;MARTINEZ VILLATORO took the incorrect number of steps and took 13 steps during his first set and 5 on his second set.    margin-left:8px"&gt;MARTINEZ VILLATORO incorrectly completed the turn by lifting his lead foot and completing the turn with both feet.   *TEST #3 ONE LEG STAND (OLS): 1/4 Prior to performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. MARTINEZ VILLATORO was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count aloud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. MARTINEZ VILLATORO was asked if he understood the test and the instructions to which he stated, Yes. MARTINEZ VILLATORO performed this test balanced on his left foot.     margin-left:8px"&gt;MARTINEZ VILLATORO put his foot down at the 15th second mark.    I offered MARTINEZ VILLATORO a preliminary breath test and he agreed to take it.  PBT taken at 0511 hours. PBT Results: .16 BrAC ARREST: Based on the following, I had reason to believe MARTINEZ VILLATORO was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of an alcoholic beverage: * MARTINEZ VILLATORO failed to control his speed to avoid a collision. * Blood shot and glassy eyes. * Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from MARTINEZ VILLATOROs breath. * MARTINEZ VILLATORO admitting to have consumed 8-9 beer bottles approximately 15 minutes prior to driving.  Due to a number of observations, I had reason to believe MARTINEZ VILLATORO was driving while under the influence of an alcoholic beverage and was unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0513 hours, I placed MARTINEZ VILLATORO under arrest for Driving While Under the Influence of Alcohol. A preliminary search of MARTINEZ VILLATORO was conducted on the scene and it revealed that he had nothing on his person. MARTINEZ VILLATORO was then transported to the MSP Rockville Barrack per departmental policy. While conducting the secondary search on MARTINEZ VILLATORO at the barrack, his oral cavity was checked and was clear and had nothing in his mouth. During the 20-minute observation period, MARTINEZ VILLATORO remained in my custody and did not introduce any foreign object in his mouth. The DR-15 Advice of Rights form was read to MARTINEZ VILLATORO at 0541 hours to which he advised he would submit to the intoximeter test. INTOXIMETER RESULT  0.15 GRAMS OF ALCOHOL PER 210 LITERS OF BREATH MARTINEZ VILLATORO was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and was released to his family/ friends at 0650 hours.  Case status: closed by arrest. All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/01/2023 05:40:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/01/2023 05:40:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Taylor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5479</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Saucerman</LastName>
            <FirstName>David</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4873</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Canizalez</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ricardo</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7087</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523746</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/30/2023 06:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19731</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 06:54:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 08:22:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523746</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/30/2023 06:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 06:54:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 08:23:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523746</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/30/2023 06:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 06:54:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 08:23:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523746</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/30/2023 06:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 06:54:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 08:24:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523746</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/30/2023 06:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 06:54:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 08:25:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523746</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/30/2023 06:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 06:54:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 08:25:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523746</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/30/2023 06:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 06:54:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 08:27:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523746</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/30/2023 06:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 06:54:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 08:20:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523746</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/30/2023 06:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 06:54:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 08:19:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>523746</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/30/2023 06:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 06:54:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 08:22:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>33</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 06:54:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/31/2023 08:28:31</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389420</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Martinez Villatoro</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alberto</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/04/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/03/2023 11:36:02</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M635</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A416</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Martinez Villatoro</LastName>
               <FirstName>Alberto</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/04/1990 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M635</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A416</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/03/2023 11:36:02</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>6249</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Fernwood</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>TER</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Riverdale Park</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20737</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1601</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.901797</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.9641</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 08:29:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 08:29:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 08:29:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 06:54:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 06:54:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157701</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7087</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 08:30:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7087</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/07/2023 08:30:46</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/03/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5FNYF5H57GB026993</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2016</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HOND</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>PLT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2FH1353</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>