<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-045384</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/24/2023 03:50:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/24/2023 03:50:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/24/2023 03:31:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/24/2023 03:31:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI: Fallken Urizar Lopez</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/24/2023 03:50:21</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP3258</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/30/2023 07:34:06</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>LAKE ST/ TANGIER ST</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>107541</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/24/2023 03:50:22</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 04:15:14</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>107541</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Lake</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Salisbury</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21801</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>ST</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.603413</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.374432</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>618-699 LAKE ST / 500-539 TANGIER ST</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/24/2023 03:50:20</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/24/2023 03:50:20</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 18:41:06</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/24/2023 03:50:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:17</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Patrol Vehicle E-15 is equipped with an in car camera Dash Camera:https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=22639b61567a46ec85a0a8768c9d2463partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 Body Camera: https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=05e20b0134b040a097e4da62e1e48f41partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 In Car Camera:https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=6c0f9a799d1e4297925dd2c1d8013bafpartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  Crime: Driving Under the Influence Weather: Clear 40 Degrees Defendant: Fallken Dietter Brayan Urizar Lopez                                                                                                                                                                                                             Date of Birth: 11/01/1995 Date of Arrest: 12/24/2023 Time of Arrest: 0350 hours License#: N/A DUI #: 23-54-250 DUI Citation #: 2X60URM Subsequent Offender: No Accident Involved: No  Scene Processing: * DR15 Advice of Rights * DR15A    CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING:  * I am trained to administer standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * I have successfully completed the Advanced Roadside Impairment Driving Enforcement course through the Maryland State Police.   NARRATIVE:  Phase #1 - Vehicle In Motion: On 12/24/23 at approximately 0331 hours, I TFC Eckrich, was on routine patrol in the area of Lake St and U.S. Rt 50. At that time I observed a white GMC bearing Maryland registration 8FB6158 traveling on Lake St towards Isabella St. The vehicle appeared to be traveling above the posted speed limit. I activated my Kustom Golden Eagle radar and obtained a speed of 32 mph in a posted 25 mph zone. In addition, I observed the vehicle suddenly swerve to the right causing the right side tires to go completely over the solid white shoulder line and almost strike the curb. I activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop in the area of Lake St and Tangier St. While the vehicle was pulling over it drove up on the sidewalk that was to the right of the roadway. Phase #2 - Personal Contact: I exited my patrol vehicle, and made contact with the operator identified by a Guatemalan identification card as FALLKEN DIETTER BRAYAN URIZAR LOPEZ (H/M 11/1/95). I advised Lopez the reason for the stop and that the stop was audibly and visually recorded. While speaking with Lopez I detected the strong odor of alcoholic beverage coming from within the vehicle. I also observed Lopezs eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. Lopez advised he did not speak much English. I noticed Lopez had a red wristband on his right hand that had Caf Italiano written on it. This establishment is known to serve alcoholic beverages. I returned to my patrol vehicle and relayed Lopezs information to MSP Salisbury.   Phase #3 - Pre Arrest Screening: I returned to Lopez and asked him to step out of the vehicle. Due to the language barrier I utilized Google Translate to explain all directions to Lopez. I explained to Lopez the reason for stepping out of the vehicle. I asked Lopez how much he had to drink and he stated he did not have anything to drink. Lopez agreed to perform standardized field sobriety tests. While speaking with Lopez outside of his vehicle, I again detected the strong odor of alcoholic beverage but this time it was coming from his breath and person.  Pre-Screening Questions: I asked Lopez a series of questions prior to performing Standardized Field Sobriety Tests: * Visual check of inside of Lopezs mouth: No * Glasses: No                                                                                                                                                                                                                                      * Injuries: No *Medications: No  I then began Standardized Field Sobriety Tests and I started with the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test.   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus:  I explained the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test to Lopez. After explaining the test, I asked him if he understood the test and if he had any questions. Lopez stated he understood the test and I began.   Resting Nystagmus: No Equal Tracking: Yes Equal Pupil Size: Yes  Lack of smooth pursuit present in both eyes Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation present in both eyes                                                                                                                                                                                    Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees was present in both eyes. Vertical Nystagmus was present  Total Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Clues: 6 of 6   Walk and Turn: Weather: Clear Surface: Level, free of any debris   I instructed Lopez into the instructional phase. During my explanation of the test Lopez could not maintain his balance and broke heel to toe. I asked Lopez if he understood the instructions and Lopez advised that he understood.  Instructional Phase: -Could not maintain balance  Walking stage 1st 9 -Incorrect number of steps: 10 Turn: Incorrect: stumbled while turning around. Did not take series of small steps as instructed.   Walking stage 2nd 9: -Stepped off-line on steps 1 and 9  -Incorrect number of steps: 11   Total Walk and Turn Clues:4 of 8  One Leg Stand: I next explained and demonstrated the One Leg Stand test to Lopez. I asked Lopez if he understood the test, and he stated he did. Lopez did not start the test correctly, so I demonstrated and explained the test a second time. Lopez picked up his right foot for the test.  Seconds 1-10: Swayed from side to side. Put foot down at 6 second mark   Seconds 11-20 Swayed from side to side Raised arms for balance at 20 second mark  Seconds 21-30 Swayed from side to side  Raised arms for balance at 23 second mark Put foot down at 24 second mark  Total One Leg Stand Clues:3 of 4  Preliminary Breath Test   Preliminary breath test was offered to Lopez. Lopez submitted to the PBT with a result of .13 BrAC  Arrest and Transport:  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Lopez was driving a motor vehicle under the influence:  * Eyes blood shot and glassy * Odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his vehicle * Odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from his breath and person *My observed signs of impairment during SFSTs.  At approximately 0350 hours, I placed Lopez under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I placed Lopez in the front passenger of my patrol vehicle. Upon placing Lopez in my patrol vehicle, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage in the vehicle that was not present prior to placing Lopez in the vehicle.    20-Minute Observation Period: I transported Lopez to the MSP Salisbury barrack. The MVA DR-15 was read to Lopez in Spanish. At 0414 hours Lopez signed the DR-15 refusing to submit to the intoximeter test.Lopez was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and was released to a sober driver. It should be noted that Lopez was polite and cooperative during the entire encounter. Lopez appeared to take the situation very seriously.  All events did occur in Wicomico County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 04:41:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7047</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 04:44:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Honsinger</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6841</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckrich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mareck</LastName>
            <FirstName>Keven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3258</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckrich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eckrich</LastName>
            <FirstName>Patrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7047</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534861</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>4382</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/24/2023 03:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>4382</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 04:16:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7047</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 04:17:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534861</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/24/2023 03:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 04:16:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7047</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 04:17:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>534861</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/24/2023 03:31:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 04:16:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7047</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 04:19:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>28</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 04:16:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7047</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 04:20:09</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>396035</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Urizar Lopez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Fallken</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dietter Brayan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/01/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/25/2023 04:08:41</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>U626</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F425</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Urizar Lopez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Fallken</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Dietter Brayan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/01/1995 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>U626</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>F425</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/25/2023 04:08:41</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>807</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>E</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Rd</StreetName>
               <City>Salisbury</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21801</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.606509</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.37872</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 04:20:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7047</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 04:20:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 04:20:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7047</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 04:20:09</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7047</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/25/2023 04:16:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7047</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/25/2023 04:16:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>