<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-042562</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/02/2023 00:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/02/2023 00:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/02/2023 00:37:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/02/2023 00:37:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>JONES "R" 23-635</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 00:56:24</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/29/2023 12:32:51</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I695 WB EXIT 26 RAMP 2,LUTHERVILLE TIMONIUM</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>714811</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 00:56:25</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 10:33:07</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>714811</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I695 Wb Exit 26</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RAMP</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.6096672666667</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.414125</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/02/2023 00:56:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/02/2023 00:56:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/09/2024 18:36:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>SENT WAITING FOR RESPONSE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/02/2023 00:56:24</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/18/2024 15:00:25</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E) TEAM* MVR Statement: The following incident was captured on in-car and Body camera. Title: JONES R 23-635. ID: 23-MSP-042562 Arrested: Jones, Darian Lavoisier. Certification and training   -Trained in Field Sobriety Test through Maryland State Police Academy.  -Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E)  -Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  - Graduated from The Institute of Advanced Law Enforcement Studies Driving Under the Influence Institute-University of Maryland.  - I am a certified EC/IR II Intoximeter operator.  - I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor.  - I have apprehended more than 270 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On December 02, 2023, at approximately 0029 hours, I, Tpr Riba Tankari # 7058 with Maryland State Police was traveling outer loop I-695 west of Lock Raven Blvd, Baltimore County, Maryland in lane #2 (middle lane). My issued patrol vehicle is Maryland State Police unmarked unit DUI-6. At that time, I observed a gray Toyota Avalon bearing Maryland registration 13455CL traveling outer loop I-695 in lane #3 (right lane) had crossed the solid white line from lane #3 into the merge lane to pass another vehicle traveling in lane #3, continued traveling in lane #2, and appeared to traveling over the posted speed limit. I followed the Toyota, accelerated to 107 MPH to get close enough, and with my properly functioning patrol vehicle Golden Eagle II radar unit set activated, I obtained a speed reading of 95 in a posted 55 MPH zone. I initiated a traffic stop on the Toyota using my emergency equipment. The Toyota delayed in coming to a stop and continued traveling at a high rate of speed. The Toyota eventually came to a stop in the area of outer loop I-695 and York Road, Baltimore County, Maryland on the right shoulder.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I made contact with the driver (the sole occupant) of the vehicle. I introduced myself and explained to him the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver if he knew the speed limit, and he stated yeah I know. I requested his drivers license and registration card. I asked the driver where he was coming from, and he stated Coming from a little situation at friend house. I asked the driver where he was heading, and he stated my girlfriend house. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle I observed that the driver had watery and glassy eyes. I observed the drivers movements were slow while he was looking for the requested documents. The driver was unable to find his drivers license and showed me his correctional officer badge and identification card. I provided the driver with pen and paper to write down his information. The driver was later identified by an MVA check of his name and date of birth he provided as Jones, Darian Lavoisier. I returned to my patrol vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with. I returned to the Toyota and requested Jones to exit his vehicle and to walk to the front of his vehicle and he complied. I asked Jones how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed, and he stated I had two Patron and Lemonade. I asked him is that bottle, cup or can, and he stated cup. I asked him around what time, and he stated that was about hour and half ago. While speaking with Jones outside his vehicle, I again detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I asked Jones to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and he agreed. The evaluation surface was dry, flat, and free of debris. No surface defects were observed. My patrol flashlight, his vehicle headlights, and overhead lamp lit the area. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Jones appeared to be in good physical conditions. I asked Jones the following questions: Medical conditions: NO. Medications: NO. Anything that will prevent you from walking on straight line or standing on one leg: NO Glasses or contact: No glasses but was wearing contacts. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: (6/6 clues observed). The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus - Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes - Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes - Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Notes: * During the HGN test, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Jones breath. WALK AND TURN: (5/8 clues observed). The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Jones stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage: Jones lost his balance to the right on two separate occasions then to the left on one occasion. Jones started too soon on one occasion. Walking Stage (1st Nine): Took ten actual steps when instructed to take 9. Stepped completely offline by one shoe width on count 2. Notes *After the tenth step, Jones stood and stated keep going? I cant remember what you said at nine.  Turn: The turn was not completed correctly; instead Jones turned to his left failing to take a series of small steps as instructed and demonstrated. Walking Stage (2nd Nine Nothing to report. One Leg Stand Test (1/4 observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Jones stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Right foot raised during the test. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: Swayed body to the right and left. Seconds 11-20: Nothing to report Seconds 21-30: Nothing to report Preliminary Breath Test:  I explained and offered a PBT to Jones. Jones elected to consent to the PBT and results were .11 BAC. ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Jones was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a motor vehicle safely:  -Driving over the posted speed limit (95 Mph in 55 Mph speed limit zone)     -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath as he conversed with me.  -Eyes watery and glassy.     -Movements slow.  -His admissions to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to driving.  -Observed signs of impairment as he performed the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  - Preliminary Breath Test result of .11 BrAC.  Jones was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a motor vehicle at 0055 hours and was transported to the Baltimore County Towson Precinct. After his arrest, Jones stated Sir, Im asking you if you could just, because this is going to affect my job, I caught a DUI already I asked him when and he stated In 2020. While securing his vehicle, I observed a black plastic bag containing a box of silver Patron on the front passenger floor mat (see attachments). A search incident to arrest revealed no contraband. Upon arrival in the Precinct, Jones was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and it was read to him from the MVA website in English, and he consented to the Intoximeter EC/IR II test at 0124 hours. 20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Jones beginning of his arrest. A search revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. He remained in my custody from that time. Nothing was introduced to his mouth at any time. The test was conducted by TFC. White Intox ID #0115 of Maryland State Police on a certified instrument and a result of .12 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath was obtained at 0137 hours. Jones was polite and cooperative during the encounter.  Jones was given pertinent paperwork, released from the Precinct and transported to his girlfriends house pending an appearance in the District Court of Maryland for Baltimore County at a later date.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 10:39:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/22/2023 10:40:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>532035</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>12/02/2023 00:55:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 10:34:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 10:35:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 10:34:14</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 10:37:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>394665</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>JONES</LastName>
               <FirstName>DARIAN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LAVOISIER</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/10/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/06/2023 10:06:52</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>JONES</LastName>
               <FirstName>DARIAN</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>LAVOISIER</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/10/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J520</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/06/2023 10:06:52</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12409</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Applecross</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Clinton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20735</Zip5>
               <Zip4>1103</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.9463242</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.7183753</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>277</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9840</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 10:37:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 10:37:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 10:37:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 10:37:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 10:37:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 10:37:49</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 10:34:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 10:34:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>159597</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/06/2023 10:39:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/06/2023 10:39:05</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>12/06/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>4T1BK36B95U014004</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2005</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>AVA</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>13455CL</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>10</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleValue>1000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>