<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-041713</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/25/2023 03:48:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/25/2023 03:48:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/25/2023 03:29:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/25/2023 03:29:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI TS - 23-621</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/25/2023 03:48:26</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 13:18:24</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>I695 / STEVENSON RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>584119</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/25/2023 03:48:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 10:41:32</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>584119</AddressId>
         <StreetName>I695</StreetName>
         <City>Pikesville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.71273</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.39182</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>RAMP FR I/L TO STEVENSON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL @ STEVENSON</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 8024-8049 STEVENSON RD89</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>I/L I-695 PRIOR TO STEVENSON ROAD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L I695 /  STEVENSON RD R/S</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L BETWEEN STEVENSON RD AND REISTERSTOWN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 OL / 0-0 STEVENSON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 0-0 STEVENSON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 0-0 STEVENSON RD LS</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 8024-8049 STEVENSON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 / 8050-8099 STEVENSON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L @ STEVENSON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 I695 IL / 0-0 STEVENSON RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>OL @ XT 21</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L PRIOR TO EXIT 21 STEVENSON RD LEFT SHOULDER</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>O/L SOMEWHERE BY EXIT 20 OR 21</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/25/2023 03:48:23</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/25/2023 03:48:23</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/13/2023 13:18:24</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/25/2023 03:48:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:13</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*This stop was captured on in-car and body worn camera* DUI #: 23-621 CASE #: 23-MSP-041713 SUSPECT: McCorkle, Charice Victoria (B/F DOB: 07/02/1992) VICTIM: Society TRAINING, KNOWLEDGE, AND EXPERIENCE:   Certified to conduct Standardized Field Sobriety Tests in January, 2018.  Graduated the Maryland State Police Training Academy in February, 2018.  Assigned to the Maryland State Police Glen Burnie Barrack in February, 2018.   Certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driver Enforcement (ARIDE) in March, 2018.  Certified as a RADAR/LIDAR operator in November, 2019.  Certified as Standardized Field Sobriety Test Instructor in January, 2020.  Graduated Basic Criminal Investigators Course in September, 2020.  Certified as Drug Recognition Expert (DRE) in June 2021.  Certified in National Traffic Incident Management (TIM) in August 2021.  Certified as Field Training Trooper (FTT) in March, 2022.   Certified as Drug Recognition Expert (DRE) Instructor in May, 2022.  Assigned to the State Police Impaired Driver Reduction Effort (SPIDRE) Team in April, 2023.  Graduated the University of Maryland DUI Institute Session XV in June, 2023.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Certified as Intoximeter EC/IR II Operator in July, 2023.  NARRATIVE:  On November 25, 2023 at approximately 0329 hours, I was on duty and in uniform operating unmarked MSP vehicle P-11. I was on routine patrol in the area of O/L I-695 at I-83, Baltimore County, Maryland, when I first observed the suspect vehicle. PHASE 1: VEHICLE IN MOTION  My attention was first drawn to the suspect vehicle as I was traveling in lane 2 at highway speed and the vehicle passed my location in lane 3 at an extremely high rate of speed. After the vehicle passed my location I began to accelerate towards the vehicle to continue making observations.  Shortly after passing me, the suspect vehicle approached the rear of a tractor trailer also in lane 3, abruptly changed lanes into lane 2 to accelerate past the tractor trailer, and then abruptly changed lanes back into lane 3 in front of the tractor trailer. As we were passing the tractor trailer, I was traveling at approximately 99 MPH to keep up with the suspect vehicle. After changing lanes back into lane 3 and as we began to navigate a slight curve in the roadway, the suspect vehicle began to slow reduce its speed and abruptly drifted to the right causing both passenger side tires to cross over the dotted lane line for lane 4 before jerking back into lane 3. After correcting back into lane 3, the suspect vehicle drifted across the lane to the left causing both driver side tires to then cross the dotted lane line for lane 2 on two separate occasions at Greenspring Avenue. On the second occasions as we passed the Greenspring Avenue exit, the suspect vehicle straddled the dotted lane line for the entire length of the curve in the roadway. Almost immediately after exiting the curve of the roadway, the suspect vehicle again drifted the left causing both driver side tires to cross over the dotted lane line for lane 2, abruptly jerked back to the right, and then caused both passenger side tires to cross over the dotted lane line for lane 4. At the same time, I was able to obtain a pace of 84 MPH in a posted 55 MPH zone.  At that time, I activated my emergency equipment to conduct a lawful traffic stop on the suspect vehicle. After activating my emergency equipment, the suspect vehicle continued to travel at a high rate of speed while not reacting to my presence. While behind the vehicle with my emergency equipment activated, the suspect vehicle again drifted to the right causing approximately half the width of the vehicle to straddle the lane line for lane 4 for several hundred feet, slowly correct back to the left all the way across lane 3, and then caused both driver side tires to cross over the dotted lane line for lane 2. After cycling my siren several times, the suspect vehicle finally began to slow its speed and moved to the right side of the roadway. The suspect vehicle came to a stop in lane 5 of the O/L I-695 at Stevenson Road, Baltimore County, Maryland. The vehicle stopped in the roadway directly adjacent to a large right shoulder. The suspect vehicle was a white GMC Acadia bearing Georgia Temporary registration S1699368. PHASE 2: PERSONAL CONTACT  I made a passenger side approach to the vehicle and made contact with the driver and sole occupant of the vehicle. When I approached the vehicle, I immediately observed the driver had just lit a cigarette and was staring looking towards the driver side of the vehicle as if she was expecting me to approach on that side, and when I made my presence known it appeared that I startled her. As I was making my initial contact with the driver, I also observed there was an empty Don Julio tequila bottle on the front passenger seat and front passenger floorboard, as well as a red solo cup in the center console that contained residue of a red liquid while the driver had a red liquid stain on her right pants leg. As I was making my initial contact with the driver, I could detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from the passenger compartment of the vehicle, and observed the drivers eyes were bloodshot and glossy. I also recognized the suspect from a DUI arrest made by another Trooper that I was assisting with on November 22, 2023 (23-MSP-041537).  When I asked the driver for her license and registration, she stated that she only had a picture of her license and that the vehicle was a rental. As the driver was looking for her registration card, she mentioned that she had lost her voice. When I asked the driver what had happened to her voice, she stated, I was at uh, at a uh, Thanksgiving, Thanksgiving. Yeah, I was just having a good time. When I asked the driver where she was coming from that night, she stated she was on her way home from a friends house. When I asked the driver how many alcoholic beverages she had consumed that night, she stated, Uh, not much. Im actually almost at my girlfriends house. When I asked her to clarify what she meant, she stated she had consumed, two or three shots. After asking about the bottles of Tequila in the vehicle, the driver stated that they belonged to a friend she had already dropped off. The driver displayed a picture of a Maryland issued ID card and was identified as Charice Victoria McCorkle (B/F DOB: 07/02/1992). When I asked McCorkle about my previous encounter with her two days prior, she initially denied involvement but then admitted to it after I gave details about the incident. McCorkle was driving the same vehicle from that incident. McCorkles license at the time was revoked and did not have a valid license to drive in any jurisdiction. McCorkle was also on probation for other driving without a license violations.  Based on my initial conversations with McCorkle, I asked her to exit the vehicle and speak with me further about the initial indicators of impairment I had observed. McCorkle agreed to exit the vehicle. After exiting the vehicle and while attempting to explain to McCorkle why I had asked her to exit the vehicle, she interrupted and stated, Yeah, I had a couple shots, but Im not as drunk as the day before. I promise you. And, please, if you can follow me to my moms house, its literally the next exit. When I asked McCorkle again about how much she had to drink that night, she stated she had two shots of Don Julio Tequila. McCorkle also again denied the bottles of tequila in the vehicle belonging to her, but stated she was drinking the same liquor. McCorkle stated that she had consumed her last shot at approximately midnight. As I spoke with McCorkle outside her vehicle, I continued to detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath as she spoke. I further continued to observe she was drowsy, her eyes were bloodshot and glossy, and her eyelids were droopy. McCorkles voice was so scratchy that it was hard to tell if her speech was slurred. While outside the vehicle I asked McCorkle, on a scale of one to ten, with one being completely sober and ten being completely drunk, where do you think you are? McCorkle replied, Like a 5. To be honest. PHASE 3: PRE-ARREST SCREENING  Based on my observations and conversations with McCorkle, I asked her to perform standardized field sobriety tests to confirm she could safely operate a motor vehicle. McCorkle agreed to submit to the tests. The tests were performed on the right shoulder in front of McCorkles vehicle, where the ground was level and free from debris. The weather at the time was clear and approximately 42 degrees Fahrenheit. McCorkle was wearing a t-shirt, unzipped jacket, jeans, and laced sneakers at the time. McCorkle stated that she does wear contact lenses and had them in at the time, but also stated that they did not change her eye color or pupil size. McCorkle stated that she does not have any vision problems, and only wears the contacts just to wear them. McCorkle stated that she does not have any recent head injuries, does not take any medications, did not have any problems with her balance or ability to walk, and did not have any recent injuries. The solid white shoulder line was used for the walk and turn test. STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS Instructions: The subject is told to stand with their feet together and their arms down at their side. A stimulus (ink pen) is held approximately twelve to fifteen inches from the subjects face, and they are asked to follow the stimulus with their eyes only and not to move their head. Prior to beginning the test, I ask the subject if they understand the instructions. I initially check for equal pupil size, resting nystagmus, and equal tracking. I next check for lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees. Finally, I check for vertical nystagmus. Both eyes are checked twice for each clue. Results: 6/6. McCorkle had brown eyes that were bloodshot and glossy. Both pupils appeared normal and equal in size. Both eyes were tracking equally and resting nystagmus was not present. All clues present. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was not present. While I was performing the test, McCorkle was swaying slightly front-to-back. WALK AND TURN Instructions: The subject is told to stand with their right foot in front of their left foot in a heel to toe manner. They are told to stay in that position and keep their arms at their side until being told to begin the test. I ask to make sure they understand and then begin explaining and demonstrating the test. The subject is instructed to take nine heel-to-toe steps on a straight, imaginary line. On the ninth step, they are instructed to leave their lead foot planted and take a series of small steps to turn 180 degrees. They are then told to take an additional nine heel-to-toe steps back down the same imaginary line. They are told to watch their feet, count their steps out loud, keep their hands at their side, touch heel-to-toe on every step, and to not stop walking until the test is completed. I then ask if they understand the instructions before having them begin the test. Results:    Cannot Keep Balance: McCorkle lost her balance and stepped out of the instructional position one time at the end of the instructions as she was getting ready to begin walking.  Steps Off Line: McCorkle stepped off line on steps three, four, and nine of the first set of steps, and on steps one, two, three, and six of the second set of steps.   Misses Heel-to-Toe: McCorkle missed heel-to-toe on step one and two of the first set of steps.   The Turn: Performed satisfactoriy. McCorkle began to spin but then corrected and took the small steps as instructed.    margin-left:8px"&gt;Other: Slow and deliberate steps. Leg tremors.   Total Clues: 3/8 ONE LEG STAND Instructions: The subject is instructed to stand with their feet together with their hands at the side while I explain the instructions and demonstrate the test. They are told to raise either foot of their choice approximately six inches off the ground. They are told to begin to count, one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-threeetc. They are told to continue counting until I tell them to stop. They are told to watch their feet, to count out loud, to keep their arms at their side, and to not put their foot down. I then ask if the subject understands the instructions. Results:    Uses Arms to Balance: McCorkle kept her arms raised greater than six inches for the first ten seconds of the test.  Sways: McCorkle periodically swayed her leg and body throughout the test.  Hops: McCorkle instantly, but briefly, began to hop as she initially raised her leg.  Other: McCorkle began the test by raising her right leg and standing on her left foot. slow count, reaching a count of 23 in an actual elapsed 30 seconds. Did not count in 1000s as instructed.   Total Clues: 3/4  While on scene, McCorkle was asked if she would submit to a preliminary breath test. I am certified by the Maryland State Police and the State of Maryland Office of the Chief Medical Examiner to conduct preliminary breath tests with the use of the Alco Sensor. This is the approved preliminary breath test for the State of Maryland. McCorkle agreed to submit to the test. While attempting to perform the test, McCorkle was not providing a breath sample as instructed, and took several attempts to accurately complete the test. The result of the test was .12. ARREST  Based on my observations, as well as my training, knowledge, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper and Drug Recognition Expert, I placed McCorkle under arrest for driving under the influence at approximately 0347 hours. McCorkle was polite and cooperative during my entire interaction with her. McCorkle was secured in my vehicle to be transported to the Baltimore County Towson Precinct for further processing. While conducting a search incident to arrest, I located a hand-rolled brown cigarette containing a greenish brown vegetable matter suspected to be cannabis. When I asked McCorkle about smoking cannabis, she stated that she did not remember the last time she had smoked. McCorkle was able to contact a friend while on scene that was close by and agreed to secure the vehicle. I remained on scene with the vehicle until the friend arrived and secured the vehicle. McCorkle was quiet on the way to the Towson Precinct and was mostly sleeping, but I could still detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. We arrived at the Towson Precinct at approximately 0404 hours.  McCorkle was escorted to the Precinct intake processing area where she was provided a copy of her DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along as an audio recording from the Motor Vehicle Administration website was played for her. When I started the recording, McCorkle stated that she could hear and understand the recording. McCorkle was holding the form in both hands and looking down at it while the recording was playing, appearing to be following along. After the recording, McCorkle stated that she understood the form and did not have any questions. McCorkle agreed to submit to an alcohol concentration test at approximately 0418 hours. Sgt. Pugh #0588, Baltimore County Towson Precinct, a certified intoximeter operator, performed the test. The result of the test was .09 grams of alcohol per 210L of breath. DISPOSITION  Due to McCorkles recent prior, her revoked license status, and her history of failing to appear for court, the decision was made to take her in front of a Baltimore County Court Commissioner for an initial appearance hearing. McCorkle was secured in my vehicle and transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack for the virtual appearance hearing. McCorkle was emotional and sobbing on the way to the Barrack after she was informed she was not being released. We arrived at the Barrack at approximately 0511 hours. After completing the appropriate paperwork for the initial appearance hearing, custody was transferred to TFC Riba Tankari #7058. TFC Riba Tankari remained with McCorkle for the remaining processing.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/30/2023 00:20:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/30/2023 00:20:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>White</LastName>
            <FirstName>Dillon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6932</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531183</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/25/2023 03:45:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 10:40:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 10:42:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>31</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 10:40:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 10:43:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>57218</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>McCorkle</LastName>
               <FirstName>Charice</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Victoria</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/02/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.12374643E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/22/2015 03:28:12</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M262</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>McCorkle</LastName>
               <FirstName>Charice</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Victoria</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/02/1992 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.12374643E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>M262</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>C620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/22/2015 03:28:12</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>801</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Truxton</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Edgewood</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21040</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.318708</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.425859</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>17</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Nutmeg</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>D</SubNumber>
               <City>Cockeysville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21030</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>648</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sequoia</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Edgewood</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21014</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.289762</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.429256</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>240</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2802</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/22/2015 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>901</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8754</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/26/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 10:43:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 10:43:07</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:29</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6932</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/29/2023 10:41:36</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6932</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/29/2023 10:41:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>