<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-044861</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>12/19/2023 14:48:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>12/19/2023 14:48:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>12/19/2023 14:16:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>12/19/2023 14:16:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>MVC/DUI/Poss CDS</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>12/19/2023 14:48:50</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5980</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/22/2024 12:23:52</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>PCS</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OXFORD ROAD / ALMSHOUSE ROAD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>716522</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/19/2023 14:48:51</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/19/2023 21:53:57</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>716522</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>27999</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Oxford</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Oxford</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21654</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.10624</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.691744</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/14/2024 01:02:13</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/14/2024 01:02:13</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/22/2024 12:23:51</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7191</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/14/2024 01:02:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP5980</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/22/2024 12:23:52</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Suspect: Jason Daniel Shaffer Date of Birth: 11/12/1985 Date of Arrest: 12/19/2023 Time of Arrest: 1751 hours Rolling Log Number: 23-MSP-044861   Training/Certifications I am trained by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) Trained and certified as Drug Recognition Expert (DRE) Attended and successfully completed 2022 DUI College Attended the 2021 DUI Conference      Breath Alcohol test   The test was conducted at the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack. Shaffer had a breath result of .00.     Interview of Arresting Officer  On 12/19/2023, I, TFC Cambra #7191, a certified Drug Recognition Expert (DRE) assigned to the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack was contacted by TFC Glover #6415 in reference to an impaired driver that he had placed under arrest. TFC Glover advised me that the suspect, identified as Jason Daniel Shaffer (DOB: 11/12/1985) was involved in a single vehicle collision where Shaffers vehicle struck a guardrail on Almshouse Rd at Oxford Rd. TFC Glover advised me that he observed Shaffer to have constricted pupils and difficulty maintaining balance. I was also advised that Shaffer believed that he was headed to Hurlock, Maryland however he was traveling West on Oxford Rd prior to the crash, headed away from Hurlock. I was also advised that Shaffer mentioned that he takes methadone.  TFC Glover administered Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) where Shaffer performed poorly and was placed under arrest. TFC Glover advised me that suspected heroin/fentanyl was recovered from Shaffers vehicle. There were also additional wax folds containing suspected heroin/fentanyl recovered from outside of the vehicle. TFC Glover advised Shaffer of his Miranda rights at 1712 hours where he waived his rights. Shaffer agreed to complete the DRE evaluation. I responded to the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack.     Preliminary Examination    I made contact with Shaffer at the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack in the DUI Room. Shaffer stated that he last had Chips and a candy bar between 1000 hours and 1100 hours that day. He stated he had a 20 oz water bottle at 1200 hours and that was also his last drink. He estimated the time to be 1730 hours at 1755 hours. Shaffer advised that he last slept last night and got about 7 hours of sleep. He denied being sick or injured. He also denied being epileptic and diabetic. He denied taking insulin or having any physical defects. Shaffer was under the care of a psychologist. Shaffer also stated that he took the following medications: Vyvanse (ADHD), Zoloft (Depression), Wellbutrin (Depression), and medications for his stomach (Unknown medication). Shaffer denied taking any further medications. While speaking with Shaffer, I observed both of his hands to be very swollen which is indicative of intravenous (IV) drug use Shaffer appeared to have slow coordination. While speaking with him, I also observed him to have a slow low raspy voice. I was unable to obtain Shaffers pulse from his wrist (Radial Artery). After multiple attempts, Shaffer agreed to allow me to take his pulse from his neck (Carotid Artery), which was successful. Shaffers first pulse was recorded to be 112 beats per minute which is above the DRE average range of 60 to 90 beats per minute.    Eye Examinations  Shaffer denied wearing glasses or contacts and he denied being blind in either of his eyes. His eyes appeared normal and his pupils were equal in size. I observed no resting nystagmus and his eyes tracked equally. Shaffers eyelids appeared to be normal. Shaffer was able to follow the stimulus. I observed no clues of Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (0/6). I observed Shaffer to display no Vertical Gaze Nystagmus. I observed a Lack of Convergence. Both of Shaffers pupils converged and then his left eye went down and out, and his right eye went nearly directly back out. On the first pass, Shaffer looked straight ahead.     Divided Attention Tests   Modified Romberg Balance:  Shaffer had a minor sway of approximately 1 front and back and approximately half of an inch side to side for the duration of the test. Shaffer stated that he reached a 30 second time frame in 29 seconds.    Walk and Turn (5/8)   Shaffer was wearing black sneakers for the test. The test was conducted in the hallway of the Maryland State Police Easton Barrack.   Instructional Phase:  Cannot Keep Balance  First 9 Steps:  Steps off Line  3, 5, 6, 7  Stops Walking  3  Raises Arms  3   Misses Heel to Toe  7, 8, 9    Second 9 Steps:  Steps off Line  1,2,5,6,7  Misses Heel to Toe  3  Raises Arms - 3  Turn:   Completed as instructed  Shaffer placed his hands on the walls of the hallways numerous times to help keep his balance. Shaffer advised me after the test that he has arthritis and has a metal plate in his left ankle. He stated that he has had the plate for a couple years and he sometimes sees a doctor for it.   One Leg Stand (4/4)   While Shaffer balanced on his left foot, he swayed while balancing, uses arms to balance, and put his foot down. Approximately 20 seconds into the test, he stopped the test as he stated that he doesnt think he will be able to do it. Shaffer stated that we can try it out for swapping his balancing foot. While Shaffer balanced on his right foot, he displayed the clues of hopping and puts foot down. After approximately 18 seconds, he stated thats not gonna work quietly and the test was concluded.   Finger to Nose  1) Left: Hovered above lip, then touched base of nose/upper lip 2) Right: Touched tip of nose with pad of finger 3) Left: Touched top of left nostril with pad of finger  4) Right: Touched tip of nose with pad of finger 5) Right: Touched tip of nose with pad of finger 6) Left: Slight hover over tip of nose, then Touched tip of nose with pad of finger    Examination of Vital Signs    Shaffers second pulse was recorded to be 118 beats per minute which is elevated above the DRE average range of 60 to 90 beats per minute. I was unable to get Shaffers pulse from his wrist (Radial Artery) due to swelling of his hands and wrists. Shaffer again allowed me to get his pulse from his neck (Carotid Artery). Shaffers blood pressure was recorded to be 122/92 mmHg with the systolic value being within the DRE average range of 120  140 and the diastolic value being above the DRE average range of 70  90. Shaffers body temperature was recorded to be 97.4 degrees Fahrenheit which is below the DRE average range of 98.6 degrees Fahrenheit (+/- 1-degree Fahrenheit).      Dark Room Examinations   In room light, Shaffers pupils were recorded to be 3.5 mm which is within the DRE average range of 2.5mm to 5mm. In near total darkness, Shaffers pupils were recorded to be 4mm which is below the DRE average range of 5.0mm to 8.5mm. In direct light, Shaffers pupils were 2.5mm which is within the DRE average range of 2.0mm to 4.5mm. Shaffers pupillary reaction was normal with no rebound dilation. Shaffers nasal area was hairy with a deviated septum. His oral cavity appeared to be dry and red. Shaffer was also missing teeth.     Examination of Muscle Tone   Shaffers muscle tone was found to be slightly flaccid at parts but mostly normal. The swelling near the lower areas of Shaffers wrists and hands could have impacted the actual muscle tone.     Examination of injection Sites  Shaffers arms had a plethora of injection sites ranging from new to old and many other marks. On Shaffers left arm, I observed one old injection site and one new/healed injection site with a bruise below his bicep, and near the center of his bicep. I found a new and healed injection site on the top of his left hand and a large scab on the side of his pointer finger.  Shaffers right arm had an open wound in the middle on the back of his forearm and an old injection site with a bruise. On the inside of Shaffers wrist, I observed new injection sites on the inside of his right wrist. I observed large amounts of bruising in the area of the sites. On the top of Shaffers right hand, I observed a cluster of fully healed injections sites. Shaffers hands and wrists were swollen. He stated that he works with machines at the Star Democrat printing area, and he handles heavy rolls of paper which was what caused him to have swollen hands and various marks on his arms. Shaffers pulse was measured for third and final time which was found to be 114 which is above the DRE average range of 60 to 90 beats per minute.     Subjects Statements and other observations  I began to speak with Shaffer, and advised him that I knew he was under the influence and I asked him to be truthful with me. He stated that he was not under the influence at that time however he was that morning. I advised him that I would say he was under the influence of a Narcotic Analgesic. I asked him what he took that morning and he stated I dont know, its hard to say what they put in that shit now (stated calmly). I asked him where he shot it and he stated that he sniffed it. He stated that he stopped shooting last week when I began to speak about it. I asked him, when he went to go purchase the substance, what did he purchase. He stated a a couple bags of heroin. He stated that he takes methadone and that hes on 44mg and he was on 110mg. He stated that he took the methadone in the morning. Shaffer stated that he didnt take his Methadone last Friday, and stuck it out over the weekend due to the long line at the clinic.   He stated that he sniffed the Heroin and then went and got his methadone. I asked him how much heroin he took that morning, he stated a bag. He stated that he used the Heroin at 0930  1000 hours and the methadone at 1100 hours in the parking lot of the Methadone Clinic. Shaffer states he only sniffs and/or injects however he stopped shooting because of knots in his arms and he stated he has been on and off heroin for about 14 years. He stated his hands are always swollen and he stated that its from the ink. I advised him they are also swollen from using. He stated that he needs to get them checked out.      Opinion  I completed a full drug influence evaluation of Shaffer. As a Certified Drug Recognition Expert (DRE), it is my conclusion that Shaffer was under the influence of a Narcotic Analgesic and is unable to operate a vehicle safely based on the following:    .00 BrAC inconsistent with psychophysical impairment   Admission to taking methadone   Suspected heroin/fentanyl recovered from suspect vehicle  Single vehicle collision  Unaware of current location at time of collision  Slow, low raspy speech  Depressed reflexes  Puncture Marks   Deviated septum   Depressed body temperature  Constricted pupils   Dry mouth  Swollen hands/wrists  Slightly flaccid muscle tone   Bruising in area of puncture marks   margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Admission of sniffing heroin and taking methadone earlier in day at the methadone clinic      Toxicology Exam  I requested Shaffer submit to a blood test to test for controlled dangerous substance. Shaffer declined the blood test. Shaffer was readvised his DR-15 rights to which he again declined the blood test at 1904 hours. DR-23 issued.   Miscellaneous  Shaffer was polite and cooperative for the duration of the evaluation.    TFC N. Cambra #7191 Maryland State Police Easton Barrack I Drug Recognition Expert #36473  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7191</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/14/2024 01:04:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7191</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/17/2024 23:53:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tassone</LastName>
            <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5980</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Cambra</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7191</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>