<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-038877</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/04/2023 01:41:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/04/2023 01:41:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/04/2023 01:06:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/04/2023 01:06:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>ORTIZ "N" 23-238</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/04/2023 01:41:54</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/18/2023 04:10:19</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>MD-193,SILVER SPRING</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>712019</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/04/2023 01:41:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/08/2023 11:07:11</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>712019</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Md-193 Silver</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>SPG</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.0049799333333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.01551605</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/04/2023 01:41:51</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/04/2023 01:41:51</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/18/2023 04:10:20</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/04/2023 01:41:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSPQ031</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/04/2023 11:32:10</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E) TEAM* MVR Statement: The following incident was captured on in-car and Body camera. Title: ORTIZ N 23-238. ID: 23-MSP-038877 Arrested: Ortiz Zurroza, Servando. Certification and training  -Trained in Field Sobriety Test through Maryland State Police Academy.  -Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E)  -Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  - Graduated from The Institute of Advanced Law Enforcement Studies Driving Under the Influence Institute-University-. of Maryland.  - I am a certified EC/IR II Intoximeter operator.  - I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor.  - I have apprehended more than 260 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On November 04, 2023, at approximately 0104 hours, I, TFC. I. Riba Tankari # 7058 with Maryland State Police was traveling westbound MD-193 east of I-495, Montgomery County, Maryland in lane #3 (right lane). My issued patrol vehicle is Maryland State Police unmarked unit DUI-6. At that time, I observed a gray Nissan Sentra bearing Maryland registration 8FL9732 appeared to stop at a red traffic signal light in lane #3 in the intersection of westbound MD-193 and the ramp from the outer loop I-495 to MD-193 approximately more than two vehicles length prior to the stop line with no other vehicle in front of it. After the traffic light turned green, I observed the Nissan still standing in lane #3 with its brakes light still activated. I immediately activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the Nissan. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the Nissan on the driver side and made contact with the driver, a male passenger sitting in the front passenger seat of the vehicle. I introduced myself and explained to him the reason for the traffic stop and the driver stated no English. I requested his drivers license and registration card. The driver stated he has no drivers license, I then asked the driver if he has an identification card, and he stated that he has an identification card. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I observed that the driver had glassy and watery eyes. While speaking with the driver I noticed his speech was slow and mumbled. I noticed his movements were slow and lethargic while retrieving his identification card from his wallet. The driver was identified through his Mexico electoral card as Ortiz Zurroza, Servando. I returned to my patrol vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with. An MVA check on the driver revealed that he had no drivers license or privilege to drive in Maryland. TFC. Seidl #7061 assisted me with the traffic stop by translating my interaction with Ortiz into Spanish. I returned to the Nissan and again explained to Ortiz the reason for the traffic stop. I asked Ortiz where he was coming from, and he stated he was coming from a party, from friends house and was going home. I requested Ortiz to exit his vehicle and to walk to the front of vehicle, and he complied. After exiting his vehicle, Ortiz stumbled, lost his balance, and used his vehicle for balance. While outside his vehicle, I again noticed his movements were slow and lethargic. I asked Ortiz how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed he stated he had four small bottles of Modelo beer twenty minutes ago. While speaking with Ortiz outside his vehicle, I again detected a strong odor of alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I asked Ortiz to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and he agreed.  The evaluation surface was dry, flat, and free of debris. No surface defects were observed. My patrol flashlight and overhead lamps lit the area. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Ortiz appeared to be in good physical conditions. I asked Ortiz the following questions: Medical conditions: No. Medications: No. Anything that will prevent you from walking on straight line or standing on one leg: No. Glasses or contact: No. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: (Incomplete). The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Nothing to report, Ortiz was unable to follow instructions due to his level of intoxication. Notes: * During the HGN test, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Ortizs breath. * I observed Ortiz swaying back and forth and side to side while standing for the test. *Not following the tip of my pen. WALK AND TURN: (5/8 clues observed). The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Ortiz stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage: Ortiz lost his balance to the left then to the right on several occasions and had difficulty staying in the instructional position. I instructed Ortiz to return to the instructional position. Walking Stage (1st Nine): Missed touching heel to toe by more than half on all counts. Stepped completely offline by one shoe width on counts 1 and 4. Turn: Nothing to report, the turn was completed correctly. Walking Stage (2nd Nine): Missed touching heel to toe by more than half inch on counts 2, 6, 7, and 9. Took eleven actual steps when instructed to take 9. Stepped completely offline by one shoe width on counts 1, 3, and 4. Stopped walking on count 3. One Leg Stand Test (2/4 observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Ortiz stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Left foot raised during the test. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: Swayed body to the right and left. Left foot hit ground one time. Seconds 11-20: Swayed body to the right and left. Left foot hit ground two times. Seconds 21-30: Swayed body to the right and left. Left foot hit ground three times. Preliminary Breath Test:  I explained and offered a PBT to Ortiz. Ortiz elected to consent to the PBT and results were .21 BAC. ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Ortiz was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a motor vehicle safely:  -Standing causing vehicle to obstruct passage of roadway.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath as he conversed with me.  -Glassy and Watery eyes.  -Movements slow and lethargic.  -His admissions to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to driving.  -Observed signs of impairment as he performed the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  - Preliminary Breath Test result of .21 BrAC.  Ortiz was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a motor vehicle at 0135 hours and was transported to the Maryland State Police Rockville Barrack. A search incident to arrest revealed no weapons or contraband. Upon arrival at the Barrack, Ortiz was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and it was read to him from the MVA website in Spanish, and he refused to consent to the Intoximeter EC/IR II test at 0213 hours. A properly functioning instrument and operator were available. Ortiz was polite and cooperative during the encounter. Ortiz was given pertinent paperwork, released from the Barrack and transported to his residence pending an appearance in the District Court of Maryland for Montgomery County at a later date.  All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/08/2023 11:13:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/14/2023 14:57:11</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Seidl</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brendon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7061</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>528342</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/04/2023 01:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/08/2023 11:08:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/08/2023 11:10:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>50</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/08/2023 11:08:16</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/08/2023 11:12:06</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>392453</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>ORTIZ ZURROZA</LastName>
               <FirstName>SERVANDO</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/10/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/08/2023 10:53:21</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>O632</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S615</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>ORTIZ ZURROZA</LastName>
               <FirstName>SERVANDO</FirstName>
               <DOB>05/10/1973 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>O632</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S615</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/08/2023 10:53:21</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>1920</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Carters Grove</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Silver Spring</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20904</Zip5>
               <Zip4>6608</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.969836</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.060438</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>828</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0904</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>11/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/08/2023 11:12:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/08/2023 11:12:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/08/2023 11:12:06</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/08/2023 11:08:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/08/2023 11:08:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158775</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/08/2023 11:13:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/08/2023 11:13:25</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>11/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>3N1AB7AP8HL644124</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SEN</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8FL9732</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>6</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleValue>1000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>