<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>24-MSP-000612</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/06/2024 15:33:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/06/2024 15:33:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/06/2024 14:58:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/06/2024 14:58:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>MSP Barrack G DUI 24-001, TA 21-901A1 (ANTHONY RAY ATWELL)</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/06/2024 15:33:17</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0670</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/12/2024 19:25:21</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>539444</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/06/2024 15:33:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/08/2024 11:38:00</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>539444</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Baltimore</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westminster</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.96177</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.556985</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>800-998 BALTIMORE BLVD / 950-999 LEIDY RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1010- BALTIMORE BLVD / 950-999 LEIDY RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 BALTIMORE BLVD / 0-0 LEIDY RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>860-998 BALTIMORE BLVD / 0-0 LEIDY RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/06/2024 15:33:14</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/06/2024 15:33:14</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/12/2024 19:25:24</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>READY TO BE PROCESSED-ORIGINAL</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/06/2024 15:33:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/19/2024 12:30:13</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>24-MSP-000612  Incident: MSP Barrack G DUI 24-001 (ANTHONY RAY ATWELL)  TA 21-902(A)(1) DUI  Date  Time: 01/06/2024, 1457 hours  Location of Offense: W/B MD 140, E/O LEIDY RD, WESTMINSTER, Carroll County, MD.  My investigation was recorded on AXON digital recording system assigned to G-39 and AXON body camera assigned to M/Tpr Fair.  Minors in Vehicle:NO  Prior DUI: YES  PBT: 0.07 BrAC at 1517 hours  EVIDENTIARY TEST:Refused at 1544hours  DRE (Drug Recognition Expert): N/A  Weather: raining, approximately 32 degrees Fahrenheit  Qualifications:  -Maryland State Police Academy (June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007)  -I am trained to administer Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through NHTSA and the Maryland State Police (MSP Academy, June 25, 2007 to December 21, 2007).  -I have attended and graduated from the University of Maryland University College Advanced DUI College (UMUC January 7-11, 2013).  -I have attended and completed training Enhanced DUI Enforcement: The Complete Arrest (MPCTC, 05/11/2016).  -A.R.I.D.E.: Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (MPCTC, 03/29-03/30/2017)  -Cannabis Impairment Detection Workshop (MPCTC, 09/29/2021)  -Preliminary Breath Test Instructor (MSP CTAU, 09/11-09/12/2023)  -Standardized Field Sobriety Test Instructor (MSP CTAU, 12/11-12/14/2023)  Driver:  MD DL A-340-067-730-072 ANTHONY RAY ATWELL 3144 BULLFROG RD TANEYTOWN, MD 21787 2/M, DOB 01/27/1964  Phase I: Reason for Stop  On 01/06/2024 at approximately 1454 hours I was on duty, in uniform, operating a marked Maryland State Police Patrol vehicle, G-39. I was stationary on the right shoulder of W/B MD 140 at Leidy Rd, Westminster, Carrol County, MD. The Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack dispatch had just given a lookout for a blue Dodge Dakota pickup truck traveling W/B MD 140, passing Reese Rd, Westminster, Carroll County, MD. The lookout was for the vehicle failing to maintain lane, and possible impaired driver. Further description was the 4-way/ hazard lights of the vehicle were flashing. I observed this vehicle traveling W/B MD 140, passing the MSP Westminster Barrack (located at 1100 Baltimore Blvd). I observed the vehicle in lane 1 (left lane of travel) swerve over the lane divider line between lane 1 and the left turn lane by half the vehicle width, correct, and swerve back three times). As the vehicle passed my location, the vehicle moved to the right lane. I was able to enter the roadway and get directly behind the vehicle. The vehicle was displaying Maryland registration 8FP5605 (2004 blue Dodge Dakota pickup truck). The vehicle did have the 4-way/ hazard lights flashing, but the passenger side rear signal was not working in unison with the drivers side (this was observed W/B MD 140, W/O Market Street). I activated my emergency equipment (specifically: overhead red and blue lights) and initiated a traffic stop of this vehicle. The vehicle came to a stop in the right turn lane of W/B MD 140, W/O Malcolm Drive, Westminster, Carroll County, MD. The driver was the sole occupant of the vehicle. The weather was raining and approximately 32 degrees Fahrenheit.  Phase II: Contact  I approached the vehicle on the drivers side. The window was already down. I greeted the driver, identified myself, advised the traffic stop was being recorded, and the reason for the contact. The driver already had his license, vehicle registration card, and insurance information ready for me. The driver was identified by his MD DL to be ANTHONY RAY ATWELL. The driver denied any alcoholic beverage consumption when asked (due to a heart condition), stated he was heading home from his daughters residence, and advised the vehicles steering and alignment was faulty. While speaking with the driver, I made the following observations:  -pupils pinpoint -eyes bloodshot -STRONG odor of an alcoholic beverage on the drivers breath -STRONG odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the passenger compartment of the vehicle -disheveled appearance: pants open and unzipped, unkept hair -multiple error and warning lights on the vehicles dash display  I returned to my patrol vehicle to enter the drivers information for the business needs of the traffic stop. I then made contact with the driver, again, and the driver was now smoking a cigarette. I asked the driver to exit the vehicle and put out the cigarette and he complied. The driver pants were open and unzipped. The driver was wearing a blue and white sweatshirt, blue jeans, and black sneakers. The driver pull his pants up slightly (not all the way) when he stood up outside the vehicle. The driver made a repetitive statement about the alignment and steering being off. I asked the driver the following questions as we stood at the front of his vehicle:  Q. Are you diabetic? A. No, sir.  Q. Do you take any medications for any sort of mental health disorder? A. No, sir.  Q. Do you take any sort of medications for main management or pain relief? A. No, sir.  Q. Do you wear contacts or glasses? A. Yes, I do. I was able to ascertain the driver is far-sighted, despite his initial confusion about the difference between near-sighted and far-sighted.  Q. Do you have any physical issues that would prevent you from standing on one leg for approximately 30 seconds or walking a straight line heel touching toe? A. Yeah, I mean, like, yeah my heart condition.  I asked the driver how his heart affects his walking. The driver advised he has had a heart attack, and his heart functions at 30 % capacity. The driver stated he was will to take a breathalyzer right now. I asked again if the driver would be able to walk 9 heel touching toe steps, conduct a turn, walk 9 heel touching toe steps back, or stand on one leg for approximately 30 seconds. The driver stated I mean I, I, I can give it a try, I can stand, I not in good health. While speaking with the driver outside the vehicle, I made the following observations:  -strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on the drivers breath and person -bloodshot eyes -pupils pinpoint -slow front to back sway while standing (approximately 1 inch) -raspy voice  Based on my observations of the vehicle in motion, and my observations of the driver (inside and outside the vehicle), I made the decision to administer the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. I specifically asked the driver if he was willing to try the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, the driver responded Ill give it a try.  Phase III: Pre-Arrest Screening  All tests were explained and demonstrated prior to asking the driver to attempt them. The tests were conducted in a flat, well-lit area, free of debris.  SFSTs:All tests were explained and demonstrated prior to me asking the driver to attempt them.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus:  The drivers eyes displayed equal pupil size (pinpoint), tracking, and reaction. I was able to observe 6 clues out of the 6 potential clues:  -both eyes lacked smooth pursuit -distinct nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes -onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degree deviation in both eyes  Additional observations:  -eyes bloodshot -pupils pinpoint -strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on breath and person -front to back swaying, approximate 1 inch  Vertical Nystagmus was not observed.   Walk  Turn:  The driver conducted this test with his shoes on. I observed 7 clues out of the potential 8 clues:  -cannot keep balance: stepped out of the instructional position twice -stooped walking: after step 1, then after the first set of steps prior to the turn -missed heel to toe on both sets of steps -stepped offline: sidestepped for balance on both sets of steps -raise arms for balance parallel to the ground/ flailed arms for balance -incorrect number of steps: 10 steps both ways -incorrect turn: did not leave front foot planted  Additional observations:  -eyes bloodshot -pupils pinpoint -strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on breath and person  One Leg Stand:  The driver conducted this test with his shoes on. The driver indicated he understood my instructions. The driver stood on his right foot and raised his left. I observed 3 out of the 4 potential clues:  -raise arms for balance parallel to the ground/ flailed arms for balance -sway side to side -put foot down 3 times  I stopped the test early for the drivers safety.  Additional observations:  -eyes bloodshot -pupils pinpoint -strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on breath and person  Additional Tests: A.R.I.D.E.  Lack of Convergence:  The lack of convergence was observed: right eye diverged from center.  Additional observations:  -eyes bloodshot -pupils pinpoint -strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on breath and person -slow sway forward  Finger To Nose:  The driver was placed in the instructional position: arms down to their side, heels together, hands in fists with index fingers extended and wrists rotated outward. The driver was instructed, when told to do so, to close their eyes and tilt their head backward. I would then give the command, either right or left, and the driver is to touch the tip of their nose with the tip of their index finger, then immediately bring their arm back down to their side. I provided the following commands: left, right, left, right, right, left.  Observations:  -used pad of finger and side of his finger, not the fingertip as instructed and demonstrated -eyelid tremors -held finger in place of first attempt -opened eyes after first attempt -strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on breath and person  Modified Romberg:  The driver was placed in the instructional position: arms down to their side and heels together. The driver was instructed when I would tell them to do so, to close their eyes, tilt their head back and estimate the passage of 30 seconds by counting quietly to themselves. After the passage of 30 seconds, the driver was instructed to bring their head down, open their eyes and say done.  Observations:  -strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on breath and person -the driver took 20 seconds (according to the digital recording) to estimate the passage of 30 seconds -eyelid tremors observed to the point his right eyelids were separated  The driver was offered a Preliminary Breath Test, which he submitted to with a result of 0.07 BrAC. The driver final admitted to alcoholic beverage consumption earlier in the day. Based on my observations of the driver during contact and the SFSTs, I made the decision to place the driver under arrest. The driver was advised he was under arrest for DUI, handcuffed, and placed in my patrol vehicle. The vehicle as not able to be moved to a safe parking space due to the mechanical issued and shut off as it was trying to be moved. The vehicle was towed from the scene by AKAL Towing.  The decision to arrest was supported by the following observations:  -STRONG odor of an alcoholic beverage on the drivers breath and person, perceptible even outside in the rain -eyes bloodshot -pupils pinpoint -the performance of the SFSTs (HGN: 6/6, OLS: 7/8, W  T:3/4) -impaired time perception -disheveled appearance: pants open, unzipped, had to be pulled up, driver hand trouble keeping his pans pulled up  The driver was transported to the MSP Westminster Barrack, located at 1100 Baltimore Blvd, Westminster, Carroll County, MD. The driver was read the DR15 Advice of Rights at 1541 hours. The driver signed the DR15 at 1544 hours, refusing the intoximeter. An intoximeter operator was readily available. The driver was able to call a ride, and made calls to him mother as well. The driver became irritated during his conversations with his mother, and was yelling at her. Routine MVA check showed the driver has a current alcohol restriction on his drivers license through the MVA (J restriction, MAB). The driver was issued the DR15, DR15A, Notice to Appear, Notice to Right of Counsel, SERO for turn signals, steering, and wheel alignment, and traffic citations MM0DJH-MM60DJH. The driver was released to a friend and advised not to drive within12 hours from the time of arrest (1517 hours).  At all times the driver was polite and cooperative with me.  All events occurred in Carroll County, MD.  Case closed on arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2024 10:53:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/11/2024 10:56:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eyler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0670</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>FAIR</LastName>
            <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5334</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>536289</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/06/2024 14:58:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2024 11:39:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2024 11:39:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>59</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2024 11:44:25</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2024 11:44:26</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>353517</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Atwell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ray</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/27/1964 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>08/24/2022 03:34:34</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A340</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Atwell</LastName>
               <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ray</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/27/1964 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>A340</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>A535</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/24/2022 03:34:34</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3144</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Bullfrog</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Taneytown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21787</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.239594</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.664993</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/08/2024 11:44:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/08/2024 11:44:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/08/2024 11:44:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/08/2024 11:44:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/08/2024 11:44:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/08/2024 11:44:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/08/2024 11:44:25</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>01/08/2024 11:44:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/08/2024 11:39:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/08/2024 11:39:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>160640</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/11/2024 11:04:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/11/2024 11:04:31</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/11/2024 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1D6HG38N64S580158</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2004</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>DAK</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>PK</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLU</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>BLU</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8FP5605</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>