<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-036038</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/14/2023 02:09:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/14/2023 02:09:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/14/2023 01:45:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/14/2023 01:45:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>I responded to a motor vehicle collision. Upon contact with the driver, the odor of an alcoholic beverage was detected. SFST's was conducted, and the driver performed poorly. Driver was sent to Charles Regional Medical Center where blood kit was utilized.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 02:09:16</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0104</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 11:50:23</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>CHARLES ST/ DENTON RUN PL</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>709850</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 02:09:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 06:18:01</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>709850</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Charles</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Charlotte Hall</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20622</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>PL</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.82874</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.47412</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13901-14100 CHARLES ST / 8849-8939 DENTON RUN PL</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/14/2023 02:09:12</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/14/2023 02:09:12</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/14/2023 11:18:53</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 02:09:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 11:18:53</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car camera and body worn camera operational.  Defendant: Suite, Michele Ruth  Date of Birth: 01/28/1982  Time of arrest: 0240 hours  Location: Westbound Route 6 in the area of Denton Run Place, Charlotte Hall, Charles County Maryland, 20622.  Maryland drivers license:S-300-603-751-075  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; DUI#: 23-181  Intoximeter results: Pending Blood Kit H-258  1stDUI  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING  *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police.  *Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement through Charles County Sheriffs Office.  NARRATIVE/ VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1):  On 10/14/2023 at approximately 0146 hours, I, Tpr. Tripp #7333 with the Maryland State Police La Plata Barrack H was dispatched to a motor vehicle collision that occurred on Westbound Route 6 in the area of Denton Run Place.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2): font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;   Upon arrival, I observed a gray Hyundai Santafe bearing Maryland registration 4ED6024, off the roadway into a tree with a heavy front-end damage. Once I made contact with the driver who was standing outside of the vehicle, I requested for her driver license, registration, and proof of insurance, which she only displayed her license and proof of insurance. I was able to identify the driver through her Maryland drivers license as, Suite, Michele Ruth (W/F, DOB: 01/28/1982). While speaking with Suite, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. While speaking with Suit, I observed her eyes to be bloodshot, glassy and her speech to be slurred. While Speaking with Suite, I observed her failing to maintain balance when either standing or being able to walk towards me when I requested. I asked Suite if she had consumed any alcoholic beverages and she advised, Yes. I then asked Suite what alcoholic beverage did she consume and she advised, Two beers. I also observed what appeared to be blood on Suites Sweatshirt. I requested Emergency Medical Services (EMS) to respond to the scene to evaluate Suite. EMS responded to the scene at 0158 hours. EMS evaluated Suite and advised to me she on has a small laceration on the back of her head. EMS also advised she has non-life-threatening injuries and Suite requested to be transported to the hospital. I then advised Suite, I needed her to perform Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs), which she agreed to take.As Suite approached the front of my vehicle, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. Prior to performing SFSTs I faced Suite away from the emergency lights (EMS vehicles) and turned my emergency lights off make sure the lights would not interfere with the test.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3): font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; CCSO assisted with the traffic stop. While standing in front of my vehicle, I asked Suite is there any medical conditions that I should be aware of and she advised, No. I asked Suite if she wears glasses or contacts and she advised, she wears contacts. I asked Suite is there any physical disabilities that I should be aware of and she advised, No. I asked Suite if she is a diabetic or have high blood pressure and she advised, No. I asked Suite if she had any head injuries or concussions and she advised, No. I then asked Suite if she was able to perform the Walk and Turn test (WAT) and the One Leg Stand test (OLS) and she advised, Yes.I then asked Suite if she could see the pen displayed approximately 12 inches away from her eyes and she advised, Yes. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS TEST: (6/6 clues observed).  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) test. The tip of my pen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Suites eyes. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping herhead still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with hereyes until told to stop. Herpupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting nystagmus. Shewas positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results.Suite swayed back and forth throughout the portion of this test.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Suite displayed equal pupil size, equal tracking and no resting nystagmus in both eyes.  Suite displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  Suite displayed nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  Suite displayed nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.  VERTICAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Suite displayed vertical gaze nystagmus in both eyes.   WALK AND TURN: (6/8 clues observed). font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Prior to Suite performing the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Suite was instructed to place herright foot directly in front of herleft foot and touch heel to toe. She was instructed and demonstrated to place herhands flat at hersides and to remain in that position until told to begin. Shewas advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. Shewas instructed to keep her hands flat at hersides, keep hereyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Suite was explained and demonstrated to keep her lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with herrear foot to turn completely around. Suite was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Shewas instructedonce she began the test she was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep her hands down by hersides, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. Suite advised she understood the test before beginning. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Suite wore black and white sneakers for this test. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Suitecould not keep her balance during instructional portion of the test. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Suite missed heel-to-toe steps on all nine steps, on her first set of nine steps. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Suite stepped off-line on her first, seventh, eighth, and ninth step, on her first set of nine steps.  Suite took approximately 12 steps, on her first set of nine steps.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Suite performed an improper turn by not taking a series of small steps to turn around.  Suite stopped after the improper turn and on her second step, on her second set of nine steps.  Suite took one step backwards.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Suite missed heel-to-toe steps on her first, second, fourth, fifth, sixth, seventh and ninth step, on her second set of nine steps. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Suite stepped off-line on her first, second, fourth, fifth, sixth, eighth and ninth step, on her second set of nine steps.  Suite approximately 13 steps, on her second set of nine steps.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; ONE LEG STAND: (3/4 clues observed) font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Prior to Suite performing the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Shewas instructed to stand with herheels together and hands down by hersides while the instructions were given. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of herchoice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While herleg was raised, she was to keep herleg straight, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Suite advised she understood the test. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Suite raised her right foot for this test.  0-10 seconds  Suite swayed at three, five, and eight seconds.   Suite raised her arms at four, five, eight and ten seconds.  Suite placed her foot down at four, five, and ten seconds.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; 21-30 seconds  Suite raised her arms at 23 and 28 seconds.  Suite placed her foot down at 22 and 27 seconds.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Suite was offered to take the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) and agreed to take the test.Her results were .17 BrAC. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Arrest: font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person.  -Bloodshot and glassy eyes.  -Admission to drinking alcoholic beverage.  -Clues displayed from the Standardized Field Sobriety Test. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; -Positive preliminary breath test. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; Suite was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol at 0240 hours.The DR-15 Advise of Rights was read to Suite, and she agreed to take the blood test at 0256 hours. Suite was transported to Charles County Medical Center (CRMC) for further processing. Once myself and Suite arrived at CRMC, Blood was drawn from Suite by nurse Cesar G. Nonot at 0344 hours.   Suite was released to the care of the hospital.  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; All events occurred in Charles County, Maryland. font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt;  font-variant-ligatures:normal; text-decoration-thickness:initial; text-decoration-style:initial; text-decoration-color:initial" /&gt; I request this case to remain open, pending BAC results. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/16/2023 03:59:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/23/2023 12:45:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alphrin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5237</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tripp</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sedrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7333</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525499</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 02:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 06:18:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 06:18:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525499</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 02:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 06:18:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 06:18:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>41</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 06:25:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 06:25:30</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>390331</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Suite</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michele</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ruth</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/28/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/14/2023 06:24:51</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Suite</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michele</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Ruth</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/28/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S300</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/14/2023 06:24:51</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>37850</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Asher</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Mechanicsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20659</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2670</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.767444</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.403471</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>536</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2328</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 06:25:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 06:25:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 06:25:30</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:22</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 06:18:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 06:18:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>158037</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/14/2023 06:26:32</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 06:26:32</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/14/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5NMS23AD7KH090448</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2019</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HYUN</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>SANTAFE</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4ED6024</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>12/10/2023 13:06:55</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>12/10/2023 13:06:55</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>57</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/14/2023 11:18:53</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 13:06:55</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>12/14/2023 11:18:53</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 11/27/2023 at approximately 0906 hours, I, Tpr. Tripp #7333, received the blood test for alcohol concentration results from the Maryland State Police Forensic Sciences Division. The test result was .18 grams of alcohol per 100 milliliters of blood.  On 12/10/2023 at approximately 1600 hours, I made contact with Suite at her residence to issue her citations and confiscate her license. A DR-15A temporary license was issued to Suite.  Suite received the following citations:  TA-21-902(a1ii) Driving under the influence of alcohol per se.  TA-21-902(a1i) Driving under the influence of alcohol.  TA-21-902(b1i) Driving while impaired by alcohol.  TA-21-901.1(a) Reckless driving.  TA-21-901.1(b) Negligent driving.  TA-21-201(a1) Failure to obey traffic control device.  TA-21-309(b) Unsafe lane change.  TA-21-301(a) Failure to drive right of center.  TA-21-801(b) Failure to control speed to avoid collision.  TA-13-409(b) Failure to display registration card.  All events occurred in Charles County, Maryland.  Case closed.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/10/2023 13:08:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 11:43:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Norman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Alphrin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5237</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>57</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tripp</LastName>
            <FirstName>Sedrick</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7333</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525499</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 02:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 11:35:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 11:35:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525499</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 02:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 11:35:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 11:36:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525499</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>A</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 02:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>A</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 11:34:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 11:34:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525499</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 02:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 11:55:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 11:55:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525499</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 02:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 11:55:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 11:55:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525499</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 02:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 11:55:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 11:55:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525499</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 02:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 11:55:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 11:55:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525499</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15558</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 02:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15558</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 11:55:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 11:55:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>525499</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15648</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>1</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/14/2023 02:40:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15648</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7333</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>12/11/2023 11:55:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7333</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/11/2023 11:55:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>