<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-041540</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>11/23/2023 01:56:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>11/23/2023 01:56:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>11/23/2023 01:49:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>11/23/2023 01:49:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>23-616 "R" ELLIOTT</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>11/23/2023 02:06:13</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6354</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 15:39:18</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>SEMINARY AT TALLY HO RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>714016</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/23/2023 03:47:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/23/2023 03:47:31</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>714016</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Tally Ho</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Timonium</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21093</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>W</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>AVE</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.654362</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.425523</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>11/23/2023 02:06:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>11/23/2023 02:06:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>12/13/2023 15:39:19</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>11/23/2023 02:06:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/09/2024 16:59:03</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E.) TEAM* The following incident was captured on in-car and body camera Defendant: Timothy Edward Elliott  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES: * I am trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (March 2013 SFST NHTSA Manual). * I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor as of February 2016. * I am a Certified Breath Test Operator by the Toxicologist of the State of Maryland as of March 2016. * I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of March 2016. * I am a distinguished graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute as of June 2015 * I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of May 2014. * I am a Preliminary Breath Test Instructor as of May 2019. * I am a RADAR and LIDAR Instructor as of October 2019. * I have apprehended more than 1,000 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On November 23, 2023 at approximately 0134 hours, I (Cpl. Wallace #6323) was on patrol in unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle DUI-1 on northbound Falls Road prior to Seminary Ave, Baltimore County, Maryland. I observed a white Lexus SUV traveling two vehicles in front of my patrol vehicle. I observed the Lexus to continue to brake and swerve. The Lexus would swerve left over the solid double yellow line and immediately jerk right. The Lexus made a right onto Seminary Ave and continued to swerve. Swerved left over the solid double yellow line on multiple occasions and jerked right. The Lexus swerved right over the dotted white line and solid white line for a right turn lane, but continued straight. When safe, I passed the vehicle that was between my patrol vehicle and the Lexus. The Lexus swerved right over the dotted white/solid white for another turn lane, but continued straight and drove on the right shoulder. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the Lexus that was bearing Maryland registration 1FF1916.   PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Lexus on the driver side and made contact with the male operator of the vehicle, who was the only occupant in the vehicle. I explained the reason for the stop and requested his drivers license and vehicle registration. He had a blank stare. He missed handing his license from his right hand to his eft hand, hit his thumb. He was identified by his Maryland drivers license as Timothy Edward Elliott. While speaking with Elliott, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I deliberately observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I returned to my patrol vehicle to notify the barrack who I was out with.   I returned to the Lexus and requested Elliott to exit his vehicle and walk to the front. He asked me what I said, and I had to repeat myself. He complied and exited his vehicle. He stumbled while exiting and missed grabbing his door with his right hand. When at the front of his vehicle he stumbled right and backwards when turning around. When asked about alcohol consumption prior to driving, he stated a little too much. He stated that he was drinking just beer (Budweiser). When asked how many he thinks he had, he stated more than he should have. While speaking with Elliott outside othe vehicle, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I informed Elliott that I wanted him to perform standardized field sobriety tests.  He stated that he was probably not okay to drive. He asked if he could have someone pick him up. I explained to him that was not an option and he stated that he would not do the tests and just admit it. His speech was slurred.  ARREST Due to the number of observations, I concluded Elliott was driving under the influence and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 0156 hours, I placed Elliott under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. He was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and was transported to Falls Road and Joppa road where the Maryland State Police Intoximeter truck was located, for processing.  He stated, do you know what is fucked up, my girlfriend is a district court judge. This is going to go over like a lead balloon.  Upon arrival at the intoximeter truck, I provided Elliott with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Elliott listened to the DR-15 Advice of Rights from the MVA website. At 0218hours, Elliott refused to take a breath test.  20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: Not applicable  INTOXIMETER RESULT: ****Refusal****  Elliott was polite and cooperative during the encounter. Elliott was given all copies of pertinent paperwork and released.   All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/23/2023 03:49:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>12/13/2023 14:26:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>59</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Anderson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6354</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>531010</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>11/23/2023 01:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/23/2023 03:48:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/23/2023 03:49:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>48</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/23/2023 03:48:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/23/2023 03:49:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>393719</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Elliott</LastName>
               <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Edward</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/14/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>11/23/2023 03:43:42</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T530</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Elliott</LastName>
               <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Edward</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/14/1975 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>E430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T530</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>11/23/2023 03:43:42</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>13109</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Manor</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Glen Arm</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21057</Zip5>
               <Zip4>9626</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.519874</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.484282</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/23/2023 03:49:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>11/23/2023 03:49:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:31</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6323</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>11/23/2023 03:48:47</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>11/23/2023 03:48:47</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>