<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012899</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/11/2023 22:01:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/11/2023 22:01:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/11/2023 21:31:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/11/2023 21:31:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI - 23-026 - Steinly</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 22:01:08</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/14/2023 22:50:43</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>690390</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 22:01:10</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/12/2023 08:28:35</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>690390</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>3379</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Chestnut Ridge</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Grantsville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-79.098007</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.699345</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/11/2023 22:01:04</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/11/2023 22:01:04</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/14/2023 22:34:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/11/2023 22:01:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Driver: Tamela Sue Steinly PA OLN: 23651984 DUI #: 23-026 Video: My in-car cameras and body worn camera were activated during the incident. Subsequent Offender: No  VEHICLE IN MOTION:  On 4/11/2023 at approximately 2131 hours, I, TFC. Bradley was working a stationary RADAR assignment, monitoring traffic traveling South on U.S. Rt. 219 @ Old Salisbury Road. At that time, I observed a vehicle approaching me from the rear at what appeared to be above the posted speed limit of 40 Miles Per Hour (MPH). I activated the rear antenna of my Golden Eagle Radar II (SN#: XE-02471) in stationary mode and obtained a reading of 66 MPH. The vehicle was the lone vehicle in my RADAR beam and when the vehicle cleared the beam, the speed dropped from the RADAR display screen. I am certified by Maryland State Police to operate RADAR, my RADAR unit was tested before and after my tour of duty and was found to be working properly. As the vehicle passed my location, I identified it as a light blue Ford Focus bearing Pennsylvania registration LKC9768. I activated the emergency equipment in my marked patrol vehicle (W-8) to conduct a traffic stop on the Ford. The Ford stopped in the parking lot of Grantsville shopping plaza. PERSONAL CONTACT:  I made contact with the driver of the Ford via drivers side approach and immediately detected the strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle and observed the drivers eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I advised the driver the reason for the traffic stop and she replied, I know, Im sorry. She handed me the registration for the Ford and I asked her for her drivers license. As she looked for her license, I asked where she was driving to, she told me she was going to her boyfriends house Grantsville. I asked how many drinks she had that night, she replied, Probably like six. I identified the driver as Tamela Sue Steinly by her Pennsylvania drivers license. I returned to the Ford and heard Steinly on an active phone call inside of the vehicle and observed she now had a lit cigarette. I asked Steinly to exit the vehicle to perform field sobriety tests, she agreed.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING:  The evaluation was performed in the parking lot of the Grantsville shopping plaza. The asphalt surface was flat and free of debris. I deactivated the front emergency lights of my patrol vehicle. The weather was clear and approximately 54 degrees Fahrenheit. Lighting conditions consisted of my vehicles headlamps, overhead streetlamps and my flashlight. Steinly appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any physical injuries, limps or limb ailments. Steinlys back faced towards my patrol vehicle. I asked Steinly the following questions: How many alcoholic beverages consumed before driving: Six. Where were they consumed: Meyersdale Moose. What kind of drinks: Crown Apple and cranberry juice, which is names Western Apple. Time of last drink: However long it takes to get here from Meyersdale. Physical/medical disabilities: No, I have seizures but thats it. Recent Injuries: No. Medications: Metoprolol and Neurontin daily. Glasses/contacts: Normally wears glasses, but not when driving. On a scale of 0 to 10 with 0 being completely sober and 10 being the most drunk you have ever been in your life, what numerical figure represents your impairment right now: Probably a four.  As I spoke with Steinly outside of the vehicle, I continued to detect the strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person and observed her eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. Steinly was wearing a black tank-top style shirt, denim shorts and gray/white shoes. HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN) TEST (6/6 CLUES OBSERVED)   The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. My black ballpoint pen was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Steinlys eyes. Steinly was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the stimulus with her eyes only until told to stop. Steinlys pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Steinly advised she understood the instructions.   Steinly displayed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.   Steinly displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.   Steinly displayed the onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.  *Steinly did not display vertical nystagmus. WALK AND TURN TEST (8/8 CLUES OBSERVED)  Prior to Steinly performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test was to be conducted. Steinly was instructed to place her right foot in front of her left and touch heel to toe. Steinly was instructed to place her hands at her side and to remain in that position until told otherwise. I asked Steinly if she understood, she advised he did. Steinly was advised to take nine (9) steps straight out in front of her, touching heel to toe on every step. She was to keep her hands down at her side, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step Steinly was demonstrated and explained to keep her lead foot planted and to take a series of small steps around with her rear foot to turn completely around without stopping. Steinly was explained and demonstrated the second series of steps to be performed identical to the first series. Steinly was advised once she started the test, she was not to stop until the test was completely finished. After explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked Steinly if she understood the instructions, she replied she did. Instructional Stage:    Steinly lost balance repeatedly throughout the instruction and demonstration.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Steinly started the test too soon three times.  First Nine:    Steinly missed heel-to-toe on steps 2 through 8.  Steinly stepped off line on steps 1 and 9.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Steinly raised her arms throughout the entire test.  The Turn:     margin-left:8px"&gt;Steinly pivoted the front of both feet to turn around, then lifted her right foot to reset and place her feet beside each other, contrary to instructions.   Second Nine:    Steinly stopped walking at the beginning of the second nine.  Steinly missed heel-to-toe on steps 6 through 9.  Steinly stepped off line on steps 2 through 5.  Steinly raised her arms throughout the entire test.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Steinly took (10) actual steps for the second nine portion of the test, contrary to instructions.  After completing the test, Steinly stated, Please do not get me for a DUI. During my observations of the test on scene, I observed and made note of seven out of eight clues. Upon reviewing my body-worn camera footage, I observed and made note of eight out of eight clues on the test.  ONE-LEG STAND TEST (3/4 CLUES OBSERVED BEFORE REFUSAL)  Prior to Steinly performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Steinly was instructed to stand with her feet together and hands down to her sides while the instructions were given and during the test. Steinly was instructed not to begin the test until she was instructed to start, and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, she was to raise the foot of her choice off the ground approximately six (6) inches. While her leg was raised, she was to keep her leg straight, keep her toe pointed forward, watch her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand two, one thousand three...) and to continue the test until told to stop (30 seconds). Steinly advised that she understood all the instructions. She balanced on her right leg with her left leg raised. Seconds 0-10:    Steinly placed her foot down twice during the first ten seconds.   Steinly raised her arms throughout the test.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Steinly swayed throughout the test.  At approximately the ten second mark, Steinly placed her foot down for the second time and told me she couldnt do the test. ALPHABET F-T:  Steinly advised she is familiar with the English alphabet and agreed to recite it from F to T.     margin-left:8px"&gt;Nothing to report.  COUNT BACKWARDS 59-36:  Steinly agreed to count backwards, starting at the number 59 and ending at the number 36.     margin-left:8px"&gt;Steinly stopped at the number 39 and asked if that was where I told her to stop. I told her she was to stop at 36. She then counted: 39, 38, 36.   PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT): I read Steinly the MSP 102 (Preliminary Breath Test Advisement of Rights) and asked her to submit to a PBT. Steinly refused to submit to a PBT at approximately 2146 hours. ARREST/DR-15 ADVICE OF RIGHTS: Due to the facts above, I placed Steinly under arrest for DUI at approximately 2147 hours. At that time, I check Steinlys mouth for any foreign objects, none were observed. Steinlys Ford was secured in the parking lot. I played Steinly the audio version of her DR-15 Advice of Rights and provided her with a physical copy to read along with if she desired to. At approximately 2159 hours, Steinly refused to submit to a breath test. Steinly was transported to the McHenry barrack for processing. During transportation to the McHenry barrack, Steinly stated without being asked, When I tell you I had six drinks, I had six Fireball shots, Ill be honest. She also stated without being asked, I speed all of the time. Steinly was provided with her copies of paperwork, advised not to drive for 12 hours and released to her friend, Kathy Bodes. As I made contact with Steinly throughout the night, I continued to detect the strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from her breath and person and observed her eyes to be bloodshot and glassy.  Case closed by arrest.  All above events occurred in Garrett County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/13/2023 02:23:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7189</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/13/2023 02:24:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Kline</LastName>
            <FirstName>Nicholas</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7112</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7189</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shrout</LastName>
            <FirstName>Timothy</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2951</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7189</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bradley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Cody</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7189</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>502303</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/11/2023 21:47:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/12/2023 08:28:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7189</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/12/2023 08:29:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>48</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/12/2023 08:28:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:00</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>374041</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Steinly</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tamela</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Sue</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/30/1974 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.88544309E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>04/11/2023 23:16:31</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S354</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Steinly</LastName>
               <FirstName>Tamela</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Sue</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/30/1974 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>1.88544309E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S354</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/11/2023 23:16:31</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>942</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Ernest Miller</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Meyersdale</City>
               <StateCode>PA</StateCode>
               <Zip5>15552</Zip5>
               <Zip4>7120</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.03956</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.773005</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>814</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>289</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9099</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/12/2023 08:30:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/12/2023 08:30:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/12/2023 08:30:44</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/12/2023 08:28:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7189</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/12/2023 08:28:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151880</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7189</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/12/2023 08:28:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7189</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/12/2023 08:28:12</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/11/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1FADP3F23EL128672</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FOC</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>LBL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>PA</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>LKC9768</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>