<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-035314</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/08/2023 02:16:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/08/2023 02:16:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/08/2023 01:59:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/08/2023 01:59:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 02:16:43</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5948</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 19:21:41</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>EMMORTON RD/ I95 S</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>598533</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 02:16:44</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 23:26:36</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>598533</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Emmorton</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Abingdon</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetSuffixCode>S</CrossStreetSuffixCode>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 EMMORTON RD / 0-0 I95 S</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/08/2023 02:16:41</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/08/2023 02:16:41</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/24/2023 14:22:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 02:16:43</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:39</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The incident was audibly and visually recorded from my BWC. MSP unmarked unit D-24 is equipped with MVR equipment. DEFENDANT: AUGUSTYNIAK, DAIM GABRIEL Date of Birth: 06/15/1999 (24 years old) Date of Arrest: 10/08/2023 Time of Arrest: 0214 hours DUI #: 23-241 (Bel Air Barrack, Harford County) Subsequent Offender: No Minor in the vehicle: No MD-DL. # A-223-135-271-447 CDL: No Certificate and Training: *I am a certified police officer in the state of Maryland with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with participants at the Maryland State Police Academy and prior DUI/DWI arrests and convictions. *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *RADAR / LIDAR Certified 2019. *Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator Certified. *Advance Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement Certified (ARIDE): Attended ARIDE with the Maryland State Police in January 2021 *UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND DUI INSTITUTE: I attended the University of Maryland DUI Institute, and I completed the course with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with live participants (From June 5 to June 10, 2022) *Certified as SFST witness expert by Honorable Judge Martin H. Schreiber II in Baltimore City Circuit Court on September 27, 2022. *Certified SFST witness expert by Honorable Judge David E. Carey in Harford County District Court on October 11, 2022. *I have apprehended more than 180 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On October 08, 2023, at approximately 0159 hours, I, Trooper First Class Reckeweg # 7214 of the Maryland State Police currently assigned to the Bel Air Barrack (unmarked MSP patrol vehicle D-24), was traveling on southbound Route 24 prior to Tollgate Road. At this time, I observed ahead of my patrol vehicle a 2022 Silver Toyota Corolla in lane one (1). The Toyota appeared to be traveling above the posted speed limit of 55 mph. I accelerated my patrol vehicle to 70 mph, attempting to pace the Toyota, but the Toyota was pulling away from my patrol vehicle at some speed greater than 70 mph. I then activated my in-car moving radar system (Golden Eagle II) and selected the front radar dish for speed acquisition. My radar system registered a continuous radar tone and speed reading of 87 mph, while there was only one vehicle (the Toyota) in front of my patrol vehicle within the operating range of my radar system. The radar tone and radar speed matched my visual speed estimate of the Toyota. I pulled behind the Toyota, and a traffic stop was initiated as I activated my emergency equipment. The Toyota stopped on the right shoulder of southbound Route 24 and I-95, Harford County. I then observed the Toyota bearing Maryland registration 3FB5588. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Toyota via the passengers side window, made contact with the driver, and explained to the driver the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver for his drivers license. The driver handed me a Maryland drivers license and was identified as AUGUSTYNIAK, DAIM GABRIEL (W/M, DOB 06/15/1999, Maryland Soundex A-223-135-271-447). I asked AUGUSTYNIAK where he was coming from and where he was going. AUGUSTYNIAK advised me that he was coming from Looneys bar and going to his house. While talking to AUGUSTYNIAK, I instantly noticed his eyes were glassy and bloodshot. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from inside the Toyota. AUGUSTYNIAKs speech was slurred. I observed that AUGUSTYNIAK had a stamp bar on the right side of the hand. I asked AUGUSTYNIAK how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed that evening, and he stated, I had four beers. I asked AUGUSTYNIAK to exit and walk to the front of my patrol vehicle. AUGUSTYNIAK exited and walked to the front of my patrol vehicle. AUGUSTYNIAK was stumbling while walking to the front of my patrol vehicle. At the front of my patrol vehicle, I could now detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on AUGUSTYNIAKs breath and person. AUGUSTYNIAK had difficulty keeping his balance, and he leaned against my patrol vehicle for balance. I advised AUGUSTYNIAK that I would perform a standardized field sobriety test on him, which he agreed to submit. The summary of the first contact is as follows: Attitude: Cooperative Eye Condition: Glassy/bloodshot Mental State: Normal. Walk: Stumbling. Speech: Slurred. I asked AUGUSTYNIAK the following questions: Medication- No Medical Conditions- No Glasses: No Any pain in the body- No PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The below standardized field sobriety tests were performed on the right shoulder on the roadway. That area of the road was level and free of debris. I turned off my front emergency lights before beginning the standardized field sobriety tests below. The weather conditions were clear. Lighting conditions consisted of my patrol vehicle headlights and my flashlight. AUGUSTYNIAK appeared in good physical condition and displayed no visible signs of injury. I explained and demonstrated the standardized field sobriety tests below to AUGUSTYNIAK. AUGUSTYNIAK stated he understood my instructions and had no questions about the standardized field sobriety test. -HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN) / (6/6 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: YES) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my index finger from my right hand was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from AUGUSTYNIAKs eyes, slightly above his eyebrows. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. AUGUSTYNIAKs pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I observed his eyes to be red. AUGUSTYNIAK was positioned to ensure passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked AUGUSTYNIAK if he understood the instructions, and he stated, Yes. The following clues and observations were made during the test: Lack of Smooth Pursuit- Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation- Present in both eyes The onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 Degrees- Present in both eyes Additional test Vertical Gaze Nystagmus- Present in both eyes -WALK AND TURN (WAT) / (5/8 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: Yes) Before AUGUSTYNIAK performed the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. AUGUSTYNIAK was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. AUGUSTYNIAK was instructed and demonstrated to put his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until instructed to begin. AUGUSTYNIAK was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line, touching heel to toe on each step. AUGUSTYNIAK was asked to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count each step out loud. On the ninth step, AUGUSTYNIAK was explained, and I demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and planted and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around to his left. AUGUSTYNIAK was again explained, and I demonstrated that the second series of nine (9) steps were to be completed identically to the first. Keep his hands by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. I asked AUGUSTYNIAK if he understood the test. AUGUSTYNIAK stated, Yes. AUGUSTYNIAK was instructed to begin the test. Instructional Stage: Cannot Keep Balance: Unable to keep balance Started before instructed Walking Stage (1st Nine) AUGUSTYNIAK stepped offline on steps 2, 5, and 7. AUGUSTYNIAK missed heel to toe by approximately 2 inches on step 4. Walking Stage (2nd nine): AUGUSTYNIAK stepped offline on steps 3, 6, and 7. AUGUSTYNIAK missed heel to toe by approximately 2 inches on steps 2, 4, and 8. Turn: Completed satisfactory -ONE LEG STAND (OLS) (LEFT LEG) (2/4 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: Yes) Before AUGUSTYNIAK performed the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. AUGUSTYNIAK was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given during the test. AUGUSTYNIAK was instructed to begin the test when he was asked to start and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to watch his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (thousand-one, thousand-two), and continue the test until told to stop. I asked AUGUSTYNIAK if he had any questions about the test (OLS), to which he replied, No. AUGUSTYNIAK raised his left foot. Instructional Stage: Nothing to report. Balance and Count Stage: AUGUSTYNIAK swayed on the 5 and 23-second mark AUGUSTYNIAK put his foot down on the 7, 15, and 24-second mark -PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT) (REFUSED)- The final test offered to AUGUSTYNIAK was the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT). AUGUSTYNIAK was advised that he could refuse this test. AUGUSTYNIAK agreed to submit to the PBT with results of .20 BrAC. ARREST Based on my knowledge, training, experience as an MSP Trooper, previous DUI arrests, and clues gathered thus far, I had reason to believe AUGUSTYNIAK was driving a motor vehicle while impaired (under the influence of Alcohol). *Driving over the posted speed limit 87/55mph zone * Physical control of a motor vehicle. *admission of consumption of alcoholic beverages. *Odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. *Bloodshot eyes. *Slurred speech. *Watery eyes. * My observed signs of impairment as he performed the standardized field sobriety. ARREST / ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) / CERTIFIED BREATH TEST (AGREED)/ Corporal Workman #6608 (Maryland State Police). I arrested AUGUSTYNIAK for driving under the influence of Alcohol at approximately 0214 hours. AUGUSTYNIAK was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to Maryland State Police Bel Air Barrack for processing, where a mouth check was performed 20 minutes before his submission to the breath test. AUGUSTYNIAK was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along with as the DR-15 advice of rights was played to him from the official MVA website. At the conclusion of the DR-15, AUGUSTYNIAK agreed to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the DR-15, indicating the same at approximately 0240 hours. AUGUSTYNIAK provided two breath examples with positive results of .18 BRAC. AUGUSTYNIAK was given all copies of pertinent paperwork, and AUGUSTYNIAK was released to a sober adult who came to Bel Air Barrack. INTOXIMETER RESULT: Results of .18 BRAC (0251 hours) AUGUSTYNIAK was cooperative during the processing. Case Status  Closed by arrest. All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/11/2023 01:33:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/20/2023 14:27:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sander</LastName>
            <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5948</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524774</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/08/2023 01:59:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 23:22:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 23:28:54</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 23:22:54</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 23:30:23</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389848</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>AUGUSTYNIAK</LastName>
               <FirstName>DAIM</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>GABRIEL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/15/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16551778E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>10/08/2023 02:58:32</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>A223</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>AUGUSTYNIAK</LastName>
               <FirstName>DAIM</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>GABRIEL</MiddleName>
               <DOB>06/15/1999 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>2.16551778E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>A223</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>D500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/08/2023 02:58:32</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 23:30:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 23:30:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 23:30:23</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 23:26:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 23:26:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157843</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/10/2023 23:36:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/10/2023 23:36:15</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JTDEPMAE9NJ209628</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3FB5588</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>