<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012356</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/07/2023 02:43:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/07/2023 02:43:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/07/2023 01:49:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/07/2023 01:49:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 02:43:59</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/30/2023 21:41:06</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>Northbound I-495, prior to Baltimore Ave.</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>689924</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 04:33:01</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/18/2023 10:45:42</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>689924</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Capital Beltway</StreetName>
         <City>College Park</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20740</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/07/2023 02:43:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/07/2023 02:43:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/18/2023 11:26:08</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 02:43:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Case #: 23-MSP-012356 Report: DUI Suspect: Wali Severus Passmore DOB: 02/07/1996  Narrative:   On April 7th, 2023, at approximately 0149 hours I, Trooper Savilisky (ID#7460), with the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack, responded to northbound I-495 prior to Baltimore Ave, College Park, Maryland, for a vehicle on the left shoulder with its hazard lights activated. I arrived on scene I observed a silver Dodge Challenger displaying Virginia registration (4565NT) on the left shoulder.   Phase 1 (Vehicle in Motion Phase)  The silver Dodge Challenger was stationary on the left shoulder on northbound I-495, prior to Baltimore Ave. The silver Dodge Challenger had its interior lights on and the engine was running prior to my arrival.         Phase 2 (Personal Contact Phase)         Upon approach of the driver side window, I observed an African American male in the driver seat. The operator appeared to be asleep. The operator of the vehicle was later identified through his Washington D.C. drivers license as Wali Severus Passmore. I opened the driver door of the silver Dodge Challenger and immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I then introduced myself and stated my body camera is recording the incident.         I asked Passmore if he was okay to which he stated I had to stop. I then asked Passmore why to which he stated everythings good, I just had to stop. I continued to ask Passmore where he was coming from to which he stated my fiends house, south-west. When asked where south-west was Passmore stated stadium. While speaking with Passmore I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the interior of the vehicle. I also observed Passmores eyes to be bloodshot, glassy, and watery. I then asked Passmore if he drank any alcohol recently to which he stated yeah. When I asked Passmore how much he stated little bit, not that much.        I continued to question Passmore about his alcohol consumption. I asked Passmore how long ago did he drink the alcohol to which he stated recently. At this time I requested another unit to my location. I proceeded to ask Passmore to step to the front of his vehicle, to which he complied. Once Passmore had stepped to the front of his vehicle, I asked him if he remembered how much he had to drink to which he stated yeah it wasnt that much though. I asked Passmore to give me an estimate on how much he had to drink to which he stated two cups. I then asked what kind of alcohol he drank to which he stated wine. When asked about how long ago he drank the alcohol Passmore stated a couple hours ago. At this time, I requested Passmore to perform Standard Field Sobriety Tests, to which he agreed.   Phase 3 (Pre-Arrest Screening)  Medications: None  Glasses/Contacts: None  Physical Injuries/Surgeries: None         Notes: The field sobriety tests were performed on northbound I-495, prior to Baltimore Avenue, on the left shoulder. The ground was dry and free of any debris. The area was illuminated by my marked patrol vehicles headlights, the silver Dodge Challengers headlights, as well as my flashlight. My front facing emergency equipment was not activated during the field sobriety tests.         Passmores Standard Field Sobriety results are as follows:        Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) (6/6 Clues.)       Instructional Phase: I instructed Passmore to stand with his feet together, keep his arms down to his side, and to follow my pen, which was used as a stimulus, with his eyes and his eyes only. Passmore was instructed not to move his head during the test. The stimulus was held approximately 12 inches away from Passmores head. When I asked if Passmore understood the instructions to the test he shook his head up and down to indicate yes.           -Passmore displayed a lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  -Passmore displayed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  -Passmore displayed onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.         Notes: Passmore displayed equal tracking and equal pupil size in both eyes.         Walk and Turn (WAT) (6/8 Clues)        Instructional Phase: I demonstrated the walk and turn test to Passmore. While demonstrating the walk and turn test, I also verbally instructed Passmore how to perform the test. Passmore was instructed to place his right foot in a heel-to-toe position in front of his left foot during the instructional phase of the walk and turn test. Passmore was instructed to take nine heel-to-toe steps in a straight line, pivot on his lead foot on the ninth step, take a small series of small steps with his opposing foot to turn himself in the opposite direction back towards the position he started from, and take another series of nine heel-to-toe steps in a straight line. Passmore was instructed to keep his arms down to his sides, look down at his feet as he stepped, and to count each step out loud. Passmore was also instructed to not stop the test until he has completed the test. When I asked Passmore understood my instructions he stated yes sir.        Notes: Although not valid clues for the walk and turn test, Passmore did not start the test in the instructional position or count his steps out loud which is contrary to my instructions        First Series of Nine Steps:        -Passmore attempted to begin the walk and turn test twice prior to being instructed to begin.       -Passmore missed heel-to-toe on steps three.       -Passmore stepped off-line on step one.       -Passmore raised his arms away from his body to maintain his balance on steps one through five and step 8.       -Passmore took a total of 11 steps on the first series of nine steps.       -Passmore did not perform the turn as I instructed and demonstrated. Passmore did not pivot on his lead foot. Passmore lifted his right foot and placed it across the left side of his left foot to maintain his balance while turning around.       Second Series of Nine Steps:      -Passmore raised his arms away from his body to maintain his balance on steps one through five, and step 11.       -Passmore missed heel-to-toe on step two.      -Passmore took a total of 12 steps on the second series on nine steps.        One Leg Stand (OLS) (0/0 Clues)       Instructional Phase: I explained and demonstrated to Passmore how to properly perform the one leg stand test. I instructed Passmore to stand on either foot of his choosing, raise the opposing foot off the ground by approximately six inches, and to point his foot level with the ground. Passmore was also instructed to keep his arms down to his sides, and to count out loud by thousands for the test until told to stop. When asked if Passmore understood the instructions for the one leg stand test he stated yes. -Passmore did not display any clues for the One Leg Stand Test.        Notes: Passmore stood on his right foot for the one leg stand test. Although not a valid clue, Passmore did not count out loud by thousands, which was contrary to my instructions.       Preliminary Breath Test (PBT)     -Upon arrival of Prince Georges County Officer. Mendoza (ID#3567), I proceeded to offer Passmore a Preliminary Breath Test, to which he agreed.     -PBT results: 0.13 Brac.      After making the above stated observations, I placed Passmore under arrest for operating a motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol. I conducted a search incident to arrest which did not reveal any contraband. Passmores silver Dodge Challenger was towed from the scene by AlleyCat Towing. I proceeded to transport Passmore to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack for processing. While transporting Passmore, I proceeded to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person while inside my patrol vehicle. Once at the barrack, Passmore was given all pertinent paper work for the incident and released to a sober driver.     All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.     I request this case to be closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/10/2023 00:00:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7460</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/10/2023 00:04:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Savilisky</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zack</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7460</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Smith</LastName>
            <FirstName>James</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6084</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Savilisky</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zack</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7460</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Savilisky</LastName>
            <FirstName>Zack</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7460</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 02:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 04:34:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7460</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 04:50:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 02:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 04:34:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7460</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 04:50:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 02:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 04:34:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7460</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 04:49:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19745</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 02:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19745</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 04:34:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7460</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 04:50:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501759</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 02:43:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17272</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 04:34:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7460</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 04:51:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>27</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 04:34:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:29</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373661</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Passmore</LastName>
               <FirstName>Wali</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Severus</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/07/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/07/2023 04:08:02</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>P256</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Passmore</LastName>
               <FirstName>Wali</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Severus</MiddleName>
               <DOB>02/07/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>P256</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/07/2023 04:08:02</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3000</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>7th</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <StreetSuffixCode>NE</StreetSuffixCode>
               <City>Washington, D.C.</City>
               <StateCode>DC</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20017</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.9963847</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.9278553</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>202</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>910</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2441</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/07/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 10:43:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 10:43:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 10:43:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/18/2023 10:43:55</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7460</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 04:34:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7460</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 04:34:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>