<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-012452</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/07/2023 23:57:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/07/2023 23:57:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/07/2023 23:39:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/07/2023 23:39:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI: 23-190 "R" TERRANOVA</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 23:57:18</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 21:09:11</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>WHITE MARSH BLVD/ BENGIES CT</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>690005</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 23:57:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/07/2023 23:57:19</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>690005</AddressId>
         <StreetName>White Marsh</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Middle River</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>CT</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.41658</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.34128</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>6400-6498 WHITE MARSH BLVD / 0-0 BENGIES CT</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/07/2023 23:57:15</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/07/2023 23:57:15</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/03/2023 21:09:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/07/2023 23:57:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:44</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E.) TEAM* The following incident was captured on in-car camera Title: DUI 23-190 R TERRANOVA ID: 23-MSP-012452 Defendant: Michael Anthony Terranova TRAINING/CERTIFICATES:    I am trained and certified in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).  I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor as of July 2021.  I have successfully completed Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) training as of September 2020.  I am a distinguished graduate from the University of Marylands DUI Institute as of August 2021.  I am trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police as of 2020.  I have apprehended more than 300 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On April 7, 2023 at approximately 2320 hours, I (TFC. Speak #7219) was on patrol in marked Maryland State Police vehicle DUI-7 on Easter Boulevard in the area of White Marsh Boulevard, Baltimore County, Maryland. I observed a gray Ford Focus attempt to make a U-turn and strike the curb resulting in a single vehicle collision. The Ford was bearing Maryland registration 9AM3626.  I observed the Ford turn from Eastern Boulevard onto White Marsh Boulevard. The Ford entered the left turn lane on White Marsh Boulevard for Bengies Court and was attempting to make a U-turn. As I continued passed the Ford to the next U-turn area, I observed the Ford cross three lanes of eastbound White Marsh Boulevard and strike the curb. The Ford drove on top the curb and drove in the grass for multiple feet. As a result of striking the curb, the Fords front passenger tire was flat and undercarriage damage causing the Ford to become disabled. Upon observing this collision, I activated my emergency equipment and stopped with the Ford on eastbound White Marsh Boulevard at Bengies Court.   As I arrived on scene and was still in my patrol vehicle, I observed the male subject walking around the Ford. The male subject was unsteady on his feet and showed poor balance and lack of coordination.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Ford and made contact with the driver, who was now at the trunk of the vehicle. While the driver walked to the trunk, I observed him to be unsteady on his feet and staggering. While talking to the driver outside of his vehicle, in an ambient environment, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. The driver was now going through his trunk to get the materials to change his tire. I then requested his drivers license and registration. He was identified by his Maryland drivers license as Michael Anthony Terranova. Terranova was unable to provide me the vehicles registration and I advised him he could have a seat in the vehicle while I ran his information. Terranova stated, I gotta change my tire, I mean, I fucked up. Terranovas eyes were bloodshot and glassy. He also had thick slurred speech. I then returned to my patrol vehicle and turned off my front emergency equipment.  I returned to the Ford and observed Terranova removing his spare tire from the trunk. Terranova was now at the front passenger tire and attempting to change the tire. I instructed Terranova to leave the spare tire where it was and come to the sidewalk on the passenger side of the Ford. I asked Terranova where he was driving from and he stated a bar. When asked how many alcoholic beverages he consumed, Terranova stated five beers. Terranova stated he stated drinking when he left work at 4:45 PM. I then asked Terranova if he was informing me he only had five beer from the time he left work until now and he stated, No, Im not saying that. I asked Terranova to give me a total number of beers he had consumed and he stated, Thats kinda hard. Ive had three beers since 8oclock and maybe five samples. When asked how long prior to driving his last alcoholic beverage was, Terranova stated, Ahh fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Hour maybe? I informed Terranova that I wanted him to perform standardized field sobriety tests, to which he agreed to the tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the sidewalk off of White Marsh Boulevard. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. Lighting conditions consisted of patrol vehicle headlights, streetlights, and flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. He appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries. He was wearing a shirt, shorts, and shoes.  I asked Terranova the following questions:  Glasses or contacts  Terranova stated he wears semi-contacts but did not have them in. Physical Injuries  None. Medication  None. Medical Conditions  None.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Terranova swayed front to back while standing stationary for the test.    Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus.     Lack of Smooth Pursuit: Present in both eyes.  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes.  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes.      margin-bottom:11px"&gt;Vertical Gaze Nystagmus  Present in both eyes.   WALK AND TURN (6/8 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Terranova stated that he understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Terranova placed a jacket on for the walk and turn test. While grabbing his jacket from the vehicle, Terranova asked me if he struck the curb. I asked Terranova if he was unaware that he hit he curb and he stated, No, I hit the curb when I turned, fuck, fuck, fuck.  Instructional Stage:    Broke instructional position to the right twice.  Walking Stage (1stNine):    Stepped completely offline on steps 1, 2, 5, 8, and 9.  Missed touching heel to toe by more than a  inch on steps 3, 4, 6, and 7.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Completed 10 steps instead of the instructed nine.  Turn:     margin-left:8px"&gt;Did not complete turn as instructed.  Walking Stage (2ndNine):    Stopped walking on step 1.  Missed touching heel to toe by more than a  inch on steps 2, 3, and 4.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Stepped completely offline on steps 1, 5, 6, 7, 8, and 9.  ONE LEG STAND The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Terranova stated that he was unable to do the test due to being cold. REFUSED  PBT #70005012: Refused  ARREST: Due to the number of observations, I concluded Terranova was driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 2341 hours, I placed Terranova under arrest for driving while under the influence of alcohol. He was placed in the front passenger seat per department policy and was transported to the Maryland State Police Golden Ring Barrack for further processing.  Upon arrival at the Barrack, I provided Terranova with a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights. Terranova was advised of his DR-15 Advice of Rights. At 0041 hours, Terranova refused to take a breath test.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: *****REFUSAL*****  Terranova was given all copies of the pertinent paperwork and transported to his residence.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 05:54:30</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7219</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 15:46:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Speak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7219</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Speak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7219</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Speak</LastName>
            <FirstName>Logan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7219</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>501855</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/07/2023 23:57:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 05:52:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7219</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 05:52:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>54</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 05:52:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>373731</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Terranova</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anthony</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/20/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 05:47:16</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>T651</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Terranova</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Anthony</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/20/1968 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>T651</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 05:47:16</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>608</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>N</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>WOODWARD</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Baltimore</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21221</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 05:54:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 05:54:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 05:54:13</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:05</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 05:52:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7219</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 05:52:21</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151744</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7219</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 05:52:21</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7219</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 05:52:21</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VehicleYear>2008</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>9AM3626</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>