<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-035284</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/07/2023 20:54:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/07/2023 20:54:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/07/2023 20:01:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/07/2023 20:01:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop resulting in the driver being arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 20:54:04</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5364</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/02/2023 13:22:21</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>TRA</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>36 MM CAPITAL BELTWAY EB, BETHESDA</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>709284</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 20:54:05</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 21:43:47</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>709284</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>36</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm Capital Beltway Eb Bethesda</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.1010445</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0176766666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/07/2023 20:54:00</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/07/2023 20:54:00</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/16/2023 04:33:31</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/07/2023 20:54:04</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:57</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP marked vehicle N-36 is equipped with a mobile recording device  Defendant: Ivan Otoniel Diaz Guevara Date of Birth: 04/07/1982 Date of Arrest: 10/07/2023 Time of Arrest: 2052 hours DUI #: 23-216  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *Trained in administering advanced standardized field sobriety tests (ARIDE) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On October 7, 2023, at approximately 2001 hours, I, Trooper Lear (#7154), was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating marked MSP vehicle N-36 in Kensington, Montgomery County, Maryland. I was traveling westbound on I-495 at Maryland Route 185 when I observed a silver Toyota Camry traveling in lane three, struggling to maintain a single lane. The Toyota crossed over the dotted white lines from lane three into lane two and lane four by more than a tires width on ten separate occasions. The Toyota was not forced by any other vehicle to cross the dotted white lines. I activated my emergency equipment and the Toyota pulled over to the right shoulder of northbound I-495, south of Maryland Route 187. The Toyota was bearing MD registration 3EH5844.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Toyota and made contact with the driver. When I made contact with the driver, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I immediately observed the drivers eyes to be bloodshot and glassy with a glazed look. The driver was identified by his MD drivers license as Ivan Otoniel Diaz Guevara (DOB: 04/07/1982, H/M). I observed Diaz Guevaras speech to be mumbled throughout our entire interaction. I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Diaz Guevara. I advised the Rockville Barrack that I would be conducting standardized field sobriety tests and needed a backup unit. A Montgomery County Police Officer arrived on scene. I asked Diaz Guevara to exit his vehicle, to which he complied. I asked Diaz Guevara if he consumed any alcoholic beverages that night. Diaz Guevara advised he did not consume any alcoholic beverages that night. Diaz Guevara advised me he was coming from his friends residence. Diaz Guevara advised me that his friends met up due to one of his friends recently passing away. During our conversation, I could detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Diaz Guevaras breath and person. Diaz Guevara advised me he was swerving in the lane due to him having to urinate. Translation was used through Google Translate.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed in front of the Toyota Camry on the right shoulder of northbound I-270 south of Maryland Route 187. The surface was dry, slight uphill grade, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 65 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of light illuminating from light poles and my patrol vehicles headlights. Diaz Guevara appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries that would prevent him from walking or standing.  I asked Diaz Guevara the following questions: - Injuries  No - Medication  No - Medical Conditions  No - Glasses/Contacts  None observed  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from Diaz Guevaras eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Diaz Guevaras pupils were equal in size, showed equal tracking, and no resting Nystagmus was observed. He was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Diaz Guevara if he understood the instructions and he stated, Yes. Translation was used through Google Translate.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 degrees  Present in both eyes  WALK AND TURN (3/8 clues observed) Prior to Diaz Guevara performing the test, I properly examined and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Diaz Guevara was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Diaz Guevara was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in the position until told to begin. Diaz Guevara was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Diaz Guevara was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Spry was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Diaz Guevara was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Diaz Guevara was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Diaz Guevara if he understood the test and he stated, Yes. Footwear: sneakers. Translation was used through Google Translate.  Instructional Stage: -Failed to maintain balance on one (1) occasion.  Walking Stage (1st Nine): -Raised arms throughout the timeframe. -Took seven (7) steps.  Turn: -Completed satisfactorily.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): -Raised arms throughout the timeframe.  I had to repeat the instructions for the turn to Diaz Guevara before the test started using Google Translate.  ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed) Prior to Diaz Guevara performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Diaz Guevara was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two), and continue the test until told to stop. I asked Diaz Guevara if he understood the test and he stated, Yes. Diaz Guevara chose to raise his left foot. Footwear: sneakers. Translation was used through Google Translate.  Instructional Stage: -No clues observed.  Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: -No clues observed.  Seconds 11-20: -Swayed throughout the timeframe. -Placed his foot down throughout the timeframe. -Raised his arms throughout the timeframe.  Seconds 21-30: -Swayed throughout the timeframe. -Placed his foot down throughout the timeframe. -Raised his arms throughout the timeframe.  Diaz Guevara failed to follow directions by not counting out loud throughout the entire test.  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Diaz Guevara was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: -Failed to maintain a single lane on ten occasions. -The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. -Eyes were glassy and bloodshot with a glazed look. -Mumbled speech throughout our entire interaction. -Struggled to understand directions. -Struggled to maintain his balance. -Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus - 6/6 clues observed. -Walk and Turn - 3/8 clues observed. -One Leg Stand - 3/4 clues observed. -Apologized for his actions.  I arrested Diaz Guevara for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 2052 hours and performed a search incident to arrest. During the search of his person, I again detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating not only from his person, but from his breath as well. Diaz Guevara was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Rockville Barrack for processing. During transport, I could detect a strong odor of alcoholic beverage emanating from Diaz Guevaras breath and person. During transport, Diaz Guevara was irritated with me and threatened to take me to court. Diaz Guevara demanded that I write my name and badge number on a piece of paper for his safe keepings. Diaz Guevara apologized for his actions when I dropped him off at his residence.  Diaz Guevara was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, so he could follow along as the DR-15 Advice of Rights audio was played out loud in Spanish. The Spanish version audio can be found on mva.maryland.gov. Diaz Guevara signed the DR-15 at approximately 2127 hours, agreeing to submit to the intoximeter test.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Diaz Guevara beginning with his arrest. A preliminary search of Diaz Guevara was conducted on the scene and it revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. I observed Diaz Guevara from the time of the arrest until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by Sgt. Tribue (#5781) of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Diaz Guevaras breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of .17 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. Diaz Guevara was released at his residence by me.  All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland.  CASE CLOSED BY ARREST.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/13/2023 05:14:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/14/2023 23:52:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lear</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quinn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7154</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tribue</LastName>
            <FirstName>Byron</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5781</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lear</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quinn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7154</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lear</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quinn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7154</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524744</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/07/2023 20:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:42:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 21:49:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524744</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/07/2023 20:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:42:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 21:48:16</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524744</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/07/2023 20:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:42:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 21:48:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524744</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/07/2023 20:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:42:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 21:46:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524744</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/07/2023 20:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:42:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 21:47:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524744</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/07/2023 20:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:42:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 21:46:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524744</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/07/2023 20:52:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:42:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 21:47:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>41</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:42:51</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 21:50:43</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389910</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Diaz Guevara</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ivan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Otoniel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/07/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/08/2023 21:31:15</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>D221</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Diaz Guevara</LastName>
               <FirstName>Ivan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Otoniel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/07/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>D221</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>I150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/08/2023 21:31:15</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>19515</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Frederick</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>TRLR</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>110</SubNumber>
               <City>Germantown</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20876</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-77.23738</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.17725</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:50:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:50:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:50:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:50:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:19</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:43:50</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 21:43:50</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157875</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/08/2023 21:42:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/08/2023 21:42:52</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>4T1BE32K64U858240</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2004</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CAM</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3EH5844</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>5</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>