<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009984</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/19/2023 22:10:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/19/2023 22:10:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/19/2023 21:55:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/19/2023 21:55:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>SINGLE VEHICLE COLLISION &amp; DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 22:10:23</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5657</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/09/2023 01:58:50</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>377383</AddressId>
      <City>MDC200</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:12:29</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/01/2023 10:27:27</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>377383</AddressId>
         <StreetName>E/B US-50 W/O I-495</StreetName>
         <City>Hyattsville</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20785</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.866874</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.944658</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/19/2023 22:10:19</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/19/2023 22:10:19</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/08/2023 17:14:53</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/19/2023 22:10:23</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Incident was recorded. Q-8 is MVR equipped. Body-worn camera is equipped. Defendant: Jovel Ramos, Jose Osmin Date of Birth: 08/01/1967 Date of Arrest: 03/19/2023 Time of Arrest: 2245 hours NC License #: 000045212355 DUI #: 23-067  TRAINING/CERTIFICATES Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Standardized Field Sobriety Test refresher course March 2023  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On 03/19/2023 at approximately 2218 hours I, Trooper Gonzales #7442 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack was operating unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle Q-8 in the area of eastbound US-50 prior to I-495. I was responding to a request for a Spanish-speaking officer from Trooper Stewart #7590 responding to a call for service of a single-vehicle collision. I observed a black Nissan Altima facing westbound with all around damage off the roadway to the right of eastbound US-50 prior to I-495. The Nissan was bearing Maryland registration 7EX2581.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I observed a Hispanic male standing in front of unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle Q-41 which was parked on the right shoulder of eastbound US-50 prior to I-495. I introduced myself and made contact with the hispanic male. I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath/person. I also observed him to have glassy and bloodshot eyes as well. I asked him if he preferred English or Spanish to which he replied he preferred Spanish. As I communicated with the operator of the Nissan regarding the specifics of the collision, I continued to detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath/person. The Hispanic male was subsequently identified as Jose Osmin Jovel Ramos (H/M DOB: 08/01/1967). A check through MVA revealed that Jovel Ramos license was expired. I asked Jovel Ramos what occurred, and he replied that he was driving home when he was forced off the road by an unknown vehicle. I also asked if he had anything to drink tonight to which he answered he had two to three beers (cervezas). I then asked of what brand, size, and how long ago to which he answered it was the Modelo brand, small sized (pequea), and he last consumed it at approximately 1600  1700 hours earlier that evening.  At that time, I asked Jovel Ramos to perform standardized field sobriety tests to determine if he was safe to drive to which he agreed.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of eastbound US-50 prior to I-495. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. Jovel Ramos appeared to be in good physical health and had a small cut on his left hand as a result of his single-vehicle collision.  I instructed Jovel Ramos to stand in front of unmarked Maryland State Police vehicle Q-41.  I asked Jovel Ramos the following questions: Glasses or contacts  none. Medical conditions  none. Injuries  a small cut on his left hand as a result of a single-vehicle collision. Jovel Ramos advised it would not interfere with his abilities to walk a straight line or maintain his balance. If he considers himself a healthy person  yes.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6 clues observed) The first test was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of a pen was used as the tests stimulus. It was held approximately 12 - 15 inches away from Jovel Ramos eyes, slightly above his eye level. Jovel Ramos was instructed to look forward, keep his head still, and follow the tip of the stimulus with his eyes and his eyes only. Jovel Ramos was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. Jovel Ramos pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes. Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes. Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was observed. It is also to be noted that Jovel Ramos was swaying while standing in place for this portion of testing.  Walk and Turn (6/8 clues observed) The test was explained and demonstrated. Jovel Ramos was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe on a straight line. Jovel Ramos was instructed to remain in that position until told to begin. Jovel Ramos was instructed to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. On the ninth step, he was instructed to keep his lead foot planted and take a series of short, choppy steps with his rear foot to turn completely around. After the turn, Jovel Ramos was instructed to complete the second series of nine (9) steps in the same heel to toe fashion. Jovel Ramos was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, count every step aloud, and once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was completed. I asked Jovel Ramos if he understood the instructions to which he replied he understands (yo entiendo).  Jovel Ramos was observed wearing brown hiking shoes.  Instructional Stage:    margin-left:8px"&gt;Cannot keep balance (three occasions)  Walking Stage (1st Nine):    Uses arms for balance (one occasion)  Steps off line (one occasion)  Misses heel-to-toe (three occasions)   margin-left:8px"&gt;Wrong number of steps (took eight steps)  Turn     margin-left:8px"&gt;Incorrectly performed. (Did not keep lead foot planted. Both feet came off the ground).  Walking Stage (2nd Nine):    Uses arms for balance (one occasion)  Misses heel-to-toe (two occasions)   margin-left:8px"&gt;Wrong number of steps (took eight steps)  One Leg Stand (3/4 clues observed) The test was explained and demonstrated. When instructed to start, Jovel Ramos was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately six (6) inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his legs straight, watch the raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand two, etc) and to keep his hands down by his side. I asked Jovel Ramos if he understood the instructions to which he states he did.  Instructional Stage:     margin-left:8px"&gt;Nothing to report  Seconds 0  10:    Puts foot down (two occasions)   margin-left:8px"&gt;Hops  Seconds 11  20:     margin-left:8px"&gt;Puts foot down (one occasion)  Seconds 21  30:    Puts foot down (two occasions)   margin-left:8px"&gt;Uses arm for balance (one occasion)  It is to be noted that initially Jovel Ramos did not perform this portion of testing as instructed. He raised a leg six inches off the ground for a second, placed it down, raised the other leg six inches off the ground for a second, placed it down, and repeated. I asked him prior to him beginning the test if he understood to which he answered yes.  While on scene, I informed Jovel Ramos of his Preliminary Breath Test Rights. Jovel Ramos was offered a PBT to which he refused.  ARREST Based on the totality of the circumstances, I had reason to believe Jovel Ramos was driving a motor vehicle while under the influence of alcohol.    Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from breath/person.  Glassy bloodshot eyes.  Initial appearance of the scene to indicate alcohol was involved in a single-vehicle collision.  Driver admitting to consuming two to three Modelo beers hours prior.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Clues during Standardized Field Sobriety Testing: HGN (6/6), WAT (6/8), OLS (3/4).  Due to the number of observations I had reason to believe Jovel Ramos was driving under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a vehicle safely.  At approximately 2245 hours, I placed Jovel Ramos under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. I immediately notified the barrack, and searched his person for weapons and contraband, both with negative results. Jovel Ramos was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and was transported to the College Park Barrack per department policy. I checked Jovel Ramos mouth and observed no foreign objects. Jovel Ramos was read his DR-15 Advice of Rights in Spanish from the Maryland Motor Vehicle Administration website. At approximately 2339 hours Jovel Ramos agreed to take an alcohol concentration test. Jovel Ramos received instructions in Spanish during the instructional phase of the alcohol concentration test.  20 MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Jovel Ramos beginning on scene. Jovel Ramos was observed from 2249 hours until the time he submitted to the test, and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by Cpl. McGee #6675 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Jovel Ramos had a result of .10 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath at 0012 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT .10 BrAC  Jovel Ramos was processed and released to a sober driver with a valid Maryland drivers license. The defendant was issued copies of the following documents:    Citations.  DR-15 Advice of Rights.  DR-15a Order of Suspension.   margin-left:8px"&gt;MSP 33.  All documents were forwarded to the Prince Georges County, States Attorneys Office.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.    </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:13:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7442</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/30/2023 06:57:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stewart</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7590</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gonzales</LastName>
            <FirstName>Javier</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7442</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McGee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gonzales</LastName>
            <FirstName>Javier</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7442</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Gonzales</LastName>
            <FirstName>Javier</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7442</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499384</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 22:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:12:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7442</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 00:21:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499384</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 22:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:12:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7442</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 00:22:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499384</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 22:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:12:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7442</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 00:22:38</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499384</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 22:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/01/2023 10:23:04</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7442</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/01/2023 10:23:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>499384</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/19/2023 22:20:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/01/2023 10:25:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7442</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/01/2023 10:25:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>55</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:12:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:44</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372301</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>JOVEL RAMOS</LastName>
               <FirstName>JOSE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>OSMIN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/01/1967 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/23/2023 03:48:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>J146</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>JOVEL RAMOS</LastName>
               <FirstName>JOSE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>OSMIN</MiddleName>
               <DOB>08/01/1967 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>J146</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/23/2023 03:48:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>729</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2278</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:24:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:24:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:24:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:58</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 04:45:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7442</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 04:45:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151188</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7442</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 00:12:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7442</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 00:12:29</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1N4BA41E68C832949</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2008</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ALT</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7EX2581</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/24/2023 04:10:26</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/24/2023 04:10:26</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>66</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/08/2023 17:14:53</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 04:10:26</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:34</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>  On March 19, 2023 at approximately 2155 hours I, Tpr. Ryan Stewart #7590 currently assigned to the Maryland State Police College Park Barrack was dispatched to the area of John Hanson Hwy (US 50) and Martin Luther King Jr Hwy. (Rt. 704) for a report of a vehicle into the woods that was smoking and occupied. I was also notified by the College Park Barrack fireboard was enroute.   Upon arrival in the area, I check US 50 both east and west bound from the Capital Beltway (I-459) to Collington Rd. (Rt. 197) and did not observe anything. While checking E/B US 50 I observed multiple fireboard units responding W/B US 50 and inquired from the barrack for a more accurate location from fireboard. I was then advised the location would be E/B US 50 in the area of 202.    As I was arriving at the scene of the crash fireboard was clearing the scene. I observed a black Nissan Altima bearing MD registration 7EX2581 facing W/B on the grassy shoulder which appeared to have rolled with all around damage. I further observed an individual wearing a light colored jacket and dark pants grabbing belongings from the vehicle and area around the vehicle. I made contact the male and identified him by his by his North Carolina drivers license as Jose Osmin Jovel Ramos (H/M 8/1/67). While attempting to speak with Jovel Ramos he advised he did not speak english. While attempting to communicate with Jovel Ramos I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. At this time I requested Trp. Javier Gonzales #7442 respond to the scene as a Spanish-speaking trooper. Tpr. Gonzales arrived on scene and assumed the investigation. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7590</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 04:11:44</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7590</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 04:11:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McGee</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6675</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>66</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Stewart</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7590</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>