<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-010666</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/25/2023 03:49:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/25/2023 03:49:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/25/2023 03:14:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/25/2023 03:14:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/25/2023 03:49:13</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/10/2023 08:09:18</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>688426</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/25/2023 03:49:15</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/25/2023 03:49:15</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>688426</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1205</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Joppa</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Joppa</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.357007</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.431298</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/25/2023 03:49:11</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/25/2023 03:49:11</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/02/2023 16:33:05</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/25/2023 03:49:14</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:21</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>The incident was audibly and visually recorded from my BWC. MSP unmarked unit D-24 is equipped with MVR equipment. DEFENDANT: MATTHEW CHRISTOPHER BENDER Date of Birth: 09/29/1987 (36 years old) Date of Arrest: 03/25/2023 Time of Arrest: 0348 hours DUI #: 23-082 (Bel Air Barrack, Harford County) Subsequent Offender: No Minor in the vehicle: No MI-DL. # MD-10273757944 CDL: No Certificate and Training: *I am a certified police officer in the state of Maryland with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with participants at the Maryland State Police Academy and prior DUI/DWI arrests and convictions. *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *RADAR / LIDAR Certified 2019. *Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Operator Certified. *Advance Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement Certified (ARIDE): Attended ARIDE with the Maryland State Police in January 2021 *UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND DUI INSTITUTE: I attended the University of Maryland DUI Institute, and I completed the course with over 40 hours of training in DUI detection with live participants (From June 5 to June 10, 2022) *Certified as SFST witness expert by Honorable Judge Martin H. Schreiber II in Baltimore City Circuit Court on September 27, 2022. *Certified SFST witness expert by Honorable Judge David E. Carey in Harford County District Court on October 11, 2022. *I have apprehended more than 150 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On March 25, 2023, at approximately 0314 hours, I, Trooper First Class Reckeweg #7214 of the Maryland State Police currently assigned to the Bel Air Barrack (unmarked MSP patrol vehicle D-24), was traveling in lane two (2) on westbound Route 40 west of Edgewood Road. At that time, I observed a maroon Jeep Wrangler ahead of my patrol vehicle. The Jeep swerved two times to the right and went over the solid line dividing lane two (2) from the right shoulder by its tire width. The Jeep regained control and returned to lane two (2). I pulled behind the Jeep, and a traffic stop was initiated as I activated my emergency equipment. The Jeep continued driving for approximately 30 seconds and stopped in the driveway at 1205 Joppa Road, Joppa, Harford County. I then observed the Jeep bearing South Carolina registration PYZ526. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the Jeep via the drivers side window, made contact with the driver (only occupant), and explained to the driver the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver for his drivers license. The driver handed me a Maryland drivers license and was identified as MATTHEW CHRISTOPHER BENDER (W/M, DOB 09/29/1987, Maryland Soundex MD-10273757944). I asked BENDER where he was coming from and where he was going. BENDER advised that he was coming from a gas station (from Royal Farm at Route 152) and going to his house. While talking to BENDER, I instantly noticed his eyes were glassy and bloodshot. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from inside the Jeep. The drivers speech was slurred. I asked the driver how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed that evening, and he stated, I am not answering any question. I am on private property I asked BENDER to exit and walk to the front of my patrol vehicle, and he refused. I ordered BENDER multiple times to exit his vehicle, and he refused, stating he was on private property. BENDER eventually complied and exited his vehicle. I observed BENDER stumble while exiting his vehicle. BENDER refused to walk to the front of my patrol vehicle and stayed in the driveway stating that he wanted to stay on private property. In the driveway, I could now detect the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on BENDERs breath and person. I advised BENDER that I had detected a strong odor of alcoholic beverage on his breath and person. I asked BENDER again how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed that evening. BENDER advised that he had one (1) or two (2) drinks prior to the traffic stop. I observed BENDER having difficulty keeping his balance as he swayed from left to right. I advised BENDER that I would performstandardized field sobriety teston him, which he agreed to submit. The summary of the first contact is as follows: Attitude: uncooperative (refused to exit his vehicle) Eye Condition: Glassy/bloodshot Mental State: Normal. Walk: Stumbling. Speech: Slurred. I asked BENDER the following questions: Medication- Yes (last time taken medication was between 4:00 pm to 8:00 pm) Medical Conditions- Yes Glasses: No Any pain in the body- Yes (Left shoulder, a lot of medical conditions) PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The below standardized field sobriety tests were performed in the driveway of 1205 Joppa Road, Joppa, Harford County. That area of the driveway was level and free of debris. Before beginning the standardized field sobriety tests below, I turned off my front emergency lights. The weather conditions were clear. Lighting conditions consisted of my patrol vehicle headlights and my flashlight. BENDER appeared in the good physical condition and displayed no visible signs of injury. I explained and demonstrated the standardized field sobriety tests below to BENDER. BENDER stated he understood my instructions and had no questions about the standardized field sobriety test. -HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (HGN) / (6/6 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: YES) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my index finger from my right hand was used as the test stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from BENDERs eyes, slightly above his eyebrows. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. BENDERs pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking. I observed his eyes to be red. BENDER was positioned to ensure passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked BENDER if he understood the instructions, and he stated, Yes. The following clues and observations were made during the test: Lack of Smooth Pursuit- Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation- Present in both eyes The onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 Degrees- Present in both eyes Additional test Vertical Gaze Nystagmus- Present in both eyes -WALK AND TURN (WAT) / (5/8 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: Yes) Before BENDER performed the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. BENDER was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. BENDER was instructed and demonstrated to put his hands flat at his side and to remain in the position until instructed to begin. BENDER was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on each step. BENDER was asked to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count each step out loud. On the ninth step, BENDER was explained, and I demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and planted and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around to his left. BENDER was again explained, and I demonstrated that the second series of nine (9) steps were to be completed identically to the first. Keep his hands by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. I asked BENDER if he understood the test. BENDER stated, Yes. BENDER was instructed to begin the test. Instructional Stage: Cannot Keep Balance: Unable to keep balance Walking Stage (1st Nine) BENDER stepped offline on steps 2, 4, and 5. BENDER missed heel to toe by approximately 2 inches on steps 6 and 8. BENDER stopped walking on step 7. Walking Stage (2nd nine): BENDER stepped offline on steps 1, 3, and 4. BENDER missed heel to toe by approximately 2 inches on steps 2, 6, and 8. BENDER stopped walking on step 2. Turn: Completed Unsatisfactory. BENDER did not leave his front foot planted and used both feet to walk in a circle. -ONE LEG STAND (OLS) (LEFT LEG) (2/4 CLUES OBSERVED) (INSTRUCTED  UNDERSTOOD / DEFENDANTS RESPONSE: Yes) Before BENDER performed the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. BENDER was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given during the test. BENDER was instructed to begin the test when he was asked to start and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to watch his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (thousand-one, thousand-two), and continue the test until told to stop. I asked BENDER if he had any questions about the test (OLS) which he replied, No. BENDER raised his left foot. Instructional Stage: Nothing to report. Balance and Count Stage: 1. Puts foot down: BENDER puts his foot down on the 01 and 21-second mark 2. Hopping: BENDER hopped on the 19-second mark. -PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST (PBT) (REFUSED)- The final test offered to BENDER was the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT). BENDER was advised that he could refuse this test. BENDER refused to submit to the PBT test (0346 hours) ARREST Based on my knowledge, training, and experience as an MSP Trooper, previous DUI arrests, and clues gathered thus far, I had reason to believe BENDER was driving a motor vehicle while impaired (under the influence of Alcohol). *Swerving on the roadway. * Physical control of a motor vehicle. *admission of consumption of alcoholic beverages. *Odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. *Bloodshot eyes. *Slurred speech. *Watery eyes. * My observed signs of impairment as he performed the standardized field sobriety. ARREST / ADVICE OF RIGHTS (DR-15) / CERTIFIED BREATH TEST (AGREED)/ S/TROOPER WHITTENBERG #6095 (Maryland State Police). I arrested BENDER for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0348 hours. BENDER was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to Maryland State Police Bel Air-Barrack for processing, where a mouth check was performed 20 minutes before his submission to the breath test. BENDER was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights to follow along with as the DR-15 advice of rights was played to him from the official MVA website. At the conclusion of the DR-15, BENDER agreed to submit to the intoximeter test and signed the DR-15, indicating the same at approximately 0440 hours. BENDER provided two breath examples with positive results of .12 BRAC (0451 hours). BENDER was given all copies of pertinent paperwork, and BENDER was released to a sober adult that came to Bel Air Barrack. INTOXIMETER RESULT: Results of .12 BRAC (0451 hours) BENDER was cooperative during the processing. Case Status  Closed by arrest. All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 20:58:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 10:37:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Atkinson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5623</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reckeweg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Enrique</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7214</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>500068</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/25/2023 03:14:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 21:07:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 21:09:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 21:07:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372487</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>O</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>BENDER</LastName>
               <FirstName>MATTHEW</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>CHRISTOPHER</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/29/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/25/2023 04:27:29</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M300</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>BENDER</LastName>
               <FirstName>MATTHEW</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>CHRISTOPHER</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/29/1987 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B536</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M300</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/25/2023 04:27:29</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 21:12:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 21:12:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 21:12:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 21:08:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 21:08:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151766</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7214</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/08/2023 21:20:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7214</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/08/2023 21:20:55</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/08/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1J4GA39198L586808</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2008</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>JEEP</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>WRG</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>MAR</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>SC</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>PYZ526</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>