<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-003101</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/25/2023 12:10:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/25/2023 12:10:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/25/2023 11:38:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/25/2023 11:38:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 12:10:40</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/30/2023 10:51:43</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>W/B MD RTE 140 @ Public Storage</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>2835</AddressId>
      <City>MDC249</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 12:10:41</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/25/2023 19:06:56</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>2835</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>1200</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Baltimore</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>BLVD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westminster</City>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/25/2023 12:10:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/25/2023 12:10:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/25/2023 23:18:59</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 12:10:40</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:22:50</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>This incident was recorded on BWC, as well as G-4s in car camera with functioning audio and video.  Attatchments: Six (6) DUI related attachments.  Driver:   Geoffrey Forrest Stewart (W/M 09/16/1980)   1913 Lennox Drive, Unit 189, Sykesvile Maryland, 21784.   771-215-6520  Narrative: On January 25, 2023, at approximately 1531 hours, a concerned citizen, Steve Zile (410-596-8994) called the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack to report an erraticdriver. The caller advised a blackAudi Passenger car bearing Maryland registration T1217794 was failing to maintain a single lane, and at times was driving on the shoulder of the roadway. The caller advisedthe audi was traveling westbound from the intersection of Maryland route 140 and Sandymount road. The caller advised after being stopped at a red light for Maryland Route 140 and Sandymount road, the driver of the Audi opened their door, and continued driving down Maryland route 140 with their door open. The caller advised they were in a white van, and were instructed to turn on their hazard lights, so they could be easily identifiedas they passed.  I responded to the area, and was sitting stationaryon Maryland route 140 west of Reese road. I observed the caller in the white van pass my location. I also observed the black Audi bearing the same Maryland registration as the caller had provided. I observed the Audi following the white van in front of it by less than one (1) car length. I positioned myself behindthe Audi, activated my emergency equipment, and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle.  I approached the drivers side of the vehicle, and contacted the driver,and sole occupant of the vehicle who I identified by his Maryland identification card as, Geoffrey Forrest Stewart (W/M 09/16/1986) A METERS/NCIC query confirmed Stewart did not currently possess a valid license to drive in Maryand. While speaking with Stewart I observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy, and his speech to be slurred. I asked Stewart how much he had to drink to which he replied, just a little bit I asked Stewart to elaborate on how much just a little bit was. Stewart advised he had consumed one (1) beer the previous evening at his girlfriends house at approximately 2100 hours.I asked Stewart to submit to the standardized field sobriety tests to which he subsequently agreed.  As Stewart let his foot off the brake, and attemptedto exit the vehicle. The vehicle drifted forward, still in drive. Stewart had to be advised to put the vehicle in park. The SFSTs were completed on a level wet surface, with a light downpour of rain, and winds occurring during the test. Stewart advised he took several medications for depression and anxiety but could not advise the names of the medications. Stewart advised he had been in a car crash recently, had to re-learn to walk, and had trouble with his balance due to back, and leg pain. As I spoke with Stewart outside the vehicle, I detected the faint odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6 OF 6 CLUES OBSERVED)   During the test, there were no front facing emergency equipment lights activated that could cause optokinetic Nystagmus. I used a black pen as a stimulus. Stewart verbally stated he understood the directions for the test. I checked both eyes and observed he had equal tracking and pupil size in both eyes.    1. Lack of smooth pursuit-Present in both eyes.   2. distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation-Present in both eyes.   3. Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees-Present in both eyes.  WALK AND TURN (5 OF 8 CLUES OBSERVED)   Prior to the test being performed, I properly demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Stewart was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Stewart was told to place his hands down at his side and remain in that position until instructed to begin. Stewart was instructed to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe every step. Stewart was told to keep his hands flat at his side, keeping his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Stewart was demonstrated and explained to keep his lead foot planted on the line, take a series of small steps with his rear foot completely around. Stewart was, again, explained and demonstrated how the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed, identically to the first series. Stewart was instructed once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was complete, keep his hands down by his side, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. Stewart verbally stated he understood the directions for completing the test.  Instruction phase:   Stewart started too soon before being advised. Stewart had to be reminded not to start the test until advised Three (3) times.   Stewart stepped off-line, in an attempt to maintain his balance, and had to be reminded to re assume the instructional position prior to performing the test.  First Set of Nine Steps:   Stewart missed heel to toe contact by more than one half inch on step 2, 3, 8   Stewart stepped off line on step 7.   Stewart took ten (10) total steps.  Second Set of Nine Steps:   Stewart missed heel to toe contact by more than one half inch on steps 2,3,4,6    ONE LEGS STAND (2 OF 4 CLUES OBSERVED)  Prior to Stewrt performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Stewart was instructed to keep his heels together and his hands down by his sides while instructions were given. Stewart was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice approximately six (6) inches off the ground. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, look at his raised foot and count out loud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Stewart was asked if he understood the test, which he verbally stated he did. Stewart elected to raise his left foot.    Seconds 1-10    Stewart swayed from side to side while balancing    Stewart placed his foot down on second 6.   Seconds 11-20   Stewart swayed from side to side while balancing.   Stewart placed his foot down on second 18    Seconds 21-30   Stewart swayed from side to side while balancing.   Stewart placed his foot down on second 30.  Lack of convergence:   I used a black pen as a stimulus, I explained to Stewart to follow the stimulus with his eyes and his eyes only. Stewart verbally stated he understood the intructions. I observed Stewarts eyes did not fail to converge.  Modified Romberg:   Stewart was advised to stand with his heels together, and arms straight down at his sides. Stewart was advised to estimate the passage of thirty seconds, and to lean his head back, close his eyes. Stewart was advised whenever he felt thirty seconds had passed, to open his eyes, and say done Stewart verbally advised he understood the instructions for the test. Stewart estimated the passage of thirty seconds in thirty seconds.  Based on my observations of Stewart both behavior and SFSTs I believed he could not operate a vehicle safely. Stewart was placed under arrest at approximately 1551 hours. Prior to placing Stewart into my patrol vehicle, I conducted a search of his person which revealed no contraband.Once seated directly beside me in my patrol vehicle, with all the windows up, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Stewarts breath, and person. Stewart was transported to the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack.  Stewart was seated and secured to a chair by his left wrist. Stewart was read and given a copy to read the Maryland DR-15 Advice of Rights. While reading the DR-15 I was seated approximately 4-5 feet directly in front of Stewart.  At approximately 1614 hours, Stewart refused to submit to the Intoximeter test. Stewart was issued the appropriate traffic citations, and given all appropriate copies of his paperwork, which he declined to sign.  Stewart was transported to the Carroll County Detention Center, and left in the custody of detention center staff.  All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.   </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 19:10:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6783</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/25/2023 21:00:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Karas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5562</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Pettis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6498</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harper</LastName>
            <FirstName>Derek</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6783</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492484</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/25/2023 15:51:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 18:27:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6783</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/25/2023 19:07:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492484</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/25/2023 15:51:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 18:27:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6783</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/25/2023 19:08:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>42</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 18:27:12</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>367202</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Stewart</LastName>
               <FirstName>Geoffrey</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Forrest</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/16/1980 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.94503546E8</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>01/25/2023 18:19:36</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S363</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G160</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Stewart</LastName>
               <FirstName>Geoffrey</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Forrest</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/16/1980 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.94503546E8</SSN>
               <SLastName>S363</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>G160</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/25/2023 18:19:36</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>771</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>215</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6520</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/25/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 19:08:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:41</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 19:08:58</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:41</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6783</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/25/2023 19:06:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6783</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/25/2023 19:06:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>