<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-008151</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/04/2023 23:50:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/04/2023 23:50:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/04/2023 23:35:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/04/2023 23:35:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect was arrested for DUI/DWI. Due to the level of intoxication, the suspect was transported to Garrett Regional Medical Center.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/04/2023 23:50:19</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2173</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/22/2023 08:40:36</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>GARRETT HWY/ FAIRGATE RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>686330</AddressId>
      <City>MDC302</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/04/2023 23:50:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 03:43:27</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>686330</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Garrett</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>McHenry</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21541</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-79.349917</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.553165</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/04/2023 23:50:16</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/04/2023 23:50:16</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/18/2023 18:41:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/04/2023 23:50:19</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*In-Car Camera, W-13 not installed. *Body-Worn Camera operable.  Defendant: James Earl Scherich  Date of Birth: 03/27/1984  Date of Arrest: 03/04/2023  Time of Arrest: 2349 hours  License#: F073504 / West Virginia Drivers License  DUI#: 23-014    On 03/04/2023 at approximately 2335 hours, I was on duty in uniform operating MSP marked unit W-13. I was traveling southbound on Garrett Highway, south of Fair Gate Road, McHenry, Garrett County, MD 21541. I observed a vehicle parked on the shoulder of the northbound lane of Garrett Highway, south ofFair Gate Road, McHenry, Garrett County, MD 21541. The vehicle had its headlights activated, the front passenger side door was open, and the vehicle appeared to be tilted and extremely close to going down into a ditch. I turned onto the northbound lane of Garrett Highway, activated my emergency equipment, and pulled over onto the shoulder, behind the vehicle. The vehicle was a green Toyota Tundra bearing West Virginia registration, FC12010.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)    No vehicle in motion.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)    Upon making contact with the driver, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I observed the driver of the vehicle was vomiting on himself and into a tissue box. I observed his eyes were bloodshot and glassy and his body movements to be slow and lethargic. I asked the driver what was going on. The driver stated, Sorry. I dont feel good. I asked the driver where he was coming from. The driver did not respond. I asked the driver if he or the passenger needed medical attention. The driver stated, No. Im coming from Deep Creek. I asked the driver how much he had to drink. The driver stated, Thats why I pulled over. I asked the driver for his drivers license. The passenger handed me her drivers license. I identified the passenger as, Margo Marie Scherich (W/F DOB:03/05/1984) by her West Virginias Drivers license. I asked the driver to be honest with me and tell me how much he had to drink. The driver stated, A couple of drinks. I asked the driver where he was drinking. Margo stated, Honi Honi. I again asked the driver for his drivers license. The driver stated, Thats hers. I asked the driver if he had his drivers license. The driver stated, Yes. I identified the driver as, James Earl Scherich (W/M DOB: 03/27/1984) by his West Virginia Drivers license. As I spoke with James, I observed his speech was thick and slurred. As I spoke with James I observed the vehicles engine was running and the radio was playing. I asked Jamesto exit the vehicle. I observed James place his right hand on the steering wheel of the vehicle and his left hand on the driver side B pillar of the vehicle to balance himself as he exited the vehicle. I asked Jamesto attemptfield sobriety tests which he agreed. While speaking with Jamesaway from the vehicle, I continued to smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. James asked if he could remove his flannel shirt because he had vomit on it. I agreed and he removed the shirt. James walked back to the driver side door of the vehicle to place the flannel shirt on the drivers seat. As James walked back to the vehicle I observed him place his left hand on the hood of the vehicle to steady himself. After James set the flannel shirt down on the drivers seat I observed him walk back to the front of the vehicle. I observed James place his right hand on the hood of the vehicle to steady himself.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE3)    The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder in front of James vehicle. The surface was dry, relatively level, and free of any debris. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlights,my patrol vehicles headlights, James vehicles headlights, and my flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Jamesappeared to be in good physical condition.  I asked Jamesthe following questions:  Glasses or Contacts - No.  Medical Conditions - No.  Injuries - No.  Medications - No.    The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my finger was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from James eyes slightly above eye level. Jameswas instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Jameswas positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Jamesif he was able to see the tip of the stimulus, and if he understood the test. Jamesreplied Yes to both questions.    Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6 clues observed)    Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes.  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation - Present in both eyes.  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes.   Note* I did not observe Vertical Gaze Nystagmus.  Walk And Turn (6/8 clues observed)    Prior to Jamesperforming the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Jameswas instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Jameswas instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in the position until told to begin. Jameswas advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Jameswas to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step out aloud. On the ninth step, Jameswas explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Jameswas again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series of nine (9) steps. Jameswas instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. Jamesstated he understood the instructions and was able to complete the test.  Instructional Stage:     Jamesbegan the test before instructionswere given on one occasion.   Walking Stage (1stNine)    Missed heel to toe by more than one half inch. (Steps 6-9).  Stepped offline by more than one half inch. (Steps 2 and 5).  Raised arms away from torso by more than 6 inches. (Steps 1-9).  Improper amount of steps. (15 steps).   Walking Stage (2ndNine)    Missed heel to toe by more than one half inch. (Steps 3-9).  Stepped offline by more than one half inch. (Steps 1-2).  Raised arms away from torso by more than 6 inches. (Steps 1-9).  Improper amount of steps. (14steps).   Turn: Unsatisfactory. (James pivoted on both balls of his feet and staggered backwards approximately 5 steps.  One Leg Stand (3/4 Clues observed)    Prior to Jamesperforming the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Jameswas instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Jamesstated he understood the instructions and was able to complete the test.  Seconds 1-10:    Raised arms away from torso by more than 6 inches. (Seconds 1-10).  Swayed (Seconds 1 and 4).  Put foot down. (Seconds 1,4,6, and 9).   Seconds 11-20:    Raised arms away from torso by more than 6 inches. (Seconds 11-20).  Swayed (Seconds 11-13 and 18).  Put foot down (Seconds 13,16, and 18).     Seconds 21-30:    Raised arms away from torso by more than 6 inches. (Seconds 21-30).  Swayed (Seconds 23,25, and 28).  Put foot down. (Seconds 23 and 25).   ARREST    Based on the following, I believed Jameswas driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath.  *Vomiting.  *Myobserved signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests.  *Glassy and bloodshot eyes, thick and slurred speech.  *Slow and lethargic body movements.  *Jamess admission to consuming alcoholic beverages.  *Margos admission to going to the Honi Honi Bar.    Jameswas offered a preliminary breath test which she agreed to take and resulted with a (BrAC) of .19. Jameswas arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 2349 hoursand was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. James began to vomit in my patrol vehicle. I transported James to the Deep Creek Volunteer Fire Department located at, 1906 Deep Creek Drive, McHenry, Garrett County, MD 21541, to have EMS render medical attention. EMS advised James was ok and appeared to just be heavily intoxicated. James refused further medical treatment. James was transported to the Maryland State Police McHenry Barrack for processing.Jamess mouth was checked at approximately 0020 hours. While at the barrack, James continued to vomit. Sgt Bond # 0200 advised he was going to have EMS respond to the barrack and transport James to the hospital. Garrett County Rescue Squad Ambulance # 952 responded to McHenry Barrack at approximately 0038 hours and transported James to Garrett Regional Medical Center located at 251 North Fourth Street, Oakland, Garrett County, Maryland, 21550. James was read the DR-15 Advice of Rights at approximately 0105 hours, at the conclusion of reading the DR-15, Jamesagreed to submit to a blood kit. RN William Beaver performed the blood kit at approximately 0125 hours.    James was given all copies of pertinent paperwork, charging him with (TA 21-902 (a1i) Driving under the influence of alcohol, (TA 21-902 (b1i) Driving while impaired, (TA 21-902 (c1i) Driving so farimpaired by alcohol, can not drive safely,(TA 21-901.1 (a) Reckless Driving, and (TA 21-901.1 (b) Negligent Driving.    Case closed by arrest.    All events occurred in GarrettCounty, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/12/2023 08:36:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/12/2023 10:15:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Ervin</LastName>
            <FirstName>Darian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6274</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Hook</LastName>
            <FirstName>Robert</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6479</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bond</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0200</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Poland</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kurt</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7213</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497550</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/04/2023 23:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 03:49:33</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 03:49:33</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497550</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/04/2023 23:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 03:49:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 03:49:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497550</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/04/2023 23:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 03:49:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 03:49:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497550</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/04/2023 23:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 03:49:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 03:49:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>497550</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/04/2023 23:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 03:49:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 03:49:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 03:55:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:54</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370770</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Scherich</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Earl</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/27/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 03:55:03</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Scherich</LastName>
               <FirstName>James</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Earl</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/27/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J520</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 03:55:03</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3800</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Lindberg</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Weirton</City>
               <StateCode>WV</StateCode>
               <Zip5>26062</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-80.60418</Longitude>
               <Latitude>40.398318</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>304</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>670</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9370</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 03:55:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:52</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 03:55:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:52</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 03:55:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:52</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 03:55:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:52</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 04:09:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:40</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>370771</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Scherich</LastName>
               <FirstName>Margo</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/05/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 04:09:14</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>S620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M620</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Scherich</LastName>
               <FirstName>Margo</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Marie</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/05/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>S620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M620</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 04:09:14</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>3800</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Lindberg</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>WAY</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Weirton</City>
               <StateCode>WV</StateCode>
               <Zip5>26062</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-80.60418</Longitude>
               <Latitude>40.398318</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>NOK</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 04:09:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>PA</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 04:09:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:46</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 03:49:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 03:49:34</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>150531</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/05/2023 04:12:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/05/2023 04:12:31</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/05/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5TFLA5DB4NX006689</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>TOYT</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>TUN</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>PK</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>DGR</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>DGR</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>WV</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>FC12010</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/18/2023 15:00:52</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/18/2023 15:00:52</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/18/2023 18:41:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 15:00:52</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:05:41</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>  On 07/27/2023 I received a copy of James blood lab results from the Maryland State Police Forensic Sciences Division. The results revealed James had a (BrAC) of .18 at the time of the incident. I attached a copy of the lab results with this report.    On 08/18/2023 at approximately 1430 hours, I made contact with James, via phone, and advised him on his blood lab results. I informed James he was entitled to a copy of the results. James advised due to the fact he lives out of state, he was not interested in receiving his copy at this time.    Case closed.    All events occurred in Garrett County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/18/2023 15:01:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/18/2023 16:30:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bond</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brett</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0200</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Poland</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kurt</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7213</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>