<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000039</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/01/2023 02:40:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/01/2023 02:40:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/01/2023 02:21:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/01/2023 02:21:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI, DWI traffic Stop</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/01/2023 02:40:57</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4792</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/26/2023 12:00:01</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OHIO AVE/ S SALISBURY BLVD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>678496</AddressId>
      <City>MDC226</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/01/2023 02:40:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/12/2023 10:50:34</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>678496</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ohio</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Salisbury</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>S</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>BLVD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.599876</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.357698</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>200-212 OHIO AVE / 660-698 S SALISBURY BLVD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/01/2023 02:40:53</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/01/2023 02:40:53</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>54</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/20/2023 16:49:06</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/01/2023 02:40:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/20/2023 16:49:06</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Case # 23-MSP-000039 This incident was recorded. Body warn camera operational. Link: https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=394f691ef2624fb7b31768a4d2a4fafepartner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1 SCENE PROCESSING:  - A visual inspection of the scene was conducted. No evidence additional evidence was located. NEIGHBORHOOD CHECK:  - Due to the location of the crime, a neighborhood check was not conducted. NARRATIVE: DUI#: 23-54-001 (Salisbury Barrack) Michel, Willy (DOB:01/02/1993) Date/time of arrest: 01/01/2023 @ 0237hrs  CERTIFICATION AND TRAINING *Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Test through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On January 1, 2023, at approximately 0221 hours, I, Tpr.Tenney (#7378) of the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack, was on patrol on Maryland Ave in the area of Waverly St. At that time I observed a dark blue Jeep stopped in the travel portion of the road way with its tail lights not activated. The Jeep was displaying Delaware Registration plate PC376028. I positioned my patrol car, MSP marked unit E-47 behind the Jeep. The Jeep was stopped for approximately 5 seconds before traveling west on Maryland Ave without its taillights activated. The Jeep then stopped at the intersection of Maryland Ave and Waverly Dr. The driver of the Jeep initiated his right turn signal then left before making his left turn onto south bound Waverly Dr. At that time, I activated my emergency equipment. The Jeep continued to travel approximately 1000 feet at the same rate of speed before make a left onto Ohio Ave before coming to a stop in a parking lot.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)   I exited my vehicle wearing my full Maryland State Police issued Class-B uniform, complete with brass breast badge. I approached the Jeep and I Identified myself, stating my name, rank, badge number, and informed him that he was being audially and visibly recorded. He acknowledged my presence. I then stated the reason for the traffic stop. As I notified the driver of the violation he stated ya, im sorry. While speaking with the driver of the Jeep, I observed his eyes to be bloodshot and glassy. I then asked the driver for his drivers license and registration card. The driver immediately reached for his wallet upon request to retrieve his driver licenses. The driver provided me with his Florida drivers license, which I identified him as Willy Michel (DOB:01/02/1993). The photo on the license matched the drivers appearance. Next, I asked the driver if he consumed any alcoholic beverages prior to driving the vehicle. Michel stated No. Michel then grabbed a soda bottle from his center console and stated that it was an energy drink.   I then contacted Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack and notified the barrack that a Fruitland City Officer was on scene with me and I would have the driver out on Field Sobriety. I then asked Michel to turn off the car and to step out of the vehicle. I then asked him to proceed to the front of his vehicle for further investigation.  Once at the front of his vehicle, I informed Michel that I detected an odor of alcohol and asked if he was willing to perform field sobriety testing. Michel stated yes.   Michel was instructed to stand in front of his vehicle facing towards me and to keep his head still while following the tip of my pen with his eyes.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  1. Lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.  2. Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  3. Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes. Michel took a drink of the soda that he removed from his vehicle. I then instructed him to set the bottle on the ground. At the time, Michel set the bottle on the ground. I then instructed Michel to put his feet together and keep his arms down at his side. Michel immediately positioned himself as instructed. Vertical Gaze Nystagmus was observed.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  Do you have any medical conditions? Michel answered No.  Do you have any pre-existing injuries? Michel stated No.  Do you take any medications? Michel answered yes. When asked what medications he was taking Michel stated at home. I then asked Michel if he understood English. He said no. I then stated, you understand some things and he stated ya. Michel was speaking broken English and following my instructions at this time.  WALK AND TURN (8/8 clues observed)   Prior to Michel performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Michel was instructed to place his left foot on an imaginary straight line and place his right foot on the same line in front of his left foot with the heel of his right foot touching the toes of his left foot. Michel was to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in this position until he was told to begin. Michel was instructed to take nine (9) steps on the straight-line touching heel to toe on each step. Michel was told to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step out loud. After completing his ninth step Michel was demonstrated and explained to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around his lead foot with his rear foot to turn completely around. Michel was then explained and demonstrated to take nine more heel to toe steps on the same line in the opposite direction of the first nine steps. The second nine steps were to be performed identical to the first nine steps. Michel was instructed that once he began the test he was not to stop walking until the test was complete. Michel was again instructed to keep his hands down at his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. After explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked Michel if he completely understood the instructions, and he stated Yes. The results were as follows:  Instruction stage:   Cannot keep balance/ breaks feet apart. Michel broke his feet from the starting position on one occasion.  Beginning test prior to instruction twice.  Michel was asked to remove his hands from his pockets during the instructional phase. Michel complied with the instructions and removed his hands from his pockets.    Walking Stage (first nine): 1. Missed heel to toe on 2. 2. Steps of line on 3. 3. Incorrect number of steps. Michel was instructed to take nine heel to toe steps, and he took 8. Michel was observed placing his hand inside his pockets several times during the test. Michel was instructed to remove his hands from his pockets, which he complied with briefly before reinserting his hands back into his pockets during the test.  The turn:  Completed unsatisfactory. Michel did keep his lead foot planted while completing the turn and used his momentum to swing his body around without taking any steps with his rear foot.  Walking Stage (second nine): 1. Missed heel to toe on step 3 2. Steps of line on step 1 3. Stops while walking on step 5. 4. Uses arms for balance 2,4,5,7 and 8 Michel was observed placing his hand inside his pockets several times during the test. Michel was instructed to remove his hands from his pockets, which he complied with briefly before reinserting his hands back into his pockets during the test.  ONE LEG STAND (0/4 clues observed) No clues were observed during testing.  PRELIMINARILY BREATH TEST Preliminary breath test results: .10 ARREST    Based on the following, I had reason to believe thatMichelwas driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:    * Observations while the driver was operating the vehicle    * Observation during personal contact while speaking with the driver I advisedMichel that he was under arrest for driving under the influence of Alcohol. Michel was transported to the Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack for processing. During transport to the barrack Michel began to tell me about his three kids and wife that he has at home in Seaford, Delaware. Michel told me that he and his family had just moved up here from Florida a few weeks ago that he does not have any friends up here. A search incident toarrest was conducted and revealed no contraband was on his person, andMichel was asked to spit his gum out of his mouth. Nothing was introduced to his mouth while he was in my custody. Once at the Barrack, Michel knowledge of the English language decreased significantly. During the secondary search at the barrack my supervisor asked Michel if he understood English. Michel stated ya a little bit. Michel was then asked if he understands English or Spanish better. Michel was asked if he would like the DR-15 read in English or Spanish. Michel stated Spanish. Michel was read the DR-15 at0319 hours and his knowledge of both English and Spanish decreased once again. I attempted to explain the DR-15 in different verbiage to further explain. Michel appeared to have significant decrease in the understanding of the English language over the course of the process. After the DR-15 was attempted to be communicated in several ways, Michel repeatedly replied I dont understand. Michel was marked down as refusal to take the intoximeter test. Michel was then asked to call and a family member or friend to come pick him up and take him home. Michel replied in English that his wife is home with his kids, and he does not have any friends. I then informed Michel that he was going to be transported to Wicomico County Department of Corrections. Before being transported to Wicomico County Department of Corrections. Michel was placed into a holding cell at Maryland State Police Salisbury Barrack. At which point, Michel in the English language asked several times to call his wife.  Michel was issued all necessary paperwork before being transported to Wicomico County Department of Corrections and released into their custody. All events occurred in Wicomico County, Maryland. Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/13/2023 14:34:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7378</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/19/2023 23:24:12</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Mareck</LastName>
            <FirstName>Keven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3258</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>54</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tenney</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7378</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>489417</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/01/2023 02:21:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/12/2023 07:50:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7378</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/12/2023 07:50:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>29</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/12/2023 07:52:45</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:16</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>365006</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Michel</LastName>
               <FirstName>Willy</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/02/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/02/2023 04:39:13</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Michel</LastName>
               <FirstName>Willy</FirstName>
               <DOB>01/02/1993 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M240</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>W400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/02/2023 04:39:13</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>301</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>N</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Hall</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>ST</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Seaford</City>
               <StateCode>DE</StateCode>
               <Zip5>19973</Zip5>
               <Zip4>2407</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.619831</Longitude>
               <Latitude>38.641134</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/12/2023 07:52:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:37</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/12/2023 07:52:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:37</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7378</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/12/2023 07:50:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7378</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/12/2023 07:50:39</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>