<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000867</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3000</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/08/2023 00:16:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/08/2023 00:16:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/07/2023 23:59:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/07/2023 23:59:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic Stop, DUI, DUI# 23-008</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 00:16:20</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5939</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/06/2023 12:21:16</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>EMMORTON RD/ W RIDING DR</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>592236</AddressId>
      <City>MDC107</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 00:16:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 02:29:39</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>592236</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Emmorton</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Bel Air</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetDirCode>W</CrossStreetDirCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>DR</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.32933</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.51372</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1501-1553 EMMORTON RD / 1-4 W RIDING DR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>1405-1407 EMMORTON RD / 1-4 W RIDING DR</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/08/2023 00:16:19</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/08/2023 00:16:19</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>53</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/01/2023 00:44:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/08/2023 00:16:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/01/2023 00:44:28</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DWI # 23-008  MD SDX: G-430-847-497-883  All events were captured on MSPAudio and Video:23-MSP-000867 6CG0G2T DUI  PHASE ONE: VEHICLE IN MOTION  On January 7, 2023 at approximately 2359 hours, I, Senior Trooper Whittenberg (#6095) of the Maryland State Police - Bel Air Barrack was on routine patrol in the area of southbound Route 924 and Linwood Avenue. While performing my duties I observed a black Jeep Cherokee traveling outbound on Route 924 in front of me. I observed the suspect vehicle travel over the double yellow center line a distance of 1/2 car width before returning to the proper lane of travel. I continued to follow the suspect vehicle and observed it travel over the right shoulder line a distance of 2 tire widths before returning to the proper lane of travel. I continued to follow the suspect vehicle and observed it to travel over the right shoulder line again prior to Forest Drive a distance of 2 tire widths before returning to the proper lane of travel. I initiated my emergency equipment and got behind the suspect vehicle and the vehicle slowed and came to a stop in the right turn lane of southbound Route 924 prior to West Riding Drive.  PHASE TWO: PERSONAL CONTACT  I made a drivers side approach to the vehicle to make contact with the driver. Upon contact with the driver I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from inside the vehicle. I told the driver why I stopped her and she stated she was trying to find her way home. She stated that she was trying to get to Baltimore. I asked the driver where she was coming from and she stated she was coming from Looneys Pub. I then asked the driver for her drivers license and registration card. I asked the driver if she still lived at the address listed on her drivers license and she stated that she did not and she advised her new address. The driver was identified through her Maryland drivers license to be Victoira Lee Gold (W/F 11/18/1983). While speaking with Gold, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from her breath and person as well as bloodshot, glassy, watery eyes and slurred speech. I asked Gold if she had anything to drink and she advised she had around 1900 hours.  PHASE THREE: PRE ARREST SCREENING  I notified the Maryland State Police - Bel Air Barrack via radio that I would be conducting Standard Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) on Gold. During the tests, Gold was wearing a skirt, shirt, and Shaw. The tests were conducted in the right turn line of southbound Route 924 prior to West Riding Drive. The testing site was well lit due to the headlights from my patrol vehicle and overhead lighting. The testing site was flat, dry, and free of debris and obstructions. There was no precipitation in the air and the air temperature was 37 degrees. There was minimal traffic due to the time and location of the test. I also observed that the Gold had an orange paper bracelet on her left wrist indicating that she had come from Looneys Pub.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6 of 6 clues)  Gold was asked if she had any medical conditions or physical disabilities that would affect any of the tests for which Gold advised she had none.HGN was performed using a silver ball point pen as a stimulus.The stimulus was passedhorizontally across Goldsface at adistance of 12-15 inches and slightly above eye level. The test was explained indetail prior to Gold attempting it. Gold verbally confirmed that she understood the instructions. Gold was faced away from the roadwayas not to distract her. Emergency lights were turned off in Golds direction as to not distract her. Gold was first checked for resting nystagmus, equal pupil size, and equal tracking. Gold did not display resting nystagmus, and had equal pupil size and equal tracking in both left and right eyes. Gold displayed lack of smooth pursuit, distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees. Gold also displayed vertical nystagmus. Gold displayed 6 of 6 clues.  WALK AND TURN TEST (4 of 8 clues)  The test was explained and demonstrated in detail prior to Gold attempting it. Gold verbally confirmed she understood the instructions. Gold elected to take her shoes off prior to exiting the vehicle and did not have shoes on during the test. During the test, Gold was to use the white line of the turn lane of southbound Route 924 prior to West Riding Drive as the line to walk along. During the instructional phase, Gold lost balance by moving her left leg to the right to maintain balance. During the walking phase, Gold missed heel to toe on all steps and stepped off line on steps 4, 7, and 8 on her first series of 9 steps. Gold did not have her arms at her sides but rather tucked in front of her. Gold missed heel to toe on all steps and stepped off line on steps 2 and 3 on her second series of 9 steps. Gold did not have her arms down at her sides but rather tucked in front of her. Gold displayed 4 of 8 clues.  ONE LEG STAND TEST (3 of 4 clues)  The test was explained and demonstrated in detail prior to Gold attempting it. Gold verbally confirmed that she understood the instructions. Gold elected to raise her left leg during the test. During the test, Gold swayed the entire length of the test in a back and forth motion of 2 inches and a side to side motion of 5 inches. Gold raised her arms throughout the test to try and maintain balance parallel with the ground. Gold fell to the right after counting to 8. Gold put her foot down at 9-30 seconds. Gold displayed 3 of 4 clues.  Gold was offered and consented to a PBT indicating a BAC of .144.  Due to my knowledge, training, and experience as a Maryland State Trooper,6 time MADD DUI Award recipient,6 time Harford County Council DUI award recipient, 2013/2015/2016 Maryland State Police Commanders Award (DUI) recipient, graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute, 4 time Impaired Driving Coalition DUI Award recipient, Advanced Roadside Intoxicated Driver Enforcement (ARIDE) graduate, a certified Intoximeter Operator, a SFST Instructor, a certified Drug Recognition Expert, as well as prior arrests and clues gathered thus far, Gold was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. Gold was then transported to the Maryland State Police - Bel Air Barrack where she was read her DR-15 Advise of Rights. Gold consented to an intoximeter test. The intoximeter test was conducted by Corporal Atkinson (#0074) of the Maryland State Police - Bel Air Barrack and Golds breath specimen was found to contain .14 grams of alcohol per 201 liters of breath.  Gold was issued all appropriate paperwork and released to a sober person, her friend.  All events occurred in Harford County, Maryland.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6095</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 02:36:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6095</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 03:34:57</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Neal</LastName>
            <FirstName>Emily</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7283</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Atkinson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5623</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>53</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3000</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Whittenberg</LastName>
            <FirstName>Stephen</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6095</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490244</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/08/2023 00:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6095</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 02:30:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6095</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 02:30:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490244</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/08/2023 00:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6095</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 02:31:10</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6095</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 02:31:10</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490244</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/08/2023 00:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6095</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 02:31:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6095</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 02:31:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490244</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/08/2023 00:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6095</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 02:32:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6095</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 02:32:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490244</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/08/2023 00:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6095</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 02:32:53</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6095</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 02:32:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490244</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/08/2023 00:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6095</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 02:33:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6095</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 02:33:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490244</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15542</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/08/2023 00:16:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15542</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6095</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 02:33:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6095</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 02:33:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>39</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6095</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 02:34:38</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:27</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>367673</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Gold</LastName>
               <FirstName>Victoria</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/18/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.6707793E7</SSN>
               <DateOfInfo>01/31/2023 02:22:24</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>G430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>V236</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Gold</LastName>
               <FirstName>Victoria</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Lee</MiddleName>
               <DOB>11/18/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SSN>5.6707793E7</SSN>
               <SLastName>G430</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>V236</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/31/2023 02:22:24</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2702</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Moorgate</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Dundalk</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21222</Zip5>
               <Zip4>4616</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.506381</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.263958</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>240</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>7072</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>01/31/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6095</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 02:34:38</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:41</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6095</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/31/2023 02:30:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6095</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/31/2023 02:30:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>