<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-004241</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>02/03/2023 01:21:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>02/03/2023 01:21:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>02/03/2023 00:45:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>02/03/2023 00:45:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI, DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>02/03/2023 01:21:58</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5372</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>02/15/2023 12:08:26</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>W/B Rte. 100 @ Rte. 108</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>682814</AddressId>
      <City>MDC261</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/03/2023 01:21:59</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 04:07:11</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>682814</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm Md-100 Wb</StreetName>
         <City>Ellicott City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.80586</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.22375</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>WB 100 AT 104</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>02/03/2023 01:21:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>02/03/2023 01:21:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>50</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/12/2023 12:40:27</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>02/03/2023 01:21:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/14/2023 18:53:20</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP Unmarked A-17 is equipped with a mobile recording device. Traffic top was recorded.  Defendant:Rodolfo Nelson Vargas Ramos Date of Birth:01/15/1983 Date of Arrest:02/03/2023 Time of Arrest: 0118 hours DUI #:23-014   CERTIFICATIONS  TRAINING    Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  Trained and certified in vehicle pace and operation of LIDAR and RADAR through the Baltimore County Police as met by Maryland State Police certification standards.   margin-left:8px"&gt;Trained and certified in administering the Preliminary Breath Test (PBT).    VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On 02/03/2023 at approximately 0045 hours, I was on routine patrol on west-bound Maryland Route 100 in the area of Snowden River Parkway, when I observed a gray colored Honda Civic, traveling at a low rate of speed in lane #2, swerving partially into lane #1 and #3. The vehicle was traveling 40-43mph in a posted 55mph zone, impeding the flow of other vehicles that slowed behind the car, prior to Snowden.The vehicle in question, a gray Honda Civic, bearing MD registration, 4FF7044, swerved partially to lane #1 and lane #3 on numerous occasions. I activated my emergency equipment, and the vehicle began to swerve to lane #1, almost striking another vehicle, before coming to the right shoulder to pull over. As the driver pulled to the right shoulder, he popped the trunk to his vehicle.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I made contact with the driver of the Civic, who was identified as Rodolfo Nelson Vargas Ramos Jr., DOB 1/15/1983, as confirmed by his Maryland drivers license. I asked Vargas Ramos where he was going, and he stated he was going home. Vargas Ramos stated he had just got off from Longhorn Steakhouse at 11:30 P.M. While speaking with Vargas Ramos, while he was seated in his vehicle, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverageemanating from the vehicle. I asked Vargas Ramos how much alcohol he consumed earlier and he stated he had 1 drink. As the conversation continued, Vargas Ramos stated he had 2 drinks. I asked Vargas Ramos if he would like to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFST) to determine if he was able to drive safely. Vargas Ramos then complied with my request and exited his vehicle to perform SFST, but indicated he did not fully comprehend English and would prefer a Spanish speaking officer. As Vargas Ramos stepped out of his vehicle, his pants fell to his ankles, and he stumbled into the roadway, in an attempt to pull his pants back up. I maneuvered to catch Vargas Ramos as I observed two tractor trailers traveling our direction in lane #2 and #3. While speaking with Vargas Ramos in front of his vehicle, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath. During this observation, I observed Vargas Ramos to have glassy, bloodshot eyes. Vargas Ramos had difficulty standing upright, consistently swaying and displayed poor coordination.  Ofc. Paulus #5969 from the Howard County Police Department arrived on scene to provide Spanish interpretation to Vargas Ramos.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The evaluation was performed on the left shoulder in front of Vargas Ramosvehicle. The weather conditions were cold and illuminated by Vargas Ramosheadlights and streetlights. Vargas Ramos was positioned away from other vehicles or flashing lights that could impair his ability to complete the tests offered. Vargas Ramos appeared to be in adequate physical condition and did not display any visible injuries.  I asked Vargas Ramos the following questions:  Medical Conditions- None. Injuries- A minor soccer injury to his knee. Medication- None. Glasses- None.    HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The stimulus that was used was the top of my pen, and was held approximately 13 inches away from Vargas Ramos eyes. I asked Vargas Ramos if he could see the pen, and he stated, Yes. Vargas Ramos was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of my pen with his eyes until told to stop. Vargas Ramos stated he understood. Vargas Ramos pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking, and resting nystagmus was not observed. I asked Vargas Ramos if he understood again all of the instructions I provided him, and he stated, Yes. Vargas Ramos was positioned away from the vehicles to prevent any distractions. Vargas Ramos pupils were glazed over glassy and bloodshot.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit- Present in both eyes.  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation- Present in both eyes.  Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 Degrees- Present in both eyes.  VGN was present in Vargas Ramos eyes.    WALK AND TURN (7/8 clues observed)  Prior to Vargas Ramos performing the test, I properly demonstrated and explained how the test should and would be conducted. Vargas Ramos was instructed to place his right foot in front of his left foot and make heel to toe contact. Vargas Ramos was instructed to put and keep his arms at his side, and I advised him to remain in that position until told to begin. Vargas Ramos was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Vargas Ramos was instructed to keep his hands flat against his side, keeping his eyes focused on his feet, and count each step aloud. On the ninth step, Vargas Ramos was explained and demonstrated to keep the lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Vargas Ramos was again explained the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Vargas Ramos was advised that once he began the test, he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands to his side, look down at his feet, and count each step aloud. I informed Vargas Ramos for demonstration purposes, that I would be taking three (3) steps, but he would be taking nine (9) steps. This information was given before and after I demonstrated the test. After explaining and demonstrating the test, I asked Vargas Ramos if he understood the instructions to which he responded that he understood.    Instructional Stage:     Left the Instructional Stage on 3 occasions.   Started the test earlier than instructed on 2 occasions.     Walking Stage (1st Nine)    Stepped off of the line on steps 1-2, 4-5, 10-12, and 18-19.  Broke heel to toe contact on step 11-19.  Vargas Ramos took 19 steps on his first set of 9 steps.  Stopped after step 11, then continued until step 19.    Walking Stage (2nd Nine)    Broke heel to toe contact on steps 1-9.    Turn: Turn completed as instructed.   ONE LEG STAND (4/4 clues observed)  Prior to Vargas Ramos performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Vargas Ramos was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his side while the instructions were given and during the test. Vargas Ramos was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch the raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Vargas Ramos was asked if he had any questions, and Vargas Ramos stated, No. Vargas Ramos was then asked if understood the instructions, to which he stated, Yes. Vargas Ramos lifted his right leg for the test.  Instructional Stage: Nothing to Report.   Balance and Counting Stage: Seconds 0-10    Placed his foot down on 2 occasions.  Waived arms from rib level to above waist level in order to maintain balance.  Swayed left to right in order to maintain balance.  Hopped to the left in order to maintain balance.     Seconds 11-20    Vargas Ramos placed his foot down on 1 occasions.  Vargas Ramos swayed from left to right in order to maintain balance.  Vargas Ramos lifted arms above waist in order to maintain balance.  Hopped to the right and left in order to maintain balance.   Seconds 21-30    Vargas Ramos placed foot down on 2 occasions.  Vargas Ramos swayed from left to right in order to maintain balance.  Vargas Ramos lifted left arm above waist height in order to maintain balance.    Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) Vargas Ramos decided to submit to a preliminary breath test. Vargas Ramos provided a valid breath sample of .22 BrAC.    ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Vargas Ramos was driving a motor vehicle while being under the influence of alcohol:  Traveling at a slow speed (40/55 zone) impeding traffic. Failure to maintain in a single lane. Vargas Ramossluggish stance, along with glassy, glazed over eyes. Vargas Ramos pants falling down, causing him to stumble into traffic. Strong odor emanating from both Vargas Ramosvehicle and his person. My observed signs of impairment as he performed the field sobriety tests. Vargas Ramosadmission to consuming alcohol earlier in the night.   I arrested Vargas Ramos for driving while under the influence of alcohol at 0118 hours. Vargas Ramos was transported to the Maryland State Police, Waterloo Barrack for processing at 0120 hours. At the barrack, I provided Vargas Ramos with a copy of the DR-015, Advice of Rights, form to follow along as I played the Spanish audio form, in its entirety, from the MVA website. Vargas Ramos followed along as the audio file read the document aloud in its entirety. At the conclusion of the form, Vargas Ramos advised he did want to submit to the Intoximeter Test and signed indicating the same at 0200 hours.  20 MINUTE WAITING PERIOD:  The 20-minute waiting period began at time of arrest 0135.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: Vargas Ramos provided a valid breath sample to the Intoximeter Test of .22 BrAC at 0241 hours.  DISPOSITION: Vargas Ramoss license was confiscated. He was issued Order of Suspension, DR-15A. I issued Vargas Ramos the appropriate citations, and he was picked up by his wife, whom he contacted.   I request this case to be closed by arrest. All events occurred in Howard County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/06/2023 00:23:27</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6683</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/12/2023 12:18:22</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Rubino</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5771</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shiveler</LastName>
            <FirstName>David </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6683</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Clark</LastName>
            <FirstName>Darryl</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0583</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shiveler</LastName>
            <FirstName>David </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6683</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>50</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Shiveler</LastName>
            <FirstName>David </FirstName>
            <InternalID>6683</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493624</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/03/2023 00:45:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/03/2023 03:36:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6683</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 04:05:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493624</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/03/2023 00:45:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/03/2023 03:36:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6683</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 04:04:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493624</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/03/2023 00:45:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/03/2023 03:36:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6683</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 04:05:03</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493624</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/03/2023 00:45:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/03/2023 03:36:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6683</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 04:00:26</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493624</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/03/2023 00:45:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/03/2023 03:36:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6683</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 04:00:44</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493624</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/03/2023 00:45:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 03:58:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6683</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 04:00:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>493624</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>02/03/2023 00:45:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 03:58:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6683</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 03:59:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>40</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 03:58:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:55:56</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>367969</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Vargas ramos</LastName>
               <FirstName>Rodolfo</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nelson</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/15/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>02/03/2023 03:20:40</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>V622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R341</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Vargas ramos</LastName>
               <FirstName>Rodolfo</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Nelson</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/15/1983 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>V622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>R341</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>02/03/2023 03:20:40</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>12104</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Little Patuxent</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>PKWY</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <City>Columbia</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21044</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.898012</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.212425</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 04:09:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:40</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 04:09:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:40</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 04:09:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:40</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 04:09:45</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:40</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6683</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/04/2023 03:56:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6683</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/04/2023 03:56:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>