<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-000756</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2300</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/07/2023 01:53:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/07/2023 01:53:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/07/2023 01:35:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/07/2023 01:35:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The driver was arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 01:53:45</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4410</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 08:58:44</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>679627</AddressId>
      <City>MDC302</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 01:53:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/07/2023 03:57:35</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>679627</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Garrett</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Mc Henry</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21541</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-79.346052</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.531588</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/07/2023 01:53:42</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/07/2023 01:53:42</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>94</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/10/2023 05:58:40</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 01:53:46</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/16/2023 12:23:09</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*In-Car Camera, W-13 notoperable. *Body-Worn Camera operable.  Defendant: Elijah Skye Malfaro  Date of Birth: 09/08/1998  Date of Arrest: 01/07/2023  Time of Arrest: 0152 hours  License#: I662280 / West Virginia Identification Card  DUI#: 23-001  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)    On 01/07/2023 at approximately 0135 hours, I was on duty, in uniform, operating MSP marked unit, W-13. I was stationary on the right shoulder of the northbound lane of Garrett Highway, north of Jeffrey Lane, Oakland, GarrettCounty, MD 21550,observing the flow of traffic. I observed a vehicle approach the intersection of Jeffrey Lane and Garrett Highway. I observed the vehicle turn onto northbound Garrett Highway and travel past my location. Without losing sight of the vehicle I pulled onto the northbound lane of Garrett Highway and began to follow the vehicle. I observed the vehicle cross the double yellow solid center lines by a tires width on one (1) occasion. I observed the vehicle swerving between the solid double yellow lines and solid white line on multiple occasions within its lane of travel.I activated my emergency equipment, and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle pulled onto the right shoulder of Garrett Highway north of Rock Lodge Road, Oakland, Garrett County, MD 21550.The vehicle was a red Chevrolet S-10 bearing Maryland registration 2EV4259.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)    Upon making contact with the driver, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person. I observed his eyes to be glassy and his body movements to be slow and lethargic. I informed the driver for the reason for the stop. I asked the driver to retrieve his drivers license and registration. I identified thedriver as,Elijah Skye Malfaro(W/M DOB: 09/08/1998) by his West Virginia Identification Card. I asked Malfarohow much he had to drink. Malfaro looked away from me and stared straight ahead out of the windshield for approximately four (4) seconds and stated, Not too much. I asked Malfaro where he was coming from. Malfaro stated, Right outside of Grantsville. I asked Malfaro why he was traveling northbound on Garrett Highway, which is the direction towards Grantsville, if he was coming from Grantsville. Malfaro stated, I just dropped my girlfriend off.I asked Malfaroto exit the vehicle.I asked Malfaroto attemptfield sobriety tests which he agreed. While speaking with Malfaroaway from his vehicle, I continued to smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE3)    The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of Garrett Highway in front of Malfaros vehicle. The surface was dry, relatively level, and free of any debris. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlights,my vehicles headlights, and my flashlight. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Malfaroappeared to be in good physical condition.  I asked Malfarothe following questions:  Glasses or Contacts- No.  Medical Conditions- No.  Injuries- No.  Medications- No.    The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of mypen was used as the tests stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Malfaros eyes slightly above eye level. Malfarowas instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Malfarowas positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Malfaroif he was able to see the tip of the stimulus, and if he understood the test. Malfaroreplied Yes to both questions.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6 clues observed)    Lack of Smooth Pursuit- Present in both eyes.  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation- Present in both eyes.  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees- Present in both eyes.   Note* I did not observeVertical Gaze Nystagmus.  Walk And Turn (5/8 clues observed)    Prior to Malfaroperforming the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Malfarowas instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Malfarowas instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in the position until told to begin. Malfarowas advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Malfarowas to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step out aloud. On the ninth step, Malfarowas explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Malfarowas again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series of nine (9) steps. Malfarowas instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. Malfarostated he understood the instructions and was able to complete the test.  Instructional Stage:    Malfarostepped offline by more than one half inch before I completed giving instructions on one(1) occasion.   Walking Stage (1stNine)    Missed heel to toe by more than one half inch. (Steps 2 and 7).  Raised arms away from torso by more than 6 inches. (Steps 1-9).     Walking Stage (2ndNine)    Missed heel to toe by more than one half inch. (Steps 4-8).  Stepped offline by more than one half inch. (Step 9).  Raised arms away from torso by more than 6 inches. (Steps 1-9).     Turn: Unsatisfactory. (Malfarodid not turn and instead chose to complete the second half of the walking stage by walking backwards).  One Leg Stand (1/4 clue observed)    Prior to Malfaroperforming the test, Iexplained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Malfarowas instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. Malfarostated he understood the instructions and was able to complete the test.  Seconds 1-10:   Nothing observed.   Seconds 11-20:   Nothing observed.   Seconds 21-30:    Sways (Second 22).         Note* At the completion of the Standarized Field Sobriety Tests, I again asked Malfaro how much he had to drink. Malfaro stated, Two beers. I asked Malfaro what size beers he had consumed. Malfaro stated, Just whatever Black Bear gave me. Just a 20 ounce.  ARREST    Based on the following, I believed Malfarowas driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath.  *Myobserved signs of impairment as he performed field sobriety tests.  *Glassy and bloodshot eyes, slowed and slurred speech.  *Lethargic body movements.  *Malfaros admission to consuming alcoholic beverages at Black Bear Tavern.  *Malfaro admission to consuming alcoholic beverages. (2 beers).    Malfarowas offered a preliminary breath test which he agreedto take and resulted in a (BrAC) of.17. Malfarowas arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0152 hoursand was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. Malfaros mouth was checked at approximately 0152 hours.Malfaro was read the DR-15 Advice of Rights at approximately 0215 hours, at the conclusion of reading the DR-15, Malfaroagreedto take the intoximeter test. Malfaro was transported to the Maryland State Police McHenry Barrack and Cpl R. Davis # 5223 administered the test at approximately 0226 hours,which resulted in a (BrAC) of .18.    Malfaro was given all copies of pertinent paperwork, charging him with (TA 21-902 (a1i) Driving under the influence of alcohol, (TA 21-902 (a1ii) Driving under the influence of alcohol per se, (TA 21-902 (b1i) Driving while impaired, (TA 21-902 (c1i) Driving so farimpaired by alcohol, can not drive safely, (TA 16-303(g) Revoked out of state license, (TA 21-901.1 (a) Reckless Driving, (TA 21-901.1 (b) Negligent Driving, and (TA 21-201 (a1) Failure to obey a traffic control device. Malfaro was released on his own recognizance to a sober driver.    Case closed by arrest.    All events occurred in GarrettCounty, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 01:16:08</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 04:25:00</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Davis</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ralph</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5223</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>94</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2300</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Poland</LastName>
            <FirstName>Kurt</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7213</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/07/2023 01:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:15</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/07/2023 01:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/07/2023 01:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14585</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/07/2023 01:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14585</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>3100</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/07/2023 01:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>3100</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/07/2023 01:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/07/2023 01:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>490133</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/07/2023 01:35:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:20</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 04:16:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:29</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>210862</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Malfaro</LastName>
               <FirstName>Elijah</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Skye</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/08/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/30/2018 14:15:33</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E420</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Malfaro</LastName>
               <FirstName>Elijah</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Skye</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/08/1998 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>M416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>E420</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/30/2018 14:15:33</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>2540</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Pigs Ear</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Grantsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21536</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.300538</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.719546</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>501</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8004</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/30/2018 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 04:20:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 04:20:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 04:20:54</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:36</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>38</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 02:15:42</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:11</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>151489</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Wilburn</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/12/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <DateOfInfo>07/21/2017 20:20:05</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>W416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Wilburn</LastName>
               <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Wayne</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/12/1984 00:00:00</DOB>
               <TitleCode>JR</TitleCode>
               <SLastName>W416</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M240</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>07/21/2017 20:20:05</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>694</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Blackberry</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Grantsville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21536</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-79.195448</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.639038</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>500</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>5369</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>07/21/2017 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 02:15:43</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:35</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/07/2023 04:07:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>148463</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7213</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/10/2023 02:16:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7213</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/10/2023 02:16:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>01/10/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1GCCS14H538234315</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2003</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>CHEV</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>PK</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>RED</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>RED</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2EV4259</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>3</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>