<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-009031</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>03/11/2023 22:17:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>03/11/2023 22:17:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>03/11/2023 22:01:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>03/11/2023 22:01:00</StartTime>
   <EndDate>03/11/2023 22:22:00</EndDate>
   <Summary>Accident / DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 22:17:02</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5932</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>04/13/2023 01:08:37</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>ACC</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>642370</AddressId>
      <City>MDC125</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 22:17:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 08:54:01</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>642370</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Augustine Herman</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Chesapeake City</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>LN</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.85587</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.46973</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>3540-4099 AUGUSTINE HERMAN HWY / 1-300 BOHEMIA MANOR FARM LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>4100-4299 AUGUSTINE HERMAN HWY / 1-300 BOHEMIA MANOR FARM LN</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>03/11/2023 22:17:00</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>03/11/2023 22:17:00</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>55</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>03/29/2023 20:49:04</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>03/11/2023 22:17:03</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/19/2023 13:20:54</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>DUI # 23-046  Accident report was submitted in ACRS and is attached to the case file.  MSP marked patrol vehicle F-43 is equipped with an Axon In-car camera system was which was actively recording during the incident.  I am equipped with an agency issued Axon Body-worn camera which was actively recording during the incident. The operator of the vehicle involved in the incident was advised that he was being audibly and visually recorded by TFC Bachu # 7184 upon the initial contact before my arrival.  NARRATIVE:  On 03/11/2023 at approximately 2202 hours, I was dispatched to respond to the area of MD 213 Augustine Herman Hwy, south of Bohemia Manor Farm Lane (prior to entrance to Chateau Bu De Winery) for a motor vehicle accident involving a single vehicle.  Upon my arrival, TFC Bachu # 7184 was already on scene and was speaking with the operator of the vehicle who was still seated in the driver seat. I observed that the vehicle had come to final rest on the northbound shoulder of MD 213 and was still facing southbound. The further observed that the vehicle had sustained extensive damage to the front right portion and the right passenger side. The vehicle was identified as a silver in color, 2017 Subaru Forester bearing Maryland registration 7EM6750. The accident investigation revealed that the Subaru was traveling southbound on MD 213, south of Bohemia Manor Farm Lane. The operator lost control of the Subaru and traveled off of the roadway to the right and struck a State Highway Administration guardrail barrier. As a result of the initial collision, the Subaru then traveled back onto the roadway and crossed all lanes of travel and came to final rest in the northbound shoulder. MD 213 in that area is described as a two lane highway (one lane - each direction) and is divided by double yellow pavement striping. There area is not illuminated as there are no light poles.  I approached the driver side door of the Subaru where TFC Bachu was speaking with the male operator (sole occupant) through the opened driver side window. I made contact with the white male operator who was actively rummaging through the console area of the vehicle. I asked the male operator where he was coming from tonight, and he stated that he was coming from a friends house in Elkton as he began scrolling through his cell phone. As I was speaking with the male operator, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from within the vehicle and on the male operators breath. I further observed that his eyes were both blood shot and glassy. The male operator could not focus or pay attention when I asked him questions as to his whereabouts that evening as he kept looking through his phone and looking through items within his vehicle. I asked the male operator how much he had to drink that night, and he said,  not much. At that time, I instructed the male operator to exit the vehicle. I asked him what he had been drinking, and he stated that he was drinking Arnold Palmers (spiked iced tea) and Titos (vodka). As the male operator exited the driver side door, he lost his balance and swayed towards the guardrail barrier. I grabbed a hold of his right arm in order to prevent him from falling over, and I then advised him to sit against the guardrail barrier. I asked the male operator how many drinks he had, and he said,  enough. I then asked the male subject if was injured and if he needed paramedics to respond as he was just involved in an accident, and he stated no. I then asked the male operator if he would take a standardized field sobriety test for me, and he first hesitated to answer and then agreed to do so. The male operator was identified as Joshua Cory Kirk DOB 04/11/1996 by his Maryland drivers license.  A visual inspection of the Subaru vehicles interior was conducted by TFC Bachu which revealed three (3) empty Arnold Palmer alcohol cans and one (1) empty Titos vodka bottle. Those items were located in plain view on the front right passenger side floorboard. An additional empty Titos vodka bottle was located in the center console.  STANDARDIZED FIELD SOBRIETY TESTS:  I am trained and certified in administering the standardized field sobriety tests.  I have also been trained in A.R.I.D.E. ( Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement) by the Maryland State Police.  All tests were performed on a smooth flat grade surface (road pavement) on the northbound shoulder of MD 213. Kirk was wearing boots at the time the tests were performed as well as eyeglasses. I asked Kirk if there were any medical conditions or any other issues that would prevent him from performing the tests, and he stated no. All tests were demonstrated and explained to Kirk prior to him performing the tests.  HORIZONTAL GAZE AND NYSTAGMUS:  I first tested Kirk for his ability to track a visual stimulus (a pen) with both eyes as well as for equal pupil dilation. Both factors were present in both eyes. Kirk was able to perform these tasks as he could see the visual stimulus clearly while wearing his eyeglasses. I observed the following clues in both of Kirks eyes: lack of smooth pursuit, distinct nystagmus at maximum deviation, and onset of nystagmus prior to forty-five degrees.  WALK AND TURN:  The following clues were observed during the walk and turn test:  Instruction Stage: Kirk separated his feet right before I instructed him to begin the test.  First Nine Steps: Kirk stepped offline on step 2 and missed heel to toe on step 3.  Turn: Completed unsatisfactorily.  Second Nine Steps: Kirk missed heel to toe on steps 5, 6, 7, and stepped offline on those steps. Kirk only took 8 steps.  ONE LEG STAND:  The following clues were observed during the one leg stand test:  Zero to ten seconds: Foot down twice. Swayed each time he placed his foot down.  Eleven to twenty seconds: Foot down 5 times. Swayed back and forth.  Twenty-one to thirty seconds: Foot down 3 times. Swayed back and forth.  Kirk never raised his foot high enough to the 6-inch height as instructed.  PRELIMINARY BREATH TEST:  I asked Kirk if he would take a preliminary breath test for me, and he refused to do so. Kirk was advised that the test results could not be used against him court.  Based on Kirks poor performance of the standardized field sobriety tests, he was placed under arrest at approximately 2222 hours. Kirk was then properly secured in my marked patrol vehicle F-43. Kirk was read his DR-15 Advice of Rights at approximately 2233 hours while still at the scene of the incident. Kirk agreed to submit to the breath test.  DISPOSITION:  Kirk was transported to the North East Barrack located at 2433 W. Pulaski Hwy, North East MD 21901 for processing. The breath test was administered by Sgt. Spayd # 5369 at approximately 2313 hours and the test results were as follows: Alcohol concentration of 0.26 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  During the course of processing, Kirk made several statements about drinking throughout the evening. Kirk stated that he had been drinking since 6pm (1800 hrs).  Kirk was issued the appropriate citations for DUI and other traffic related offenses.  All events occurred in Cecil County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.      </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP4999</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 09:01:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4999</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 12:00:36</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Bachu</LastName>
            <FirstName>Farhan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7184</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Proctor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4999</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Spayd</LastName>
            <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5369</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Proctor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4999</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>55</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Proctor</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4999</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>498430</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>03/11/2023 23:59:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4999</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 08:54:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4999</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 08:55:53</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>26</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4999</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 08:54:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:33</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>372430</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Kirk</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Cory</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/11/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 08:21:51</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Kirk</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Cory</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/11/1996 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>K620</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 08:21:51</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>211</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Ariel</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Cecilton</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21913</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-75.864492</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.406496</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>RES</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>920</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>2555</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>667</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>392</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9894</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4999</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 08:56:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP4999</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 08:56:51</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:59</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4999</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 08:54:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4999</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 08:54:49</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>151226</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AC</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP4999</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>03/24/2023 09:00:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP4999</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>03/24/2023 09:00:03</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>03/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>JF2SJAGC8HH502216</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2017</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>SUBA</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>FOR</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>7EM6750</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2025</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>2</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>