<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-002769</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP4700</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>01/23/2023 00:55:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>01/23/2023 00:55:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>01/23/2023 00:38:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>01/23/2023 00:38:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop resulting in the arrest of the operator for Driving Under the Influence of alcohol.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 00:55:49</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4792</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>03/10/2023 14:21:58</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>OCEAN HWY/ ALLEN RD</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>269130</AddressId>
      <City>MDC217</City>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 00:55:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 00:46:50</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>269130</AddressId>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Princess Anne</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21853</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-75.676146</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.24844</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>13390-13655 OCEAN HWY / 13390-13746 ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>0-0 OCEAN HWY / 0-0 ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>12350-13389 OCEAN HWY / 13390-13746 ALLEN RD</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/23/2023 00:55:47</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/23/2023 00:55:47</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>01/29/2023 16:12:34</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/23/2023 00:55:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP2864</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 17:14:11</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Maryland State Police Princess Anne Barrack X Tpr. J. D. Revel III, IBM 7146 Field Operation Bureau January 23rd, 2023  Maryland State Police Patrol Vehicle:X-11 is a maroon unmarked 2021 Ford Explorer equipped with MVR system. Type of Report:DUI//DWI DUI Case Number:22-95-007 Driver/Suspect:Bryon Fitzgerald Britt Date of Birth:12/28/1963 License Number:T60647304  VA Class D Drivers License Subsequent Offender:No Accident Involved:No MVR Recordings:  Serial: text-decoration:underline"&gt;X60A61415 Model: Axon Body 3 Link:https://mdsp.evidence.com/axon/evidence?evidence_id=7864471a883b4bec92a3db6b68c66be4partner_id=5ed6a168304e40eb9a0cfb1a226ef1a1  Troopers Training/Experience:  * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA).  * Trained and certified to operate Radar and LiDAR through the Maryland State Police.  * NHTSA certified in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E).  * Attended numerousNHTSA certified cannabis impairment detection workshops.  * Federal Motor Carrier Safety Administration (FMCSA) certified commercial vehicle weights officer.  * FMCSA certified North American Standard (NAS) Level III Commercial Vehicle Inspector.  * Attended the 2021 Middle Atlantic-Great Lakes Organized Crime Law Enforcement Network (MAGLOCLEN) Conference.  * Certified At-Scene (Level I) Crash Reconstructionist through the Baltimore County Police Department and Maryland Crash Reconstruction Committee (MCRC).  * Certified in Advanced (Level II) Crash Investigation through the Montgomery County Police Department and Maryland Crash Reconstruction Committee (MCRC).  * Attended the 2022 Maryland Impaired Driving Conference hosted by the Maryland Department of Transportation and Zero Deaths Maryland.  * Trained in Human Trafficking investigation and recovery through the Federal Bureau of Investigation and the Maryland State Police.  * Certified Standardized Field Sobriety Instructor through the Maryland State Police.   Narrative:  This report has been prepared based upon the observations of this trooper and/or those of other troopers relative to the offense(s). The facts contained herein are intended solely to give the prosecuting authority a basic understanding of the facts pertaining to this case. The facts contained herein are not intended to be an exhaustive recitation of the facts pertaining to pretrial or trial issues. Instead, this trooper anticipates that during the pretrial proceedings in this case, the prosecutor will take the opportunity to interview this trooper in order to ascertain any and all relevant facts which might be the subject of this troopers testimony during court proceedings.  Phase #1 - Vehicle in Motion: On the morning of January 23rd, 2023, I was on proactive patrol along US Route 13 in Princess Anne, Somerset County, Maryland. At approximately 0039 hours, I was traveling northbound on US Route 13 when I observed a white Toyota Avalon in front of me approaching MD Route 822. I observed the Toyota approach the stop line at MD Route 822 and stop approximately 25 feet past the white line. The Toyota left the traffic light heading northbound in lane two. I observed the following driving behavior sequentially while following the Toyota:    Crossed the center dotted white line by a tire width  Crossed the shoulder fog line by a tire width  Tapping the brakes for no apparent reason  Crossed the center dotted white line again by a tire width  Due to the drivers inability to stop behind the pavement marking paired with the above listed abnormal driving behavior, I performed a traffic stop on the vehicle. I was able to identify the license plate as UUS1254, through the State of Virginia. The final location of the traffic stop was northbound on US Route 13 at MD Route 529. I never lost sight of this vehicle during the observation process.  Phase #2 - Personal Contact: I exited my patrol vehicle and approached the drivers door where I contactedthe operator, later identified as Bryon Fitzgerald Britt (DOB: 12/28/1963) via his Virginia Drivers License. I introduced myself, stated the reason for the traffic stop, and advised him that he was being audibly and visually recorded.I immediately detected an overwhelmingly strong and distinct odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the drivers compartment of the vehicle. I observed Britts eyes to be bloodshot and glassy.  I asked Britt for his license and registration. As he was grabbing his information, I asked him where he was coming from. Britt replied Chesapeake before handing me his Drivers License. I then asked where he was heading to, and he advised To the hospital, my sister is there. While he was still looking for the registration card, I asked Britt how much he had to drink that night. He stated Two beers.  Phase #3 - Pre-Arrest Screening: I asked Britt to exit the vehicle, and he did as I asked. As he exited the drivers seat, I observed him to be wearing black and white high-top shoes, gray sweatpants, and a white shirt covered by a blue Adidas sweatshirt on top. His movements exiting the vehicle were very slow and lethargic. I asked Britt to stand at the front of his vehicle while I asked him a few questions. While he walked to the front of the car, Britt could barely walk straight and had to use his car for balance. I asked again what kind of beer he had drank and he advised Coors Lite. He further stated that it was out of the can. As I spoke with Britt outside the vehicle, I continued to detect the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person.  Based on Britts driving that I observed and his admission paired with the odor of alcohol, he was offered field sobriety testing as a means to determine his level of impairment. He agreed to participate in the field sobriety testing at approximately 0042 hours. Starting off the introduction, I asked Britt if he wore glasses or contacts or was prescribed to be wearing them, and he stated No. I also asked Britt if he had taken or is prescribed any medication. He advised Just reading glasses. I asked Britt if he had suffered any traumatic head injuries recently, and he advised that he had not. He did advise that he was taking pain medication and had a hip transplant performed in 2018. I began the testing with the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus  I explained the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test to Britt. I instructed him to stand still with his feet together, hands down by his side, and to follow the stimulus (my pen) with his eyes and eyes only, keeping his head straight.He advisedthat he understood and could see the stimulus clearly, so I began the test.  Resting Nystagmus: No Equal Tracking: Yes Equal Pupil Size: Yes Eye Color: Brown  - Lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes - Distinct and sustained Nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes - Onset of Nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes  Note: Failed to track with his eyes multiple times, following with head and sometimes just staring straight at me.  Total Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Clues6of6  Walk and Turn  Weather:Slight rain Surface:Flat paved surface free of any debris/used imaginary straight line  I explained and demonstrated the Walk and Turn test to Britt. He was instructed to assume the starting position by placing his left foot on the imaginaryline and his right foot directly in front, heel touching toe, and to maintain this position while I explained the test. He was also instructed not to start or stop the test until instructed to do so.  He was advised totake nine heel-to-toe steps along the imaginaryline while looking down at his feet and counting each step out loud. Once he reached nine steps, he was instructed to leave his lead foot planted and take a series of small steps to turn himself around, then take nine more heel-to-toe steps back along thatline.During the test, he was also instructed to keep his hands down by his side. I asked Britt if he had questions, and he repeatedly replied Im trying.  I asked Britt if he was comfortable performing this test in the shoes he was wearing now, and he stated Yes. Due to the slight rain, I also asked if he was comfortable performing in this weather or if he would like to do so in a different environment. He advised No, lets just get it done.  While explaining and demonstrating, I observed Britt to lose his balance, break the heel-to-toe position immediately, and stand normally, contrary to my instruction.  Instruction Stage - Cannot keep balance in starting position - Starts too soon  Walking Stage 1st 9 Steps - Misses heel to toe on 3rd step - Stepped off the line by approximately 3 inches on 2nd, 5th step - Used arms for balance - Took 9steps total  Turn - Lost balance and stumbled off of the line after pivot.  Walking Stage 2nd 9 Steps - Misses heel to toe on 1st and 4th step - Stepped off the line by approximately 3 inches on 3rd step - Used arms for balance - Took4steps total before stopping and discontinuing the test on his own.  Total Walk and Turn Clues 8of8  One Leg Stand  Weather:Same as Above Surface:Same as Above  I explained and demonstrated the One Leg Stand test to Britt. He was instructed to lift one foot of his choice about six inches off of the ground, look down at his raisedfoot, and count out loud by the method given -one-thousand one, one-thousand two, one-thousand-three, etc. He was also advised to keep his hands down to his side and to not stop counting nor stop the test until he is instructedto do so. I asked Britt if he understood the test, and he advised me that he did.Britt then began the test by lifting his rightfoot from the ground.  Seconds 0-10 - Immediately dropped lifted foot after two seconds and did not pick it back up - Used arms for balance - Sways from side to side approximately 4 inches  Seconds 11-20 - Foot was still down, was trying to show me a card from his wallet  Seconds 21-30 - Picked foot back up on 24th second - Uses arms for balance - Sways from side to side approximately 4 inches  Ended test at 27 seconds  Total One Leg Stand Clues3of4   Alphabet F to Z  I asked Britt if he knew the English Alphabet, and he advised that he did. I asked Britt to recite the English Alphabet from the letter F to Z without singing it. Britt said: F, D, F, G, hold man, Im retired. Then he paused. He resumed at H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, P, Q, R, S. Britt then stopped and for approximately 15 seconds stood there shaking his head before I concluded this test.  Count From 31 to 19  I asked Britt to count from 31 to 19. Britt recited this properly.  Preliminary Breath Test  I explained the reasons for using apreliminarybreath test and Britt wasoffered the opportunity to submit abreath sample.Britt agreed and submitted a breath sample of .120 BrAC.  Arrest and Transport  At 0055 hours, I placed Britt under arrest for Driving Under the Influence of alcohol. Britt was placed into the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle. I pulled up a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights on my computer in front of Britt and asked if he could see the form. Britt advised that he could, and I played the DR-15 audio directly from the MVA website, having Britt follow along. After the reading was complete, Britt stated that he would like to submit a breath sample.  At the barrack, I performed a secondary search and checked Britts mouth for foreign objects. I did not locate any foreign objects.  Breath Test  Sgt. Barkley, a certified Intoximeter operator, arrived and contacted Britt. At 0141 hours, Sgt. Barkley administered the Intoximeter Test with a result of .11 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath.  Charging  Britt was charged with the following:    DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL  DRIVING VEHICLE WHILE UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL PER SE  DRIVING VEHICLEWHILE IMPAIRED BY ALCOHOL  RECKLESS DRIVING VEHICLE IN WANTON AND WILLFUL DISREGARD FOR SAFETY OF PERSONS AND PROPERTY  NEGLIGENT DRIVING VEHICLE IN CARELESS AND IMPRUDENT MANNER ENDANGERING PROPERTY, LIFE AND PERSON  FAILURE TO STOP BEHIND DESIGNATED PAVEMENT LINE  FAILURE TO OBEY A TRAFFIC CONTROL DEVICE  UNSAFE LANE CHANGE  Britt was given all appropriate documentation and released to a sober friend, Horace Raymond Waters (DOB: 7/18/1959) at 0226 hours without incident.  All events did occur in Somerset County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 01:00:58</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/29/2023 06:55:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barfield</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jacob</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7185</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Salgueiro</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brandon</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7370</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Revel</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7146</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492152</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/23/2023 00:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492152</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/23/2023 00:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492152</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/23/2023 00:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492152</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/23/2023 00:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492152</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/23/2023 00:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492152</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/23/2023 00:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492152</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15535</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/23/2023 00:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>492152</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>30</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15558</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>01/23/2023 00:38:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>59</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 00:58:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:31</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>367035</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>A</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>U</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Britt</LastName>
               <FirstName>Bryon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Fitzgerald</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/28/1963 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>01/24/2023 00:58:20</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Britt</LastName>
               <FirstName>Bryon</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Fitzgerald</MiddleName>
               <DOB>12/28/1963 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B630</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>B650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>01/24/2023 00:58:20</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 15:34:57</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:34</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 15:45:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:41</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 15:45:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:41</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:18</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>01/24/2023 00:57:18</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>01/29/2023 15:34:57</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>01/29/2023 15:34:57</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>95</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>02/23/2023 17:14:10</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>01/29/2023 15:34:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>02/23/2023 17:14:13</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Added Attachments.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7146</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>02/18/2023 01:52:13</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7146</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>02/18/2023 01:52:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Schur</LastName>
            <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2864</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>95</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP4700</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Revel</LastName>
            <FirstName>John</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7146</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>