<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-016855</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>05/11/2023 19:43:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>05/11/2023 19:43:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>05/11/2023 19:26:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>05/11/2023 19:26:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI/DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>05/11/2023 19:43:33</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4539</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>11/09/2023 15:00:47</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>693692</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/11/2023 19:43:34</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 13:40:14</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>693692</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>11549</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Ocean</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>GTWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Easton</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21601</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.06096</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.866432</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>05/11/2023 19:43:30</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>05/11/2023 19:43:30</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>Y</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/09/2023 15:00:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>05/11/2023 19:43:33</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 20:19:43</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Alcohol Influence Report Patrol Vehicle Information  I-26 (Marked). I was equipped with a BWC (Body Worn Camera) only.  Defendant: Krasic, Steven Date of Birth: 09/10/1974 Date of Arrest: 05/11/2023 Time of stop: 1926 Time of Arrest: 1942 Maryland SDX: K-622-777-005-704 License Status  Valid License Restrictions  None Registration Violations  None  Officers Training/Experience * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Anne Arundel County Police Department, Maryland State Police Department, and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police Department * Certified Drug Recognition Expert since 2017 * Graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute 2019 *2023 Frederick Police Department Green Lab  *Repeat Offender* - YES  On 05/11/2023, at approximately 1926 hours, I, Trooper Koehler #7524, was conducting stationary patrol on west bound Route 50 at Plugge Road, Easton, Talbot County Maryland. I was parked, perpendicular to Route 50, looking at west bound traffic, on the side of the road, directly in front the Woodlawn Memorial Park, located at 11365 Ocean Gateway, Easton, Talbot County Maryland. It should be noted that I was equipped with a handheld LIDAR unit Maryland State Police #2 (SN: LF04548). The unit was calibrated and found to be in working order.   VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  I observed a vehicle in lane number 2 traveling west bound on Route 50, prior to Plugge Road. Immediately after seeing this vehicle, I observed another vehicle traveling behind it, and quickly change lanes into lane number 1, passing it very quickly. It appeared that the passing vehicle was traveling at a speed above the posted speed limit. I had a clear view of this vehicle, as it passed, and received a digital speed reading on it, at 95 mph in a 55 mph zone. The vehicle continued traveling west bound on Route 50, now passing my stationary location. I immediately activated my emergency equipment, attempting to stop this vehicle. The vehicle was observed to be a gray 2011 Audi S5 convertible with the top down, displaying Maryland registration 1EF8986. I noticed that as I entered onto the Highway, the Audi, changed lanes into lane 2, and pulled over into the shoulder quickly. I pulled behind the vehicle, exited my patrol car and made contact with the driver.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the driver side B pillar of the vehicle and made contact with the driver/sole occupant, who was later positively identified via his Maryland drivers license as Steven Krasic (W/M, DOB: 09/10/1974). Krasic was advised that I was a Maryland State Trooper and the stop was being recorded with audio and video. I could see that Krasics face was flush red and he was avoiding eye contact as he was reaching in his passenger side glove compartment, already attempting to obtain documents. As I was speaking with him, he appeared to have difficulty identifying his registration expiration. Krasic stated he was just coming from the Hog Neck Golf Course, located at 10142 Old Cordova Road, Easton, Talbot County Maryland. (Approximately 4 miles from stop location)  While speaking with him about his travel plans Krasic struggled closing his passenger side glove compartment. Krasic stated he was headed home. Krasics eyes were observed to be bloodshot. I could smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from inside the vehicle. Krasic was questioned about his alcohol consumption, stating that he had two beers on the course during the first nine holes. Krasic stated that he had played 18 holes. Krasic was asked if he knew why I stopped him. Krasic stated, I mean I came out of there kinda quick. Krasic stated he did not know how fast he was going, but confirmed that he passed someone in front of him. I informed Krasic of the speed he was observed to be traveling. Krasic, stated, really?!, appearing to be in disbelief. Krasic further stated, that he didnt realize he was going that fast.  Krasic was asked, and agreed to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests. I then walked back to my patrol vehicle, requested for back up and continued with the traffic stop. Trooper Dassoulas #7348 responded to assist.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  I asked Krasic to step out of the vehicle, and noticed, that he was now chewing a mint odor gum, commonly used to mask the odor of an alcoholic beverage. Krasic was asked to remove the gum, which he complied. Krasic removed his seat belt and walked to the front of his vehicle. Krasic confirmed again, with me, that he had only consumed two beers on the front nine, and stopped drinking after. Krasic also confirmed with me, that he had just left the golf course. When asked about medical issues, Krasic stated he had diabetes and hearing loss. Krasic was asked if he had any other medical issues, which he stated, no. Krasic stated he was not sick or injured. Krasic stated he was not epileptic. Krasic stated he does take insulin for his diabetes.  Prior to any testing, my overhead forward flashing lights were deactivated. The temperature was in the low 80s, sunny and clear with minimal wind. Krasic was wearing a blue colored shirt with blue shorts. While speaking with me outside of his car, directly in front of me, I could now smell a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The red light of my pen was used as the stimulus, and held approximately 12 inches from Krasics eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Krasics pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking with no resting Nystagmus. When asked, Krasic stated that he understood the instructions.  1.) Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both eyes 2.) Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes 3.) Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Vertical Nystagmus  Not present  OBSERVATION: Krasic had to be reminded to keep his head still and only move his eyes. Krasic was asked about contacts and glasses, stating he did not have contacts in his eyes and did not required glasses to drive.  WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed)  Prior to Krasic performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Krasic was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. He was instructed to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in that position until told to begin. He was advised to take nine (9) steps on a straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. He was instructed to keep his hands flat at his sides, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and to count every step aloud. On the ninth step, he was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line, and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Krasic was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. He was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his sides, look down at his feet, and count each step out loud. After providing the instructions, Krasic stated he understood, the best I do.  Krasic was offered to conduct this test barefoot, or wearing his open toe flip flops. Krasic decided to conduct this test with his flip flops, stating he didnt walk in the street.  Instructional Stage: - Started too soon.  Walking Stage (1st Nine): - Stepped off line on step 2                      -missed heel to toe on step 4,                        Turn : Incorrect, failing to keep his lead foot planted on the ground.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): -missed heel to toe on steps 1 and 2                        Observation: During the instructional stage, when asked to place his left foot on the line, Krasic moved his right foot and placed it on the imaginary line. Also failed to count out loud, as instructed. Krasic informed me during the instructional stage, that his balance was full blown terrible.   ONE LEG STAND (3/4 clues observed)  Prior to Krasic performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off of the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until told to stop. After explaining the test, Krasic stated that he understood, but stated, he didnt know if he could do them.  Instructional Stage: Remained as demonstrated  Balance and Count Stage:  -swayed while balancing                       -used arms for balance                       -puts foot down after 2 seconds, 4 seconds, and 5 seconds. ( after falling almost completely over, he stated that he couldnt do this at any point in his life) Krasic tried again, putting his foot down three more times. Prior to the 30 seconds being completed, Krasic, stated, that was all he had. The test was completed.  Krasic wanted to know what the requirement was in terms of holding his foot in a raised position. Krasic wanted to attempt the One Leg Stand, this time, barefoot. Krasic tried again, still showing multiple clues of impairment, including swaying, using arms for balance, and putting his foot down several times again.  PBT was offered and refused.   ARREST Based on the following, I had reason to believe Krasic was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol -6/6 HGN -4/8 WAT -3/4 OLS -Red flushed face  -Poor balance and coordination during SFSTs -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from breath -Admitted to drinking alcohol prior to operating his motor vehicle  Due to the number of observations, I concluded Krasic was driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a vehicle safely. I placed Krasic under arrest at 1942 hours. Krasic was placed in handcuffs and seated in the front seat of my patrol vehicle. Krasics vehicle was parked and secured off the roadway.  Krasic was read aloud the DR-15 Advice of Rights form using the MVA audio file. After reading the form aloud, Krasic, stated, when asked if he wished to provide a breath specimen, Im definitely not taking the test, further clarifying, Ive always been advised not to do that.  Krasics license status at the time of this incident was valid with no restrictions. A DR-15A form was completed and Krasic was issued a temporary license. Krasic was provided with his copies of the MVA related forms, and his traffic citations.   Krasic was issued the following traffic citations: driving vehicle under the influence of alcohol, driving vehicle while impaired by alcohol, negligent driving, reckless driving, and exceeding the speed limit, and driving at a speed greater than reasonable and prudent. A sober driver responded to the barrack and took control of Krasic with no further incident.  All events occurred in Talbot County, Maryland.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: REFUSED </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 15:29:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/15/2023 21:39:08</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Moore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Scott</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2269</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dassoulas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Hayley</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7348</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Dadds</LastName>
            <FirstName>Brian</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5551</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Koehler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Justin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7524</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>506280</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>05/11/2023 19:26:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 15:34:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 15:34:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>48</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 15:41:02</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:57:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>376853</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Krasic</LastName>
               <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/10/1974 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>05/12/2023 15:39:38</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>K622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Krasic</LastName>
               <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
               <DOB>09/10/1974 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>K622</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S315</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>05/12/2023 15:39:38</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>759</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Cougar </StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>CT</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Millersville</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21108</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.620196</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.090046</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 15:41:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 15:41:02</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:56</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 15:34:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 15:34:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152925</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7524</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/12/2023 15:51:57</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7524</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/12/2023 15:51:57</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>05/12/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WAUVGAFH4BN003748</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2011</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>AUDI</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>S5</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleStyleCode>CV</VehicleStyleCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>GRY</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>1EF8986</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>7</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/25/2023 14:48:16</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/25/2023 14:48:16</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>Y</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>58</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>11/09/2023 15:00:49</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP3450</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/25/2023 14:48:16</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>11/15/2023 20:19:43</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>On 10-25-23 the District Court of Talbot County has requested this DWI case involving Steven Krasic to be expunged from our files. This case involving Steven Krasic was expunged on 10-25-2023.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP3450</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/25/2023 14:49:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP3450</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/25/2023 14:51:09</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Williams</LastName>
            <FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4539</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>58</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Weems</LastName>
            <FirstName>Clinton</FirstName>
            <InternalID>3450</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>