<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-034644</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP5600</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>10/02/2023 21:57:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>10/02/2023 21:57:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>10/02/2023 21:45:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>10/02/2023 21:45:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect was arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 21:57:11</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6327</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/25/2023 02:11:11</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>571919</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:47:13</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 23:47:20</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>571919</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>BRANCH</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>AVE</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>CLINTON</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>20735</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <CrossStreetTypeCode>RD</CrossStreetTypeCode>
         <Longitude>-76.879685</Longitude>
         <Latitude>38.746601</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>10/02/2023 21:57:09</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>10/02/2023 21:57:09</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>61</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/25/2023 02:11:12</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 21:57:11</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:54</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In-Car (L-21) and Body Worn Camera Operational.   Defendant: Julio Cesar Luna-Cruz  Date of Birth: 01/08/1982  Date of Arrest: 10/02/2023  Time of Arrest: 2156 Hours    DUI:  23-310  Certificate and Training:  Trained in Administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) through the Maryland State Police (MSP) and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA)  Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E.)  Soundex:  L-526-454-112-025/MD  Narrative: VEHICLE IN MOTION (Phase 1):  On October 2, 2023, at approximately 2133 hours, I, Trooper J. Barlow #7186, of the Maryland State Police, currently assigned to the Forestville Barrack, was on duty in my marked patrol vehicle traveling southbound Branch Avenue at Surratts Road, Clinton, Prince Georges County, Maryland 20735, in lane 2. I observed a gray Dodge Ram bearing Maryland registration 6DX5739 traveling in the same direction in lane 1, which was coming to an end. Instead of the operator reducing their speed and merging in behind my patrol vehicle, the operator accelerated in speed, drove off the roadway to the left and overtook my vehicle position. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. While signaling the operator to stop over to the right shoulder, the operator came to a slow stop on the center median of the roadway.    PERSONAL CONTACT (Phase 2):  Upon stopping the vehicle, I made a driver side approach where I observed the vehicle was occupied one time. While talking to the operator, I advised the reason for the traffic stop to which he stated, I know, it was a bad idea. I requested the drivers license and registration card from the operator to which he provided me with a Maryland identification card who I identified him as Luna-Cruz, Julio Cesar (H/M DOB: 01/08/1982.) Luna-Cruz was unable to provide me with the registration card since he had items blocking his glove compartment. I observed Luna-Cruzs eyes to be bloodshot and glossy. I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Luna-Cruzs breath and person. I asked Luna-Cruz had he consumed alcoholic beverage to which he stated, Yes. I asked Luna-Cruz how many drinks had he consumed to which he stated, Four. I asked Luna-Cruz what brand of alcoholic beverage did he consume to which he stated, Corona. I asked Luna-Cruz how long ago had he consumed his alcoholic beverage to which he stated, About 45 minutes ago. I asked Luna-Cruz if he would perform the voluntary Standardized Field Sobriety Tests (SFSTs) to which he agreed to perform. I turned off my front facing emergency equipment and turned away my spot light. I requested Luna-Cruz to exit and step to the front of his vehicle to which he stepped out stumbled in the grass. Luna-Cruz then stood outside of his vehicle where I had to advise Luna-Cruz to walk to the front of his vehicle once again.   PRE-ARREST SCREENING (Phase 3):  Before performing SFSTs, I asked Luna-Cruz if he takes medications and have any injuries to which he advised he did not. I asked Luna-Cruz if he wore glasses or contacts to which he advised he does but does not have them with him.   Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (HGN) 6 out of 6 clues observed:  Before performing HGN, I instructed Luna-Cruz to stand with his legs and feet together with his arms down by his sides. I instructed Luna-Cruz not to move from this position until I instructed him to do so. I asked Luna-Cruz if he could see the silver tip of my stimulus to which he advised he could. I instructed Luna-Cruz to follow the silver tip of my stimulus with his eyes only, without moving his head, neck, or shoulders. I asked Luna-Cruz if he understood the instructions I gave him to which he advised he understood. Luna-Cruz exhibited equal pupil size in both eyes. Luna-Cruz did not exhibit Resting Nystagmus and showed equal tracking in both eyes. Luna-Cruz moved his head multiple times even after advising he understood not to move his head.   Lack of Smooth Pursuit:  Luna-Cruz showed lack of smooth pursuit in both eyes.   Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation:  Luna-Cruz showed distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation in both eyes.  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees:  Luna-Cruz showed onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees in both eyes.   Vertical Gaze Nystagmus:  Luna-Cruz did not show vertical gaze nystagmus.  Walk and Turn (WAT) 2 out of 8 clues observed:  Prior to performing WAT, I advised Luna-Cruz to imagine there was a straight line in front of him. I instructed Luna-Cruz to stand with his right foot in front of his left foot touching heel to toe with his arms down by his sides. I advised Luna-Cruz to take nine (9) heel to toe steps down the imaginary line, looking down at his feet, and counting each step out loud. I instructed Luna-Cruz once he got to his 9th step to leave his lead foot planted, take a series of small steps turning around, and take 9 more heel to toe steps back down the imaginary line. I instructed Luna-Cruz once he starts the test, do not stop until he completed the test. I demonstrated how the test should be performed and asked Luna-Cruz if he understood the instructions and demonstration to which he advised he understood. I instructed Luna-Cruz to begin the test.  Instructional Phase:  Luna-Cruz broke instructional phase stance, separating his feet by more than one half inch.   Walking Stage (1st Series):  No clues observed.  Turn:  No clues observed.  Walking Stage (2nd Series):  Luna-Cruz stepped off line by more than one half inch on step 6.   One Leg Stand (OLS) 3 out of 4 clues observed:  Before performing OLS, I instructed Luna-Cruz to stand with his legs and feet together with his arms down by his sides. I instructed Luna-Cruz not to move from this position until I instructed him to do so. I instructed Luna-Cruz to lift either leg of his choice six inches off the ground. I instructed Luna-Cruz to count out loud in the manner of one-thousand-one, one-thousand-two, one-thousand-three, and so on until I instructed him to stop. I demonstrated how the test should be performed and asked Luna-Cruz if he understood the instructions and demonstration to which he advised he understood. I instructed Luna-Cruz to begin the test.   Puts Foot Down:  Luna-Cruz put his foot down on second 23.  Uses Arms for Balance:  Luna-Cruz used arms for balance on seconds 2-3.  Sways:  Luna-Cruz swayed to the side by more than one half inch from center.  Hops:  No clues observed.  Arrest:    Failure to obey traffic control device  Driving off roadway while passing vehicles  The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from his breath and person  Glossy eyes  The admittance of consuming alcoholic beverages   margin-left:8px"&gt;The observations during SFSTs   Preliminary Breath Test:  Refused.  At approximately 2155 hours, Luna-Cruz was advised of his Preliminary Breath Test (PBT) rights and offered a PBT. Luna-Cruz refused to submit to the PBT. At approximately 2156 hours, Luna-Cruz was placed under arrest for driving under the influence of alcohol. Luna-Cruz was searched prior to being placed in my marked patrol vehicle to be transported to the Forestville Barrack. While enroute to the Barrack, Luna-Cruz was provided a digital copy of the Advice of Rights (DR-015) from the mva.maryland.gov website to follow along while I played the audio version downloaded from the same website in its entirety.   Intoximeter Test:  .16BrAC  After having been read the DR-015, at approximately 2214 hours, Luna-Cruz agreed to submit to take the Intoximeter Test. The Intoximeter Test was administered by Sgt B. Sorenson #5368 with a result of .16BrAC.   Luna-Cruz was charged with DUI/DWI and other traffic related incidents.    It should be noted, Luna-Cruz was in possession of an identification card through Maryland because his license was suspended for a previous DUI arrest. An MVA referral has been submitted on Luna-Cruz.  Luna-Cruz was released to a sober driver from the Forestville Barrack.  Case closed by arrest.  All events occurred in Prince Georges County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 02:38:56</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 02:52:35</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Butt</LastName>
            <FirstName>Mohammad</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6534</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>York</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6327</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>61</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP5600</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Barlow</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7186</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524102</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16616</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/02/2023 21:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16616</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 23:59:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524102</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>9</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/02/2023 21:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19731</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 00:03:32</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524102</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16824</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>10</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/03/2023 21:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16824</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 00:05:04</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524102</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/02/2023 21:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 00:04:05</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524102</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17510</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/02/2023 21:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17510</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 00:00:15</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524102</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/02/2023 21:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 23:56:51</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524102</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/02/2023 21:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 23:57:42</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524102</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19747</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/02/2023 21:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19747</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 23:55:01</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524102</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>9</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/02/2023 21:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 23:54:06</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524102</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>10</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19741</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/02/2023 21:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19741</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 23:56:13</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>524102</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>11</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>17272</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>11</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>10/02/2023 21:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>17272</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 00:05:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>41</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 00:14:34</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>389376</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Luna-cruz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Julio</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Cesar</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/08/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 23:19:32</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>L526</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Luna-cruz</LastName>
               <FirstName>Julio</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Cesar</MiddleName>
               <DOB>01/08/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>L526</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 23:19:32</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>240</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>899</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8784</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 00:14:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:17</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 00:14:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:17</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 00:14:34</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:17</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/02/2023 23:50:31</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157679</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7186</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>10/03/2023 00:07:39</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7186</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/03/2023 00:07:39</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>10/02/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1D7RV1GP6AS171283</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2010</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>DODG</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>R15</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>TK</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>GRY</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>6DX5739</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>6</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>