<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-029277</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>08/19/2023 04:32:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>08/19/2023 04:32:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>08/19/2023 04:12:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>08/19/2023 04:12:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI / DWI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 04:32:48</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP1174</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/31/2023 00:23:55</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>12 MM I695 NB, CATONSVILLE</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>704289</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 04:32:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 05:07:08</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>704289</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>12</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I695 Nb Catonsville</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.742931</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.2989125</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>08/19/2023 04:32:45</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>08/19/2023 04:32:45</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>67</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>08/20/2023 00:35:36</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 04:32:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 17:04:55</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>R-29 equipped with in-car camera and body-worn camera. Contact Sgt. Twardowski (joseph.twardowski@maryland.gov) for camera footage.  Case# 23-MSP-029277 Defendant: Luis Miguel Velasquez-Salvadorena Date of Birth: 03/06/1988  Date of Arrest: 08/19/2023 Time of Arrest: 0435 hours DUI #: 23-442 Citation #: 5G10XD0 Breath Result: Refused   Certificates and Training *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration  *Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (ARIDE) Certified  *Certified Emergency Medical Technician by the Maryland Institute of Emergency Medical Services Systems  *Certified RADAR/LIDAR operator by the Maryland State Police  *Certified License Plate Reader (LPR) operator by the Maryland State Police  *Apprehended over 150 impaired drivers while working as a Maryland State Trooper  *2023 Distinguished graduate of the University of Maryland DUI Institute  Vehicle In Motion (Phase 1)  On August 19th, 2023 at approximately 0412 hours I, Trooper Sigman #7376, currently assigned to the Golden Ring Barrack, was on routine patrol of the inner loop of I695 prior to I70 when I observed a black Nissan Pathfinder bearing Maryland registration of 4EZ4415 traveling in lane 2 causing traffic to back up. I then paced the Pathfinder at 40mph in a posted 50mph zone while in lane 2. I then observed that the Pathfinder was unable to maintain a single lane of travel and repeatedly drifted from lane 2, across the dashed white line, and into lane 1 with both drivers side tires. I then observed the Pathfinder begin to drive half in lane 2 and half in lane 3 on top of the dashed white line. I then activated my emergency equipment and initiated a traffic stop on the black Nissan Pathfinder bearing Maryland registration of 4EZ4415. The Pathfinder then abruptly pulled to the right shoulder and came within inches of striking the guardrail.  Personal Contact (Phase 2) I then made a drivers side approach of the black Nissan Pathfinder bearing Maryland registration of 4EZ4415. Upon arriving at the drivers window I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I observed two Corona beers in the center console. I observed that the driver displayed bloodshot glassy eyes, slurred speech upon conversation, and uncoordinated movements. I then identified myself, the reason for the stop, and requested the drivers license. The driver stated that he did not have a license then handed me a passport which identified him as Luis Miguel Velasquez-Salvadorena. Velasquez-Salvadorena advised that he spoke English and stated that he was driving home from work. I then asked Velasquez-Salvadorena how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed prior to driving. Velasquez-Salvadorena denied consuming any alcoholic beverages. A METERS/MVA check of the vehicle showed it to be suspended for insurance lapse. It also revealed Velasquez-Salvadorena did not have a license in any state and had 3 active warrants through Anne Arundel County.  I then requested Velasquez-Salvadorena to exit and walk to the front of my vehicle. I observed that Velasquez-Salvadorena displayed gait ataxia. I also detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on Velasquez-Salvadorenas breath and person. Velasquez-Salvadorena then began to lean against the hood of his vehicle for balance. I again asked Velasquez-Salvadorena how many alcoholic beverages he had consumed prior to driving. Velasquez-Salvadorena replied Maybe one beer. Velasquez-Salvadorena continued to lean against his vehicle for balance. I then asked Velasquez-Salvadorena if he would submit to standardized field sobriety testing. Velasquez-Salvadorena agreed.  Pre-Arrest Screening (Phase 3)  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of I695 prior to I70. The surface was dry, level, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 78 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of streetlights, and overhead lights, and my vehicles takedown lights. My vehicles front facing emergency lights were deactivated for the duration of the field sobriety tests. Velasquez-Salvadorena appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries and or defects.  I asked Velasquez-Salvadorena the following questions:  Injuries- none Medical conditions- none Medications- none Glasses or contacts- none Alcoholic beverages- none Controlled dangerous substance- one beer    Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The test was explained. I then began the test. I did not observe any resting nystagmus. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit - present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - present in both eyes *Vertical Gaze Nystagmus - Present in both eyes  During the test Velasquez-Salvadorena had difficulty maintaining balance. Velasquez-Salvadorena also had difficulty following the stimulus and had to be reminded multiple times to keep his head still.     Walk and Turn (7/8 clues observed)  Prior to Velasquez-Salvadorena performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. I asked Velasquez-Salvadorena if he had any questions. Velasquez-Salvadorena stated that he understood the test.    Instructional Stage: Steps out of starting position (two times) Starting walking prior to being instructed to do so (three times)   Walking Stage (1st Nine):  Steps off line Misses heel to toe Takes 15 steps Raises arms for balance Stops walking    Walking Stage (2nd Nine):  Not attempted. After taking 15 steps Velasquez-Salvadorena stopped walking and ended the test.      Turn: Not attempted  One Leg Stand (3/4)  Prior to Velasquez-Salvadorena performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Velasquez-Salvadorena advised that he understood the test.  Instructional Stage: Sways from side to side     Balance and Count Stage  Seconds 0-10: Sways from side to side Raises arms for balance Puts foot down      Seconds 11-20: Sways from side to side Raises arms for balance Puts foot down      Seconds 21-30: Sways from side to side Raises arms for balance Puts foot down    I then offered my PBT to Velasquez-Salvadorena. Velasquez-Salvadorena agreed, however, he was unable to follow directions on how to provide a breath sample.  Arrest  Based on the following, I had probable cause to believe Velasquez-Salvadorena was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:  *Unable to maintain a single lane of travel *Traveling significantly below the posted speed limit *Multiple alcoholic beverages in the center console *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle *Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath and person *Glassy eyes *Admission to consuming an alcoholic beverage *slurred speech *Gait ataxia *Poor SFST     At this time Velasquez-Salvadorena was placed under arrest for DUI. Velasquez-Salvadorena was then handcuffed, searched, and placed in the front seat of R-29 and seat belted inside. A physical copy of the DR15 was then handed to Velasquez-Salvadorena and stated that he could see and understand it. The audio version was played aloud. At the conclusion of the audio Velasquez-Salvadorena stated that fuck that indicating that he did not wish to take the intoximeter test. The time was 0451 hours.  20-Minute Observation Period:  N/A     Intoximeter Result:  N/A  Velasquez-Salvadorena was then transported to the Golden Ring Barrack where he was placed in front of the Essex Commissioner. Velasquez-Salvadorena was then released on personal recognizance. Velasquez-Salvadorena was then issued the appropriate citations as well as a DR15A. Velasquez-Salvadorena was then released to his fianc in the front parking lot of the Golden Ring Barrack.  All above events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 07:17:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 08:04:02</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wilson</LastName>
            <FirstName>Edward</FirstName>
            <InternalID>4772</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>67</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Sigman</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ethan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7376</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518725</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 04:12:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518725</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 04:12:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518725</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 04:12:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518725</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 04:12:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518725</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15525</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 04:12:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15525</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518725</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 04:12:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518725</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19731</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 04:12:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19731</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>518725</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>8</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16604</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>8</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>08/19/2023 04:12:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16604</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>35</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 07:10:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 07:10:41</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>363746</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Velasquez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Luis</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Miguel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/06/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>12/15/2022 14:06:30</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>V422</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>VALASQUEZ SALVADORENA</LastName>
               <FirstName>LUIS</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>V422</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Velasquez</LastName>
               <FirstName>Luis</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Miguel</MiddleName>
               <DOB>03/06/1988 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>V422</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>12/15/2022 14:06:30</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>M</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>VALASQUEZ SALVADORENA</LastName>
               <FirstName>LUIS</FirstName>
               <SLastName>V422</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>08/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>50</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Glen Ridge</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <SubTypeCode>APT</SubTypeCode>
               <SubNumber>B3</SubNumber>
               <City>Glen Burnie</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21061</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.615199</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.185757</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>362</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>0497</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>12/15/2022 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 07:10:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>C</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 07:10:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 07:10:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 07:10:41</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:23</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:23</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 05:10:23</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>156258</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7376</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>08/19/2023 07:15:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7376</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/19/2023 07:15:35</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>08/19/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5N1DR2MMXJC619507</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2018</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>PATHFINDER</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4EZ4415</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>