<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-031738</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MD324SP00</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/09/2023 23:14:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/09/2023 23:14:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/09/2023 22:23:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/09/2023 22:23:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>HACHEM "R" 23-488</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/09/2023 23:14:53</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP6323</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/06/2023 20:20:55</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>91 MM I70 EB, WINDSOR MILL</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>706458</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/09/2023 23:14:54</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 10:37:38</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>706458</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>91</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I70 Eb Windsor</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>ML</StreetTypeCode>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.7661979</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.30705875</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/09/2023 23:14:50</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/09/2023 23:14:50</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>07</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>10/06/2023 20:20:55</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/09/2023 23:14:53</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:45:13</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>*STATE POLICE IMPAIRED DRIVING REDUCTION EFFORT (S.P.I.D.R.E) TEAM* MVR Statement: The following incident was captured on in-car and Body camera. Title: HACHEM R 23-488. ID: 23-MSP-0311738 Arrested: Hachem, Sabine Ali. Certification and training  -Trained in Field Sobriety Test through Maryland State Police Academy.  -Trained in Advanced Roadside Impaired Driving Enforcement (A.R.I.D.E)  -Trained and certified to operate RADAR and LIDAR through the Maryland State Police.  - Graduated from The Institute of Advanced Law Enforcement Studies Driving Under the Influence Institute-University of Maryland.  - I am a certified EC/IR II Intoximeter operator.  - I am NHTSA certified Standardized Field Sobriety Testing Instructor.  - I have apprehended more than 250 impaired drivers during my tenure with the Maryland State Police to date. VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1)  On September 09, 2023, at approximately 2221 hours, I, TFC. I. Riba Tankari # 7058 with Maryland State Police was traveling eastbound I-70 west of Security Blvd, Baltimore County, Maryland in lane #1 (left lane). My issued patrol vehicle is Maryland State Police unmarked unit DUI-6. At that time, I observed a white Mercedes GLA250 bearing Maryland registration 4BR0682 traveling eastbound I-70 in lane #2 (middle lane) unable to stay within a single lane. I observed the Mercedes had swerved from lane #2 into lane #3 (right lane) by more than one tire width on occasion. I observed the Mercedes had swerved to the left towards the dotted white line and drove on the line on two separate occasions. I followed the Mercedes and observed the vehicle had swerved from lane #2 into lane #1 by more than one tire on one occasion. I changed lane into lane #2 and observed the Mercedes had changed lane into lane #3. I continued to follow the Mercedes and observed the vehicle had swerved to the left towards the dotted white line on several occasions. On one occasion I observed the Mercedes had swerved from lane #3 into lane #2 by one tire. I initiated a traffic stop on the Mercedes using my emergency equipment. The Mercedes came to a stop in the area of eastbound I-70 and west I-695, Baltimore County, Maryland on the right shoulder. PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)  I approached the Mercedes on the driver side and made contact with the driver (sole occupant) of the vehicle. I introduced myself and explained to her the reason for the traffic stop. I asked the driver where she was coming from, and she stated Eldersburg. I asked her where she was heading, and she stated Elkridge. I requested her drivers license and registration card. I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I observed that the driver had watery and glassy eyes. I observed the drivers movements were slow while attempting to retrieve the requested documents. While speaking with driver, I noticed her speech was slow. The driver was identified through her Maryland drivers license as Hachem, Sabine Ali. I returned to my patrol vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with. I returned to the Mercedes and requested Hachem to exit her vehicle and to walk to the front of her vehicle and she complied. While outside her vehicle, Hachem stumbled, lost her balance and stood against her vehicle for balance. I asked Hachem how many alcoholic beverages she had consumed, and she denied having any alcoholic beverages. While speaking with Hachem outside her vehicle, I again detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. I asked Hachem to submit to Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and she agreed.  The evaluation surface was dry, flat, and free of debris. No surface defects were observed. My patrol flashlight lit the area. My patrol vehicles forward emergency lights were deactivated during all three tests. Hachem appeared to be in good physical conditions. I asked Hachem the following questions: Medical conditions: No. Medications: No. Anything that will prevent you from walking on straight line or standing on one leg: No Glasses or contact: No. PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS: (6/6 clues observed). The Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test was explained and administered per the NHTSA SFST Manual. - Equal pupil size and equal tracking, no resting nystagmus - Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes - Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes - Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees  Present in both eyes Notes: * During the HGN test, I continued to detect a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from Hachems breath. * I observed Hachem swaying back and forth while standing for the test. WALK AND TURN: (5/8 clues observed). The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Hachem stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Instructional Stage: Hachem lost her balance to the right on several occasions and to the left on two separate occasions and had difficulty staying in the instructional position. I instructed Hachem to return to the instructional position on several occasions. Walking Stage (1st Nine): Missed touching heel to toe by more than one inch on count 8. Raised her arms for balance more than six (6) inches away from her body on all counts. Stepped completely offline by one foot width on counts 1, 3, and 9. Turn: The turn was not completed correctly; instead Hachem turned to her right failing to take a series of small steps as instructed and demonstrated. Walking Stage (2nd Nine): Missed touching heel to toe by more than half inch on counts 7, 8, and 9. Stepped completely offline by one shoe width on counts 3, 4, and 5. Raised her arms for balance more than six (6) inches away from her body on all counts. Notes *stumbled and lost balance. One Leg Stand Test (3/4 clues observed) The test was properly explained and demonstrated per the NHTSA SFST Manual. Hachem stated that she understood the instructions and how the test was to be performed. Left foot raised during the test. Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: Swayed body to the right and left. Raised arms more than six (6) inches from her side for balance. Left foot hit the ground one time. Seconds 11-20: Swayed body to the right and left. Raised arms more than six (6) inches from her side for balance. Left foot hit the ground two times. Seconds 21-30: Swayed body to the right and left. Left foot hit the ground two times. Notes * I am really sorry, I dont have the balance. Preliminary Breath Test:  I explained and offered a PBT to Hachem. Hachem elected to consent to the PBT and results were .19 BAC. Notes *While PBT was loading results, I asked again asked Hachem how many alcoholic beverages she had consumed, and she stated I had one beer. I asked her what kind of beer, and she stated it was IPA. I asked if it was a bottle or cup, and she stated one cup. I asked her around what time, and she stated it was two and half hours ago. ARREST  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Hachem was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol and was unable to operate a motor vehicle safely:  -Unable to stay within a single lane/driving patterns.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from vehicle.  -Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath as she conversed with me.  -Glassy and watery eyes.  - Stumbled and had difficulty maintaining balance.  -Her admissions to consuming alcoholic beverages prior to driving.  -Observed signs of impairment as she performed the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  - Preliminary Breath Test result of .19 BrAC.  Hachem was arrested for driving under the influence of alcohol and unable to operate a motor vehicle at 2257 hours. While securing her vehicle, Hachem exited my patrol vehicle and attempted to hide from me behind the Guardrail. Hachem was located and was transported to the Baltimore County Towson Precinct. While in transport, Hachem was crying and apologizing for trying to hide from me and stated I am really sorry, I was scared, I have never been in this situation. Hachem continued crying, begging me not to charge her, and stated I work for the Department of Defense, I have top secret clearance, so please give me a chance. Upon arrival at Precinct, Hachem was given a copy of the DR-15 Advice of Rights, and it was read to her from the MVA website in English, and she elected to consent to the Intoximeter EC/IR II test at 2344 hours. 20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Hachem at 2319 hours. She remained in my custody from that time. Nothing was introduced to her mouth at any time. A search revealed that she had nothing in her mouth. The test was conducted by OFC. Washburn Intox ID #585 of the Baltimore County Police Department on a certified instrument and Hachem failed to provide sufficient breath sample. The testing procedure was explained. During the test, Hachem bit the mouthpiece and failed to blow into the tube by blowing on the other side of her mouth. Hachem was given pertinent paperwork and released from the Precinct to a family member pending an appearance in the District Court of Maryland for Baltimore County at a later date.  All events occurred in Baltimore County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest.</NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 10:49:46</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>10/04/2023 19:01:14</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>H</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Wallace</LastName>
            <FirstName>Anthony</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6323</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>X</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>07</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MD324SP00</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Tankari</LastName>
            <FirstName>Idrissa</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7058</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>521190</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/09/2023 22:57:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 10:39:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 10:41:25</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>41</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 10:39:35</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 10:42:49</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>387710</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>M</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>HACHEM</LastName>
               <FirstName>SABINE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ALI</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/14/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/13/2023 10:15:39</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S150</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>HACHEM</LastName>
               <FirstName>SABINE</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>ALI</MiddleName>
               <DOB>07/14/1982 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>H250</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S150</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/13/2023 10:15:39</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>5920</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Cypress Springs</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Elkridge</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21075</Zip5>
               <Zip4>5479</Zip4>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.720113</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.216275</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>410</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>300</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>3981</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 10:42:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 10:42:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 10:42:49</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:25</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 10:39:59</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 10:39:59</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157059</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>OT</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7058</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/13/2023 10:49:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7058</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/13/2023 10:49:24</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/13/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>WDDSJ4GB2EN123819</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2014</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>MERZ</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>CLCLASS</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>4BR0682</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>9</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleValue>1000</VehicleValue>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>