<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-015148</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP2100</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/29/2023 00:36:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/29/2023 00:36:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/29/2023 00:29:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/29/2023 00:29:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>DUI</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/29/2023 00:36:57</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP4425</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>05/04/2023 13:24:25</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>692287</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/29/2023 00:36:58</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/29/2023 02:14:49</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>692287</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>14926</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>National</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>HWY</StreetTypeCode>
         <StreetSuffixCode>NW</StreetSuffixCode>
         <City>Cumberland</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-78.861556</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.640379</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/29/2023 00:36:56</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/29/2023 00:36:56</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>52</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>05/04/2023 10:47:28</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/29/2023 00:36:57</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>05/22/2023 18:30:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Attachments Include:  Digital Photographs DR-15 DR-15A Form 33 Results Photo copy of citations Photo copy of drivers license  This incident was captured on a body worn camera. Marked Maryland State Patrol vehicle C-36 is NOT equipped with a video recording device.  Certificates and Training *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration *Advanced Roadside Impairment Detection Enforcement certification  Narrative:  Phase 1: Vehicle in Motion   On 08/29/2023 at 0029 hours I, TFC DeMoss of the Maryland State Police Cumberland Barracks, was on routine patrol on RT 40 in the area of Braddock Run. I was operating marked patrol vehicle C36.  I was traveling WB on RT 40 toward Frostburg when I observed a vehicle heading EB on RT 40 toward LaVale at a high rate of speed. My radar unit activated and obtained a speed of 67 mph in a marked 50 mph zone. My radar was checked and working correctly at the beginning of shift and has been properly calibrated. I executed a U-turn and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle, a white Hyundai Elantra bearing Maryland registration 3DD4425, on EB RT 40 at 84 Lumber.  Phase 2: Personal Contact   I conducted a driver side approach to the vehicle and made contact with the driver, identified as Joshua Allan Nolan. Upon speaking with Nolan, I detected an odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. While speaking with Nolan I also observed Nolan to display glassy eyes. I asked Nolan where he was coming from this evening and Nolan stated he was coming from Lashbaughs West. I asked Nolan how many alcoholic beverages he had this evening and Nolan admitted to have 3 beers at Lashbaughs West. I returned to my vehicle and notified the barrack who I was out with and that Id have the driver out on Standardized Field Sobriety Testing (SFST). I returned to Nolan and asked him to step from the vehicle to perform SFSTs which Nolan agreed to do so. Upon speaking with Nolan at the front of Nolans vehicle, I detected an odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Nolans breath and person.  Phase 3: Pre-Arrest Screening  The evaluation was performed on the right shoulder of Rt 40 at 84 Lumber. The surface was dry, a grade downhill, and free of any major debris. The weather was clear and the area was lit from my emergency vehicle but not in a way that effected Nolan. Nolans clothing appeared to be dry and not soiled with any fluids or alcoholic beverages. I asked Nolan the following questions: *Contacts or Glasses: None * Injuries: None * Medication: None  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus (6/6 Clues observed)   The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. Nolans eyes were checked and his eyes displayed equal tracking and equal pupil size. Nolan was instructed to follow the stimulus with his eyes only, keeping his head still. After stating he understood the instructions, Nolan attempted the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test.  1) Lack of smooth pursuit  Present in both eyes 2) Distinct and sustained nystagmus at maximum deviation  Present in both eyes 3) Onset of nystagmus prior to 45 degrees  Present in both eyes  Walk and Turn (3/8 clues observed)  Prior to Nolan performing this test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Nolan was instructed to put his left foot on the straight, imaginary line and his right foot in front of it with his right heel touching the toe of his left foot. Nolan was instructed to stand in this manner with his hands to his sides until the test instructions were completed and test demonstrated. Nolan stood in the position instructed. Nolan was also instructed not to begin the test until told to start. Nolan was further instructed to take nine steps along the straight line in a heel to toe manner. After the ninth step he was to stop and turn around keeping his lead foot on the ground, taking several small steps with the other foot to turn around. After turning around he was to take nine steps in a heel-to-toe manner back along the line, in the direction he had come from. Nolan was further instructed to watch his feet at all times while walking, keep his arms down to his side, and to count his steps out loud and not to stop walking until he had completed the test. After the test was demonstrated, Nolan stated he understood the instructions and was instructed to begin the test.  Instructional Stage:    margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Nothing to report   Walking Stage (1st nine)     margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Stepped off line on step 5, 6 and 8   margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Missed heel to toe on step 5, 6 and 7   margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Stopped walking after first 9 steps   Walking Stage (2nd nine)     margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Missed heel to toe on steps 3   margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Stepped off line on step 3 and stumbled   Turn Unsatisfactory. After the first 9 steps, Nolan pivoted on the lead foot and reset himself in order to attempt the second set of 9 steps.  One Leg Stand (4/4)  Prior to Nolan performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Nolan was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down to his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. Nolan was instructed not to begin the test until he was instructed to start, and after the test had been demonstrated. When instructed to start, Nolan was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand one, one thousand two, one thousand three) and to continue the test until told to stop (30 seconds). After this test was demonstrated and indicating he understood the instructions, Nolan began the test.  Instructional Phase:     margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Nothing to report  Balance and Count Stage  Seconds 0-10     margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Sways   margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Used arms to maintain balance more than 6 inches from the body   Sways Seconds 11-20     margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Sways   margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Used arms to maintain balance more than 6 inches from the body   margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Put foot down on count 12, 17   margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Hops   Seconds 21-30     margin-bottom:1px; margin-left:8px"&gt;Unable to perform   On steps 14-17, Nolan began to hop multiple times in order to maintain balance. Nolan placed his foot down at 17 and for Nolans safety and the safety of traffic in the area, this test was concluded.  Based on the following, I had reason to suspect Nolan was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol:     margin-bottom:1px"&gt;Driving above the posted speed limit in inclimate weather   margin-bottom:1px"&gt;Glassy eyes   margin-bottom:1px"&gt;Admittance to drinking   margin-bottom:1px"&gt;An odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Nolans breath and person   margin-bottom:1px"&gt;My observed signs of impairment during SFSTs   I arrested Nolan for driving under the influence of alcohol at 0036 hours. Nolan was transported to the Maryland State Police Cumberland Barracks for processing. I detected an odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from Nolans breath and person throughout transport to the barrack. While at the barrack, Nolan was read his DR-15 Advice of Rights form and agreed to submit to a test of breath at 0053 hours. The sample was collected at 0106 hours with a result of 0.11 BrAC. Test administered by Cpl Schoenadel #4590 of the Maryland State Police Cumberland Barracks. Nolan was polite and cooperative throughout the entire process.  Case closed by Arrest.  All events occurred in Allegany County, Maryland.  </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>05/03/2023 10:19:26</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>05/03/2023 10:19:52</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Spicer</LastName>
            <FirstName>Phillip</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5513</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Langley</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>2726</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>52</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP2100</ORINumber>
            <LastName>DeMoss</LastName>
            <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6570</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>504567</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/29/2023 00:29:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/29/2023 02:15:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/29/2023 02:15:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>34</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>R</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/29/2023 02:22:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:52</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375612</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Nolan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Allan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/10/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/29/2023 02:21:57</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>N450</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Nolan</LastName>
               <FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Allan</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/10/1989 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>N450</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J200</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/29/2023 02:21:57</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>15001</StreetNumber>
               <StreetDirCode>SW</StreetDirCode>
               <StreetName>Winchester</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Cumberland</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21502</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>301</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>707</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>6891</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>04/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/29/2023 02:27:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6570</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/29/2023 02:27:09</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:48:57</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/29/2023 02:15:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/29/2023 02:15:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152460</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>AR</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6570</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/29/2023 02:27:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6570</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/29/2023 02:27:43</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/29/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>1</StatusCode>
         <VIN>KMHLR4AF6MU104998</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2021</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>HYUN</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>ELN</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>WHI</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>3DD4425</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>11</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>