<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-033167</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP3500</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>09/21/2023 16:44:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>09/21/2023 16:44:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>09/21/2023 15:56:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>09/21/2023 15:56:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Driving under the influence of alcohol.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 16:44:17</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP0507</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>10/30/2023 15:22:10</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>707610</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 16:44:18</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 19:14:35</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>707610</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>97.1</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I95 Nb</StreetName>
         <City>North East</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-75.999319</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.616246</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>09/21/2023 16:44:15</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>09/21/2023 16:44:15</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>62</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>09/28/2023 02:42:57</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>09/21/2023 16:44:17</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>10/27/2023 16:44:56</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Date of arrest: 9/21/2023  Time: 1633  Weather: clear  Location: N/B I95 @ 97.1 mile marker  Patrol vehicle: M-13  Camera: This stop was captured audibly and visually on M-13 in-car/body worn camera.  Defendant: Morgan Sophie Hickman (Dob 7/12/1999)  New Jersey drivers license: H-41075638257992  Subsequent offender: unknown  DWI #:23-079  Field sobriety: HGN 6/6 clues (Vertical Nystagmus present)  WAT: 7/8 clues  OlS: unable to perform  -TRAINING/CERTIFICATES- I am trained by the Maryland State Police and the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration to administer standardized field sobriety tests. I am certified as a RADAR/LIDAR operator through the Maryland State Police. I am a certified Preliminary Breath Test operator through the Maryland State Police. I am trained in Advanced Roadside Impairment Detection Enforcement through the Maryland State Police.  -DESCRIPTION OF VIOLATION / TRAFFIC STOP (VEHICLE IN MOTION phase 1): On 9/21/2023, I TFC Caraway #6565 was dispatched to N/B Interstate 95 @ the 97.1 mile marker in reference to a disabled vehicle. The barrack was also informed by a courtesy patrol unit that the operator appeared to clearly be intoxicated. Upon my arrival, I observed a red Ford van not bearing any registration with the operator later identified by her New Jersey drivers license as Morgan Sophie Hickman (Dob 7/12/1999). I then made contact with the witnesses identified as Samuel K Easterling (Dob 04/12/1978) and Molly Theresa Irrgang (Dob 10/16/1997). While speaking with the witnesses they advised that they were traveling behind the Ford Van in lane 1 when they observed the vehicle swerving all over the roadway and onto the shoulder almost striking the guardrail multiple times. Easterling and Irrgang stated that they noticed the vehicle starting to smoke from the hood at which time the Ford Van pulled onto the left shoulder. After pulling onto the shoulder Easterling and Irrgang pulled over with the vehicle to check on the operator. Both Easterling and Irrgang observed Hickman being the operator and sole occupant in the vehicle. They continued to explain that while speaking with Hickman they smelled the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. Another witness identified as Hunter Burton (Dob 2/16/2004) advised that he also witnessed Hickman pull over onto the shoulder placing the vehicle in park. Burton continued to explain that Hickman walked over to him and while speaking he could smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath.   Personal contact (phase 2): After speaking with the witnesses, I made contact with Hickman. While speaking with Hickman, I immediately detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath and person. Hickmans eyes were bloodshot/ glassy and had slurred speech. Hickman stated that she just purchased the vehicle in Maryland and was driving back to New Jersey. Hickman admitted to operating the vehicle an being the sole occupant in the vehicle. A check through the barrack revealed that the Ford van was not registered or insured. When asked how many drinks she had prior to driving, Hickman initially stated that she had 2 glasses of wine approximately 6 hours ago. When asked again about her alcohol intake she advised that she was coming from a bar in downtown Baltimore. She stated that while at the bar she had a couple of mixed drinks and a beer (Blue Moon) mixed with vodka. When asked on a scale of 1 through 10, 1 being the lowest and 10 being the highest, how intoxicated would she say she was Hickman stated a rating of 4. Hickman also stated that she can still feel the alcohol in her. Hickman had slurred speech and her mood would fluctuate. Hickman advised that she took medication for Schizophrenia at 6 am however knows that she is not supposed to consume alcohol with it. Due the above listed indicators and witness statements, Hickman was asked to perform standardized field sobriety which she agreed to do so. Hickman refused to the preliminary breath test.  Pre-arrest screen (Phase 3): The evaluation was performed on the side of the road on a dry level surface free from any debris or obstructions. The emergency front lights of the patrol unit were deactivated. Hickman was wearing a leg brace and advised that she had multiple surgeries on her leg. Hickman advised that she does not wear eye glasses or contacts.  Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus: (6/6 clues observed)  The first test was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as a stimulus and held approximately 12 inches from Hickmans face, slightly above eye level. She was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping her head still while following and focusing on the tip of the pen with her eyes only until told to stop. Hickman pupils were equal in size and showed equal tracking and no resting Nystagmus was observed. She was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Hickman if she understood the instructions and she stated, Yes.  Walk and Turn: (7/8 clues observed)  The second test was the Walk and Turn test. Prior to Hickman performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Hickman was instructed to place her left foot on an imaginary line directly in front of her. She was then advised to place her right foot directly in front of her left foot touching heel to toe. Hickman was instructed to place her hands flat at her side and to remain in the position until told to begin. Hickman was advised to take a series of nine steps on that imaginary straight-line touching heel to toe on every step. She was to keep her hands flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and count every step aloud. I explained that on her ninth step, keep her left foot planted on the line, and to take a series of small steps with her right foot returning back to the line. Hickman was explained the second series of steps were to be performed identical to the first series. Hickman had to be instructed multiple times to return back to the starting position. After completely explaining and demonstrating the test to Hickman she stated that she completely understood the instructions and did not have any questions.  During Hickmans first series of the Walk and Turn, she took a total of 16 steps. After completing the first series of steps she advised that she took 15 steps. Hickman missed heel to toe on step 8. During Hickmans second series of steps she took a total of 19 steps. When asked how many steps she took after completing the second series she advised 11 steps. Hickman missed heel to toe on steps 4,6,15,18 and 19. She stepped off of the line on steps 4, 6 and 15. Hickman used her arms for balance during the first series raising them more than 6 inches away from her side. During her second series she stopped while walking on step 4.  One leg Stand: Unable to perform.  Hickman was offered to take a Preliminary breath test which she initially agreed to do so. While going to retrieve the instrument, Hickman stated, Wait I think Im drunk! while laughing. She then started walking away from me towards her vehicle at which time I stopped her and she asked if she could call her mother. Hickman starting to become agitated and stated that she does not want to take the preliminary breath test. Due to the above indicators, SFST clues, witness statements and consumption admissions, Hickman was placed under arrest for driving under the influence at 1633 hours. While trying to retrieve her necessities (Cell phone/ wallet), assisting Troopers located a near empty bottle of Deep Eddy vodka located in her purse on the floorboard next to the drivers seat within her reach. While transporting Hickman to the Maryland State Police JFK Highway barracks she began to become irate yelling and screaming. I attempted to play the audio version of the DR-15 with a copy placed on her lap for her to read along. Hickman continued yelling and screaming and refused to listen to the audio. While trying to get Hickman to calm down, she kicked my mobile laptop in my patrol vehicle slamming it shut.  After arriving at the JFK Highway barracks for processing she continued to be irate and uncooperative. Hickman was read the DR-15 in its entirety which she refused at 1700 hours.  After being placed in the holding cell for processing, Hickman continued to kick and scream while banging on the door and yelling racial and provocative words. While doing a routine check of Hickman in the holding cell, she bounced up from the concrete bench screaming racial slurs ran towards the door way and attempted to exit the cell at which time TFC McDonald #7117 blocked the doorway using his body. While blocking her from exiting she then spit on TFC McDonalds face and uniform (See attached photos). While being held in the holding cell, Hickman defecated and smeared on the cell floor, and took her shirt off exposing her breast. After Defecating on the floor Hickman stated, I dont have to clean it up, you do!. Hickman also stated, Ill be out tomorrow so I dont give a Fuck!. She continued with, My mom is a lawyer all of this will get dropped.   Hickman was charged with several traffic charges including driving under the influence and 2nd degree assault on a police officer.  After being charged I requested the Cecil county Sheriffs office to respond to the JFK Highway barracks with a cage car due to her irate and violent behavior. Hickman was later transported the Cecil county commissioners office for a hearing. While at the commissioners office waiting to be heard, Hickman continued her irate behavior yelling provocative language at the commissioner. After being warned by the commissioner to stop, Hickman continued the behavior and kicked the table over knocking miscellaneous item off at which time the commissioner issued her a temporary commitment at the Cecil county Detention center. Due to her violent behavior and having assaulting a police officer I put a spit mask over her head to prevent her from further assaulting anyone. Hickman was transported by the Cecil county Sheriffs office to the detention center where she was held.  All event occurred in Cecil county Maryland. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:09:49</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6565</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/28/2023 01:57:27</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>McDonald</LastName>
            <FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7117</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Warble</LastName>
            <FirstName>Richard</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6762</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Harten</LastName>
            <FirstName>Steven</FirstName>
            <InternalID>1581</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>62</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP3500</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Caraway</LastName>
            <FirstName>Isaac</FirstName>
            <InternalID>6565</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522622</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/21/2023 15:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:15:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6565</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 19:15:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>522622</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>1 1416</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>25</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>09/21/2023 15:56:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>1 1416</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:44:19</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6565</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 19:44:19</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>24</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>O</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:19:06</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6565</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/28/2023 01:42:08</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388569</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Hickman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Morgan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Sophie</MiddleName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 19:17:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>H255</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M625</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Hickman</LastName>
               <FirstName>Morgan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Sophie</MiddleName>
               <SLastName>H255</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M625</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 19:17:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 01:42:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 01:42:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/28/2023 01:42:08</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>25</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:21:48</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 19:21:48</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388570</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Irrgang</LastName>
               <FirstName>Molly</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Theresa</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/16/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 19:21:39</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>I625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M400</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Irrgang</LastName>
               <FirstName>Molly</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Theresa</MiddleName>
               <DOB>10/16/1997 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>I625</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>M400</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 19:21:39</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>226</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Old Farmington</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>North East</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-75.96479092569372</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.64509251825816</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>610</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>781</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>9070</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:21:48</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:28</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>45</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:23:52</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 19:23:52</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388571</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Easterling</LastName>
               <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>K</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/12/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 19:23:45</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>E236</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S540</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Easterling</LastName>
               <FirstName>Samuel</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>K</MiddleName>
               <DOB>04/12/1978 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>E236</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>S540</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 19:23:45</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:23:52</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>19</ApproxAge>
         <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:25:40</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 19:25:40</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388572</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Burton</LastName>
               <FirstName>Hunter</FirstName>
               <DOB>02/16/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 19:25:34</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>B635</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H536</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Burton</LastName>
               <FirstName>Hunter</FirstName>
               <DOB>02/16/2004 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>B635</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>H536</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 19:25:34</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>W</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:25:40</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:26</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>00</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>U</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:48:05</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 19:48:05</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>388575</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>W</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>McDonald</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trooper First Class</FirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 19:46:37</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>M235</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T616</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>McDonald</LastName>
               <FirstName>Trooper First Class</FirstName>
               <SLastName>M235</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>T616</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 19:46:37</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetName>TURNPIKE</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>DR</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>PERRYVILLE</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <Longitude>-76.06826595381345</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.59575304151666</Latitude>
               <SubBeat>624</SubBeat>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>VPO</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:48:05</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:18</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:15:17</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6565</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 19:15:17</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>157379</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP6565</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>09/23/2023 19:27:34</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP6565</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>09/23/2023 19:27:34</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>09/23/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1DFEE755688720478</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>1994</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>FORD</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>RED</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>N/A</VehicleLicNumber>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>