<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-014238</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0400</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>04/22/2023 03:37:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>04/22/2023 03:37:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>04/22/2023 03:12:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>04/22/2023 03:12:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>Traffic stop leading to driver being arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 03:37:20</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP5364</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 11:52:15</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <IncAddrComment>2 MM I270 SB, BETHESDA</IncAddrComment>
      <AddressId>691572</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 03:37:21</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 23:36:04</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>691572</AddressId>
         <StreetNumber>2</StreetNumber>
         <StreetName>Mm I270 Sb Bethesda</StreetName>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-77.1402228333333</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.0332831666667</Latitude>
         <AddressCommonName>
            <CommonPlaceName>FROM CALIBER MOBILE</CommonPlaceName>
         </AddressCommonName>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>04/22/2023 03:37:16</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>04/22/2023 03:37:16</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>63</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>04/25/2023 02:05:23</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>NOT REPORTABLE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>04/22/2023 03:37:20</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 02:05:23</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>MSP marked vehicle N-36 is equipped with a mobile recording device.  Defendant: Juan Carlos Chu Che Date of Birth: 05/12/1985 Date of Arrest: 04/22/2023 Time of Arrest: 0336 hours DUI #: 23-092 SUBSEQUENT OFFENDER  CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING *Trained in administering standardized field sobriety tests through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *Trained in administering advanced standardized field sobriety tests (ARIDE) through the Maryland State Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. *Trained in detection and administering advanced standardized field sobriety tests for Cannabis Intoxication through the Montgomery County Police and National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) On April 22, 2023 at approximately 0312 hours, I, Trooper Lear #7154, was on duty in official capacity as a Maryland State Trooper operating marked MSP vehicle N-36 in Bethesda, Montgomery County, Maryland. I was traveling northbound on I-270 at MD Rt. 187 when I observed a black Ram 1500 failing to maintain a single lane. The Ram crossed into lane one from lane two by more than a tires width on one occasion. Traffic was light and no other vehicle forced the Ram to change lanes. I activated my emergency equipment and conducted a traffic stop on the vehicle. The vehicle was further identified as a black Ram 1500 bearing MD registration 2EX9914.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2) I approached the vehicle and made contact with the driver. When I made contact with the driver, I detected a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from the vehicle. I immediately observed the drivers eyes to be bloodshot and glassy with a glazed look. The driver was identified by his MD drivers license as Juan Carlos Chu Che (DOB: 05/12/1985, H/M). I returned to my patrol vehicle to conduct routine checks on Chu Che. During my routine check of Chu Che, I noticed that Chu Che had one prior DUI in 2011. Montgomery County Police Officer Lanham #2871 arrived on scene to provide back up. I advised the Rockville Barrack that I would be on field sobriety. When I asked Chu Che to exit the Ram, his body movements were slow and lethargic. Chu Che was struggling to walk and maintain his balance. Chu Che admitted to consuming six to eight Heineken beers at his employment in Fairfax, VA. During field sobriety, Chu Che wanted to give me his keys to the truck. Chu Che advised me that I was going to fail him. Chu Che advised me that he was going to fail as well. I later observed Chu Ches zipper to his jeans was unzipped.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3) The evaluation was attempted in front of the Ram 1500 on the right shoulder of northbound I-270 north of Rockledge Drive, Bethesda, MD. The surface was dry, slight down hill grade, and free from any obvious debris. The weather was clear and approximately 60 degrees. Lighting conditions consisted of light illuminating from light poles and my patrol vehicles headlights. Chu Che appeared to be in good physical condition and did not display any visible injuries that would prevent him from walking or standing.  I asked Chu Che the following questions: - Injuries  No - Medication  No - Medical Conditions  No - Glasses/Contacts  Prescription glasses were being worn  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed) The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus and held approximately 12 to 15 inches from Chu Ches eyes. He was instructed to look straight ahead, keeping his head still while following and focusing on the tip of the stimulus with his eyes until told to stop. Chu Ches pupils were equal in size, showed equal tracking, and no resting Nystagmus was observed. He was positioned in a manner to ensure the headlights of passing traffic would not interfere with the test results. I asked Chu Che if he understood the instructions and he stated, Yes. I had to ask Chu Che to follow the stimulus on nine occasions throughout the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus test. Chu Che was observed swaying to the left and right side throughout the test as well.  Lack of Smooth Pursuit  Present in both eyes Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation  Present in both eyes Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 degrees  Present in both eyes  WALK AND TURN (4/8 clues observed) Prior to Chu Che performing the test, I properly examined and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Chu Che was instructed to place his right foot directly in front of his left foot and touch heel to toe. Chu Che was instructed and demonstrated to place his hands flat at his sides and to remain in the position until told to begin. Chu Che was advised to take nine (9) steps in a straight line touching heel to toe on every step. Chu Che was to keep his hands flat at his side, keep his eyes focused on his feet, and count every step aloud. On the ninth step, Chu Che was explained and demonstrated to keep his lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps around with his rear foot to turn completely around. Chu Che was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identically to the first series. Chu Che was instructed that once he began the test that he was not to stop walking until the test was completed, keep his hands down by his side, look at his feet, and count each step out loud. I asked Chu Che if he understood the test and he stated, Yes. Footwear: sneakers. Chu Che removed his sneakers to perform the test.  Instructional Stage: -Could not keep balance- on two (2) occasions.  Walking Stage (1st Nine): -Stepped off the line on all nine (9) steps. -Missed heal to toe contact on all nine (9) steps. -Stopped walking between the turn and the second series of nine (9) steps.  Turn: -Completed satisfactorily.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): -Stepped off the line on all nine (9) steps. -Missed heal to toe contact on all nine (9) steps.  ONE LEG STAND (1/4 clues observed) Prior to Chu Che performing the test, I properly explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted. Chu Che was instructed to stand with his heels together and hands down by his sides while the instructions were given and during the test. When instructed to start, he was to raise the foot of his choice off the ground approximately 6 inches. While his leg was raised, he was to keep his leg straight, watch his raised foot, count out loud by thousands (one-thousand one, one-thousand two), and continue the test until told to stop. I asked Chu Che if he understood the test and he stated, Yes. Chu Che chose to raise his right foot. Footwear: sneakers. Chu Che removed his sneakers to perform the test.  Instructional Stage: -Nothing to report.  Balance and Count Stage: Seconds 0-10: -Puts foot down throughout the time frame.  Seconds 11-20: -Puts foot down throughout the time frame.  Seconds 21-30: -Puts foot down throughout the time frame.  Chu Che attempted to raise his right foot on three (3) occasions during a time frame of thirty-five (35) seconds.  Based on the following, I had reason to believe Chu Che was driving a motor vehicle under the influence of alcohol: -Unable to maintain designated lane direction. -The strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emanating from his breath and person. -Eyes were glassy and bloodshot with a glazed look. -Body movements were slow and lethargic. -Mumbled and slurred speech. -Struggling to walk and maintain balance. -Admitting to potentially failing field sobriety. -Admission to consuming six to eight Heineken beers at his employment that night. -Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus  6/6 clues observed -Walk and Turn  4/8 clues observed -One Leg Stand  1/4 clues observed  I arrested Chu Che for driving under the influence of alcohol at approximately 0336 hours and performed a search incident to arrest. Chu Che was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicle and transported to the Rockville Barrack for processing. After arriving at the barrack, I gave Chu Che a copy of the DR-15 form in English to review while I played the entire form in English audio to him in the barrack. Chu Che signed the DR-15 at approximately 0404 hours, agreeing to submit to the intoximeter test.  20-MINUTE OBSERVATION PERIOD: I conducted the 20-minute observation period with Chu Che beginning with his arrest. A preliminary search of Chu Che was conducted on the scene and it revealed that he had nothing in his mouth. I observed Chu Che from the time of the arrest until the time he submitted to the test and he did not put anything in his mouth. The test was conducted by Cpl. Moore #5995 of the Maryland State Police on a certified instrument. Chu Ches breath specimen was found to contain an alcohol concentration of .21 grams of alcohol per 210 liters of breath. Chu Che was relayed back to his residents by me.  All events occurred in Montgomery County, Maryland. CASE CLOSED BY ARREST. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 01:38:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 01:39:46</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Moore</LastName>
            <FirstName>Tyler</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5995</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>63</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0400</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Lear</LastName>
            <FirstName>Quinn</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7154</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503652</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19739</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/22/2023 03:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19739</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 23:37:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 23:38:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503652</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16357</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/22/2023 03:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16357</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 23:38:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 23:38:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503652</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/22/2023 03:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 23:39:41</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 23:39:41</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503652</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>4</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>19743</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>4</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/22/2023 03:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>19743</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 23:40:24</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 23:40:24</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503652</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>5</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15664</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>5</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/22/2023 03:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15664</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 23:41:07</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 23:41:07</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503652</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>6</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>6</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/22/2023 03:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 23:41:55</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 23:41:55</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>503652</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>7</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>00</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>15560</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>7</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>04/22/2023 03:36:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>15560</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 23:42:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 23:42:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>37</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>C</ResidentStatusCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 00:18:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:53</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>375226</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>H</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>M</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>H</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Chu Che</LastName>
               <FirstName>Juan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Carlos</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/12/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>04/24/2023 23:22:07</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Chu Che</LastName>
               <FirstName>Juan</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Carlos</MiddleName>
               <DOB>05/12/1985 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C200</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>J500</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>04/24/2023 23:22:07</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>130</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Duvall</StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>LN</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Gaithersburg</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>20877</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
            </PersonAddress>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>DR</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 00:18:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>O</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 00:18:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 00:18:37</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:01</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/24/2023 23:37:43</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/24/2023 23:37:43</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>152319</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7154</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>04/25/2023 00:19:20</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7154</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>04/25/2023 00:19:20</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>04/24/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>12</StatusCode>
         <VIN>1C6SRFFT3NN146400</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2022</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>RAM</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>150</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>BLK</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>2EX9914</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2023</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>12</VehicleLicMonth>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>