<Incident xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="file:///C:/DATA/EJS/SVN_Root/Ejustice/trunk/XMLTransformations/OnlineRMSInternalToIncident/IAOnlineRMSIncidentImport.xsd">
   <IncidentReportNum>23-MSP-022425</IncidentReportNum>
   <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
   <ORINum>MDMSP0200</ORINum>
   <ReportDate>06/22/2023 17:12:00</ReportDate>
   <ReportTime>06/22/2023 17:12:00</ReportTime>
   <StartDate>06/22/2023 16:37:00</StartDate>
   <StartTime>06/22/2023 16:37:00</StartTime>
   <Summary>The suspect was arrested for DUI/DWI.</Summary>
   <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
   <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 17:12:48</CreatorDate>
   <UpdatorId>MSP2523</UpdatorId>
   <UpdatorDate>07/17/2023 13:58:01</UpdatorDate>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DUI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentType>
      <IncidentTypeCode>DWI</IncidentTypeCode>
   </IncidentType>
   <IncidentAddress>
      <AddressId>698590</AddressId>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 17:12:49</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 18:56:39</UpdatorDate>
      <Address>
         <AddressId>698590</AddressId>
         <StreetDirCode>S</StreetDirCode>
         <StreetName>New Washington Rd @ Hook</StreetName>
         <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
         <City>Westminster</City>
         <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
         <Zip5>21157</Zip5>
         <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
         <Longitude>-76.98809</Longitude>
         <Latitude>39.544272</Latitude>
      </Address>
   </IncidentAddress>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>0</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/22/2023 17:12:37</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/22/2023 17:12:37</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/15/2023 22:58:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 17:12:48</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:25</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Original Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>In car camera (G-12) and BWC fully operational at time of incident.  Defendant: Lorraine Jebet Chebon Date of Birth: 09/20/1979 Date of Arrest: 06/22/2023 Time of Arrest: 1709 Maryland DL: MD-10272082318 DUI #: 23-104 Officers Training/Experience * Trained in administering Standardized Field Sobriety Tests through the Maryland State Police. * Trained and certified to operate Radar and Lidar through the Maryland State Police. *Repeat Offender*No  VEHICLE IN MOTION (PHASE 1) Not observed.  PERSONAL CONTACT (PHASE 2)   On 06/22/2023 at approximately 1639 hours, I (TFC J. Reid #7215) responded to the area of Southbound New Washington Rd (MD 97) in the area of Hook Rd for the report of a vehicle parked in the ditch next to the road with the driver unconscious behind the wheel. EMS personnel was also dispatched to the scene due to the possibility of it being a medical emergency. While I was still en route to the scene, I was advised over the radio that Fire and EMS personnel are on scene and the vehicle drove away. Several moments later, I was advised that the vehicle had returned to the scene.  Upon my arrival, I observed a silver Nissan Pathfinder bearing Maryland registration 8CE9253 parked on the right shoulder, still running, with a black female in the drivers seat. A firefighter approached me and advised he believed he could smell the odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath. EMS advised they checked the drivers blood sugar and advised her blood sugar was normal eliminating the possibility of a diabetic emergency. I walked to the drivers side window and made contact with the female driver/sole occupant who stated she is recording me on her phone. I advised the driver of my name and ID number and asked her for her drivers license. The driver eventually complied. I was able to positively identify the driver by the photograph on her Maryland drivers license as, Lorraine Jebet Chebon (B/F DOB: 09/20/1979. I asked Chebon where she was coming from and where she was going to. Chebon advised she was coming from her boyfriends house and going back to her house in Owings Mills, Maryland. While speaking with Chebon, I detected the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from her breath, and observed her eyes to be bloodshot and watery, and observed her to have slurred speech. I asked Chebon if she has had anything to drink, and she stated, No. While speaking with Chebon, her behavior quickly escalated into her yelling and screaming and beginning to cry. Due to her slurred speech, I could not understand what she was saying. I asked Chebon if she was willing to perform the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests, and she continued to yell and cry. Chebon eventually agreed to submit to the standardized Field Sobriety Tests.  PRE-ARREST SCREENING (PHASE 3)  The test and evaluation was performed on the side of New Washington Rd (MD 97).   Prior to the test being conducted, I asked Chebon the following questions:   Medical Conditions: She stated she has down syndrome.  Injuries: None.  Medication: She stated she takes blood pressure medication but did not advise what kind of blood pressure medication.   While speaking with Chebon, I continued to smell the strong odor of an alcoholic beverage emitting from her breath, and I again observed her eyes to bloodshot and watery, and her to be slurring her speech. Chebon was very emotional and did not pay attention to the instructions I gave to her. Chebon swayed back and fourth when she did stand still. Chebon continued to yell and scream incoherently while crying despite my efforts at verbally de-escalating her.  HORIZONTAL GAZE NYSTAGMUS (6/6 clues observed)  The first test given was the Horizontal Gaze Nystagmus Test. Prior to the test being conducted, I properly explained how the test should be conducted. The tip of my pen was used as the stimulus. The stimulus was held approximately 12 inches from Chebons eyes. I instructed Chebon to follow and focus on the tip of the stimulus with her eyes and her eyes only, and to keep her head completely still. I asked Chebon if she understood the test and the instructions. Chebon said what do you want from me? I again asked Chebon if she understood the test and my instructions and she eventually said, yes. Chebons eyes were equal in size, and showed equal tracking with no resting Nystagmus. Test Results:  Lack of Smooth Pursuit - Present in both Eyes  Distinct and Sustained Nystagmus at Maximum Deviation - Present in both eyes.  Onset of Nystagmus Prior to 45 Degrees - Present in both eyes.  Vertical Nystagmus  Present in both eyes. Chebon had to be advised to keep her head still and follow the stimulus with her eyes and her eyes only after the test had begun.   WALK AND TURN (6/8)  I advised Chebon the next test is the walk and turn test. Prior to Chebon performing the test, I explained and demonstrated how the test should be conducted.The solid white line on the side of the road was used for the test. I instructed Chebon to place her left foot on the line and then to placeher right foot directly in front of her left foot, touching heel to toe. Chebon began yelling incoherently and was not listening to my instructions. After several minutes of getting her to calm down again, she eventually complied with my instructions, however, she did not stay in the instructional position and had to be told several times to stay in the position I explained to her and to pay attention. She was then instructedto place her arms flat at her sides. Iadvised Chebon this was theinstructionalposition and she was not to begin the test until I specifically instructed her to do so. Chebon again began crying and I had to stop giving her instructions in order to get her to calm down again. I advised Colman when I instructed her to begin, she was to take nine (9) heel to toe steps on the line. She was instructed to keep her arms flat at her sides, keep her eyes focused on her feet, and to count every step out loud. I then explained and demonstrated to Chebon on the ninth step, she was to keep her lead foot on the line and to take a series of small steps with her rear foot to turn completely around. Chebon was again explained and demonstrated the second series of nine (9) steps were to be performed identical to the first series. She was again instructed to keep her arms down by her sides, look down at her feet, and count each step out loud. Before I could finish explaining the test, Chebon again started screaming incoherently and crying. I continued explaining and demonstrating the test to Chebon. At the conclusion of giving her instructions, I asked Chebon if she understood the test and my instructions, and she stated, yes.  Instructional Stage: Chebon repeatedly removed her feet from the instructional position despite being told to remain in that position. Chebon started walking too soon before I instructed her to begin.  Walking Stage (1st Nine): Chebon took 6 steps stopped walking, stepped completely off the line and started yelling and crying again. Chebon stated she wanted to restart the test and then did not do the test again. She continued to mumble incoherently. Miss heel to toe on step - 5 Turn:  Turn not performed.  Walking Stage (2nd Nine): Chebon did not finish the test.  ONE LEG STAND (1/4 clues observed) Prior to Chebon performing the test, Iproperly explained and demonstrated how the test should be performed. Chebon was instructed to stand with her heels and toes together, and to place her arms down by her sides. I explainedto Chebon when I instructed her to begin, she was to raise the foot of her choice off of the ground by approximately 6 inches. I explained and demonstrated while her leg was raised she was to keep her leg straight, point her toe, look down at her raised foot, and to count out loud by thousands (one thousand-one, one thousand-two) and to continue the test until instructedto stop. I asked Chebon if she understood the test and the instructions, and she stated, What do you want me to do? I again explained and demonstrated the test to Chebon. I asked her if she was paying attention and she started the test before I instructed her to begin. I instructed Chebon to wait to start the test until I instructed her to begin.  Balance and Count Stage:  Chebon picked up her right foot and started counting. Chebon counted to two, and put her foot down. Chebon the raised her left foot and began counting again. Chebon put her foot down again and then raised her right foot again and started counting. Chebon then put her foot down and started to stumble backwards. Chebon then raised her right foot again, raised her arms for balance and started counting. Chebon put her foot down again.  While on scene, Chebon submitted to a preliminary breath test with a result of .16 BrAC. M/Tpr Fair administered the preliminary breath test. See M/Tpr Fairs supplement for further information.  ARREST  Based on the following,Ihad reason to believe Chebon was driving a motor vehicle under the influence: 1) Strong odor of an alcoholic beverage coming from her breath. 2) Bloodshot and glassy eyes. 3) Stumbling while walking. 4) Slurred Speech. 5) Clues during field sobriety testing.   Due to my numerous observations, I concluded Chebon had been driving under the influence, and was unable to operate a vehicle safely. At approximately 1709hours, I placed Chebon under arrest for driving while under the influence. Chebon was placed in the front passenger seat of my patrol vehicleper MSP policy.The entire time Chebon continued to yell and scream and cry.  Chebon was subsequently transported to the Maryland State Police Westminster Barrack for processing. While at the Westminster Barrack, Chebon was played the English version of the DR-15 Advice of Rights audio from the MVAs website and provided a copy in English to read over. Chebon talked the entire time the DR-15 advice of rights audio was being played. Chebon signed the DR-15 Advice of Rights form andagreed to submit to the Intoximeter Test. Before the intoximeter test could be conducted, Chebon grabbed and ripped up the Dr-15 form. Chebon became extremely agitated and when I told her to calm down, she started apologizing. A new Dr-15 form was given to Chebon which she signed again and again agreed to submit to the intoximeter test at approximately 1744 hours.  INTOXIMETER RESULT: ***.23 BrAC***  Chebon was charged with Driving Under the Influence or Alcohol, Driving While Impaired by Alcohol, and Negligent Driving. Chebon was given copies of all pertinent paperwork and released into the custody of a sober driver.  All events occurred in Carroll County, Maryland.  Case closed by arrest. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 20:48:22</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>07/11/2023 14:15:58</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>FAIR</LastName>
            <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5334</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Horner</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jonathan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5895</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>A</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Frye</LastName>
            <FirstName>Ryan</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7198</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Karas</LastName>
            <FirstName>Michael</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5562</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Reid</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jason</FirstName>
            <InternalID>7215</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511861</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>1</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>16356</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>1</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/22/2023 16:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>16356</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 18:58:28</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 18:58:28</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511861</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>2</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>14583</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <CSAUCode>C</CSAUCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>2</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/22/2023 16:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <AttemptedCompletedCode>C</AttemptedCompletedCode>
         <ArrestChargeCode>14583</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 18:58:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 18:58:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentOffense>
         <IncidentId>511861</IncidentId>
         <OffenseNumber>3</OffenseNumber>
         <OffenseStatusCode>02</OffenseStatusCode>
         <OffenseCode>21334</OffenseCode>
         <PlaceCode>13</PlaceCode>
         <BiasCode>88</BiasCode>
         <SupplementSeq>0</SupplementSeq>
         <UCRNumber>3</UCRNumber>
         <OffenseStatusDate>06/22/2023 16:37:00</OffenseStatusDate>
         <ArrestChargeCode>21334</ArrestChargeCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 18:58:29</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 18:58:29</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentOffense>
      <IncidentPerson>
         <ApproxAge>43</ApproxAge>
         <ResidentStatusCode>S</ResidentStatusCode>
         <ClearMultiArrestCode>N</ClearMultiArrestCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 19:10:03</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>08/01/2023 01:56:58</UpdatorDate>
         <Person>
            <PersonId>380558</PersonId>
            <RaceCode>B</RaceCode>
            <SexCode>F</SexCode>
            <EthnicityCode>N</EthnicityCode>
            <PersonVerified>Y</PersonVerified>
            <PersonPrimaryName>
               <LastName>Chebon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lorraine</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jebet</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/20/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <DateOfInfo>06/22/2023 19:09:09</DateOfInfo>
               <SLastName>C150</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L650</SFirstName>
            </PersonPrimaryName>
            <Alias>
               <NameTypeCode>P</NameTypeCode>
               <LastName>Chebon</LastName>
               <FirstName>Lorraine</FirstName>
               <MiddleName>Jebet</MiddleName>
               <DOB>09/20/1979 00:00:00</DOB>
               <SLastName>C150</SLastName>
               <SFirstName>L650</SFirstName>
               <DateOfInfo>06/22/2023 19:09:09</DateOfInfo>
            </Alias>
            <PersonAddress>
               <StreetNumber>9701</StreetNumber>
               <StreetName>Sherwood Farm </StreetName>
               <StreetTypeCode>RD</StreetTypeCode>
               <City>Owings Mills</City>
               <StateCode>MD</StateCode>
               <Zip5>21117</Zip5>
               <CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
               <CountyCode>NaN</CountyCode>
               <Longitude>-76.819646</Longitude>
               <Latitude>39.408831</Latitude>
            </PersonAddress>
            <PersonPhone>
               <PhoneTypeCode>CEL</PhoneTypeCode>
               <PhoneArea>443</PhoneArea>
               <PhonePrefix>362</PhonePrefix>
               <PhoneSuffix>8062</PhoneSuffix>
               <DateOfInfo>06/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
            </PersonPhone>
         </Person>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>A</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/23/2023 17:52:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
         <IncidentPersonRole>
            <RoleType>S</RoleType>
            <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
            <CreatorDate>06/23/2023 17:52:56</CreatorDate>
            <UpdatorId>MSP</UpdatorId>
            <UpdatorDate>12/05/2023 01:49:10</UpdatorDate>
         </IncidentPersonRole>
      </IncidentPerson>
      <IncidentBusiness>
         <BusinessNumber>240000001</BusinessNumber>
         <BusinessName>SOCIETY</BusinessName>
         <IncBusinessRoleCode>V</IncBusinessRoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/23/2023 17:50:37</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/23/2023 17:50:37</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentBusiness>
      <IncidentVehicle>
         <VEHICLE_ID>154428</VEHICLE_ID>
         <RoleCode>SU</RoleCode>
         <CreatorId>MSP7215</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/22/2023 19:18:00</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP7215</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/22/2023 19:18:00</UpdatorDate>
         <DateOfInfo>06/22/2023 00:00:00</DateOfInfo>
         <StatusCode>16</StatusCode>
         <VIN>5N1AR2MM3DC638505</VIN>
         <VehicleYear>2013</VehicleYear>
         <VehicleMakeCode>NISS</VehicleMakeCode>
         <VehicleModelCode>PATHFINDER</VehicleModelCode>
         <VehicleTypeCode>AT</VehicleTypeCode>
         <VehPriColorCode>SIL</VehPriColorCode>
         <VehSecColorCode>SIL</VehSecColorCode>
         <VehicleLicStateCode>MD</VehicleLicStateCode>
         <VehicleLicNumber>8CE9253</VehicleLicNumber>
         <VehicleLicYear>2024</VehicleLicYear>
         <VehicleLicMonth>1</VehicleLicMonth>
         <VehicleLicTypeCode>PC</VehicleLicTypeCode>
      </IncidentVehicle>
   </IncidentSupplement>
   <IncidentSupplement>
      <SupplementSequence>1</SupplementSequence>
      <IncSupplementStatusCode>A</IncSupplementStatusCode>
      <SuppReportDate>06/23/2023 08:59:08</SuppReportDate>
      <SuppReportTime>06/23/2023 08:59:08</SuppReportTime>
      <AgencyOnly>N</AgencyOnly>
      <SecurityLevel>1100</SecurityLevel>
      <SuppAgencyCode>56</SuppAgencyCode>
      <UnknownNoOffenders>N</UnknownNoOffenders>
      <DsIcrDate>07/15/2023 22:58:48</DsIcrDate>
      <DsIcrSubmissionStatus>PROCESS COMPLETE</DsIcrSubmissionStatus>
      <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
      <CreatorDate>06/23/2023 08:59:08</CreatorDate>
      <UpdatorId>TAMI.ANDREASSEN@INTERACT911.COM</UpdatorId>
      <UpdatorDate>07/21/2023 17:23:25</UpdatorDate>
      <IncidentSuppNarrative>
         <NarrativeNumber>1</NarrativeNumber>
         <NarrativeTitle>Supplement #1 Narrative</NarrativeTitle>
         <NarrativeText>Supplement Report 23-MSP-022425  BK G DUI 23-103  TA 21-902A1 (LORRAINE JEBET CHEBON)  Date/Time of Incident:  06/22/2023, 1637 HOURS  Location: MD 97 at Hook Rd, Westminster, Carroll County, MD.  My actions were captured on Body Worn Camera and uploaded to Axon Evidence under this case number.  Narrative:  On 06/22/2023 at approximately 1637 hours, I responded at the request of TFC Reid to the area of MD 97 at Hook Rd, Westminster, Carroll County, MD, to assist him with a possible impaired driver. Upon my arrival, TFC Reid began to attempt to administer the Standardized Field Sobriety Tests to the driver, who was identified as LORRAINE JEBET CHEBON. I observed CHEBON to be unsteady on her feet (swaying side to side), and having difficulty focusing on the instructions given by TFC Reid. CHEBON was walking back and forth, very emotion and agitated to the point where she was crying. At the conclusion of the SFSTs, TFC Reid offered her a Preliminary Breath Test which she agreed to.  I activated my BWC and administered the PBT to the driver. The driver continued to be emotional and agitated. The driver would blow hard, stop blowing prior to my instruction to do so, and interrupt the airflow before I was able to get a valid sample for the PBT. I was finally able to get a sample of breath for the PBT to analyze. The result of the PBT was 0.16 BrAC. TFC Reid placed the driver under arrest and her level of agitation increased further. The driver was yelling and crying as she was placed in the front passenger seat of TFC Reids patrol vehicle. During my contact with the driver, I made the following observations:  -very strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on the drivers breath and person -eyes bloodshot -swaying when she did stand still -emotional and agitated: crying, yelling and moving all about -inability (or unwillingness) to follow instructions provided in a clear and quiet manner  I looked in the vehicle (MD tag 8CE9253 on a gray Nissan Pathfinder SUV), to locate keys, and observed a green cap for NEW AMSTERDAM Apple Vodka in plain sight behind the front passenger seat, well within reach of the driver. The bottle was approximately  full. I poured out the contents, which smelled strongly of alcoholic beverage, into the grass on the side of the roadway in view of TFC Reids patrol vehicles dash camera.  Due to the very high level of agitation and possible high level of intoxication of the driver, I followed TFC Reid to the MSP Westminster Barrack, where the driver was further processed for DUI.  All events occurred in Carroll County, MD. </NarrativeText>
         <CreatorId>MSP5334</CreatorId>
         <CreatorDate>06/23/2023 09:01:11</CreatorDate>
         <UpdatorId>MSP5334</UpdatorId>
         <UpdatorDate>06/23/2023 09:21:40</UpdatorDate>
      </IncidentSuppNarrative>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>P</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>Eyler</LastName>
            <FirstName>Jeffery</FirstName>
            <InternalID>0670</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
      <IncidentOfficer>
         <OfficerRoleCode>R</OfficerRoleCode>
         <Officer>
            <AgencyCode>56</AgencyCode>
            <ORINumber>MDMSP0200</ORINumber>
            <LastName>FAIR</LastName>
            <FirstName>JOHN</FirstName>
            <InternalID>5334</InternalID>
         </Officer>
      </IncidentOfficer>
   </IncidentSupplement>
</Incident>